<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mobile Development on </title>
    <link>/tags/mobile-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mobile Development on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 18:00:33 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/mobile-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building Android Widgets from Scratch ( Learn 8 Widgets)</title>
      <link>/building-android-widgets-from-scratch-learn-8-widgets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 18:00:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/building-android-widgets-from-scratch-learn-8-widgets/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our course 
Learn How to build 8 Android Widgets right from scratch in just 2 hours
If you are an Android developer who has a good understanding of the application basics, then here&#39;s your chance to expand your Android knowledge and move to the next-level in Android development.
In this course, you will learn how to build 8 commonly-used widgets on Android all on your own. The Instructor has opted for a hands-on approach to teaching these concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Android-Kotlin Development Guide [Arabic Edition]</title>
      <link>/the-android-kotlin-development-guide-arabic-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 12:05:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-android-kotlin-development-guide-arabic-edition/</guid>
      <description>هذه الدورة المفصلة في المستوى الاول والثاني من الاندرويد بأستخدام كوتلن حيث افترض الشخص الذي امامي لا يعرف اي شي عن الاندرويد ستوديو
 ستتمكن من خلال هذه الدورة من الدخول الى عالم تطوير تطبيقات الاندرويد تتميز هذه الدورة بأنها مفصلة ولكن ليس فيها تشعبات وتفاصيل غير اساسية

لقد غطيت في هذه الدورة العديد من المواضيع مثل
Layouts
Res Files
Toast
View
SetOnClickListener
Intent
WebView
Ic Icon Luncher</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Flutter Development Guide [Arabic Edition]</title>
      <link>/the-complete-flutter-development-guide-arabic-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 12:05:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-flutter-development-guide-arabic-edition/</guid>
      <description>Notice: The Maximilian[Academind] course was adopted as a primary reference for this course ...
ملاحظة: تم اعتماد دورة ماكس كمرجع اساسي لهذه الدورة...

في هذه الدورة المتكاملة فلاتر [المرجع الشامل] افترض الشخص اللي امامي لا يعرف اي شيء عن الفلاتر وعن البرمجة التطبيقات اصلا
سأخذك خطوة بخطوة من الصفر الى انشاء تطبيقات حقيقية للاندرويد والايفون

Join the most comprehensive &amp;amp; bestselling Flutter course and learn how to build amazing iOS and Android apps!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginners guide to Android App Development (Step by Step)</title>
      <link>/beginners-guide-to-android-app-development-step-by-step/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/beginners-guide-to-android-app-development-step-by-step/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our course &#34;A beginners guide to Android App Development (step by step)&#34;.
A Beginner&#39;s Guide to Android App Development
Looking to launch your own app on Google Play Store but don&#39;t know where to begin? Then here&#39;s your chance to learn the basics and build your skills in Android development. Before you read further, it is an essential prerequisite for a student to have a good understanding of Java (OOPs and Threads, in particular) The Android development course is a collection of Android Application Development tutorial videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android App Development Bootcamp with Kotlin - Masterclass</title>
      <link>/android-app-development-bootcamp-with-kotlin-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/android-app-development-bootcamp-with-kotlin-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
Google considers Kotlin an official (first-class) android Developing Language
Android has ruled the app market for the past decade, and developers are increasingly looking to start building their own Android apps. How to Build Android Apps with Kotlin starts with the building blocks of Android development, teaching you how to use Android Studio, the integrated development environment (IDE) for Android, with the programming language Kotlin for app development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Stack Mobile Application Development - Master Class</title>
      <link>/full-stack-mobile-application-development-master-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/full-stack-mobile-application-development-master-class/</guid>
      <description>There’s strong motivation for companies to find someone who can “do it all”. 
This Course explores the features of full-stack mobile development environments and covers several core native and hybrid mobile alternatives and the factors that influence the selection of each platform.
Full-stack mobile app development lies at the nexus of content and technology. Billions of people worldwide now use smartphones and tablets, which form the client side of the full-stack app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Dart Learning Guide</title>
      <link>/the-complete-dart-learning-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-dart-learning-guide/</guid>
      <description>تم الانتهاء من تحديث دورة الدارت
التحديثات شملت:
١- تحديث الاكواد المكتوبة في الدورة لتعمل على اخر اصدار في الدارت بدون مشاكل.
٢- تم توسيع دورة الدرات باضافة قسم كامل للبرمجة الغير متزامنة (Asynchronous Programming) لتتضمن شرح مواضيع (Future, Stream, Async/Await, get Api, File system)
٣- أضافة شرح لدوال الفلترة او التصفية (where, indexWhere, map, any, وغيرهم)
٤- أضافة مشروع تطبيقي في نهاية الدورة.
٥- أضافة شرح مفصل لمفهوم ال null safety والتحديثات الجديدة مثل required وال late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence in App Creation: Beginners Edition</title>
      <link>/artificial-intelligence-in-app-creation-beginners-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artificial-intelligence-in-app-creation-beginners-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the sixth course in Term 2 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Today, Artificial Intelligence (AI), Machine Learning, and Deep Learning technologies are used in diverse fields as part of the daily life of large organizations across the globe. The rapid speed of AI growth demonstrates that it is a groundbreaking technology designed to transform the way people use devices and conduct business: achievements in unmanned aerial vehicles, the ability to beat people in chess and sporting games, automated customer service, and analytical systems - of course.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
