<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>3D &amp; Animation on </title>
    <link>/tags/3d-animation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 3D &amp; Animation on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/3d-animation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Learn Cinema 4D: Low Poly Planet</title>
      <link>/learn-cinema-4d-low-poly-planet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-cinema-4d-low-poly-planet/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to learn 3D modelling quickly &amp;amp; easily by creating trendy low poly artwork? You can do it in this course and learn the basics of Cinema 4D by creating a Low Poly Planet! This class is perfect for web designers, graphic designers, illustrators and anyone else who would like to learn a bit of 3D modelling to add to their designs. Get started with 3D modelling &amp;amp; take this course now to learn Cinema 4D in just a few hours!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Voice to 3D Animation Course</title>
      <link>/the-ultimate-voice-to-3d-animation-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-ultimate-voice-to-3d-animation-course/</guid>
      <description>&#34;3D animation is a technique which allows for each object or person to have their own three-dimensional space; this can create the illusion of depth while simultaneously creating motion within that world.&#34; Good 3D animation is hard to create or execute and we all know it. What we must further be aware of is what is harder still is being committed to it in the long run as 3D animation is a vast, tiring and long process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Adobe Animate Megacourse: Beginner to Expert</title>
      <link>/complete-adobe-animate-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-adobe-animate-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to learn how to animate? From childhood and adult favourites like Disney, to advertisements and short films, animation is all around us. Whether you’re an artist out to create original and fan content like short films and sketches, or a designer looking to expand their professional portfolio, animation isn’t just for the professionally-trained artist. Even someone with no animation background can learn the skills and start creating beautiful pieces of art - and we’re here to teach you how.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
