<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Video Design on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/video-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Video Design on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/video-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Videoscribe Whiteboard Animations : MasterClass With Project</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/videoscribe-whiteboard-animations-masterclass-with-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/videoscribe-whiteboard-animations-masterclass-with-project/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our Videoscribe Whiteboard Animations: MasterClass With Project course!
This course is designed for VideoScribe v3.7, to ensure you are using the most up-to-date version we recommend updating your app from your Sparkol account page.
My name is Chetan Pujari. I’ve been creating videos and teaching courses on how to get the most out of VideoScribe for over 5 years.
In this course, I’ve captured our top hints and tips so you can quickly learn how easy it is to create engaging whiteboard animation videos using VideoScribe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filmora 11/X/9:  Zero to Hero in Video Editing (2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/filmora-11/x/9-zero-to-hero-in-video-editing-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/filmora-11/x/9-zero-to-hero-in-video-editing-2022/</guid>
      <description>Who Is This For?
This course was made for YouTubers, filmmakers, Vloggers, professional video editors, who want to edit for others like freelance. Content creators for YouTube and social media often want a simplified workflow, and Filmora certainly provides that kind of editing experience. But does that mean it’s something experienced editors should ignore? Not necessarily. Filmora9 does not have the features of professional software like Premiere, Final Cut, Media Composer, or Resolve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Correction &amp; Grading with Adobe Premiere Pro 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/color-correction-grading-with-adobe-premiere-pro-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/color-correction-grading-with-adobe-premiere-pro-2022/</guid>
      <description>This complete course will take you to the essentials of color correction with the Lumetri color tools inside Premiere Pro. You will learn different techniques while also understanding how color philosophy works. (Footage Included)
We&#39;ll fly together through this wonderful world of colors. And on the end you will be able to fix color issues and take your shots to a higher professional level.
What will I learn?
You will learn a complete essential training of color correction and grading in Premiere Pro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Editing with Adobe Premiere Pro CC 2022 for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-editing-with-adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2022-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-editing-with-adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2022-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Start your Video Editing Career with Premiere Pro CC 2022 and create professional productions for Film, TV and Youtube!!
Adobe Premiere Pro is the best video editing program you can use &amp;amp; it&#39;s so compatible with the Adobe family which a great plus for the program and makes your workflow easy and productive. Premiere Pro is used by professionals internationally for every type of production &amp;amp; it could seem overwhelming and hard when you open it for first time but with this course within an hour you will able to do Creative video editing !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Grading and Video Editing with Davinci Resolve 17</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/color-grading-and-video-editing-with-davinci-resolve-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/color-grading-and-video-editing-with-davinci-resolve-17/</guid>
      <description>DaVinci Resolve 16 Beginners Course DaVinci Resolve 16 is a free professional video editing application used by professionals and amateurs. It’s easy and simple to use. It provides you with simple to use yet powerful tools to edit your videos and achieve high quality production.
This course is for beginners. You do not need any previous knowledge in DaVinci Resolve 17 or video editing experience.
You will dive straightaway into creating your first video and add music, graphics, text and couple of transitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Produce A Low Budget Independent Feature Film!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-produce-a-low-budget-independent-feature-film/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-produce-a-low-budget-independent-feature-film/</guid>
      <description>When I was younger and decided to become a filmmaker I decided to come to London and study film at the university. Six months into my course I quit university when I realized that the information provided there was not sufficient for me to make a film. I was young, broke, and all I had was a dream, all I needed was the information and guidance.
As times changed, I had to adapt to constantly changing technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro 2022 Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-2022-ultimate-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-2022-ultimate-guide/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone and welcome to Adobe Premiere Pro 2022 Ultimate Guide.
In this video, we&#39;re going to go over a course overview of what we&#39;re going to be learning throughout the course.
So in Section two, we&#39;re going to be covering creative cloud plans.
So we&#39;ll cover individuals, business students and teachers and schools and universities.
Then we&#39;ll learn how to set up a free creative cloud account.
Next, we&#39;ll work on Adobe Creative Cloud Web and learn how to install Adobe Premiere Pro 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movavi Video Editor Guide - Video Editing for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/movavi-video-editor-guide-video-editing-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/movavi-video-editor-guide-video-editing-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Imagine being able to edit videos like a pro. Imagine editing them with only two clicks, no need for overlays, transitions or music. Video editing is kind of complicated. Or is it?
Movavi video editor is a simple and powerful video editing software that will make your video magic happen. It can be used to edit and convert videos, create 3D effects, stabilize shaky footage, add audio tracks to your video, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Editing Mastery With Camtasia In Hindi/Urdu 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-editing-mastery-with-camtasia-in-hindi/urdu-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 20:12:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-editing-mastery-with-camtasia-in-hindi/urdu-2022/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to learn Camtasia to edit your videos like a pro and produce professional videos for your courses or a youtube channel or social media. (All my Udemy courses are edited on this software &amp;amp; I am showing how I do it) I have recorded/edited thousands of hours of videos in Camtasia and you will learn from my experience where you only need to spend only 2 hours of your life to master this software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Beautiful Photo and Video Slideshows with Animoto</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-beautiful-photo-and-video-slideshows-with-animoto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-beautiful-photo-and-video-slideshows-with-animoto/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this superb and impressive Udemy course focussed on &#34;Create Beautiful Photo and Video Slideshows with Animoto&#34; in 2022.
Take charge and learn quick, amazing and easy methods for creating and editing powerful web and social media promo videos like a professional in the fastest time possible with the power of Animoto.
Whether you are an entrepreneur, employee, content creator, teacher, author, or social media enthusiast, over the last few years it has become extremely important and of course - CRUCIAL to know how to do a little bit of everything online, including how to make your brand stand out with videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro CC 2022: Video Editing for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2022-video-editing-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 15:08:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2022-video-editing-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>This course is a one-stop shop that has everything you need to become a confident editor inside Premiere Pro.
If you&#39;ve taken a quick look at Adobe Premiere Pro and are completely overwhelmed by the features and have no clue how to start editing your first video, you have come to the right course.
In this complete guide to the Adobe Premiere Pro video editing course, you&#39;ll not only learn all of the editing tools available in Premiere Pro but also how to edit with the mindset of a professional editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DaVinci Resolve 17: Video editing course for beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/davinci-resolve-17-video-editing-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 15:08:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/davinci-resolve-17-video-editing-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>In this course I&#39;ll teach you how to use DaVinci Resolve. In this course I included only the most important and main tools from DaVinci, to teach anyone (you need 0 experience) how to edit a good video. I guess you&#39;ll learn the most on your own, but first you need to know how to use such a magical tool as DaVinci, that&#39;s what I&#39;m going to teach you in this course (from making simple cuts to transitions / visual effects and even color grading) all of that in this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro 2022 Projects</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-2022-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-2022-projects/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Edit Video but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Videos and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Premiere Pro 2022 Projects is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Video Editing is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start Editing Videos like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TikTok pop-up editing tool----CapCut</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tiktok-pop-up-editing-tool----capcut/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 21:29:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tiktok-pop-up-editing-tool----capcut/</guid>
      <description>In this video editing course you will learn how to edit videos from raw clips to TikTok pop-up videos.we have covered all main features of TikTok&#39;s pop-up video editing like cutting, trimming, transitions, enhancing, speed up and so on.
What can you expect learning our course?
1,Master CapCut and be CONFIDENT Editing Your Own TikTok Videos
2,Edit an entire video from beginning to end, using the simplest and most practical technique</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videoscribe Whiteboard Animations Masterclass for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/videoscribe-whiteboard-animations-masterclass-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 15:38:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/videoscribe-whiteboard-animations-masterclass-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome guys my name is Anwer Khan and I will be your instructor throughout this course. In this course, I will talk straight to the point. Therefore, we will cover more in less time. Videoscribe for Beginners course!
VideoScribe is software for creating whiteboard animations automatically. In order to use videoscribe you don&#39;t need any graphic designing skills. Videoscribe is easy to learn, quick and inexpensive. You can create great animated videos in no time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streamlabs OBS von A bis Z der exklusive Komplettkurs</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/streamlabs-obs-von-a-bis-z-der-exklusive-komplettkurs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:36:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/streamlabs-obs-von-a-bis-z-der-exklusive-komplettkurs/</guid>
      <description>Über mich
Mein Name ist Andreas und ich befasse mich seit ca. 3 Jahren aktiv mit Streamlabs OBS. Ich habe mich sehr intensiv mit der Streaming Software auseinander gesetzt und vielen anderen auch schon erfolgreich geholfen Streamlabs OBS einzurichten. Meine Erfahrungen mit der Stream Plattform Twitch ist auch ziemlich hoch, weil ich auch selber Twitch Streamer bin und die Szene aktiv verfolge. Genau deswegen kenne ich auch die größten Probleme und die meist gestellten Fragen, die in diesem Kurs alle abgedeckt werden mit 115 Lektionen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Guide to InVideo and InVideo Video Creation</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-guide-to-invideo-and-invideo-video-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-guide-to-invideo-and-invideo-video-creation/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Complete Guide to InVideo and InVideo Video Creation!
The only course you will need to start with InVideo, one of the best online video creators and editors on the market. With InVideo you can create short-form and long-form content for any social media platform, including Instagram, YouTube, TikTok, Facebook, Pinterest, and many more. In addition to all that you are also able to transform your blog posts into full-length videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Editing In Adobe Premiere Pro Mega Pack 5 Courses In 1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-editing-in-adobe-premiere-pro-mega-pack-5-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-editing-in-adobe-premiere-pro-mega-pack-5-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>90% OFF for 1 month USE COUPON CODE : EARLYBIRD90 Video editing is one of the most demanding and lucrative skills of 21st century . From mobile screens , social media to theater every sector requires video editing in some form or other . Hence learning the industry standard software are a must . In this course you will learn video editing using adobe premiere pro with practical examples . And follow along pattern ensures that all changes will happen in front of your eyes .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
