<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Video Design on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/video-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Video Design on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 01:39:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/video-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Grading and Video Editing with Davinci Resolve 17</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/color-grading-and-video-editing-with-davinci-resolve-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 01:39:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/color-grading-and-video-editing-with-davinci-resolve-17/</guid>
      <description>DaVinci Resolve 16 Beginners Course 
DaVinci Resolve 16 is a free professional video editing application used by professionals and amateurs. It’s easy and simple to use. It provides you with simple to use yet powerful tools to edit your videos and achieve high quality production.
This course is for beginners. You do not need any previous knowledge in DaVinci Resolve 17 or video editing experience.
You will dive straightaway into creating your first video and add music, graphics, text and couple of transitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Correction &amp; Grading with Adobe Premiere Pro 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/color-correction-grading-with-adobe-premiere-pro-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/color-correction-grading-with-adobe-premiere-pro-2022/</guid>
      <description>This complete course will take you to the essentials of color correction with the Lumetri color tools inside Premiere Pro. You will learn different techniques while also understanding how color philosophy works. (Footage Included)
We&#39;ll fly together through this wonderful world of colors. And on the end you will be able to fix color issues and take your shots to a higher professional level.
What will I learn?
You will learn a complete essential training of color correction and grading in Premiere Pro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Guide to InVideo and InVideo Video Creation</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-guide-to-invideo-and-invideo-video-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-guide-to-invideo-and-invideo-video-creation/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Complete Guide to InVideo and InVideo Video Creation!
The only course you will need to start with InVideo, one of the best online video creators and editors on the market. With InVideo you can create short-form and long-form content for any social media platform, including Instagram, YouTube, TikTok, Facebook, Pinterest, and many more. In addition to all that you are also able to transform your blog posts into full-length videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Editing In Adobe Premiere Pro Mega Pack 5 Courses In 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/video-editing-in-adobe-premiere-pro-mega-pack-5-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/video-editing-in-adobe-premiere-pro-mega-pack-5-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>90% OFF for 1 month USE COUPON CODE : EARLYBIRD90 Video editing is one of the most demanding and lucrative skills of 21st century . From mobile screens , social media to theater every sector requires video editing in some form or other . Hence learning the industry standard software are a must . In this course you will learn video editing using adobe premiere pro with practical examples . And follow along pattern ensures that all changes will happen in front of your eyes .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro 2021 Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/adobe-premiere-pro-2021-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/adobe-premiere-pro-2021-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Edit Video but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Videos and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Premiere Pro 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Video Editing is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start Editing Videos like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Editing with Adobe Premiere Pro CC 2021 for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/video-editing-with-adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2021-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 10:06:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/video-editing-with-adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2021-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Start your Video Editing Career with Premiere Pro CC 2021 and create professional productions for Film, TV and Youtube!
Adobe Premiere Pro is the best video editing program you can use &amp;amp; it&#39;s so compatible with the Adobe family which a great plus for the program and makes your workflow easy and productive. Premiere Pro is used by professionals internationally for every type of production &amp;amp; it could seem overwhelming and hard when you open it for first time but with this course within an hour you will able to do Creative video editing !</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>