<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Human Resources on </title>
    <link>/tags/human-resources/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Human Resources on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 20:12:17 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/human-resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Cultural Management Made Easy</title>
      <link>/cross-cultural-management-made-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 20:12:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cross-cultural-management-made-easy/</guid>
      <description>Do you know the cost of failure of cross-cultural awareness and lack of cross-cultural competence? The cost for cultural integration of Upjohn Pharmaceutical Company of USA to integrate the newly acquired company (in 1995), Pharmacia of Sweden was close to 1 Bn $ almost 300 Million $ above expectations. Despite such huge costs the company disintegrated and vanished from the world market within a decade of the merger.
When handled properly world cultural diversity can be converted to the key success factor of a business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diversity At Workplace</title>
      <link>/diversity-at-workplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/diversity-at-workplace/</guid>
      <description>Diversity in the workplace is vital for employees because it manifests itself in building a great reputation for the company, leading to increased profitability and opportunities for workers.
Workplace diversity is important within the organization as well as outside.
Diversity in the workplace means that a company’s workforce includes people of varying gender, age, religion, race, ethnicity, cultural background, sexual orientation, religion, languages, education, abilities, etc.
Why is workplace diversity so important?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practice Tests for SHRM-CP and SHRM-SCP Exam Questions(2021)</title>
      <link>/practice-tests-for-shrm-cp-and-shrm-scp-exam-questions2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/practice-tests-for-shrm-cp-and-shrm-scp-exam-questions2021/</guid>
      <description>HR certifications such as the SHRM-CP/SCP® can help you with job advancements and pay raises as well as enhance the chance of new applicants getting a job. They improve the employer&#39;s perception of you and your human resources expertise. Passing an SHRM certification exam will keep your knowledge and skills fresh and give you a boost of confidence as an HR professional.
In addition, The SHRM now shares a partnership with CPHR; hence you will be able to transfer your SHRM certification to gain the CPHR designation if required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming A Recruitment And Selection Specialist</title>
      <link>/becoming-a-recruitment-and-selection-specialist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/becoming-a-recruitment-and-selection-specialist/</guid>
      <description>A good recruitment process can reduce the time involved in searching, interviewing, recruiting, and training. It can streamline these procedures and make your search more efficient for viable candidates.
Remember, top talent will not always find you.
You must seek out people to fill the positions that you have open. So, in this course, we&#39;ll learn together, the following:
Defining recruitment
Understanding the selection process
Recognising the GROW model
Interview and question process</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talento Humano 3.0 analizando lo nuevo de recursos humanos</title>
      <link>/talento-humano-3.0-analizando-lo-nuevo-de-recursos-humanos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talento-humano-3.0-analizando-lo-nuevo-de-recursos-humanos/</guid>
      <description>Las ciencias administrativas han desarrollado importantes investigaciones sobre los individuos y grupos en las organizaciones, que quizás pareciera un tema nuevo. Por tanto, al referirse al Talento Humano se hace mención a ese recurso importante desde una concepción más actualizada considerando los cambios y avances en la sociedad del siglo XXI, con matices más específicos dentro de una organización social. Como resultado, se han presentado diversas posiciones y conceptos, en relación a ese individuo con características muy concretas y complejas que interactúa en una organización bien sea pública, privada, pequeña mediana o gran empresa, pero que algunos gerentes parecieran no valorar.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
