<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Human Resources on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/human-resources/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Human Resources on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/human-resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Conflict Resolution and De-Escalation Skills</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/conflict-resolution-and-de-escalation-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/conflict-resolution-and-de-escalation-skills/</guid>
      <description>MULTIPLE CONFLICTS, ONE SINGLE CONFLICT
Conflict is something present in our lives.
Conflicts may occur big and small, in our personal or professional lives, and for multiple reasons.
But despite these reasons, one thing is true - and a constant.
Knowing how to solve conflicts is crucial.
This is what we will explore in this course.


WHY THIS COURSE?
Naturally, you will find multiple courses on social skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiring Process: Talent Management</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/hiring-process-talent-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 11:17:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/hiring-process-talent-management/</guid>
      <description>By adopting a structured and comprehensive hiring process, you&#39;re taking the first step in positioning your business for success by attracting the right talent. The type of talent that will help build the company culture, drive sales and ultimately position the company as a leader in the industry.
So in this course we will learn:
Learn how to present the current open position
Develop a workable hiring strategy
Know how to determine which candidates to interview</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HR Analytics using MS Excel for Human Resource Management</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/hr-analytics-using-ms-excel-for-human-resource-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/hr-analytics-using-ms-excel-for-human-resource-management/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re looking for a complete course on understanding HR Analytics using Excel to drive business decisions, right?
You&#39;ve found the right HR Analytics using MS Excel course! HR analytics provides scientific support to decision-making concerning a firm&#39;s human resources. This course on HR analytics addresses the topic of HR analytics with a practical focus, focusing especially on demystifying analytics for Human Resource managers, from both statistical and computing point of view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming A Recruitment And Selection Specialist</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/becoming-a-recruitment-and-selection-specialist/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:43:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/becoming-a-recruitment-and-selection-specialist/</guid>
      <description>A good recruitment process can reduce the time involved in searching, interviewing, recruiting, and training. It can streamline these procedures and make your search more efficient for viable candidates.
Remember, top talent will not always find you.
You must seek out people to fill the positions that you have open. So, in this course, we&#39;ll learn together, the following:
Defining recruitment
Understanding the selection process
Recognising the GROW model
Interview and question process</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diversity At Workplace</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/diversity-at-workplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/diversity-at-workplace/</guid>
      <description>Diversity in the workplace is vital for employees because it manifests itself in building a great reputation for the company, leading to increased profitability and opportunities for workers.
Workplace diversity is important within the organization as well as outside.
Diversity in the workplace means that a company’s workforce includes people of varying gender, age, religion, race, ethnicity, cultural background, sexual orientation, religion, languages, education, abilities, etc.
Why is workplace diversity so important?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jetpack 1.0: Artificial Intelligence and Automation in HR</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/jetpack-1.0-artificial-intelligence-and-automation-in-hr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/jetpack-1.0-artificial-intelligence-and-automation-in-hr/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the third course in Term 3 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Today, we are seeing an increasing number of applications of AI-based solutions across fields like eCommerce Marketing, Personalised Recommendations, Targeted Marketing, Finance Industry, etc. Artificial Intelligence (AI) seemed to be a distant reality for the HR function, until today. Artificial Intelligence (AI) usage for Human Resources (HR) seemed to be a narrative similar to every support function across organizations across India and the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Cultural Management Made Easy</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cross-cultural-management-made-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cross-cultural-management-made-easy/</guid>
      <description>Do you know the cost of failure of cross-cultural awareness and lack of cross-cultural competence? The cost for cultural integration of Upjohn Pharmaceutical Company of USA to integrate the newly acquired company (in 1995), Pharmacia of Sweden was close to 1 Bn $ almost 300 Million $ above expectations. Despite such huge costs the company disintegrated and vanished from the world market within a decade of the merger.
When handled properly world cultural diversity can be converted to the key success factor of a business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practice Tests for SHRM-CP and SHRM-SCP Exam Questions(2021)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/practice-tests-for-shrm-cp-and-shrm-scp-exam-questions2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/practice-tests-for-shrm-cp-and-shrm-scp-exam-questions2021/</guid>
      <description>HR certifications such as the SHRM-CP/SCP® can help you with job advancements and pay raises as well as enhance the chance of new applicants getting a job. They improve the employer&#39;s perception of you and your human resources expertise. Passing an SHRM certification exam will keep your knowledge and skills fresh and give you a boost of confidence as an HR professional.
In addition, The SHRM now shares a partnership with CPHR; hence you will be able to transfer your SHRM certification to gain the CPHR designation if required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talento Humano 3.0 analizando lo nuevo de recursos humanos</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/talento-humano-3.0-analizando-lo-nuevo-de-recursos-humanos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/talento-humano-3.0-analizando-lo-nuevo-de-recursos-humanos/</guid>
      <description>Las ciencias administrativas han desarrollado importantes investigaciones sobre los individuos y grupos en las organizaciones, que quizás pareciera un tema nuevo. Por tanto, al referirse al Talento Humano se hace mención a ese recurso importante desde una concepción más actualizada considerando los cambios y avances en la sociedad del siglo XXI, con matices más específicos dentro de una organización social. Como resultado, se han presentado diversas posiciones y conceptos, en relación a ese individuo con características muy concretas y complejas que interactúa en una organización bien sea pública, privada, pequeña mediana o gran empresa, pero que algunos gerentes parecieran no valorar.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
