<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Human Resources on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/human-resources/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Human Resources on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/human-resources/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Diversity At Workplace</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/diversity-at-workplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/diversity-at-workplace/</guid>
      <description>Diversity in the workplace is vital for employees because it manifests itself in building a great reputation for the company, leading to increased profitability and opportunities for workers.
Workplace diversity is important within the organization as well as outside.
Diversity in the workplace means that a company’s workforce includes people of varying gender, age, religion, race, ethnicity, cultural background, sexual orientation, religion, languages, education, abilities, etc.
Why is workplace diversity so important?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming A Recruitment And Selection Specialist</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/becoming-a-recruitment-and-selection-specialist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/becoming-a-recruitment-and-selection-specialist/</guid>
      <description>A good recruitment process can reduce the time involved in searching, interviewing, recruiting, and training. It can streamline these procedures and make your search more efficient for viable candidates.
Remember, top talent will not always find you.
You must seek out people to fill the positions that you have open. So, in this course, we&#39;ll learn together, the following:
Defining recruitment
Understanding the selection process
Recognising the GROW model
Interview and question process</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Management Coaching Course - Executive Coaching</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-management-coaching-course-executive-coaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-management-coaching-course-executive-coaching/</guid>
      <description>Complete Management Coaching Course - Executive CoachingManagement Coaching - Learn all Aspects of Coaching, Career Coaching and Executive Coaching - Master Coaching
Welcome to the world of the management coaching. It’s a $3 billion global business where the median rate for executive coaches is $500 an hour.
The news gets even better. You can be a management coach from where ever you are. I have worked with clients throughout North America, the UK, France, Switzerland, Germany, and Denmark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Recruiting Masterclass - HR Resources - Hiring</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-recruiting-masterclass-hr-resources-hiring/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-recruiting-masterclass-hr-resources-hiring/</guid>
      <description>Recruiting is the world where candidates rule. Human resource managers are competing for the best and brightest. Talent management today means being able to attract people who “add ease and clarity”. This course is an introduction into the topic of recruiting the best from the market. Jump in to avoid major mistakes HRs and team leaders make when closing the key vacancies.
You will benefit from this course the most if you are:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jetpack 1.0: Artificial Intelligence and Automation in HR</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/jetpack-1.0-artificial-intelligence-and-automation-in-hr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/jetpack-1.0-artificial-intelligence-and-automation-in-hr/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Jetpack 1.0&#34;.
Today, we are seeing an increasing number of applications of AI-based solutions across fields like eCommerce Marketing, Personalised Recommendations, Targeted Marketing, Finance Industry, etc. Artificial Intelligence (AI) seemed to be a distant reality for the HR function, until today. Artificial Intelligence (AI) usage for Human Resources (HR) seemed to be a narrative similar to every support function across organizations across India and the world.
Welcome to experience &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiring Process: Talent Management</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hiring-process-talent-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 21:50:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hiring-process-talent-management/</guid>
      <description>By adopting a structured and comprehensive hiring process, you&#39;re taking the first step in positioning your business for success by attracting the right talent. The type of talent that will help build the company culture, drive sales and ultimately position the company as a leader in the industry.
So in this course we will learn:
Learn how to present the current open position
Develop a workable hiring strategy
Know how to determine which candidates to interview</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BCBA Board Certified Behavior Analyst Exams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bcba-board-certified-behavior-analyst-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:57:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bcba-board-certified-behavior-analyst-exams/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to crush the BCBA Board Certified Behavior Analyst and get certified?
Today is a competitive world and the smartest, best, and most qualified get paid a lot of money to work in amazing fields. But you don’t need a college degree, certification is an amazing path that opens up new opportunities and shows employers that you are the cream of the crop. We know that BACB certification will add some flair to that resume and help you get amazing new roles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BCABA Board Certified Assistant Behavior Analyst Exams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bcaba-board-certified-assistant-behavior-analyst-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bcaba-board-certified-assistant-behavior-analyst-exams/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to crush the BCABA Board Certified Assistant Behavior Analyst and get certified?
Today is a competitive world and the smartest, best, and most qualified get paid a lot of money to work in amazing fields. But you don’t need a college degree, certification is an amazing path that opens up new opportunities and shows employers that you are the cream of the crop. We know that BACB certification will add some flair to that resume and help you get amazing new roles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HR Analytics using MS Excel for Human Resource Management</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hr-analytics-using-ms-excel-for-human-resource-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hr-analytics-using-ms-excel-for-human-resource-management/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re looking for a complete course on understanding HR Analytics using Excel to drive business decisions, right?
You&#39;ve found the right HR Analytics using MS Excel course! HR analytics provides scientific support to decision-making concerning a firm&#39;s human resources. This course on HR analytics addresses the topic of HR analytics with a practical focus, focusing especially on demystifying analytics for Human Resource managers, from both statistical and computing point of view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EIQ2 Coaching for Improved Performance and Superior Results</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/eiq2-coaching-for-improved-performance-and-superior-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/eiq2-coaching-for-improved-performance-and-superior-results/</guid>
      <description>EIQ-2 Learning and Positive Psychology are based on Self-Awareness; Self-Management; Empathy/Social Awareness and Relationship Management.
Training, Development and Continuous Improvement are the tools to respond to a volatile, uncertain, complex, ambiguous world. For the individual, team, organization and community, the skills that brought you this far are inadequate to face the challenges of tomorrow. Learning is the answer. It needs to connect different types of thinking, memory, as well as the tools to transform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing People From Different Cultures in Export Business</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/managing-people-from-different-cultures-in-export-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/managing-people-from-different-cultures-in-export-business/</guid>
      <description>How do you deal with business persons with different cultural backgrounds globally? Do you know the cost of failure of cross-cultural awareness and lack of cross-cultural competence? For example, the cost for the failure of cultural integration of Upjohn Pharmaceutical Company of USA to integrate the newly acquired company (in 1995), Pharmacia of Sweden was close to $1 Bn. It was almost $300 Million above expected costs. Despite such huge costs, the company disintegrated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2022 Professional Job Interview Questions and Answers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2022-professional-job-interview-questions-and-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 14:54:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2022-professional-job-interview-questions-and-answers/</guid>
      <description>Boost your opportunities and interview skills
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily
The ultimate goal is to select an individual who will meet the expectations of the position, and in most cases be able to retain them long-term. Here, we’ll focus on the most essential qualities I’ve found effective interviewers possess.
How do I describe my skills in an interview?
Follow these tips when describing what skills you can bring to the company:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HR Analytics &amp; Dashboarding - Beginner to Intermediate</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hr-analytics-dashboarding-beginner-to-intermediate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 11:19:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hr-analytics-dashboarding-beginner-to-intermediate/</guid>
      <description>HR analytics is the process of collecting and analysing Human Resource (HR) data in order to improve an organization’s workforce performance.
This method of data analysis takes data that is routinely collected by HR and correlates it to HR and organizational objectives. Doing so provides measured evidence of how HR initiatives are contributing to the organization’s goals and strategies.
An HR dashboard is an advanced analytics tool that displays important HR metrics using interactive data visualizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Artificial Intelligence in the Workplace</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-artificial-intelligence-in-the-workplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 13:01:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-artificial-intelligence-in-the-workplace/</guid>
      <description>This short course will explore how Artificial Intelligence (AI) will impact a workplace from an L&amp;amp;D and HR perspective. You will learn the gap in skillsets that are required for the future workforce. We will explore the benefits and pitfalls of AI and what organisations need to do. You will learn the basics of Artificial Intelligence and how L&amp;amp;D is the main driver for this transformational change and the importance of AI Ethics Codes of Practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EIQ-2 Teamwork Makes the Dream Work</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/eiq-2-teamwork-makes-the-dream-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 21:12:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/eiq-2-teamwork-makes-the-dream-work/</guid>
      <description>Turn your group into a high functioning team. Using Emotional Intelligence, you can transform your company into a tightly knit team that excels in fulfilling whatever mission your company or group is focused on.
Discover how you can positively impact your group and take quantum leaps towards superior execution.
A great team is in the habit of performing at a high level. Enrol Today!
Ratings: 4.26/5
Enrollments: 8917
Coupon Code: EIQ2TWEXPDEC52021</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workplace Communication: Effectively Deliver Criticism</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/workplace-communication-effectively-deliver-criticism/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/workplace-communication-effectively-deliver-criticism/</guid>
      <description>Imagine being able to give employees, colleagues and clients constructive criticism in the workplace, and they follow your advice, and actually appreciate your insights. Wouldn&#39;t it be nice to know that you can deliver criticism to colleagues in the workplace and they will take your criticism to heart and feel better about you in the process? In this How to Deliver Criticism in the Workplace course, you will learn the following: *How to avoid the common blunders other people make when delivering criticism in the workplace *How to build trust first with colleagues *How to make your criticism seem objective and credible *How to package your criticism so that it will be acted upon This course is delivered primarily through spoken lecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conflict Resolution and De-Escalation Skills</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/conflict-resolution-and-de-escalation-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/conflict-resolution-and-de-escalation-skills/</guid>
      <description>MULTIPLE CONFLICTS, ONE SINGLE CONFLICT
Conflict is something present in our lives.
Conflicts may occur big and small, in our personal or professional lives, and for multiple reasons.
But despite these reasons, one thing is true - and a constant.
Knowing how to solve conflicts is crucial.
This is what we will explore in this course.
WHY THIS COURSE?
Naturally, you will find multiple courses on social skills.
So... why this one?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practice Tests for SHRM-CP and SHRM-SCP Exam Questions(2021)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/practice-tests-for-shrm-cp-and-shrm-scp-exam-questions2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/practice-tests-for-shrm-cp-and-shrm-scp-exam-questions2021/</guid>
      <description>HR certifications such as the SHRM-CP/SCP® can help you with job advancements and pay raises as well as enhance the chance of new applicants getting a job. They improve the employer&#39;s perception of you and your human resources expertise. Passing an SHRM certification exam will keep your knowledge and skills fresh and give you a boost of confidence as an HR professional.
In addition, The SHRM now shares a partnership with CPHR; hence you will be able to transfer your SHRM certification to gain the CPHR designation if required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talento Humano 3.0 analizando lo nuevo de recursos humanos</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/talento-humano-3.0-analizando-lo-nuevo-de-recursos-humanos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/talento-humano-3.0-analizando-lo-nuevo-de-recursos-humanos/</guid>
      <description>Las ciencias administrativas han desarrollado importantes investigaciones sobre los individuos y grupos en las organizaciones, que quizás pareciera un tema nuevo. Por tanto, al referirse al Talento Humano se hace mención a ese recurso importante desde una concepción más actualizada considerando los cambios y avances en la sociedad del siglo XXI, con matices más específicos dentro de una organización social. Como resultado, se han presentado diversas posiciones y conceptos, en relación a ese individuo con características muy concretas y complejas que interactúa en una organización bien sea pública, privada, pequeña mediana o gran empresa, pero que algunos gerentes parecieran no valorar.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
