<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Leadership on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/leadership/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Leadership on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/leadership/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First impression hack - cheat based on scientific evidence!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/first-impression-hack-cheat-based-on-scientific-evidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/first-impression-hack-cheat-based-on-scientific-evidence/</guid>
      <description>You’ll never get a second chance to make a great first impression.Summary of the courseIn other words, when you meet someone for the first time, you need to be on top of your game from the very beginning. The key is to build rapport. Rapport is the lubricant for social communication. When rapport is established, communication barriers go down and you will have the opportunity to make a lasting connection. This practice is used actively by the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) to get interviewees to open up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking: A tactical approach</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-a-tactical-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-a-tactical-approach/</guid>
      <description>This course was born from frustration! Frustration that no one seems to be able to do what they’re teaching when it comes to speaking and communication. Everyone is either trying to teach you how to be a motivational speaker or some BS on overcoming your fears. In other words, it’s all self-help. But what does facing your fears and embracing your passion have to do with your regional sales report? Or a meeting with five people?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Become a Facilitator: 7 Effective Skills Summary</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-become-a-facilitator-7-effective-skills-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-become-a-facilitator-7-effective-skills-summary/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever felt like the task of becoming a leader and leading people to success is impossible? Well, it is no secret that the task may seem quite daunting and out of the realms of our possibilities. Well, the beauty of life is that nothing is impossible and with courage and willpower one can overcome their greatest fears and lead people to greatness.
That is one of the main functions of a facilitator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Psychology for Stress and Leadership</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/advanced-psychology-for-stress-and-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/advanced-psychology-for-stress-and-leadership/</guid>
      <description>This isn&#39;t a managing program, it&#39;s psychology. It&#39;s about YOU. Your thoughts, blocks, obstacles, stressors, and how they affect you and the people you care for. Within every craft there is always a mental side of performance, and leadership is not different.
There are many ways stress can be viewed in our normal day-to-day struggle, but I’ll do my best to try not to treat it like a superficial topic, and while I wrote this with the intention of it being clear and practical, this is not a how-to guide or a tutorial on deep breathing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to be a good PR</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-be-a-good-pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-be-a-good-pr/</guid>
      <description>This course is presented by me: Alhassan Ahmed younes Ahmed a good PR in many teams. You will gain a lot of knowledge from my experience in this committee. You will learn how to pass any interview in this field, how to complete any form in registering in any team.

You will learn all of the information of this topic in student activities.

You will learn how to make deals from zero to hero, and I will help you with some important contact numbers of some people are very famous around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>