<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Leadership on </title>
    <link>/tags/leadership/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Leadership on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 09:14:03 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/leadership/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Become a Facilitator: 7 Effective Skills</title>
      <link>/how-to-become-a-facilitator-7-effective-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 09:14:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-become-a-facilitator-7-effective-skills/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever felt like the task of becoming a leader and leading people to success is impossible? Well, it is no secret that the task may seem quite daunting and out of the realms of our possibilities. Well, the beauty of life is that nothing is impossible and with courage and willpower one can overcome their greatest fears and lead people to greatness.
That is one of the main functions of a facilitator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First impression hack - cheat based on scientific evidence!</title>
      <link>/first-impression-hack-cheat-based-on-scientific-evidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 12:05:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/first-impression-hack-cheat-based-on-scientific-evidence/</guid>
      <description>You’ll never get a second chance to make a great first impression.Summary of the courseIn other words, when you meet someone for the first time, you need to be on top of your game from the very beginning. The key is to build rapport. Rapport is the lubricant for social communication. When rapport is established, communication barriers go down and you will have the opportunity to make a lasting connection. This practice is used actively by the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) to get interviewees to open up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to be a good PR</title>
      <link>/how-to-be-a-good-pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-be-a-good-pr/</guid>
      <description>This course is presented by me: Alhassan Ahmed younes Ahmed a good PR in many teams. You will gain a lot of knowledge from my experience in this committee. You will learn how to pass any interview in this field, how to complete any form in registering in any team.

You will learn all of the information of this topic in student activities.

You will learn how to make deals from zero to hero, and I will help you with some important contact numbers of some people are very famous around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
