<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Productivity on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/personal-productivity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal Productivity on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/personal-productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Time Management Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>No matter what business or industry you’re involved in, learning how to effectively manage your time is one of the most important skills that will set you on the path towards ongoing success.
This course will help you get more done in less time by levelling up your productivity score quickly and easily.
The strategies contained in this course are designed to help you learn to value your time, make informed decisions about the kind of work you’re focused on and ultimately, beat the clock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10x your Productivity with Time Management</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/10x-your-productivity-with-time-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/10x-your-productivity-with-time-management/</guid>
      <description>Time…..the most scarce resource of life. Whatever job you do, you feel scarcity of only one thing i.e time. This scarcity does not differentiate rich or poor, black or white, tall or short, it&#39;s equal for everyone.
Even the most powerful person on earth has faced this scarcity.
In This Course I&#39;ll Teach You:
How to have Time Freedom. When you have time freedom you can focus your time on setting and achieving the biggest goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management for Personal &amp; Professional Productivity</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-for-personal-professional-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-for-personal-professional-productivity/</guid>
      <description>Hi ! I’m Pradeep Prajapati, your Instructor for this course. I know you are facing problems in your life for managing the most valuable asset of your life, and that asset is your time. In this course you will learn This course lays a common frame of understanding by exploring what people believe about time management, enumerating the benefits of time management, formally defining the term time management, briefly going over the history of time management, and showing how time management can lead to success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management for Professionals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-for-professionals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-for-professionals/</guid>
      <description>&#34;I must govern the clock, not be governed by it.&#34;
But how many of us can realize this dream? Not many, right? In today&#39;s fast-paced, hyper-connected world, you are not alone if you feel that there simply isn&#39;t enough time to get everything done at work. Even if we put in extra time, it seems like more tasks pile up and some even get lined up for the weekend, when we expect to have some uninterrupted time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn To Focus: Meditation &amp; Mindfulness For ADHD</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-to-focus-meditation-mindfulness-for-adhd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-to-focus-meditation-mindfulness-for-adhd/</guid>
      <description>ADD and ADHD can make it hard to focus &amp;amp; get things done. You have lots of mental energy (that&#39;s why you&#39;re so smart!) but you have a hard time directing it to one thing at a time. Many people go through their entire lives in this scatter-brained state, jumping from thing to thing, never fully concentrating on, or actually enjoying, anything. This can lead to major school &amp;amp; career problems (not paying attention in class, not paying attention at work, not caring about what you&#39;re working on, bouncing from job to job, career to career, etc), and problems becoming a successful adult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Time Management and Productivity (Bonus Free eBook)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-time-management-and-productivity-bonus-free-ebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-time-management-and-productivity-bonus-free-ebook/</guid>
      <description>Make the most of EVERY second, because when it is gone, you can NEVER have it back!
Wouldn’t it be absolutely liberating if you could decrease your hours and increase your productive output at the same time?
Is life not too short to waste your precious seconds on unproductive endeavors, feeling stressed, overwhelmed and asking yourself how it is all worthwhile?
Are you tired of feeling tired, overworked and on the verge of burning out because you have too much to do and to little time in which to do it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser Focus Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/laser-focus-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/laser-focus-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>We live in an era of information overload. We are bombarded with media, technology, entertainment, and notifications every day. It seems there are hundreds of people and things competing for your attention at any given time.
There is no wonder why in the last few years, our attention spans have become shorter and our ability to focus has decreased.
Not being able to focus can have a negative effect on how successful we are at work and in our personal lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management Mastery: 10X Your Time, Join the New Rich</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-mastery-10x-your-time-join-the-new-rich/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-mastery-10x-your-time-join-the-new-rich/</guid>
      <description>Time management is essential for the growth and success of any individual. The majority of the world&#39;s billionaires or successful people have excellent time management skills. They use their limited time so productively that the rest of the population finds it hard to emulate.
Good time management skills aren&#39;t about the amount of time available to implement a task. It&#39;s about making the little time you have to be as productive as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comunicación Asertiva y Empática</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/comunicaci%C3%B3n-asertiva-y-emp%C3%A1tica/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/comunicaci%C3%B3n-asertiva-y-emp%C3%A1tica/</guid>
      <description>Te ha pasado ¿Qué no logras crear confianza en un negocio? o te preguntas muy seguido ¿por qué no me entiendo con un compañero(a) de trabajo? o incluso has pensado que algo pasa contigo ¿por qué no atraes la relación de pareja que esperas?, en este curso podrás responderte a ti mism@ estos interrogantes, porque vas a potencializar tus habilidades comunicativas, las cuales te permitan crear lazos de confianza y empatía, en tus negocios, en las relaciones con los compañeros del trabajo, en los vínculos afectivos y en todas tus interacciones interpersonales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management &amp; Productivity Masterclass- Beat Overwhelm</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-productivity-masterclass-beat-overwhelm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 20:03:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-productivity-masterclass-beat-overwhelm/</guid>
      <description>Objective 1: Learn Time Management Fundamentals
Objective 2: Learn how to get all your thoughts out of your mind and on paper or in software
Objective 3: Learn the Time Management 80/20 Rule
Objective 4: Can you really Multi-task?
Objective 5: Learn from Elon Musk and Warren Buffet time management tools
Objective 6: Learn how to take back your day and get the most done
FACT 1: Despite time tracking apps, hints and tips being available, only 17% of people track their own time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Invaluable Benefits of integrity</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-invaluable-benefits-of-integrity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-invaluable-benefits-of-integrity/</guid>
      <description>Act confident: the best way to develop courage in front of an audience is to act as if you already have it. It also helps to take a few deep breaths before you begin speaking, to get the oxygen flowing to your brain. Stand tall, look your audience in the eyes, and don&#39;t fidget.
About Mehreen Siddiqui &amp;amp; Alexis Lenihan
Mehreen Siddiqui is a Certified High Performance Coach and John Maxwell Trainer and Facilitator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management &amp; Productivity for Effective Time Management</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-productivity-for-effective-time-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:57:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-productivity-for-effective-time-management/</guid>
      <description>Three reasons to TAKE THIS COURSE right now! The unique reasons for taking this course are: Complete, Concise, Confident Overview of Personal Productivity Hacks and Time Management Course especially if you want a certification to prove it - You will be confident that you have a complete overview of Time Management &amp;amp; Personal Productivity as the experts intended it, because I only teach accurately based on the expert teachings of the pros like Brian Tracy and Tony Robbins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acing Time Management &amp; Productivity: Your ultimate Program</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/acing-time-management-productivity-your-ultimate-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/acing-time-management-productivity-your-ultimate-program/</guid>
      <description>WHY THIS COURSE on Productivity and Time Management?
Are you here because you feel you are always behind with your work and that makes you feel stressed? Well congratulations for wanting to do something about it, as opposed to waiting for things to change.
This course will allow you to not only get back on top of your To-do list, but also will ensure you never get overwhelmed by your workload, which is really the main goal: You managing your to-do list and not Your list managing you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Telecommuting Course - Remote Work - Work Life</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-telecommuting-course-remote-work-work-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-telecommuting-course-remote-work-work-life/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Telecommuting Course - Remote Work - Work Life
Telecommuting - Remote Working - Tools for Working from Home - Better Organization for Work Live Balance &amp;amp; Productivity
Telecommuting and remote working from home can be a great way to live a professional life if you plan accordingly and learn this new way of doing business.
The recent public health crisis has forced millions of executives around the globe out of their offices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are you privacy savvy? A Beginner&#39;s Guide to Privacy Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/are-you-privacy-savvy-a-beginners-guide-to-privacy-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 22:09:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/are-you-privacy-savvy-a-beginners-guide-to-privacy-basics/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that Facebook Messenger, Skype, WhatsApp, Zoom, or other applications you use to connect with your family, friends, and colleagues record what you are chatting, talking and capture the data you present? They don’t share your private data; at least, they try to protect your data from hackers. However, these organizations use your data for analytics, which age group using which applications, topics in your conversations, etc.
The Privacy Act defines personal information as any recorded information about an identifiable individual, including race, national or ethnic origin, color, religion, age or marital status.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Organization Masterclass - Organize - Decluttering</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-organization-masterclass-organize-decluttering/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:15:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-organization-masterclass-organize-decluttering/</guid>
      <description>Complete Organization Masterclass - Organize - Decluttering
Organize for a Peak Performance Life - Improve Organization Skills Time Management Personal Productivity Decluttering
You can live a well organized life! Imagine if every aspect of your home, your office, your health, and your life were well organized?
You can make this happen. Organization can become part of your self identity.
Self development expert TJ Walker is a master at developing organization habits and individuals and organizations around the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neuroplasticity And CBT Complete Certification Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/neuroplasticity-and-cbt-complete-certification-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 22:17:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/neuroplasticity-and-cbt-complete-certification-course/</guid>
      <description>CBT is an intensive, short-term, problem-oriented approach. It was designed to be quick, practical and goal-oriented and to provide people with long-term skills to keep them healthy. The focus of cbt is on the problems that come up in a person’s day-to-day life. cbt helps people to look at how they interpret and evaluate what is happening around them and the effects these perceptions have on their emotional experience.
Childhood experiences and events, while not the focus of cbt, may also be reviewed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>German Productivity Hacks</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/german-productivity-hacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 11:27:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/german-productivity-hacks/</guid>
      <description>Germans are supposed to be highly productive and efficient but why is that? It&#39;s a combination of typical productivity hacks &amp;amp; habits which are hard wired into our culture and a bunch of strange habits which are sometimes counterproductive. But even those habits help us to succeed at the end of the day.
This course will both educate and entertain you: Learn how Germans work and why they are productive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organize your online business for busy entrepreneurs</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/organize-your-online-business-for-busy-entrepreneurs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 13:29:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/organize-your-online-business-for-busy-entrepreneurs/</guid>
      <description>Still working like a charm in 2022!
Join over 70,000 students from 190+ countries worldwide taking my courses today!
no fluff, no filler content, just straight to the point course that you can start and actually finish in 1 day!
A hard drive full of unfinished projects, a head that&#39;s spinning from too many things you need to get done, and everything around you seems like a huge mess?
It is time to get organized the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Productivity Powers Unleashed (2021 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/productivity-powers-unleashed-2021-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/productivity-powers-unleashed-2021-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the thirteenth course in Term 3 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Paul J. Meyer once said that &#34;Productivity is never an accident. It is always the result of a commitment to excellence, intelligent planning, and focused effort&#34;. The reality is it can be hard to stay productive at work or at home. We know the benefits of productivity. Being productive and efficient will help your company improve and maximize the use of human capital resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Productivity Plan &amp; Execute Effectively, Getting things done</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/productivity-plan-execute-effectively-getting-things-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 16:53:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/productivity-plan-execute-effectively-getting-things-done/</guid>
      <description>Research shows that a large number of professionals fail to execute their action plan successfully. The problem often isn’t with planning but with executing the planning. It is very important to take a well-structured approach to implement and execute what is planned.
The Art of Being Productive: Planning &amp;amp; Effective Execution is an online course, that will help professionals to overcome their most challenging execution obstacles on a working day and execute their tasks effectively to achieve better results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management Success</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 13:19:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-success/</guid>
      <description>Like many people I struggled with Time Management and Productivity for many years. It was an immense area of frustration for me because I tried all the strategies which, worked for a while; then everything seemed to go back to how it was.
I desperately searched for a lasting change.
I found it about 12 months ago when I instituted new thinking patterns and actions into my everyday living. I can honestly say that right now, my productivity has increased and I feel in control of my time and activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time management and life management to increase productivity</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-and-life-management-to-increase-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-and-life-management-to-increase-productivity/</guid>
      <description>Every second is important and precious in our lives, and if we spend it in the wrong manner, we risk losing what strive and seek for. So, don&#39;t lose any second or minute on trivial things which might make regret later.
If you don&#39;t know yet the importance of time and how can you invest it in the correct way, you are in the right place. Because I designed this course to suit every person who is looking for ways to manage his time more effectively and feels that he is always busy and does not have free time, and it is suitable for every person who does not know how to balance his studies or work with his personal life and always feels that he does not have enough time to do everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master And Overcome Remote Work Information Overload</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-and-overcome-remote-work-information-overload/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 13:13:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-and-overcome-remote-work-information-overload/</guid>
      <description>About The Course
This dynamic and unique course offers a different perspective on the nature of remote work, how it differs from face-to-face work and what you can do to make the most of it. Drawing from psychological research, the history of office-based work and the latest technologies in productivity, this is a practical guide on how to beat information overload at remote distances.
The lectures in this course cover not only psychological, technological and productivity issues, but also the social factors that can make remote work a challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goal Setting Mastery</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/goal-setting-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/goal-setting-mastery/</guid>
      <description>Setting Goals are paramount if you want to achieve true success in life. This course gives you the Step by Step plan to * Set and reach your Goals and thus achieve Success in your Life. * Multiply your Productivity.
* Stay Focused and get Results.
* Visualize your Goals.
* Review and Reflect your Goals.
* Be more accountable towards your Goals.
* Develop Winning Habits.
* Handle Obstacles during the process of reaching your Goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peak Productivity Hacks – Triple Your Productivity</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/peak-productivity-hacks-triple-your-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/peak-productivity-hacks-triple-your-productivity/</guid>
      <description>In this Peak Productivity course you will learn how the pros teach people how to maximize productivity. Get more done with the same hours you have and create more time and freedom for things that matter most!
Do you sometimes spend hours or even the entire day at your work desk, but can’t seem to get much done? Do you wish to be more productive for your time? Here’s the GOOD NEWS … There is a simple FORMULA to put an end to procrastination and get more done in less time … And we will share it with you in this course!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management Techniques 101: The Beginner&#39;s Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-techniques-101-the-beginners-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-techniques-101-the-beginners-guide/</guid>
      <description>Planning your day does not necessarily mean filling out all your available hours with tasks and ending up working all day. Working non-stop all day will end up burning you out and you will end up not finishing and getting behind your schedule instead
Finding the right moment for your different priorities you will find that you can accomplish more with less time.
The goal of this course is you are going to be more effective and efficiency by getting things done with less time so that you have time to do things you enjoy doing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flexible Laundry Systems for the Creative ADHD  Business Mum</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/flexible-laundry-systems-for-the-creative-adhd-business-mum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/flexible-laundry-systems-for-the-creative-adhd-business-mum/</guid>
      <description>WHO I AM AND WHY I AM EQUIPPED TO GUIDE YOU
I have ADHD. I am a mum of 5 successful ADHD children.
Throughout my life I have had my share of challenges and struggles related to ADHD. I have searched long and hard for the tools to unlock my ADHD. Searching for those answers has been one of the most difficult tasks of my life. I have found those answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management And Goal Planning: The Productivity Combo</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-and-goal-planning-the-productivity-combo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-and-goal-planning-the-productivity-combo/</guid>
      <description>What about setting 48-Hour Productivity from a 24-hour day? So many things, so little time, right? Wrong!
Time management is all about working SMARTER, not harder!
Time management, focus and motivation are the basis for planning and achieving our goals and being more productive. Distraction turns seemingly busy days into wasted time, producing a negative impact on our productivity.
This course will show you the best time management and goal planning strategies to focus on what really matters, prioritizing those actions that lead to the achievement of our short and long term goals in order to fulfill your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Put a Dead-Halt Stop to Self-Sabotage and Get Motivated</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/put-a-dead-halt-stop-to-self-sabotage-and-get-motivated/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 10:48:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/put-a-dead-halt-stop-to-self-sabotage-and-get-motivated/</guid>
      <description>Are you a lifelong student of personal development of transformation?
Do you need help with motivation, stress management, or productivity?
If you said &#34;yes&#34; to any of those, a MindMastery course is right for you.
Specifically, students who take our Put a Dead-Halt Stop to Self-Sabotage and Get Motivated course experience these roadblocks:
Self-sabotage
Procrastination and bad habits
A lack of motivation
And they report these benefits from the MindMastery experience:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Creative Way to Declutter and Organise with Your ADHD</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-creative-way-to-declutter-and-organise-with-your-adhd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-creative-way-to-declutter-and-organise-with-your-adhd/</guid>
      <description>Are you a woman with ADHD or ADHD tendencies? Are you a busy professional mum, struggling to balance your life and the life of your ADHD child? Only you know of the dark side lurking behind your front door. The clutter, the mess and general chaos. I know, because I have ADHD myself. I have struggled mightily for many years to find systems that work for my brain. I searched high and low.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Master Your Origin Challenge</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-master-your-origin-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-master-your-origin-challenge/</guid>
      <description>This course includes:
1 hours of on-demand video instruction
7 video sections
Over 30 downloadable exercises &amp;amp; resources
Downloadable book chapter
Full lifetime access
Access on mobile and TV
Certificate of completion
What you’ll learn:
Learn who and what you are and why.
Discover the “origin programming” done by your parents, etc. during your first 18 years of life.
Identify which of your traits and relationship characteristics come from your origin programming.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
