<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Productivity on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/personal-productivity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal Productivity on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:43:31 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/personal-productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Time Management Techniques 101: The Beginner&#39;s Guide</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/time-management-techniques-101-the-beginners-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:43:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/time-management-techniques-101-the-beginners-guide/</guid>
      <description>Planning your day does not necessarily mean filling out all your available hours with tasks and ending up working all day. Working non-stop all day will end up burning you out and you will end up not finishing and getting behind your schedule instead
Finding the right moment for your different priorities you will find that you can accomplish more with less time.
The goal of this course is you are going to be more effective and efficiency by getting things done with less time so that you have time to do things you enjoy doing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flexible Laundry Systems for the Creative ADHD  Business Mum</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/flexible-laundry-systems-for-the-creative-adhd-business-mum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/flexible-laundry-systems-for-the-creative-adhd-business-mum/</guid>
      <description>WHO I AM AND WHY I AM EQUIPPED TO GUIDE YOU
I have ADHD. I am a mum of 5 successful ADHD children.
Throughout my life I have had my share of challenges and struggles related to ADHD. I have searched long and hard for the tools to unlock my ADHD. Searching for those answers has been one of the most difficult tasks of my life. I have found those answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management And Goal Planning: The Productivity Combo</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/time-management-and-goal-planning-the-productivity-combo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/time-management-and-goal-planning-the-productivity-combo/</guid>
      <description>What about setting 48-Hour Productivity from a 24-hour day? So many things, so little time, right? Wrong!
Time management is all about working SMARTER, not harder!
Time management, focus and motivation are the basis for planning and achieving our goals and being more productive. Distraction turns seemingly busy days into wasted time, producing a negative impact on our productivity.
This course will show you the best time management and goal planning strategies to focus on what really matters, prioritizing those actions that lead to the achievement of our short and long term goals in order to fulfill your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peak Productivity Hacks – Triple Your Productivity</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/peak-productivity-hacks-triple-your-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/peak-productivity-hacks-triple-your-productivity/</guid>
      <description>In this Peak Productivity course you will learn how the pros teach people how to maximize productivity. Get more done with the same hours you have and create more time and freedom for things that matter most!
Do you sometimes spend hours or even the entire day at your work desk, but can’t seem to get much done? Do you wish to be more productive for your time? Here’s the GOOD NEWS … There is a simple FORMULA to put an end to procrastination and get more done in less time … And we will share it with you in this course!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Put a Dead-Halt Stop to Self-Sabotage and Get Motivated</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/put-a-dead-halt-stop-to-self-sabotage-and-get-motivated/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 10:48:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/put-a-dead-halt-stop-to-self-sabotage-and-get-motivated/</guid>
      <description>Are you a lifelong student of personal development of transformation?
Do you need help with motivation, stress management, or productivity?
If you said &#34;yes&#34; to any of those, a MindMastery course is right for you.
Specifically, students who take our Put a Dead-Halt Stop to Self-Sabotage and Get Motivated course experience these roadblocks:
Self-sabotage
Procrastination and bad habits
A lack of motivation
And they report these benefits from the MindMastery experience:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Creative Way to Declutter and Organise with Your ADHD</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-creative-way-to-declutter-and-organise-with-your-adhd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-creative-way-to-declutter-and-organise-with-your-adhd/</guid>
      <description>Are you a woman with ADHD or ADHD tendencies? Are you a busy professional mum, struggling to balance your life and the life of your ADHD child? Only you know of the dark side lurking behind your front door. The clutter, the mess and general chaos. I know, because I have ADHD myself. I have struggled mightily for many years to find systems that work for my brain. I searched high and low.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn To Focus: Meditation &amp; Mindfulness For ADHD</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-to-focus-meditation-mindfulness-for-adhd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 10:29:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-to-focus-meditation-mindfulness-for-adhd/</guid>
      <description>ADD and ADHD can make it hard to focus &amp;amp; get things done. You have lots of mental energy (that&#39;s why you&#39;re so smart!) but you have a hard time directing it to one thing at a time. Many people go through their entire lives in this scatter-brained state, jumping from thing to thing, never fully concentrating on, or actually enjoying, anything. This can lead to major school &amp;amp; career problems (not paying attention in class, not paying attention at work, not caring about what you&#39;re working on, bouncing from job to job, career to career, etc), and problems becoming a successful adult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art of stress free Productivity -Plan &amp; Execute Effectively</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/art-of-stress-free-productivity-plan-execute-effectively/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/art-of-stress-free-productivity-plan-execute-effectively/</guid>
      <description>Objectives: Research shows that a large number of professionals fail to execute their action plan successfully. The problem often isn’t with planning but with executing the planning. It is very important to take a well-structured approach to implement and execute what is planned.
The Art of Being Productive: Planning &amp;amp; Effective Execution is an online course, that will help professionals to overcome their most challenging execution obstacles on a working day and execute their tasks effectively to achieve better results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser Focus Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/laser-focus-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/laser-focus-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>We live in an era of information overload. We are bombarded with media, technology, entertainment, and notifications every day. It seems there are hundreds of people and things competing for your attention at any given time.
There is no wonder why in the last few years, our attention spans have become shorter and our ability to focus has decreased.
Not being able to focus can have a negative effect on how successful we are at work and in our personal lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Master Your Origin Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-master-your-origin-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-master-your-origin-challenge/</guid>
      <description>This course includes:
1 hours of on-demand video instruction
7 video sections
Over 30 downloadable exercises &amp;amp; resources
Downloadable book chapter
Full lifetime access
Access on mobile and TV
Certificate of completion

What you’ll learn:
Learn who and what you are and why.
Discover the “origin programming” done by your parents, etc. during your first 18 years of life.
Identify which of your traits and relationship characteristics come from your origin programming.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
