<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Productivity on </title>
    <link>/tags/personal-productivity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal Productivity on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 12:13:34 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/personal-productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Time Management Techniques 101: The Beginner&#39;s Guide</title>
      <link>/time-management-techniques-101-the-beginners-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 12:13:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/time-management-techniques-101-the-beginners-guide/</guid>
      <description>Planning your day does not necessarily mean filling out all your available hours with tasks and ending up working all day. Working non-stop all day will end up burning you out and you will end up not finishing and getting behind your schedule instead
Finding the right moment for your different priorities you will find that you can accomplish more with less time.
The goal of this course is you are going to be more effective and efficiency by getting things done with less time so that you have time to do things you enjoy doing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management And Goal Planning: The Productivity Combo</title>
      <link>/time-management-and-goal-planning-the-productivity-combo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 17:46:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/time-management-and-goal-planning-the-productivity-combo/</guid>
      <description>What about setting 48-Hour Productivity from a 24-hour day? So many things, so little time, right? Wrong!
Time management is all about working SMARTER, not harder!
Time management, focus and motivation are the basis for planning and achieving our goals and being more productive. Distraction turns seemingly busy days into wasted time, producing a negative impact on our productivity.
This course will show you the best time management and goal planning strategies to focus on what really matters, prioritizing those actions that lead to the achievement of our short and long term goals in order to fulfill your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser Focus Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/laser-focus-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/laser-focus-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>We live in an era of information overload. We are bombarded with media, technology, entertainment, and notifications every day. It seems there are hundreds of people and things competing for your attention at any given time.
There is no wonder why in the last few years, our attention spans have become shorter and our ability to focus has decreased.
Not being able to focus can have a negative effect on how successful we are at work and in our personal lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Master Your Origin Challenge</title>
      <link>/how-to-master-your-origin-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-master-your-origin-challenge/</guid>
      <description>This course includes:
1 hours of on-demand video instruction
7 video sections
Over 30 downloadable exercises &amp;amp; resources
Downloadable book chapter
Full lifetime access
Access on mobile and TV
Certificate of completion

What you’ll learn:
Learn who and what you are and why.
Discover the “origin programming” done by your parents, etc. during your first 18 years of life.
Identify which of your traits and relationship characteristics come from your origin programming.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
