<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web Design on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/web-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web Design on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/web-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Dreamweaver 2021 Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/adobe-dreamweaver-2021-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/adobe-dreamweaver-2021-projects/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Edit Websites but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Websites and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Dreamweaver 2021 Projects is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Web Tools are an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start Editing Websites like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Web Front End Learning Guide [Arabic Edition]</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-web-front-end-learning-guide-arabic-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-web-front-end-learning-guide-arabic-edition/</guid>
      <description>في هذه الدورة افترض الشخص الذي امامي لا يعرف اي شي عن عالم الويب
سكتون الدورة من الصفر فلا تحتاج لاي مؤهلات للدخول للدورة الدورة مركزة اكثر للمبتدئين، للاشخاص اللذين يريدون الدخول لعالم الويب
يعتبر تصميم الويب هو الجزء الابسط والامتع من الويب
هذه الدورة عبارة عن خمس دورات مجمعة في دورة واحدة

JavaScript is THE most important programming language you need to learn as a web developer - and with this course, you make sure that you will not miss a single thing you have to know as a JavaScript developer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A complete Website Development tool without Programming</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/a-complete-website-development-tool-without-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/a-complete-website-development-tool-without-programming/</guid>
      <description>Free Website Designing without Programming Language :
Once you pay for your web design, you are the owner of your website. We don’t use any proprietary software to keep you locked down. You’re free to take your website with you and make any changes.
Dynamic CMS
Get a site with all dynamic options of CMS. Site will be mobile ready and fit itself into any browser.
Features
We give you Blog, Photo / Video Gallery, News, Testimonial, Contact Form with Map with easy frontend editing option.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
