<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web Design on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/web-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web Design on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/web-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Web Design for Beginners: Build Websites in HTML &amp; CSS 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/web-design-for-beginners-build-websites-in-html-css-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/web-design-for-beginners-build-websites-in-html-css-2022/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to get started with web design, front-end development, or web development in general? If the answer is yes then you are in for a treat. In this course, you are going to learn everything you need to know about HTML and CSS which are basically the starting point of your career as a web developer. So why choose this course? why not any other course? Because I have made sure that every part of the course is informative, fun, and practical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Animate 2022 Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-animate-2022-ultimate-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-animate-2022-ultimate-guide/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Animate Video but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Videos and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Animate 2022 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Animation is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start Animating Videos like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Dreamweaver 2022 Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-dreamweaver-2022-ultimate-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-dreamweaver-2022-ultimate-guide/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Edit Websites but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Websites and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Dreamweaver 2022 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Web Tools are an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start Editing Websites like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Web Front End Learning Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-web-front-end-learning-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-web-front-end-learning-guide/</guid>
      <description>في هذه الدورة افترض الشخص الذي امامي لا يعرف اي شي عن عالم الويب
سكتون الدورة من الصفر فلا تحتاج لاي مؤهلات للدخول للدورة الدورة مركزة اكثر للمبتدئين، للاشخاص اللذين يريدون الدخول لعالم الويب
يعتبر تصميم الويب هو الجزء الابسط والامتع من الويب
هذه الدورة عبارة عن خمس دورات مجمعة في دورة واحدة
JavaScript is THE most important programming language you need to learn as a web developer - and with this course, you make sure that you will not miss a single thing you have to know as a JavaScript developer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress for Complete Beginners!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/wordpress-for-complete-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/wordpress-for-complete-beginners/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re here because you want to create your own WordPress websites, right?
You don&#39;t Need Coding Ath All no Javascript no html no css no Php
This WordPress for Beginners course is the perfect place to start. This complete WordPress course is designed for beginners like you who have never built a WordPress website (or any website for that matter).
WordPress is the perfect tool for creating a fully customized website for any purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cómo Crear una Tarjeta De Presentación con WordPress</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/c%C3%B3mo-crear-una-tarjeta-de-presentaci%C3%B3n-con-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/c%C3%B3mo-crear-una-tarjeta-de-presentaci%C3%B3n-con-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>WORDPRESS es una plataforma para construir y diseñar sitios web, sin tener experiencia en diseño web y programación, de forma rápida y sencilla.
El 38% de los sitios web de Internet han sido creados con WordPress. Es una herramienta muy fácil de aprender, en el cual puede personalizar un sitio web desde cero para cualquier propósito. Ya sea que desee crear una tarjeta digital interactiva, un blog o una tienda online para vender sus productos y servicios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curso WordPress 2022:  Cómo Crear una Página Web Desde Cero</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-wordpress-2022-c%C3%B3mo-crear-una-p%C3%A1gina-web-desde-cero/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 21:50:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-wordpress-2022-c%C3%B3mo-crear-una-p%C3%A1gina-web-desde-cero/</guid>
      <description>WORDPRESS es una plataforma para construir y diseñar un sitio web, sin tener experiencia en diseño web y programación, de forma rápida y sencilla.
El 38% de los sitios web de Internet han sido creados con WordPress. Es una herramienta muy fácil de aprender, en el cual puede personalizar un sitio web desde cero para cualquier propósito. Ya sea que desee crear un portafolio personal, un blog o un sitio web comercial para vender sus productos y servicios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cómo Crear una Tienda Online con WordPress Desde Cero 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/c%C3%B3mo-crear-una-tienda-online-con-wordpress-desde-cero-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/c%C3%B3mo-crear-una-tienda-online-con-wordpress-desde-cero-2022/</guid>
      <description>¿QUIERES CREAR UNA TIENDA ONLINE CON WORDPRESS Y VENDER TUS PRODUCTOS POR INTERNET?
Únete a nuestro curso completo para mostrarte cómo crear una tienda online profesional y totalmente personalizada en WordPress. Independientemente del propósito de tu tienda online, este curso te mostrará todo lo que necesita saber para crear una tienda online impresionante. He estado creando y usando tiendas virtuales durante más de 5 años para mis negocios en línea, lo que me convierte en el más calificado para enseñarte sobre cómo crear una tienda online con WordPress desde cero.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cómo Crear una Landing Page con WordPress Desde Cero 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/c%C3%B3mo-crear-una-landing-page-con-wordpress-desde-cero-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 19:20:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/c%C3%B3mo-crear-una-landing-page-con-wordpress-desde-cero-2022/</guid>
      <description>WORDPRESS es una plataforma para construir y diseñar sitios web, tales como blogs, tiendas virtuales, escuelas virtuales y landing pages (páginas de aterrizaje), sin necesidad de tener experiencia en diseño web y programación, puedes diseñar cualquier tipo de sitio web de forma fácil y simple.
El 38% de los sitios web de Internet han sido creados con WordPress. Es una herramienta muy fácil de aprender y se puede personalizar un sitio web de WordPress para cualquier propósito.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducción al diseño web: HTML y CSS</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introducci%C3%B3n-al-dise%C3%B1o-web-html-y-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 16:17:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introducci%C3%B3n-al-dise%C3%B1o-web-html-y-css/</guid>
      <description>El lenguaje de marcado de hipertexto (HTML) es el lenguaje de marcado estándar para los documentos diseñados para ser vistos en un navegador web. Puede ayudarse de tecnologías como las hojas de estilo en cascada (CSS). CSS describe cómo deben mostrarse los elementos HTML en la pantalla, en el papel o en otros medios.
Juntos entenderemos cómo crear una página web utilizando HTML y CSS
HTML5, CSS3, Head, Body, Semantic Tags.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curso de HostGator 2022: El Hosting Ideal Para WordPress</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-de-hostgator-2022-el-hosting-ideal-para-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 22:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-de-hostgator-2022-el-hosting-ideal-para-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>HOSTGATOR es un servicio de alojamiento web que proporciona alojamiento compartido, alojamiento en la nube, soluciones empresariales, alojamiento de correo electrónico y registro de dominio. Es uno de los proveedores de hosting (alojamiento web) más populares y con más demanda del internet. Es uno de los mejores hosting para sitios de WordPress y te permite publicar sitios web de manera fácil y rápida.
HostGator proporciona servicios de alojamiento web para sitios web de WordPress , Joomla , Magento , Drupal , PrestaShop y WooCommerce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/wordpress-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/wordpress-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to learn how to instantly create an amazing website for your business, blog or any other endeavor? Would you like me to teach you how to setup said website in under two hours, with your only upfront costs being hosting and a domain name ? Can you follow the easy instructions I will lay down for you in order to setup your very own commerce or entertainment platform?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Dreamweaver 2021 Projects</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-dreamweaver-2021-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-dreamweaver-2021-projects/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Edit Websites but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Websites and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Dreamweaver 2021 Projects is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Web Tools are an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start Editing Websites like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A complete Website Development tool without Programming</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/a-complete-website-development-tool-without-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/a-complete-website-development-tool-without-programming/</guid>
      <description>Free Website Designing without Programming Language :
Once you pay for your web design, you are the owner of your website. We don’t use any proprietary software to keep you locked down. You’re free to take your website with you and make any changes.
Dynamic CMS
Get a site with all dynamic options of CMS. Site will be mobile ready and fit itself into any browser.
Features
We give you Blog, Photo / Video Gallery, News, Testimonial, Contact Form with Map with easy frontend editing option.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
