<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Media Marketing on </title>
    <link>/tags/social-media-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social Media Marketing on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/social-media-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Complete Guide to Pinterest &amp; Pinterest Growth 2021</title>
      <link>/complete-guide-to-pinterest-pinterest-growth-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-guide-to-pinterest-pinterest-growth-2021/</guid>
      <description>Hey there, Nick Nyxson here.
Welcome to PinHeroes.
Only Pinterest course EVER to teach you how to grow your profile on Pinterest from 0 to 1 Million monthly viewers in just short few months.
Pinterest is one of the fastest-growing social media platforms and its main appeal is its unconventional way treat the content. It is an ONLY social media platform that Not just NOT RESTRICT&amp;nbsp;external content but actively encourages it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced LinkedIn Advertising: LinkedIn Ads Advanced B2B</title>
      <link>/advanced-linkedin-advertising-linkedin-ads-advanced-b2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/advanced-linkedin-advertising-linkedin-ads-advanced-b2b/</guid>
      <description>This B2B LinkedIn advertising course builds on my previous one by showing you how to build more scalable full-funnel campaigns, instead of just focusing on the low-hanging fruit when it comes to lead generation. You will learn how to build an efficient lead generation campaign with the appropriate content. Learn from someone who has been doing LinkedIn advertising since 2011, has worked for companies of varying sizes (including the Fortune 100), and has a top-tier marketing MBA from Philip Kotler&#39;s school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Ads B2B: Facebook Advertising&#43; Facebook Ads for B2B</title>
      <link>/facebook-ads-b2b-facebook-advertising-facebook-ads-for-b2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/facebook-ads-b2b-facebook-advertising-facebook-ads-for-b2b/</guid>
      <description>This is the ultimate course on business-to-business Facebook advertising!
I’ve been advertising on Facebook for over a decade. I was a VP of Marketing for a Google accelerator startup, a global marketing manager for Sony, and I’ve helped countless small businesses with digital advertising. I taught college-level digital marketing, and I studied digital marketing at the #1 ranked business school for marketing - the Kellogg School of Management. This is where the father of marketing, Philip Kotler, teaches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SnapChat Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/snapchat-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/snapchat-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Uncover the secrets to creating extremely successful marketing campaigns on Snapchat!
Snapchat is pretty much the hottest thing going these days, especially among the younger millennial crowd. The site allows users to send “Snaps”, which are pictures or videos, to their followers. These Snaps disappear after a short period of time, giving users the (somewhat false) sense that anything they do won’t last forever.
Snapchat can actually be extremely useful for your business, especially if you market to the younger crowd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Marketing B2B: Proven Social Media Marketing</title>
      <link>/social-media-marketing-b2b-proven-social-media-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/social-media-marketing-b2b-proven-social-media-marketing/</guid>
      <description>This is the ultimate course on business-to-business social media marketing. I’ve been doing B2B marketing on social media platforms like LinkedIn and Facebook for over a decade. I was a Vice President of Marketing for a Google accelerator startup, and I was a Global Marketing Manager for Sony. I also held numerous positions helping small startups with their social media marketing.
I taught college-level digital marketing, and I studied digital marketing and B2B marketing at the Kellogg School of Management, the #1-ranked business school for marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Marketing on Autopilot with Missinglettr</title>
      <link>/social-media-marketing-on-autopilot-with-missinglettr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/social-media-marketing-on-autopilot-with-missinglettr/</guid>
      <description>Did you know? The technique of automating social media activities in order to improve the results generated from social media channels is known as social media automation. It saves time and effort spent on administering social platforms, communicating with prospects, and increasing brand exposure for marketers.&amp;nbsp;Let&#39;s now ask you a quick question.
Have you ever dreamt of automating your social media campaigns with a magical platform that creates, schedules and provides reports of branded social media content while you&#39;re busy doing something else?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social media marketing strategy 2021. Launch your SMM!</title>
      <link>/social-media-marketing-strategy-2021.-launch-your-smm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/social-media-marketing-strategy-2021.-launch-your-smm/</guid>
      <description>What is social media marketing and its role in modern society?
Social media marketing is the use and management of different social media platforms to promote your brand, products, and services. It is a great tool to communicate with your existing customers and reach new ones. Social media marketing helps you drive traffic to your website, increase sales, build engagement and customer loyalty.
The use of social media is a fast-growing global trend.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
