<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Career Development on </title>
    <link>/tags/career-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Career Development on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/career-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Modern Job Interview Preparation, Tips &amp; Tricks Masterclass</title>
      <link>/modern-job-interview-preparation-tips-tricks-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/modern-job-interview-preparation-tips-tricks-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Modern businesses are hiring for culture, not just skills. Having a spot-on resume and cover letter is necessary, but it’s only the one third of the battle. Who you are as a person is just as important to your next employer as what you can do for them.
Most of us have been taught a specific traditional method for job interviewing. Once we learn the traditional method, it can be hard to change our approach!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Common Job Interview Questions with Answer</title>
      <link>/most-common-job-interview-questions-with-answer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/most-common-job-interview-questions-with-answer/</guid>
      <description>(The course content has updated according to students&#39; interest on 16th August 2019)
‘Why did you leave your last job?’ ‘What are your weaknesses?’ ‘If you were a type of fruit, what would you be, and why?’
OK, so some interview questions are easier to answer than others. But whilst you can’t predict exactly what you’ll be asked, any question has the potential to make you stumble – unless, of course, you’ve prepared in advance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automate your Job-Search with LoopCV in 2021</title>
      <link>/automate-your-job-search-with-loopcv-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:42:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/automate-your-job-search-with-loopcv-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the fifth course in Term 2 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Just imagine, how much time do you spend applying to jobs and all you get is a rejection letter after a week or a month&#39;s time?
Let&#39;s get this right as we elaborate on this problem faced by every job-seeker out there.
Do you actually spend a lot of time applying to a job, only to wait for weeks without any kind of positive feedback or response from recruiters and hiring managers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Become a Firefighter!</title>
      <link>/how-to-become-a-firefighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:42:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-become-a-firefighter/</guid>
      <description>Learn how a career as a firefighter can provide you with financial stability, allowing you to give back to your community and make you excited to come to work. Firefighting is a rewarding career that offers great opportunity for growth and advancement, amazing medical benefits and a high level of job satisfaction. This course will teach you how to prepare for your new career full of thrills and excitement while helping your community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Career Coaching Course - Career Development</title>
      <link>/the-complete-career-coaching-course-career-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-career-coaching-course-career-development/</guid>
      <description>Coaching is a $3 billion a year global business that&#39;s growing at rate of 7% annually. And one of the most important segments in this accelerating industry of career coaching where the median rate is $500 per hour. Tens of millions of people either want a new job, change their fields, or substantially improve their performance at their current occupation. We&#39;re going to give you the skills to help your clients reach success in both their personal and professional lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview Success</title>
      <link>/interview-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/interview-success/</guid>
      <description>This course is for anyone wanting to do better at Job interviews and successfully get a Job offer in the career you want!
Created by practising Recruitment professionals with decades of experience in Business and Executive Recruitment from both Corporate leadership and Recruitment Agency backgrounds, we know what interviewers are looking for and what it takes to stand out - the competition is tougher than ever and we will help you shine!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
