<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Career Development on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/career-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Career Development on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/career-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automate your Job-Search with LoopCV in 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/automate-your-job-search-with-loopcv-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/automate-your-job-search-with-loopcv-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the fifth course in Term 2 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Just imagine, how much time do you spend applying to jobs and all you get is a rejection letter after a week or a month&#39;s time?
Let&#39;s get this right as we elaborate on this problem faced by every job-seeker out there.
Do you actually spend a lot of time applying to a job, only to wait for weeks without any kind of positive feedback or response from recruiters and hiring managers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career Coaching Summary: TOP 5 Secrets of Effcient Sessions</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/career-coaching-summary-top-5-secrets-of-effcient-sessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/career-coaching-summary-top-5-secrets-of-effcient-sessions/</guid>
      <description>Hello, everyone! Thanks for paying attention to this lection!
Our world today is one that celebrates being busy. Being busy is something that we strive for, despite the feeling of overwhelm - the feeling of having no time like you’re drowning. Surely, being busy is a sign of success?
Well, not necessarily. You can be busy, but be in a job that you hate. One that makes you dread each morning, or you’re sat at your desk each day, bored and unfulfilled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career Change: The 5 Key Skills To Change Your Career</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/career-change-the-5-key-skills-to-change-your-career/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/career-change-the-5-key-skills-to-change-your-career/</guid>
      <description>This is a step by step course on HOW TO CHANGE YOUR CAREER!

Welcome to this 2 hour course that will teach you the five key skills that high achievers use to change their careers!

My name is Paul and I&#39;ll be your instructor. :-) I&#39;m a Career Coach, Finance Director &amp;amp; ex PriceWaterhouseCoopers Consultant.

I guarantee that this course will help you change careers - or your money back, no questions asked!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win at Job Interviews for High Potential Candidates</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/win-at-job-interviews-for-high-potential-candidates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/win-at-job-interviews-for-high-potential-candidates/</guid>
      <description>In many High Profile, Consultancy, Leadership and Strategic roles, employers are looking not only for High performers but also for candidates who are High Potentials to advance and significantly contribute to an organisation and potentially advance to Senior Executive Leadership roles based on their evidenced Behavioral and Competency skill set. If you want to get on a fast Management or a High Potential training track within top organisations you need to demonstrate how you excel in key areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win at Job Interviews for Recent Graduates</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/win-at-job-interviews-for-recent-graduates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/win-at-job-interviews-for-recent-graduates/</guid>
      <description>This course is for anyone wanting to do better at Job interviews and successfully get a Job offer in the career you want!
This course is not just about getting any job, its about getting the job that will set you firmly on your career path with your ideal brand name and chosen professional direction.
Ideal for Recent Graduates and people with relatively little professional working experience.
Fulfilling your career ambitions is a daily mission, and Winning at critical job interviews for that job you want is just the start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview Essentials</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/interview-essentials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/interview-essentials/</guid>
      <description>This course provides insights and best practices to help enhance your skills to land an entry-level or mid-level job. Here are some of the topics covered in this course:
Interview skills: learn key skills you need to have to do well in an interview.
Job application: learn best practices to use when filling out job applications.
Resume: learn some quick tips to help you put together a professional resume.
Your internet presence: learn how to present yourself online to ensure you don’t scare off potential employers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to find first Job in certain fields/ Common tips</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-find-first-job-in-certain-fields/-common-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-find-first-job-in-certain-fields/-common-tips/</guid>
      <description>The goal of hiring managers is not just to hire people who need a job. It’s to hire people who believe in their organization, its mission and the work that’s involved in the job position. Every hiring manager knows: Hire people to do a job and they’ll work for your money. Hire people who believe in the work and they’ll work for their passion.

And this is not a case of “fake it until you make it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern Job Interview Preparation, Tips &amp; Tricks Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/modern-job-interview-preparation-tips-tricks-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/modern-job-interview-preparation-tips-tricks-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Modern businesses are hiring for culture, not just skills. Having a spot-on resume and cover letter is necessary, but it’s only the one third of the battle. Who you are as a person is just as important to your next employer as what you can do for them.
Most of us have been taught a specific traditional method for job interviewing. Once we learn the traditional method, it can be hard to change our approach!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Common Job Interview Questions with Answer</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/most-common-job-interview-questions-with-answer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/most-common-job-interview-questions-with-answer/</guid>
      <description>(The course content has updated according to students&#39; interest on 16th August 2019)
‘Why did you leave your last job?’ ‘What are your weaknesses?’ ‘If you were a type of fruit, what would you be, and why?’
OK, so some interview questions are easier to answer than others. But whilst you can’t predict exactly what you’ll be asked, any question has the potential to make you stumble – unless, of course, you’ve prepared in advance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Become a Firefighter!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-become-a-firefighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:42:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-become-a-firefighter/</guid>
      <description>Learn how a career as a firefighter can provide you with financial stability, allowing you to give back to your community and make you excited to come to work. Firefighting is a rewarding career that offers great opportunity for growth and advancement, amazing medical benefits and a high level of job satisfaction. This course will teach you how to prepare for your new career full of thrills and excitement while helping your community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Career Coaching Course - Career Development</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-career-coaching-course-career-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-career-coaching-course-career-development/</guid>
      <description>Coaching is a $3 billion a year global business that&#39;s growing at rate of 7% annually. And one of the most important segments in this accelerating industry of career coaching where the median rate is $500 per hour. Tens of millions of people either want a new job, change their fields, or substantially improve their performance at their current occupation. We&#39;re going to give you the skills to help your clients reach success in both their personal and professional lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview Success</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/interview-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/interview-success/</guid>
      <description>This course is for anyone wanting to do better at Job interviews and successfully get a Job offer in the career you want!
Created by practising Recruitment professionals with decades of experience in Business and Executive Recruitment from both Corporate leadership and Recruitment Agency backgrounds, we know what interviewers are looking for and what it takes to stand out - the competition is tougher than ever and we will help you shine!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
