<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Other Teaching &amp; Academics on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/other-teaching-academics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Other Teaching &amp; Academics on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/other-teaching-academics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>master layer farm management the business of millionaires</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-layer-farm-management-the-business-of-millionaires/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-layer-farm-management-the-business-of-millionaires/</guid>
      <description>introduction history of industry POULTRY-KEEPING is interesting because it gives pleasure as well as profit to persons of both sexes, all ages all walks in life m all sections of the country It is useful alike on the farm and in the City back-yard In the cold in the sunny, in the hill and mountain country, or on the plain It may be conducted as an exclusive business or as a side line It affords pleasure and profit for rich and poor It is the universal agricultural industry he best way to start a poultry enterprise is to begin modestly and let the business build its increases It is believed that poultry production started in Asia over 3000 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation - Part 1 &#43; Live Class</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-part-1--live-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-part-1--live-class/</guid>
      <description>Do you remember the &#34;Jetsons show&#34;? The Jetsons fascinated me and everyone else around me. Thoughts of moving sidewalks, self-driving vehicles and robot housekeepers - fuelled my daydreams to the core. Let&#39;s now talk about the present time and the tech that is evolving.
Nowadays, I can command a robotic tool, device or tech to tell me the next day’s weather, read an e-book to me, play my preferred podcasts and even vacuum my flooring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General bacteriology a concise course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/general-bacteriology-a-concise-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/general-bacteriology-a-concise-course/</guid>
      <description>Bacteriology basics principles in half hour in in easy way it is suitable for professional need to refresh their knowledge and for beginners i and for student in secondary school and medical student science students agriculture students
In this course we introduce basics in interesting methods slides quizzes assignments we give a brief about history of microbiology he beginnings of bacteriology paralleled the development of the microscope. The first person to see microorganisms was probably the Dutch naturalist van Leeuwenhoek, who in 1683 described some animalcules, as they were then called, in water, saliva, and other substances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>practical bacteriology from scratch</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/practical-bacteriology-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/practical-bacteriology-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>practical bacteriology from scratch your safety first take care when working with pathogenic microorganisms wear coat when you are in lab and remove after finish keep the lab disk for equipment only wear gloves when dealing with microorganisms clean clean table before and after test mask eye protect keep your hand away from mouth and eye and nose use mechanical pipetting report the spill and disinfect the area well wash hands after any procedure deal well with fire smooth small one with towel large one use expenditure follow the instructions included in lab safety manual be professional in handling microscope there are many types with many uses bright field microscope dark field microscope phase contrast microscope fluorescent microscope electro microscope it is essential tool practice using the microscope with low power medium power high power and take care when use oil immersion lens sterilization the most important topic in microbiology without keeping your environment sterile it is impossible to obtain Apure culture sterilization methods heat sterilization sterilization by radiation sterilization by disinfectant chemicals use of antimicrobial bacterial culture is a method for isolate bacteria the culture may be natural in origin or synthetic or both culture may be ordinary enriched blood agar is enriched media They contain substances Blood ,Serum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2022 - Part 3</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2022-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2022-part-3/</guid>
      <description>Ready to create ebooks in minutes in 2022?
Welcome to this superb course that will walk you through the future of content creation and eBook generation. Taking a leap from RoboAuthor Part 2, this Part 3 course taught by Digital Marketing Legend Srinidhi Ranganathan will continue your adventure in content writing to unlock opportunities for ultra-fast eBook writing and creation with the power of Artificial Intelligence. We must know that artificial intelligence will create amazing content today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing a scientific research article</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/writing-a-scientific-research-article/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/writing-a-scientific-research-article/</guid>
      <description>This course is here to help people who are relatively new to writing scientific research articles with the writing process. I tried to make the course that I wish I had when I was writing my own first research article. It is meant to help you become more effective at writing, and to get you started writing immediately, while taking this course. In section one, you will
Learn about the different types of scientific article</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desafío Súper Profesionales 3.0 Exponencial</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/desaf%C3%ADo-s%C3%BAper-profesionales-3.0-exponencial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/desaf%C3%ADo-s%C3%BAper-profesionales-3.0-exponencial/</guid>
      <description>La inteligencia humana va más allá de los aspectos cognitivos e intelectuales. Existen muchos estudios que demuestran que las carencias en las habilidades de Inteligencia Emocional afectan a los seres humanos dentro y fuera del contexto social.
Las personas emocionalmente inteligentes no sólo son más hábiles para percibir, comprender y manejar sus propias emociones, sino también son más capaces de extrapolar sus habilidades de percepción, comprensión y manejo a las emociones de los demás.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invade Your Classroom with Digital Robot Teachers in 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/invade-your-classroom-with-digital-robot-teachers-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 22:09:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/invade-your-classroom-with-digital-robot-teachers-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience the online course &#34;Invade Your Classroom with Digital Robot Teachers in 2022&#34;.
Get ready to provide professional training using computer avatars that directly interact and engage with users. The impact of avatars on education is simply incredible. Avatar-guided programs allow teachers like you to train in a virtual classroom.
What&#39;s having an avatar all about?
An avatar is a figure or character that can be created and customized using cloud-based tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insight to Post Pandemic: Importance of Lean Six Sigma</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/insight-to-post-pandemic-importance-of-lean-six-sigma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/insight-to-post-pandemic-importance-of-lean-six-sigma/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this ultimate course on &#34;Insight to Post Pandemic: Importance of Lean Six Sigma&#34; that contains vaulable lessons taught by &#34;Casey Ang&#34; and &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34;.
Since its introduction as a corporate strategy by Jack Welch at General Electric in 1995, Six Sigma has come a long way. Since then, it has been widely adopted in a variety of industries.
The Greek letter sigma is used by statisticians to represent the variation in a process and we all know that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2022 - Part 5</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2022-part-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2022-part-5/</guid>
      <description>Ready to see how Artificial Intelligence (AI) will take over the fiction-writing world by storm?
Welcome to experience &#34;RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2022 - Part 5&#34;.
Computer-generated fiction might seem like a tipping point for artificial intelligence (AI), but it could help us to understand the incredible world we live in and how technology has changed from time to time. The real issue of machine intelligence and literature is always compared with the potential of what human intelligence could do and machines cannot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ajedrez Esencial. Aprende a jugar Ajedrez desde CERO</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ajedrez-esencial.-aprende-a-jugar-ajedrez-desde-cero/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 16:17:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ajedrez-esencial.-aprende-a-jugar-ajedrez-desde-cero/</guid>
      <description>Actualmente, el ajedrez ha tomado gran protagonismo, luego de la gran serie de Netflix &#34;Gambito de dama&#34;, muchos han buscado cómo aprender a jugar y adentrarse en el deporte.
En este curso, te enseñaré a comenzar en el ajedrez sin ningún conocimiento previo, aprenderás desde las bases y comprenderás la manera de jugar al ajedrez.
Aprenderás a mover las piezas, temas estrategicos, temas tácticos, temas de finales... Con este conocimiento podrás jugar al Ajedrez con tus amigos, familiares o incluso en alguna plataforma de Ajedrez Online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aromaterapia Veterinaria - Aceites Esenciales en el Perro</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aromaterapia-veterinaria-aceites-esenciales-en-el-perro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aromaterapia-veterinaria-aceites-esenciales-en-el-perro/</guid>
      <description>¡Bienvenidos a este curso de Aromaterapia Veterinaria Canina!
El uso de aceites esenciales en medicina veterinaria esta en pleno auge. Muchas preguntas surgen acerca de la posibilidad de su empleo en el perro: cómo, cuánto, cuándo y cuáles aceites se pueden elegir. Este curso pretende contestar a esas preguntas, proponiendo un uso racional y medido de los aceites esenciales en el perro.
Dedicado a veterinarios, estudiantes de veterinaria, criadores y dueños responsables de mascotas, este curso permite resolver los casos más comunes con la ayuda de la aromaterapia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curso de Fitoterapia Canina : Plantas Medicinales para Perro</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-de-fitoterapia-canina-plantas-medicinales-para-perro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-de-fitoterapia-canina-plantas-medicinales-para-perro/</guid>
      <description>¡Bienvenidos a este curso de Fitoterapia Veterinaria Canina!
El uso de plantas medicinales en medicina veterinaria esta en pleno auge. Muchas preguntas surgen acerca de la posibilidad de su empleo en el perro: cómo, cuánto, cuándo y cuáles plantas se pueden eligir. Este curso pretende contestar a esas preguntas, proponiendo un uso racional y medido de las plantas en el perro.
Dedicado a veterinarios, estudiantes de veterinaria, criadores y dueños responsables de mascotas, este curso permite resolver los casos más comunes con la ayuda de la fitoterapia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2021 - Part 4</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-4/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this marvelous course that will walk you through powerful content writing tools that will aid you in your career as a content creator. Taking a leap from RoboAuthor Part 3, this Part 4 course taught by Digital Marketing Legend Srinidhi Ranganathan and Saranya Srinidhi will continue your adventure in content writing to unlock opportunities for more ultra-fast writing and creation with the ultimate power of Artificial Intelligence (AI). Until now, people believed that machines are unable to mimic the dynamic thought process or what we call imagination - that humans leverage to write.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2021 - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:30:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this superb course that will walk you through the future of content creation. Taking a leap from RoboAuthor Part 1, this Part 2 course taught by Digital Marketing Legend Srinidhi Ranganathan and MasterMind Saranya Srinidhi will continue your adventure in content writing to open a new door of opportunities that is incredibly futuristic. It is undoubtedly one of the most challenging tasks to create content for your digital marketing campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fisioterapia Veterinaria : Masajes en pequeños animales</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fisioterapia-veterinaria-masajes-en-peque%C3%B1os-animales/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 13:37:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fisioterapia-veterinaria-masajes-en-peque%C3%B1os-animales/</guid>
      <description>Bienvenido al mundo apasionante de la terapia con las manos !
Un sistema sencillo empleado desde los inicios, resultando muchas veces en una acción instintiva, cuando nos golpeamos y nuestras madres nos frotaba la zona con la mano para calmar el dolor.
En medicina veterinaria tuvo su comienzo en los caballos en los emperadores de Roma, a los cuales se les aplicaba distintas formas de masajes. Todo esto determinado por factores económicos y sociales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corso base di  Scrittura Creativa Vol. 1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-base-di-scrittura-creativa-vol.-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 18:19:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-base-di-scrittura-creativa-vol.-1/</guid>
      <description>Questo corso è per i veri appassionati di scrittura, per chi prova l&#39;irrefrenabile desiderio di passare da accanito lettore a scrittore cambiando l&#39;ottica e la veduta. Al contempo è destinato anche a coloro che non ambiscono ancora ad alcuna pubblicazione di opere personali ma hanno semplicemente una smoderata passione per la scrittura e aspirano a scoprirne di più per una pura passione personale.
Se tu che mi stai leggendo hai sempre nutrito il desiderio di scrivere un libro (a prescindere dal genere che esso rappresenti), ma ti sei sentito bloccato alla prima pagina, rimasta a lungo &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Paper Writing via Advanced Research Methods</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/professional-paper-writing-via-advanced-research-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 14:59:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/professional-paper-writing-via-advanced-research-methods/</guid>
      <description>This course will provide a prospect for participants to establish or progress their considerate of optimization algorithms through critical examination of research process, approaches and publishing dimensions.
The course introduces elements of the research process within quantitative, qualitative, and mixed methods domains. Participants will use these underpinnings to begin to critically understand design thinking, large scale optimization, graph mining and hashing algorithms. They would be able to develop understanding to formulate a research question and answer it by framing an effective research methodology based on market algorithms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book of 1 Thessalonians Bible Study &amp; 5 Insightful Lessons</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/book-of-1-thessalonians-bible-study-5-insightful-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 13:01:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/book-of-1-thessalonians-bible-study-5-insightful-lessons/</guid>
      <description>Why did Paul write the letter to the Thessalonians?
To ensure they remained in faith because he was unable to visit them, therefore, he had to send Timothy. He also wrote the letter to the Thessalonians to encourage them in faith so that they will not be unsettled by Paul’s trials (1 Thessalonians 2v17-3v3). He also wrote the letter to silence those who felt he took advantage of the people of Thessalonica.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrivere per Bambini e Ragazzi - Scrittura Creativa Vol. 2</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/scrivere-per-bambini-e-ragazzi-scrittura-creativa-vol.-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 12:13:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/scrivere-per-bambini-e-ragazzi-scrittura-creativa-vol.-2/</guid>
      <description>In questo corso di scrittura creativa per bambini e per ragazzi parlerò delle tecniche che vi sono dietro lo scrivere in base a due fattori: la fascia di età e il genere. In questo corso in particolar modo i nostri lettori vengono suddivisi in quattro fasce di età:
1. al di sotto dei 5 anni
2. dai 5 ai 7 anni
3. dagli 8 agli 11
4. dai 12 ai 14</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corso completo di Teatro: esercizi pratici (Per Formatori)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-completo-di-teatro-esercizi-pratici-per-formatori/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:15:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-completo-di-teatro-esercizi-pratici-per-formatori/</guid>
      <description>Essere un Formatore Teatrale non è semplice, ci si ritrova ogni volta in contesti differenti, con persone di età diverse e che giungono con motivazioni più disparate. Per tali motivi ho cercato di non tralasciare alcun aspetto sul come impostare un Laboratorio Teatrale: dall&#39;organizzazione delle lezioni, alla tempistica, e poi tutti gli esercizi più importanti per fare un laboratorio teatrale, ognuno spiegato nei minimi particolari.
A dispetto di tanto impegno per fare un laboratorio di teatro, alla fine si hanno grandi soddisfazioni: si assiste lezione dopo lezione alla crescita degli aspiranti attori, li si vede affrontare i vari ostacoli e superarli, ed io stessa dopo ogni laboratorio mi sento arricchita, è qualcosa che solo chi ha sentito il profumo di un palco può capire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Allama Iqbal Poetry Explanation Course in Urdu</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-allama-iqbal-poetry-explanation-course-in-urdu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 20:19:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-allama-iqbal-poetry-explanation-course-in-urdu/</guid>
      <description>Allama Muhammad Iqbal is one of the most outstanding poet-philosophers of the Indian sub-continent belonging to the modern period. His intellectual genius has reigned supreme in the arena of Islamic philosophy during the twentieth century and is likely to direct and influence the Islamic Intellectual tradition in the twenty first century as well. His sublime poetry and philosophy inspired millions of Muslims to wake up to the reality of the times and forge a destiny for themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improvvisazione Teatrale e Comica: dalla teoria alla pratica</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/improvvisazione-teatrale-e-comica-dalla-teoria-alla-pratica/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/improvvisazione-teatrale-e-comica-dalla-teoria-alla-pratica/</guid>
      <description>Cos&#39;è un&#39; improvvisazione? E se si chiama IMPROVVISAZIONE perché studiarla in un corso?
Perché sono state scritte tonnellate di libri a tal riguardo?
L&#39;improvvisazione è una vera e propria Arte e come tale necessita di studio, tecnica ed esperienza. Non si può improvvisare senza possedere le conoscenze adatte.
Esistono due differenti forme di improvvisazione, quella &#34;muta&#34; nella quale l&#39;unico strumento comunicativo è rappresentato dal corpo e quella &#34;parlata&#34; durante la quale voce(storytelling) e corpo agiscono all&#39;unisono, quest&#39;ultima è l&#39;improvvisazione di cui ti parlerò in questo corso.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
