<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Operations on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/operations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Operations on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/operations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Global Logistics in Supply Chain Management &amp; Urban Planning</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/global-logistics-in-supply-chain-management-urban-planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/global-logistics-in-supply-chain-management-urban-planning/</guid>
      <description>This course provides the concepts and skill sets to undertake urban landuse planning and transportation planning for urban transportation along with Logistics and Supply Chain Management and to analyze the impact of various policies either related to infrastructure development, environmental regulation and urban expansion and how to smoothen the cargo flow in Logistics and Supply Chain. This will help future planners to plan for our smart cities in a more comprehensive way to make sure that the Urban transportation management and Logistics in Supply Chain operate smoothly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified Supply Chain Professional (CSCP) PRO Tests</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-supply-chain-professional-cscp-pro-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-supply-chain-professional-cscp-pro-tests/</guid>
      <description>Certified Supply Chain Professional (CSCP) PRO Tests
Most Professional questions for Supply Chain Professional (CSCP); Pass with 99% of confidence
In commerce, supply chain management (SCM) is the management of the flow of goods and services, between businesses and locations, and includes the movement and storage of raw materials, of work-in-process inventory, and of finished goods as well as end to end order fulfillment from point of origin to point of consumption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Accounting–Inventory &amp; Merchandising Transactions</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accountinginventory-merchandising-transactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accountinginventory-merchandising-transactions/</guid>
      <description>We cover merchandising transactions and cost flow assumptions.
Merchandising transaction, those transaction that deal with inventory, including the purchase of inventory and the sale of inventory. We will discuss related topics including sales discounts, purchase discounts, sales return and allowances, shrinkage and the cost of goods sold calculation. We will also compare and contrast a perpetual inventory system and periodic inventory system, listing and describing the pros and cons of each, explaining when each may be most appropriate in practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APICS Certified Supply Chain Professional CSCP Practice Exam</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/apics-certified-supply-chain-professional-cscp-practice-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/apics-certified-supply-chain-professional-cscp-practice-exam/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to crush the APICS Certified Supply Chain Professional and get certified?
Today is a competitive world and the smartest, best, and most qualified get paid a lot of money to work in amazing fields. But you don’t need a college degree, certification is an amazing path that opens up new opportunities and shows employers that you are the cream of the crop. We know that APICS certification will add some flair to that resume and help you get amazing new roles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transportation System Planning Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/transportation-system-planning-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 20:03:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/transportation-system-planning-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Transportation System Planning Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn industry specific knowledge about system planning such as that found in the transportation industry.
I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on how to develop the key knowledge needed to do effective strategic decision making throughout the transportation planning process.
I will teach you the basic concepts of the transportation planning framework as well as different bits and pieces on how to create an effective transportation plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Disaster Recovery - IT &amp; Business Continuity Planning (BCP)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/disaster-recovery-it-business-continuity-planning-bcp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/disaster-recovery-it-business-continuity-planning-bcp/</guid>
      <description>Over this course, we&#39;ll be covering the basics surrounding DR and BCP planning, as well as some different types of disasters and the best ways to mitigate against them.
Topics on this course are as follows:
* Overview of Disaster Recovery (DR) and Business Continuity Planning (BCP)
* Mitigating against different types of disasters and maximising the chances of data recovery
* Common issues than can occur during a DR test or real world disaster</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSCP (Certified Supply Chain Professional) APICS Exams 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cscp-certified-supply-chain-professional-apics-exams-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 21:29:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cscp-certified-supply-chain-professional-apics-exams-2022/</guid>
      <description>Certified Supply Chain Professional (CSCP) Practice Exams
Get a passing grade in your CSCP exam on the first try
The 700+ questions in these practice exams are designed so you understand where your gaps are and how ready you are for the real one. The first three practice exams elaborate on the knowledge area and the other two exams are designed to determine your level of readiness.
If you are reading this sentence right now, you are in one of two groups of supply chain professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inventory Control: Beginner&#39;s Guide to Warehouse Management</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/inventory-control-beginners-guide-to-warehouse-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 21:10:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/inventory-control-beginners-guide-to-warehouse-management/</guid>
      <description>Keeping track of inventory as a multichannel retailer, wholesaler, or internet brand can be a difficult task. However, organizations may now use systems, processes, and technology to help them streamline their supply chains. Inventory control solutions allow you to track your Warehouse efficiently and correctly. This tutorial will teach you all you need to know about inventory control. Any organization, large or little, will benefit from the easy-to-understand professional advice, guidance, formulae, methods, policy formulation, and software guidance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become a Corporate Receptionist</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/become-a-corporate-receptionist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 17:04:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/become-a-corporate-receptionist/</guid>
      <description>Receptionist jobs are often seen as short-term roles, part-time positions, or stepping stones on your overall career path. But being a career receptionist can actually be an incredibly fulfilling career path in itself, with great earning potential. If you’re looking for a new role and are looking for something rewarding, fun, and with great prospects, then this course is for you.
+++ Pay can be generous
Many receptionists will start out on average salaries, but there’s ample opportunity for that to grow over time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Air Logistics Management in Supply Chain Management</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/global-air-logistics-management-in-supply-chain-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/global-air-logistics-management-in-supply-chain-management/</guid>
      <description>This Course will prove to be a boon to you and help you boost your logistics and supply chain management knowledge as it is a specialized course on Aviation Logistics in Supply chain management as Air Logistics Management is very important if your aim is to move your cargo on urgent basis with minimum risk, As in International Trade , Supply chain management &amp;amp; Shipping there are many risks involved.Its a base for inventory Movement and is ideal for Amazon FBA, Drop Shipping, Outsourcing , Retail business owners, Inventory, Logistics and Supply chain management professionals as it is prepared with focus on practical knowledge which you can use in you day to day work as the instructor himself is a Supply Chain and Logistics Management professional managing Shipping, Freight Forwarding, Surface Transport, Aviation Logistics for many exporters and importers and has a professional qualification in then Feild of Logistics Management and Supply Chain Management Why is Logistics and Supply chain management the Future ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conflict Resolution and De-Escalation for Upset Customers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/conflict-resolution-and-de-escalation-for-upset-customers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/conflict-resolution-and-de-escalation-for-upset-customers/</guid>
      <description>CLIENT MANAGEMENT IS CONFLICT MANAGEMENT
Client management is not an easy position. In fact, any relationship management position is tough.
Namely, because clients are frequently angry or disappointed at your company.
And whose job is it to fix the mess? Yours.
Not to mention that you have to both make the company AND the client satisfied.
All in all, it&#39;s not a very easy position.
What most professionals underestimate, however, is the role of conflict management in client management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Production and Inventory Management professional</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2021-production-and-inventory-management-professional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:50:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2021-production-and-inventory-management-professional/</guid>
      <description>2021 Production and Inventory Management professional
TOP common and Most Frequent questions with answers for Production and Inventory Management professional
This course will qualify you with the latest and most common questions about Production and Inventory Management
Inventory management refers to the process of ordering, storing and using a company&#39;s inventory. This includes the management of raw materials, components and finished products, as well as warehousing and processing such items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business of Logistics - Cargo and inventory management</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/business-of-logistics-cargo-and-inventory-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/business-of-logistics-cargo-and-inventory-management/</guid>
      <description>This course will give you a good understanding of the Business of Logistics and what is the role of it from our daily operational experience. You will learn what is logistics Management, supply chain management, and procurement as well as we will discuss the transportation of cargo processes via Air cargo and Ocean Cargo. Topics like inventory and warehouse management will be covered.
Business of logistics is your guide to develop your logistics skills by knowing what is the role of it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
