<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Operations on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/operations/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Operations on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/operations/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Air Logistics Management in Supply Chain Management</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/global-air-logistics-management-in-supply-chain-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/global-air-logistics-management-in-supply-chain-management/</guid>
      <description>This Course will prove to be a boon to you and help you boost your logistics and supply chain management knowledge as it is a specialized course on Aviation Logistics in Supply chain management as Air Logistics Management is very important if your aim is to move your cargo on urgent basis with minimum risk, As in International Trade , Supply chain management &amp;amp; Shipping there are many risks involved.Its a base for inventory Movement and is ideal for Amazon FBA, Drop Shipping, Outsourcing , Retail business owners, Inventory, Logistics and Supply chain management professionals as it is prepared with focus on practical knowledge which you can use in you day to day work as the instructor himself is a Supply Chain and Logistics Management professional managing Shipping, Freight Forwarding, Surface Transport, Aviation Logistics for many exporters and importers and has a professional qualification in then Feild of Logistics Management and Supply Chain Management</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conflict Resolution and De-Escalation for Upset Customers</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/conflict-resolution-and-de-escalation-for-upset-customers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/conflict-resolution-and-de-escalation-for-upset-customers/</guid>
      <description>CLIENT MANAGEMENT IS CONFLICT MANAGEMENT
Client management is not an easy position. In fact, any relationship management position is tough.
Namely, because clients are frequently angry or disappointed at your company.
And whose job is it to fix the mess? Yours.
Not to mention that you have to both make the company AND the client satisfied.
All in all, it&#39;s not a very easy position.
What most professionals underestimate, however, is the role of conflict management in client management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Production and Inventory Management professional</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-production-and-inventory-management-professional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:50:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-production-and-inventory-management-professional/</guid>
      <description>2021 Production and Inventory Management professional
TOP common and Most Frequent questions with answers for Production and Inventory Management professional

This course will qualify you with the latest and most common questions about Production and Inventory Management

Inventory management refers to the process of ordering, storing and using a company&#39;s inventory. This includes the management of raw materials, components and finished products, as well as warehousing and processing such items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business of Logistics - Cargo and inventory management</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/business-of-logistics-cargo-and-inventory-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/business-of-logistics-cargo-and-inventory-management/</guid>
      <description>This course will give you a good understanding of the Business of Logistics and what is the role of it from our daily operational experience. You will learn what is logistics Management, supply chain management, and procurement as well as we will discuss the transportation of cargo processes via Air cargo and Ocean Cargo. Topics like inventory and warehouse management will be covered.
Business of logistics is your guide to develop your logistics skills by knowing what is the role of it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>