<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Network &amp; Security on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/network-security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Network &amp; Security on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/network-security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Practical Cisco Networking Labs in Cisco Packet Tracer</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/practical-cisco-networking-labs-in-cisco-packet-tracer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/practical-cisco-networking-labs-in-cisco-packet-tracer/</guid>
      <description>This course&#39;s goal is to teach you some of the most important computer networking concepts, but also provide practical, real-life scenario labs &amp;amp; guide you through configuring those successfully. Some of the labs come from CCNA, but they&#39;re mostly original topologies I created for my Computer Networking students. They were very successful so I decided to post them on Udemy as well. Hope you will find them useful and feel free to send ideas on additional labs I might add!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CheckPoint-NGFW Security : Basic Introduction</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/checkpoint-ngfw-security-basic-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/checkpoint-ngfw-security-basic-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Learn all the Concepts about the Features of CheckPoint - Next Generation Firewall, Learn how to evaluate or Review a Firewall. Why are Firewalls needed and how its&#39; features justify the Deployment in modern Day networks in spite of ACLs on Router, Packet filters &amp;amp; Proxy based Firewalls. You will learn all the additional features they provide on top of other traditional Networking and legacy security solutions. Learn about Stateful Inspection and how it is Used in Firewall to provide security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SolarWinds ARM / Access Monitoring / Prevent Data Breaches</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/solarwinds-arm-/-access-monitoring-/-prevent-data-breaches/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/solarwinds-arm-/-access-monitoring-/-prevent-data-breaches/</guid>
      <description>SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) is designed to assist IT and security administrators in quickly and easily provisioning, deprovisioning, managing, and auditing user access rights to systems, data, and files, so they can help protect their organizations from the potential risks of data loss and breaches. By analyzing user authorizations and access permissions, you get visualization of who has access to what, and when they accessed it. With just a few clicks, customized reports can be generated to help demonstrate compliance with many regulatory requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Troubleshooting with Palo Alto Firewalls</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-troubleshooting-with-palo-alto-firewalls/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-troubleshooting-with-palo-alto-firewalls/</guid>
      <description>*** The only Palo Alto Networks Firewall course on Udemy 100% Troubleshooting oriented .***
When things turn wrong, the Admin guide or Google search will have their limits very quickly! Troubleshooting takes time, a logical methodology and sharp skills: This training will give you the tools to find most problem root causes and help you to become quick at solving them on Palo Alto Networks firewalls.

WHAT OTHER STUDENTS SAY</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question For CERTIFIED ETHICAL HACKER (CEH) EXAM</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-for-certified-ethical-hacker-ceh-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-for-certified-ethical-hacker-ceh-exam/</guid>
      <description>Dear Students,
Are you preparing for CEH Exam ? Don’t be stressed, Take our Practice Test for CERTIFIED ETHICAL HACKER EXAM. Here we Discuss the Practical Questions on the Different topics of Ethical Hacking Such as MALWARE, DENIAL OF SERVICE, SYSTEM HACKING, FOOTPRINTING, EVASION and WI-FI and Bluetooth Hacking.
Certified Ethical Hacker EXAM is not so difficult. If you have basic knowledge about Different programming languages, servers and Computer networking it will be easy for you and I hope these Practice test will help you for Success in CEH Exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Application of Ethical Hacking</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-application-of-ethical-hacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-application-of-ethical-hacking/</guid>
      <description>Dear Students,
Are you preparing for Job Exam and Interview in Ethical Hacking)?
Don’t be stressed, Take our Ethical Hacking Based Practice Test and prepare yourself for the Interview. Here we Discuss the Practical Questions on the Ethical Hacking.
Here we are going to build your confidence by Providing Practice Test on Ethical Hacking based questions. There will be a series of practice Tests where you can test your Knowledge in the field of Ethical Hacking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL Injection Attacks: The 2021 Guide</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sql-injection-attacks-the-2021-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sql-injection-attacks-the-2021-guide/</guid>
      <description>About the course:
Welcome to this course on SQL injection attacks! In this course, we explore one of the biggest risks facing web applications today. We start out by creating a safe and legal environment for us to perform attacks in. Then, we cover the core concepts of SQL and injections. After that, we learn SQL injection techniques with the help of cheat sheets and references. At that point, we start to gather information about our target in order to find weaknesses and potential vulnerabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of Network Security</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-network-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-network-security/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in IT Industry? Don’t be stressed, take our Network Security Course and prepare yourself for your Interview
We know that Network Security is the basic Requirement of IT Company, so it is necessary for every students on IT Industry that he learn the Basic Concept of Network Security. In this Course You Will Learn the fundamentals of Network Security and take the first leap to the world of IT Industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teramind Employee Monitoring &amp; Data Loss Prevention</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/teramind-employee-monitoring-data-loss-prevention/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/teramind-employee-monitoring-data-loss-prevention/</guid>
      <description>Teramind offers employee monitoring, insider threat detection, and data loss prevention (DLP) solutions. Teramind UAM monitors user activities on applications, websites, file systems, network, email, social media and more. Behavioral rules can be created to automatically warn, block, notify, lockout or take other actions when an anomaly is detected. Its session recording feature allows investigation of incidents with video and optional audio recordings of users&#39; desktop.
Teramind DLP comes with all the features available in Teramind UAM plus: automated data discovery and classification with built-in support for many sensitive data types for personal information, health and financial information (PII/PHI/PFI).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Forensics - Complete Digital Forensics Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-forensics-complete-digital-forensics-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-forensics-complete-digital-forensics-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
Most comprehensive Digital Forensics Course, You will learn Depth understanding of how computers work and how to do digital forensics.
Upgrading every week 2021 Course Computer Forensics
Digital Forensics is defined as the process of preservation, identification, extraction, and documentation of computer evidence which can be used by the court of law. It is a science of finding evidence from digital media like a computer, mobile phone, server, or network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Programming Masterclass™:Java Socket, TCP/IP, Server</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/network-programming-masterclassjava-socket-tcp/ip-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/network-programming-masterclassjava-socket-tcp/ip-server/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
The world is becoming interconnected on an unprecedented scale with more services being provided on the Internet. Applications ranging from business transactions to embedded applications, such as those found in refrigerators, are connecting to the Internet. With isolated applications no longer being the norm, it is becoming increasingly important for applications to be network enabled. The goal of this course is to provide the student with the necessary skills to develop Java applications that connect and work with other applications and services across a network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncle Rat&#39;s XXE Handbook</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/uncle-rats-xxe-handbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/uncle-rats-xxe-handbook/</guid>
      <description>Who am i?
An experienced instructor with over 10 000 happy students on udemy, i spend my time making complex topic reacheable for anyone wanting to learn and understand them. As a dad of a toddler, i know what it means to have to simplify things but even before all this i was already emerged in the world of training IT profiles in software test automation and performance testing, having gotten my neoload expert certification in Paris so i could teach that software in a 3 day course that would prepare staff for neoload certification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pentesting and Securing Web Applications (Ethical Hacking)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pentesting-and-securing-web-applications-ethical-hacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pentesting-and-securing-web-applications-ethical-hacking/</guid>
      <description>Computer security is one of the biggest job gaps in history, with a shortage of 3.5 million skilled workers needing to tackle a problem estimated to be worth $6 trillion. This is one of the biggest opportunities in history.
When I was at university I did a lot of security courses and to be honest I was pretty frustrated at how they were taught. The concepts and their importance captured my imagination but I knew it could be taught in a better way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Beginner&#39;s guide to Cyber Security</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-beginners-guide-to-cyber-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 12:05:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-beginners-guide-to-cyber-security/</guid>
      <description>Why should you enroll? Since we&#39;ve been working in this field for over 15 years, we wanted to share part of what we&#39;ve learned in all these years with people that are completely new to Cyber Security, or people that would like to understand the 2021 basics in this field. You will find the general information mixed with real-life scenarios and real tips &amp;amp; tricks on how to protect from different threats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Ethical Hacking Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ultimate-ethical-hacking-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ultimate-ethical-hacking-course/</guid>
      <description>What is ethical hacking?
Ethical hacking involves an authorized attempt to gain unauthorized access to a computer system, application, or data. Carrying out an ethical hack involves duplicating strategies and actions of malicious attackers. This practice helps to identify security vulnerabilities which can then be resolved before a malicious attacker has the opportunity to exploit them.
Also known as “white hats,” ethical hackers are security experts that perform these assessments. The proactive work they do helps to improve an organization’s security posture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Engineering, Debugging and Malware Analysis - 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/reverse-engineering-debugging-and-malware-analysis-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/reverse-engineering-debugging-and-malware-analysis-2021/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
Breaking something down and putting it back together is a process that helps people understand how things were made.
 A person would be able to redo and reproduce an origami by unfolding it first. Knowing how cars work requires understanding each major and minor mechanical part and their purposes. The complex nature of the human anatomy requires people to understand each and every part of the body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Forensics for Pentesters - Hands-on Learning</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-forensics-for-pentesters-hands-on-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-forensics-for-pentesters-hands-on-learning/</guid>
      <description>Digital forensics is becoming very important in Cyber Security to detect and backtrack Black Hat Criminals. It is essential to remove Hackers’ malicious backdoors/malware and trace them back to avoid possible future incidents. Digital forensics is becoming very important in Cyber Security to detect and backtrack Black Hat Criminals. Digital forensics is essential to remove Hackers’ malicious backdoors/malware and trace them back to avoid possible future incidents.
This course acts as a digital forensics’ primer for pentesters and cybersecurity professionals wanting to expand their knowledge and add additional tools and skills to their resumes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethical Hacking - Hands-On Training - Part I</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ethical-hacking-hands-on-training-part-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 20:19:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ethical-hacking-hands-on-training-part-i/</guid>
      <description>Course Overview
This course provides learners with a basic level of competency using a hands-on approach to gaining practical experience as a penetration tester or an ethical hacker (white, grey, or black). This course provides a fundamental look at offensive security concepts and techniques using a virtual install of Kali Linux and three different target victims, Windows XP, Windows 7, Server 2008, and Linux (Metesploitable2). This course provides a 100% hands-on approach to learning to be an ethical hacker or a pentester.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermediate Ethical Hacking Hands-on Training</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/intermediate-ethical-hacking-hands-on-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 20:19:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/intermediate-ethical-hacking-hands-on-training/</guid>
      <description>Alert -
Intermediate Ethical Hacking Hands-on Training is a continuation of Ethical Hacking - Hands-on Training Part I. Before taking this course, students should have completed an introduction to an ethical hacking or pentesting course. Students should have completed Ethical Hacking - Hands-on Training Part I for best results before signing up for the intermediate course. 
Intermediate Ethical Hacking Hands-on Training picks up where Part I leaves off. In Part I, students was taught the fundamentals of pentesting while being introduced to some basic skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete CompTIA Network&#43; (N10-007) Video Training Series</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-comptia-network-n10-007-video-training-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-comptia-network-n10-007-video-training-series/</guid>
      <description>** Get Ready to Crush Your CompTIA Network+ (N10-007) Exam **
Embark on (or continue) your IT certification journey with CompTIA’s Network+ certification. The Network+ certification acts as a “sampler platter” of networking, where you get to “taste test” a wide variety of technologies, like cloud, wireless, software defined networking, route/switch, security, troubleshooting, network management, and so many others.
Guiding you through each step of your journey is award-winning instructor and double CCIE (Cisco Certified Internetworking Expert) Kevin Wallace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Introduction to Cybersecurity 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-introduction-to-cybersecurity-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-introduction-to-cybersecurity-2021/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Complete Introduction to Cybersecurity 2021. In this course, you will learn the fundamentals of I.T. while learning the working components of cybersecurity. No prior knowledge or skill is required. If you are a cybersecurity student, aspiring security professional, security enthusiast or someone intrigued to learn more about the industry, this course will provide a springboard for you to learn the basics. As a current cybersecurity student, I know exactly what type of questions, doubts, and thoughts you are experiencing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethical Hacking for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ethical-hacking-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ethical-hacking-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>This course is for anyone interested in becoming an ethical hacker, no matter your current skill level. The curriculum is designed for absolute beginners interested in a career as a security professional, beginning with the absolute basics of penetration testing, and progressing to advanced topics and techniques. Get started today in your Ethical Hacking career.
The goal of ethical hacking is to find security vulnerabilities in an organization’s digital systems and networks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethical Hacking: Introduction to Exploits</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ethical-hacking-introduction-to-exploits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ethical-hacking-introduction-to-exploits/</guid>
      <description>In a corner of the internet where there are no rules, there is a group of people who do not play by the rules. These are the hackers and crackers who cross lines and get away with it.
It&#39;s been around for a long time. There are entire generations of hackers that merely know how to utilize exploits; So what is an exploit?
In the security software industry, an exploit is a piece of software, a chunk of data, or a sequence of commands that takes advantage of a bug or vulnerability in order to cause unintended or unanticipated behavior to occur on computer software, hardware, or something electronic (usually computerized).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacking Ético: Fundamentos de Rede e Ataques de Camada</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/hacking-%C3%A9tico-fundamentos-de-rede-e-ataques-de-camada/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/hacking-%C3%A9tico-fundamentos-de-rede-e-ataques-de-camada/</guid>
      <description>Hola,
Bem-vindos ao curso de segurança cibernética “Segurança Cibernética: Fundamentos de Rede &amp;amp; Ataques de Camada de Rede“.
Para se tornar um Hacker Ético e aprender a hackear, o curso Fundamentos de Rede &amp;amp; Ataques de Camada de Rede é o começo perfeito para você. Este é um meio divertido porque a gente pode realmente olhar para os dados que vão nas redes como: como farejar a rede e coletar informações da rede.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Android Hacking For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-android-hacking-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-android-hacking-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>We will use msfvenom for creating a payload and save it as an apk file. After generating the payload, we need to setup a listener to Metasploit framework. Once the target downloads and installs the malicious apk then, an attacker can easily get back a meterpreter session on Metasploit. An attacker needs to do some social engineering to install apk on the victim’s mobile device.
in this course we gonna learn different kind of lauching attacks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireshark: Packet Analysis and Ethical Hacking: Core Skills</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/wireshark-packet-analysis-and-ethical-hacking-core-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/wireshark-packet-analysis-and-ethical-hacking-core-skills/</guid>
      <description>Learn Wireshark practically. Wireshark pcapng files provided so you can practice while you learn! There is so much to learn in this course:
- Capture Telnet, FTP, TFTP, HTTP passwords. - Replay VoIP conversations. - Capture routing protocol (OSPF) authentication passwords.
- Troubleshoot network issues.
- Free software.
- Free downloadable pcapng files.
- Answer quiz questions.
The course is very practical. You can practice while you learn!
Learn how to analyze and interpret network protocols and leverage Wireshark for what it was originally intended: Deep Packet Inspection and network analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
