<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Content Marketing on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/content-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Content Marketing on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/content-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Content Marketing 2022. Content that Sells!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/content-marketing-2022.-content-that-sells/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/content-marketing-2022.-content-that-sells/</guid>
      <description>What is content marketing?
Content marketing is a marketing method for creating and distributing valuable, relevant, and consistent content for a specific audience.
The goal of content marketing is to help your audience cope with challenges, improve their quality of life, and to establish yourself as a trusted thought leader.
The Role of Content Marketing in 2021
The impact of the coronavirus is being felt around the world.
Shopper needs and habits are rapidly changing, which poses new challenges for marketers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Podcast Marketing For Natural Health Practitioners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-podcast-marketing-for-natural-health-practitioners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-podcast-marketing-for-natural-health-practitioners/</guid>
      <description>Are you a Massage Therapist? Naturopath? Energy Worker? Healer? EFT Practitioner? Yoga Instructor? Acupuncturist? Reiki Master? Homeopathy Healer?
Do you wonder how you can leverage yourself to teach more people how they can live fuller, healthier lives?
Do you think: &#34;If only more people knew what I do and how much other people have been helped by my practice...&#34;?
Then this course is for you.
Tim Cooper and Scott Paton will lay out a proven plan for you to reach hundreds and thousands more prospects than you do today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copywriting: Make Money From Home WRITING WORDS</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/copywriting-make-money-from-home-writing-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:33:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/copywriting-make-money-from-home-writing-words/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to make money online Writing Words?
I&#39;ve been doing that already for years and now I&#39;ll reveal to you the Best Secrets of copywriting.
Once you make money with copywriting, you&#39;ll have a lot of freedom.
You can make money...
ANYWHERE you want
ANYTIME you want
WRITING about something you love
NEVER showing your face unless you want
In a nutshell, you can simply open your laptop and start making money whenever you want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEO Link Building &amp; Content Writing Course: Get HQ Backlinks</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/seo-link-building-content-writing-course-get-hq-backlinks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/seo-link-building-content-writing-course-get-hq-backlinks/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our SEO Ultimate Guide to Building Backlinks, we’re so glad you’ve joined us today, as we have lots of tips and techniques to share with you so you can get amazing links. This SEO Link Building &amp;amp; Content Writing Course is clearly organised as 14 days challenge. It has been filled with animated videos, screen recordings, face2face explanations, practical writing assignments as well as quizzes making learning fun. You will not only watch this course, but actually, you will also write your own content for blog and backlinks outreach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn 4 STEPS to Make Money Online by Blogging!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-4-steps-to-make-money-online-by-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-4-steps-to-make-money-online-by-blogging/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to wake up in the morning, check your phone and see how much money you made while you&#39;ve been sleeping?
That&#39;s my morning routine.
Every single morning I like to check out from my phone how much money I have made last night.
But of course, things weren&#39;t always so good for me so let&#39;s go back in time back to 2015...
How Did I Learn to Make Money Blogging?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2022 - Part 6</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2022-part-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2022-part-6/</guid>
      <description>You must already have been wondering about the recent rise of Artificial Intelligence (AI) tools in content writing and development. True! The world of digital marketing is changing day by day. Artificial Intelligence (AI) already is playing a significant role in the field of content marketing nowadays and is helping us all to automate processes at a time of immense content overload. You’ve probably even read content written by an algorithm without noticing it - did you ever realize that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Content Marketing Quiz (2022 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-content-marketing-quiz-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-content-marketing-quiz-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>Content is truly termed as &#34;The King&#34;.
&#39;Content marketers always say that with our clients we want to build close, trusting relationships&#39;. But how many of our respected personal relationships are marked by a lack of feeling? The best way to create those genuinely meaningful relationships we all want to have with our clients is to concentrate on making stories more personally resonant, situationally important, and emotionally intelligent. Greater empathy is the real key to every goal - we have (as content marketers, and as people).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copywriting Secrets Course – Become A PRO Copywriter Expert</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/copywriting-secrets-course-become-a-pro-copywriter-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:57:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/copywriting-secrets-course-become-a-pro-copywriter-expert/</guid>
      <description>WANT TO BE A BETTER COPYWRITER?
If you’d like to start taking copy seriously in 2022, The Copywriting secrets course is a fast and proven way to learn…
Even If You’re Not A Copywriter!
**BRAND NEW CONTENT &amp;amp; UP TO DATE 2020! - COMPLETE UDEMY COURSE!**
How to craft “overnight copy” your customers, clients or patients will be POWERLESS to resist.
Even if you haven’t written a single word since high school!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copywriting: B2B Copywriting, Content Writing, Copy Writing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/copywriting-b2b-copywriting-content-writing-copy-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/copywriting-b2b-copywriting-content-writing-copy-writing/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to get more customers in this groundbreaking, definitive course on B2B copywriting and content marketing. Master the art &amp;amp; science of copywriting to push people down your funnel to become active, paying customers, instead of just &#34;leads.&#34; Generate pipeline revenue and serious financial results instead of inflating vanity metrics, such as captured &#34;emails&#34; that never convert into paying customers. This is the ultimate course on B2B copywriting and content marketing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best of Content Marketing, SEO &amp; Copywriting &#43; 23 Templates</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/best-of-content-marketing-seo-copywriting--23-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:16:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/best-of-content-marketing-seo-copywriting--23-templates/</guid>
      <description>Learn Content Marketing, SEO &amp;amp; Copywriting with Our Easy &amp;amp; Entertaining Learning System HQ Video Animated Explainers, Quizzes, &amp;amp; Assignments that Make Learning Fun, Fast, &amp;amp; Easy. Get Pro 23 Content Creation Templates you can Customise. Max Leads &amp;amp; Sales, Boost Search Ranking, or Land your Dream Marketing Job.
&#34;The course is really amazing. Easy to understand. I love the assignments included in it. The assignment is a great way for me to test my ability as a content creator, already know the area to improve on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best of Copywriting &amp; SEO: Content, Copywriting &amp; SEO Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/best-of-copywriting-seo-content-copywriting-seo-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:16:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/best-of-copywriting-seo-content-copywriting-seo-course/</guid>
      <description>Learn highly persuasive SEO copywriting techniques – seamlessly boost your SEO while pushing your customer’s buttons. Write for sales success with our expert guide from a pro content creator – includes easy walkthroughs to max your SEO copywriting results. This SEO &amp;amp; copywriting course is completely animated and optimised for beginners to learn fast. This course also includes a pro copywriting pdf guide, pdf checklist and 23 content marketing templates, so you can create content like an expert, and sell more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create your marketing calendar for busy entrepreneurs</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-create-your-marketing-calendar-for-busy-entrepreneurs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 18:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-create-your-marketing-calendar-for-busy-entrepreneurs/</guid>
      <description>Still working like a charm in 2022!
Join over 70,000 students from 190+ countries worldwide taking my courses today!
no fluff, no filler content, just straight to the point course that you can start and actually finish in 1 day!
If you are a digital entrepreneur, coach, consultant, affiliate marketer, blogger, or own any type of online business, You know how important marketing is for your business. And with the never-ending to-do list that we have as busy entrepreneurs, managing our marketing and planning and executing marketing campaigns and measuring the results is a top business priority but so many entrepreneurs don&#39;t have a solid system in place to plan their marketing and this is why I created this course!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2021 - Part 8</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-8/</guid>
      <description>Content curation is the method of collecting appropriate information for a given subject or field of interest, typically with the aim of adding value. Individuals sharing and delivering content on a particular niche or topic to the appropriate target audience are termed, curators. Businesses, as well as end-users, can use the curation tools and services for viral reach.
Content curation tools (mostly cloud-based ones) help you find relevant and new content (or content ideas).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start Your Own Blogging Business For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/start-your-own-blogging-business-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 15:38:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/start-your-own-blogging-business-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>⇉ My Udemy courses have been taken by 48,924 students⇉ 60+ how to make money with your WordPress blog as soon - today &#34;⇉ No Prior knowledge needed &#34;Guaranteed&#34;⇉ All future &amp;amp; additional lectures will always be FREE of charge
About this course:
Over 48,924 very happy students
Full, free lifetime access
All future extra lectures and upgrades are always included for free
Unconditional Udemy 30 day money-back guarantee - that&#39;s my personal promise of your success!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Guide to Tailwind - Master Pinterest with Tailwind</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-guide-to-tailwind-master-pinterest-with-tailwind/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 15:38:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-guide-to-tailwind-master-pinterest-with-tailwind/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Complete Guide to Tailwind - Master Pinterest with Tailwind!
The only course you will need to start with Tailwind, one of the best Pinterest Management Tools on the market (if not the best).
Tailwind is the service that will help you to manage practically all aspects of Pinterest and most importantly it allows you to create Pinterest Pins (Right from the browser), Schedule your pins and manage them, all from one convenient spot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Ultimate Guide to YouTube Channel &amp; YouTube Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2021-ultimate-guide-to-youtube-channel-youtube-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2021-ultimate-guide-to-youtube-channel-youtube-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to TubeHeroes 1.5!
An Only Course you need to start making and growing your YouTube channel!
The YouTube industry is as big as ever was and it will only continue to grow in the coming years. And it does not matter whether you want to grow your personal following or to grow your business, YouTube is a practically essential social media platform to be active on.
But you have no idea where to start?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginner &amp; Advanced Udemy Course Creation – Unofficial</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/beginner-advanced-udemy-course-creation-unofficial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/beginner-advanced-udemy-course-creation-unofficial/</guid>
      <description>Note: This course is not sponsored by or affiliated with Udemy, Inc.
Beginner &amp;amp; Advanced Udemy Course Creation Training. Inside this Online Course you will learn how to make Udemy courses the fast, simple &amp;amp; easy way. You will also be shown how to make an amazing amount of steady and recurring passive income on Udemy.
I SHARE ALL MY SECRETS IN THIS COURSE
Learn how the “Gurus” on Udemy really make their money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basics of Proofreading</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basics-of-proofreading/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basics-of-proofreading/</guid>
      <description>Proofreaders are normally the members of the publishing team that make sure that documents look and read their best before they are sent to print. Along with being able to recognize errors in written materials, proofreaders must be able to correctly mark the documents for corrections.
However, nowadays, with the help of freelancer marketplaces anyone can become a proofreader and offer their services online.
Proofreaders can charge around $20-$50 per hour</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Creation &amp; Content Writing for B2B Content Marketing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/content-creation-content-writing-for-b2b-content-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/content-creation-content-writing-for-b2b-content-marketing/</guid>
      <description>ATTENTION business-to-business writers and marketers!
Do you want to learn how to develop world-class B2B content from a former VP of Marketing with Fortune 100 experience, a top-tier MBA, and college-level teaching experience? Do you want to take your content writing and content creation to the next level? This is the course for you. This course goes into the details of B2B content writing &amp;amp; content creation using case studies and real-world examples.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
