<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Content Marketing on </title>
    <link>/tags/content-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Content Marketing on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 10:29:20 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/content-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Complete Guide to Tailwind - Master Pinterest with Tailwind</title>
      <link>/complete-guide-to-tailwind-master-pinterest-with-tailwind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 10:29:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-guide-to-tailwind-master-pinterest-with-tailwind/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Complete Guide to Tailwind - Master Pinterest with Tailwind!
The only course you will need to start with Tailwind, one of the best Pinterest Management Tools on the market (if not the best).
Tailwind is the service that will help you to manage practically all aspects of Pinterest and most importantly it allows you to create Pinterest Pins (Right from the browser), Schedule your pins and manage them, all from one convenient spot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basics of Proofreading</title>
      <link>/basics-of-proofreading/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/basics-of-proofreading/</guid>
      <description>Proofreaders are normally the members of the publishing team that make sure that documents look and read their best before they are sent to print. Along with being able to recognize errors in written materials, proofreaders must be able to correctly mark the documents for corrections.

However, nowadays, with the help of freelancer marketplaces anyone can become a proofreader and offer their services online.

Proofreaders can charge around $20-$50 per hour</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Ultimate Guide to YouTube Channel &amp; YouTube Masterclass</title>
      <link>/2021-ultimate-guide-to-youtube-channel-youtube-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021-ultimate-guide-to-youtube-channel-youtube-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to TubeHeroes 1.5!
An Only Course you need to start making and growing your YouTube channel!
The YouTube industry is as big as ever was and it will only continue to grow in the coming years. And it does not matter whether you want to grow your personal following or to grow your business, YouTube is a practically essential social media platform to be active on.
But you have no idea where to start?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn 4 STEPS to Make Money Online by Blogging!</title>
      <link>/learn-4-steps-to-make-money-online-by-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-4-steps-to-make-money-online-by-blogging/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to wake up in the morning, check your phone and see how much money you made while you&#39;ve been sleeping?
That&#39;s my morning routine.
Every single morning I like to check out from my phone how much money I have made last night.
But of course, things weren&#39;t always so good for me so let&#39;s go back in time back to 2015...
How Did I Learn to Make Money Blogging?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Marketing 2021. Content that Sells!</title>
      <link>/content-marketing-2021.-content-that-sells/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/content-marketing-2021.-content-that-sells/</guid>
      <description>What is content marketing?
Content marketing is a marketing method for creating and distributing valuable, relevant, and consistent content for a specific audience.
The goal of content marketing is to help your audience cope with challenges, improve their quality of life, and to establish yourself as a trusted thought leader.

The Role of Content Marketing in 2021
The impact of the coronavirus is being felt around the world.
Shopper needs and habits are rapidly changing, which poses new challenges for marketers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copywriting: B2B Copywriting, Content Writing, Copy Writing</title>
      <link>/copywriting-b2b-copywriting-content-writing-copy-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/copywriting-b2b-copywriting-content-writing-copy-writing/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to get more customers in this groundbreaking, definitive course on B2B copywriting and content marketing. Master the art &amp;amp; science of copywriting to push people down your funnel to become active, paying customers, instead of just &#34;leads.&#34; Generate pipeline revenue and serious financial results instead of inflating vanity metrics, such as captured &#34;emails&#34; that never convert into paying customers. This is the ultimate course on B2B copywriting and content marketing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Creation &amp; Content Writing for B2B Content Marketing</title>
      <link>/content-creation-content-writing-for-b2b-content-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/content-creation-content-writing-for-b2b-content-marketing/</guid>
      <description>ATTENTION business-to-business writers and marketers!
Do you want to learn how to develop world-class B2B content from a former VP of Marketing with Fortune 100 experience, a top-tier MBA, and college-level teaching experience? Do you want to take your content writing and content creation to the next level? This is the course for you. This course goes into the details of B2B content writing &amp;amp; content creation using case studies and real-world examples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Content Marketing Quiz (2021 Edition)</title>
      <link>/the-ultimate-content-marketing-quiz-2021-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-ultimate-content-marketing-quiz-2021-edition/</guid>
      <description>Content is truly termed as &#34;The King&#34;.
&#39;Content marketers always say that with our clients we want to build close, trusting relationships&#39;. But how many of our respected personal relationships are marked by a lack of feeling? The best way to create those genuinely meaningful relationships we all want to have with our clients is to concentrate on making stories more personally resonant, situationally important, and emotionally intelligent. Greater empathy is the real key to every goal - we have (as content marketers, and as people).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
