<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2021 PMP Mock Practice Tests</title>
      <link>/2021-pmp-mock-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021-pmp-mock-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>These mock tests are specially created to assist PMP® aspirants to get familiar with the new 2021 PMP® Exam format and test their understanding of the PMP® Exam syllabus.
After taking these prep tests, you will get a clear idea about your readiness for the real exam and you will be able to identify and focus on your weakness points. This preparation course includes a sum of 380 questions to make sure you’ll be able to face all possibilities and scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Creative Cloud 2021 Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>/adobe-creative-cloud-2021-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/adobe-creative-cloud-2021-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Adobe Creative Cloud but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Designs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Creative Cloud 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Adobe Creative Cloud is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start working with Adobe Creative Cloud like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asana Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>/asana-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/asana-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Asana but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Projects and bring your ideas to life?
Then Asana 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Asana is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start projects like an expert with Asana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beat Procrastination in Turbulent Covid Era</title>
      <link>/beat-procrastination-in-turbulent-covid-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/beat-procrastination-in-turbulent-covid-era/</guid>
      <description>Procrastination is one of the principle boundaries obstructing you from getting up, settling on the correct choices, and carrying on with the fantasy life you&#39;ve considered.

Ongoing investigations have shown that individuals regret more the things they haven&#39;t done than the things they have done. Furthermore, sensations of disappointment and blame coming about because of botched freedoms will in general remain with individuals any longer.

Some of the time every one of our chances appear to be on our fingertips, however we can&#39;t contact them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming A Recruitment And Selection Specialist</title>
      <link>/becoming-a-recruitment-and-selection-specialist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/becoming-a-recruitment-and-selection-specialist/</guid>
      <description>A good recruitment process can reduce the time involved in searching, interviewing, recruiting, and training. It can streamline these procedures and make your search more efficient for viable candidates.
Remember, top talent will not always find you.
You must seek out people to fill the positions that you have open. So, in this course, we&#39;ll learn together, the following:
Defining recruitment
Understanding the selection process
Recognising the GROW model
Interview and question process</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEST of SEO: #1 SEO Training &amp; Content Marketing Course 2021</title>
      <link>/best-of-seo-#1-seo-training-content-marketing-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/best-of-seo-#1-seo-training-content-marketing-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>In our increasingly online world, if you want to be successful, you need the latest digital skills. In this SEO &amp;amp; CONTENT MARKETING MASTERY course, I bring you CONSTANTLY UPDATED CUTTING-EDGE STRATEGIES AND TECHNIQUES so you can THRIVE in Content Marketing and SEO. This is my brand new 2021 SEO Training and Content Marketing Course! Now UPDATED to include many more topics to give you EVEN MORE VALUE and ensure your and SEO Success, with input from multiple experts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contracts Management in Construction Projects</title>
      <link>/contracts-management-in-construction-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contracts-management-in-construction-projects/</guid>
      <description>Every construction project is bound by a Contract. Proper Contract Management plays a major role in the effective management of your construction projects. Adhering to all the Contractual obligations, the terms and conditions can save both cost and time. There are a few standard Contract Forms that is followed in a Construction project mainly FIDIC (International Federation of Consulting Engineers), NRM (New Rules of Measurement), JCT (The Joint Contracts Tribunal). The procedures to commence work, the documents required at each stage of the project, variation procedures, payment terms, basis for termination and suspension of works by either parties, completion of work, roles and responsibilities of all the stake holders and their staffs, dispute resolution methods, Arbitration procedures etc are all mentioned in the contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Course: Learn to Make Money Online WORLDWIDE!</title>
      <link>/cryptocurrency-course-learn-to-make-money-online-worldwide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cryptocurrency-course-learn-to-make-money-online-worldwide/</guid>
      <description>Last years have been HUGE for cryptocurrencies. Many millionaires were made all over the world. Technologies went forward and new innovations were created. On the other hand, many people lost money because they didn&#39;t know what they were doing. They threw money here and there because other people were doing so.
If you want to make money with cryptocurrencies you need to learn important action steps that I teach you in this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front End Web Development Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>/front-end-web-development-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/front-end-web-development-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Hi and Welcome to Front End Web Development Ultimate Course 2021
I&#39;m you instructor Josh Werner and I&#39;ll be leading you through this course
Have you always wanted to learn how to code but don&#39;t know where to start?	Would you like to make amazing websites and bring your ideas to life?	Then Front End Web Development Ultimate Course 2021 is for you!
Programming is the most in-demand skill in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Workspace (G Suite) Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>/google-workspace-g-suite-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/google-workspace-g-suite-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Google Workspace but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to manager accounts and bring your ideas to life?
Then Google Workspace 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Google Workspace is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start adding accounts like an expert with Google Workspace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Income Tax Complete Certification Course</title>
      <link>/indian-income-tax-complete-certification-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/indian-income-tax-complete-certification-course/</guid>
      <description>Do you find it difficult to understand the Income Tax laws?
Or are you struggling with filing your own income tax return?
Many a time we hear people saying that they don’t understand tax, they are not aware of when tax is to be deducted (TDS), they find it difficult to apply for their own PAN number or they find it difficult to file their return of income.
So, friends to simplify all your problems and giving you an excellent clarity of all concepts, we have made this course on “Income Tax” presented by Direct and Corporate Tax expert CA Natasha Shah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Credit and Credit Repair from Scratch</title>
      <link>/learn-about-credit-and-credit-repair-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-about-credit-and-credit-repair-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>Sadly, many people get into a debt spiral that soon goes out of control. They have trouble keeping their head above water, and soon they fall under as the weight of debt drags them down.

Thankfully, credit can be managed and all it takes is having the ability to change how one lives their life. By implementing the lessons explained in this course, an individual will be able to take their credit and repair it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Bootstrap - For Beginners</title>
      <link>/learn-bootstrap-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-bootstrap-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Students learn to create the front-end component of mobile-responsive web applications, using the Bootstrap framework.
The techniques explored in this course will ensure your web applications adhere to strict development standards to avoid cross-browser and cross-device compatibility issues.
The course starts with the fundamental concepts, including embedding Bootstrap into web pages. We then explore the Bootstrap Grid system and popular mobile responsive web layouts.
Students will gain a solid understanding of almost every Bootstrap component available, from typography, carousels, panels, drop-down menus, and collapsible nav-bars to forms, popovers, modals and tool tips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn CSS - For Beginners</title>
      <link>/learn-css-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-css-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Students learn to harness the true power of front-end development using CSS (Cascading Style Sheets). Through comprehensive, hands-on exercises, students will develop stylish, responsive web layouts using CSS properties and style definitions.
We start with basic concepts such as the parts of a CSS rule and working with Classes, Divisions and IDs. Next we explore an intensive collection of style definition, from working with text, backgrounds and transparency, right to CSS positioning, link styling, and popular layout development techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn HTML - For Beginners</title>
      <link>/learn-html-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-html-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Students will learn how to create engaging web pages using HTML5, which is an integral part of the development process.
The material covers an intensive array of HTML5 elements including images, videos, lists, tables, forms, iframes and much more.
The course includes several hands-on projects to ensure comprehension of course materials.
By the end of the training, students will be proficient with coding in HTML and ready to tackle the more advanced scripting languages that follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn JavaScript - For Beginners</title>
      <link>/learn-javascript-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-javascript-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Students learn to add dynamic, interactivity to web pages using JavaScript.
We start with exploring the fundamental concepts, including JavaScript placement and output functions. We then transition to working with arithmetic operators, math functions, arrays, sorting, conditional statements and loops. Students also learn to work with events and functions.
The course includes several hands-on exercises to help students master this essential scripting language.
 Ratings: 4.24/5
Enrollments: 173172
Coupon Code: YOUACCEL12105</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn PHP - For Beginners</title>
      <link>/learn-php-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-php-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Students learn to integrate client-server communication into web pages to create dynamic functionality using PHP.
We start with the fundamentals, including PHP syntax and variable declaration. The course transitions into working with objects, arithmetic operators, conditional statements, loops, functions and arrays.
Students will also learn to utilize server side form validation techniques to maintain data integrity.
 Ratings: 4.23/5
Enrollments: 154451
Coupon Code: YOUACCEL12105
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Options Trading MasterClass: Options Trading In Simple Terms</title>
      <link>/options-trading-masterclass-options-trading-in-simple-terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/options-trading-masterclass-options-trading-in-simple-terms/</guid>
      <description>In this Options Trading course, President of Capstone Financial &amp;amp; Author of &#34;Options Trading Strategies for Monthly Income&#34; David J. Melilli will educate you on every aspect of options trading. David will implement his unique options trading process utilizing his extensive knowledge in the area of options trading. David has spent over fifteen years in the options trading arena. This options trading course is taught in an easy to understand, user friendly manner that will excite and help build the confidence to master options trading and it has been designed to educate and enhance every individual that wants to really develop the skills required in the world of options trading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP &amp; MySQL - Certification Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>/php-mysql-certification-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/php-mysql-certification-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the PHP &amp;amp; MySQL Certification Course for Beginners.This course offers a comprehensive guide to learning how to code in PHP. We also explore integrating MySQL Databases into your PHP Projects for dynamic, user driven functionality.We start with PHP basics, including variable declaration and data output. The lessons then transition into working with objects, conditional statements, loops, functions, arrays, form validation, sorting, and much more.After the PHP Section, students learn to unleash the true power of dynamic page development with MySQL database integration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP for Beginners 2021: The Complete PHP MySQL PDO Course</title>
      <link>/php-for-beginners-2021-the-complete-php-mysql-pdo-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/php-for-beginners-2021-the-complete-php-mysql-pdo-course/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my full stack PHP, MySQL, and PDO course where you will learn everything you need to know about one of the most three hot technologies right now. This course is organized systematically from the programming language (PHP) to The most well-known database (MySQL) to the best PHP tool to connect to this database which is (PDO) to give the most interesting, fun, informative, and worthy opportunity for learning web development the right way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portrait Photography for Absolute Beginners</title>
      <link>/portrait-photography-for-absolute-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portrait-photography-for-absolute-beginners/</guid>
      <description>=== students reviews regarding this course ===
&#34;This course really helps me to improve my photography knowledge and I would like to thanks all of those who help this to be a success.&#34; -- Wijekoon
&#34;so far the course is about what i really want to learn especially about basic portrait photography. i learn a lot of new things from this course&#34; - Fadila
&#34;Good for an absolute beginner. If you have just bought a DSLR camera and don&#39;t know anything about photography, it&#39;s good way to get your feet wet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stress Management - For Relief From Stress of Life &amp; Work</title>
      <link>/stress-management-for-relief-from-stress-of-life-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stress-management-for-relief-from-stress-of-life-work/</guid>
      <description>Stress Management: Stress can weigh you down until you can hardly think straight! Beat it Today with this Comprehensive Stress Management Course filled with Cutting-Edge Tools &amp;amp; Strategies - Feel better TODAY! Created by Master Therapist &amp;amp; Multiple Award-Winning Educator Prof. Paul J. Cline Ed.D ... Get His 35+ years of Expertise in Helping others Beat Stress ... Condensed down into this Training.
Here Are Just A Few Of the Skills You Will Gain:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning to Religion to reduce STRESS</title>
      <link>/turning-to-religion-to-reduce-stress/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/turning-to-religion-to-reduce-stress/</guid>
      <description>Notice: Please do NOT enrol on this course on impulse, thinking you might watch it later. Maybe show an interest on impulse, yes, but before you enrol, watch the Preview videos, read the Course Description and then make a decision. If you then enrol then please start the course as soon as possible. Watch the lectures, look at the workbooks and join in the discussions. Joining my courses is a serious business and I want you to get the most out of your study – but I also want you to enjoy the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Level PMP Mock Questions</title>
      <link>/advanced-level-pmp-mock-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/advanced-level-pmp-mock-questions/</guid>
      <description>2021 Advanced PMP Exam Simulator: Boost your confidence and proficiency before taking the PMP certification exam.

This course offers a simulation of the updated 2021 PMP exam, providing 180 highly realistic mock questions to help you test your understanding of project management knowledge areas &amp;amp; approaches.

These practice tests were created to prepare you for the real PMP Exam, identifying any knowledge gaps and clearing any hard-to-understand concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AD’s Hacker 1.0: Growth Hacking Certification for Marketers</title>
      <link>/ads-hacker-1.0-growth-hacking-certification-for-marketers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ads-hacker-1.0-growth-hacking-certification-for-marketers/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the third course in Term 2 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Time to set the advertising industry on fire with AD&#39;s Hacker 1.0 !!!
There is no denying that we have changed the way we work on the World Wide Web and the Internet. For presents or gifts, we no longer visit the city centre– we’re going to an eCommerce marketplace like Amazon and getting it shipped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI-102 Microsoft Azure AI Engineer Associate Exam Tests</title>
      <link>/ai-102-microsoft-azure-ai-engineer-associate-exam-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ai-102-microsoft-azure-ai-engineer-associate-exam-tests/</guid>
      <description>With help of these AI-102 Practice Tests, you will be able to develop confidence inside you and these practice tests will help you to develop an understanding of all the concepts of AI-102 to pass the AI-102 exam. If you are willing to instantly get AI-102 certified this practice test is for you. I am not including extra questions in these practice tests to save your time. This test contains only real exam questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI-900 Azure AI Fundamentals Real Only Practice Set</title>
      <link>/ai-900-azure-ai-fundamentals-real-only-practice-set/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ai-900-azure-ai-fundamentals-real-only-practice-set/</guid>
      <description>With help of these AI-900 Practice Tests, you will be able to develop confidence inside you and these practice tests will help you to develop an understanding of all the concepts of AI-900 to pass the AI-900 exam. If you are willing to instantly get AI-900 certified this practice test is for you. I am not including extra questions in these practice tests to save your time. This test contains only real exam questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-204 PracticeTest Developing Solutions for Microsoft Azure</title>
      <link>/az-204-practicetest-developing-solutions-for-microsoft-azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/az-204-practicetest-developing-solutions-for-microsoft-azure/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Azure Developer Associate exam is tougher than compared to Azure Fundamentals. The exam will test your Azure knowledge on all the topics. It&#39;s highly recommended to take a practice test before taking the official exam.
These Azure Developer Associate training practice papers are developed by the industry experts &amp;amp; are followed by multiple students. This set involves all the latest topics covered under AZ-204.
What do we offer in our Developing solution Microsoft Azure training test?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS &amp; JavaScript - Certification Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>/css-javascript-certification-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/css-javascript-certification-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the CSS &amp;amp; JavaScript – Certification Course for BeginnersThis two part series provides a detailed overview of the fundamentals of coding using CSS and JavaScript. Students will learn how to create responsive web pages using project based learning. The CSS section explores almost every aspect of CSS development. This includes:
Working with IDs, Classes, and Divisions.
CSS Text Properties, Borders and Backgrounds
Styling Images and Links
CSS Display Properties</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing Course for Fitness Professionals</title>
      <link>/digital-marketing-course-for-fitness-professionals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/digital-marketing-course-for-fitness-professionals/</guid>
      <description>To succeed in the fitness industry or field, your company must stand out from the crowd and competition. That means developing and implementing a solid and proven digital marketing strategy that is powered by Artificial Intelligence (AI). Social media marketing allows you to showcase your skills and expertise while also allowing people to learn about your company. It&#39;s a great, low-cost way to get more customers. But manual implementation of the same takes a lot of time, effort and resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DP-900 - Azure Data Fundamental - Practice Tests</title>
      <link>/dp-900-azure-data-fundamental-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dp-900-azure-data-fundamental-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>With the help of these DP-900 Practice Tests, you will be able to develop confidence inside you and these practice tests will help you develop an understanding of all the concepts of DP-900 to pass the AI-900 exam. If you are willing to instantly get DP-900 certified this practice test is for you. I am not including extra questions in these practice tests to save your time. This test contains only real exam questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML &amp; CSS - Certification Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>/html-css-certification-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/html-css-certification-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the HTML &amp;amp; CSS – Certification Course for BeginnersThis two part series provides an in-depth look at the fundamentals of coding in HTML and CSS. We start with exploring HTML Development using some of the most commonly used tags and attributes. Students will learn the composition of an HTML file, and some of the essential components. Students will work with HTML Spacing, Text Formatting, Lists, Images, Embedding Videos, Link Creation, Tables, and Forms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insight to Post Pandemic: Importance of Lean Six Sigma</title>
      <link>/insight-to-post-pandemic-importance-of-lean-six-sigma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/insight-to-post-pandemic-importance-of-lean-six-sigma/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this ultimate course on &#34;Insight to Post Pandemic: Importance of Lean Six Sigma&#34; that contains vaulable lessons taught by &#34;Casey Ang&#34; and &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34;.
Since its introduction as a corporate strategy by Jack Welch at General Electric in 1995, Six Sigma has come a long way. Since then, it has been widely adopted in a variety of industries.
The Greek letter sigma is used by statisticians to represent the variation in a process and we all know that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Audo Studio: AI-Powered Noise Cancellation Tool</title>
      <link>/learn-audo-studio-ai-powered-noise-cancellation-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-audo-studio-ai-powered-noise-cancellation-tool/</guid>
      <description>Background sounds such as fans, people talking, cars or trucks moving by, the buzz from defective audio wiring or other ambient noises that shouldn&#39;t be in your movie are all examples of audio noise. Your viewers and listeners will be distracted from the crucial information provided by the individual speaking in your video - if the audio is too loud too. When it comes to crafting a decent video, solid audio goes a long way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditation For Beginners</title>
      <link>/meditation-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/meditation-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Meditation is one of the most powerful things that you can do, as a human being. It trains you to be in control of you mind and your emotions, in ways that you never knew were possible. It allows you to be happy just to be alive, even in the most difficult of circumstances; even when you&#39;re injured, or suffering a loss, stressed out at work, overwhelmed, depressed or anxious. It allows you to find the basic happiness of being alive, and that pervades everything else, so that you can deal with everything else much better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditation Masterclass</title>
      <link>/meditation-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/meditation-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you&#39;ll learn meditations from all around the world, from mindfulness to zen to breath-work, chakras, Tibetan bowls, and everything in between.
This course is for anyone who&#39;s interested in meditation, from n00bs to zen masters alike; no matter what your level of experience, you can gain a lot from exploring this course. By the end, you&#39;ll have experience with over a dozen different styles of meditation.
This course is accredited by The Meditation Organization as a Certified Teacher Training Course -- AMC (Accredited Meditation Course) #39283 -- so once you receive your diploma at the end of this course, you&#39;ll be able to teach meditation to others as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft 365 Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>/microsoft-365-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/microsoft-365-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Microsoft 365 but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to manager accounts and bring your ideas to life?
Then Microsoft 365 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Microsoft 365 is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start adding accounts like an expert with Microsoft 365.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New-Age Technologies For Fitness Trainers</title>
      <link>/new-age-technologies-for-fitness-trainers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/new-age-technologies-for-fitness-trainers/</guid>
      <description>Technology is a flourishing sector today, with a plethora of intriguing and innovative products as well as new learning opportunities. Apps and wearable technology, as well as digital fitness platforms and equipment, are among the most popular fitness technologies today. Putting aside the excitement of new developments, the convenience that technology may provide is unrivalled. Long before the pandemic, the mix of fitness technology and digital fitness was altering our market; both areas were rising at a rapid pace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PL-600 : MS Power Platform Solution Architect Practice Tests</title>
      <link>/pl-600-ms-power-platform-solution-architect-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pl-600-ms-power-platform-solution-architect-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Exam PL-600 Microsoft Power Platform Solution Architect: Tests
Exam PL-600 candidate for the Power Platform Solution Architect Expert certification, you work with stakeholders and focus on solutions that affect your organization’s broad business and technical needs. A solution architect has functional and technical knowledge of the Power Platform, Dynamics 365 customer engagement apps, related Microsoft cloud solutions, and other third-party technologies. Microsoft Power Platform solution architects lead successful implementations and focus on how solutions address the broader business and technical needs of organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2021 - Part 1</title>
      <link>/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Do you remember the &#34;Jetsons show&#34;? 
The Jetsons fascinated me and everyone else around me. Thoughts of moving sidewalks, self-driving vehicles and robot housekeepers - fuelled my daydreams to the core. Let&#39;s now talk about the present time and the tech that is evolving.
Nowadays, I can command a robotic tool, device or tech to tell me the next day’s weather, read a e-book to me, play my preferred podcasts and even vacuum my flooring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Computer Basics Guide for Beginners: 2021</title>
      <link>/the-complete-computer-basics-guide-for-beginners-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-computer-basics-guide-for-beginners-2021/</guid>
      <description>The Computer Defined, Data versus Information, Classification of Computers based on how data is handled (Analog Computers, Digital Computers Hybrid Computers)
Computers for Individual Users or Personal Computers (Desktop Computers,Workstations, Laptops, Notebooks, Tablets, Handheld PCs, Smartphones)
Computers for Organizations (Network Server, Mainframes, Minicomputers, Supercomputers)
Parts of Computer System (Hardware , Software, User and Data)
Information Processing Cycle (Input, Processing, Output, Storage)
Computer Hardware Categorized ( Processing Devices, Memory Devices, Input and Output Devices, Storage Devices, Bus Interconnection)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Ultimate Guide to YouTube Channel &amp; YouTube Masterclass</title>
      <link>/2021-ultimate-guide-to-youtube-channel-youtube-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021-ultimate-guide-to-youtube-channel-youtube-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to TubeHeroes 1.5!
An Only Course you need to start making and growing your YouTube channel!
The YouTube industry is as big as ever was and it will only continue to grow in the coming years. And it does not matter whether you want to grow your personal following or to grow your business, YouTube is a practically essential social media platform to be active on.
But you have no idea where to start?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Kanban: Kanban for Software Development Teams</title>
      <link>/agile-kanban-kanban-for-software-development-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/agile-kanban-kanban-for-software-development-teams/</guid>
      <description>Kanban is not a software development lifecycle methodology or an approach to project management.
It requires that some process is already in place so that Kanban can be applied to
incrementally change the underlying process.
—David Anderson, Kanban
Kanban is a popular framework used to implement agile and DevOps software development. It requires real-time communication of capacity and full transparency of work. Work items are represented visually on a kanban board, allowing team members to see the state of every piece of work at any time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Money Laundering Concepts: AML, KYC and Compliance</title>
      <link>/anti-money-laundering-concepts-aml-kyc-and-compliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/anti-money-laundering-concepts-aml-kyc-and-compliance/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the course on Anti-Money Laundering (AML), where you will learn about the key issues faced by financial institutions today: Money Laundering and Terrorist Financing. This course will educate you on Money Laundering and Terrorist Financing laws, Know Your Customer, Customer Due Diligence, Economic Sanctions and Politically Exposed Persons. This is a comprehensive course that captures all relevant concepts required for training employees of an organization.
We will start the course by understanding the term Money Laundering and will then cover the process &amp;amp; impact of the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Antike Astrologie 2</title>
      <link>/antike-astrologie-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/antike-astrologie-2/</guid>
      <description>Dieser Kurs baut auf seiem Vorgänger Antike Astrologie 1 auf und erweitert die erste gelernte Technik mit der Methode der Elementarherrscher. Kannst du mit der Technik des Herrschers des Aszendenten (Kurs 1 ) das Generelle Lebenesthema bestimmen, so geht es hier um eine erste Timing - Technik.
Du erfährst wie du 3 grundlegende Planeten ermittelst und diese anschließend evaluierst. Dadurch wird das Leben des Horoskopstellers in 2 Hälften geteilt, die jeweils von den 3 Elementarherrscheerplaneten unterstützt werden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aprende las bases para invertir en la bolsa</title>
      <link>/aprende-las-bases-para-invertir-en-la-bolsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aprende-las-bases-para-invertir-en-la-bolsa/</guid>
      <description>En este curso aprenderás a leer los 3 estados financieros más importantes que reportan las empresas que cotizan en la bolsa americana (empresas públicas.) Estos son el estado de ingresos, la hoja de balance y el flujo de caja. Con el conocimiento ganado podrás reconocer si ha mejorado o empeorado el desempeño de una empresa pública. De esta forma, sabrás si es conveniente invertir en la empresa analizada. Estaremos usando Yahoo Finanzas para analizar los estados financieros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin For Beginners: How To Earn Bitcoin Online For Free</title>
      <link>/bitcoin-for-beginners-how-to-earn-bitcoin-online-for-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bitcoin-for-beginners-how-to-earn-bitcoin-online-for-free/</guid>
      <description>This is a course that the Government doesn&#39;t want you to see! Bitcoin is the BEST-PERFORMING asset of the decade.
It&#39;s not a coincidence that Bitcoin has been growing over 200%/year on average!
Every smart person has already realized that Bitcoin is clearly superior compared to government money (=USD, EUR, PHP, INR, etc.)
That&#39;s why Bitcoin grows rapidly.
Smart people are trying to accumulate as much Bitcoin as possible before the rest of the population gets educated about the benefits of Bitcoin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap &amp; jQuery - Certification Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>/bootstrap-jquery-certification-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bootstrap-jquery-certification-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Bootstrap &amp;amp; jQuery – Certification Course for BeginnersWith over 64% of the world using mobile devices to browse web pages, it’s no surprise that Bootstrap and jQuery have become the industry leaders in front-end scripting languages.This course starts right from the foundational concepts and gradually progresses to intermediate topics. Through a project-style learning approach, students will have the opportunity to build mobile-responsive web pages, complete with animation and interactivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build A Search Engine With Python: Computer Science &amp; Python</title>
      <link>/build-a-search-engine-with-python-computer-science-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/build-a-search-engine-with-python-computer-science-python/</guid>
      <description>AStateOfData.Com™ Computer Science With Python: An Absolute Beginners Guide To Computer Science
Introduction
WHY THIS COURSE IS DIFFERENT?	Many of the online courses teach you to code but not the theory/way of thinking behind it why would we choose a while but not a for loop, why should we pass 2 parameters to a function but not only one? This course will teach you how to think about solving coding problems throughout quizzes, there are 112 video format quizzes that aim to keep you engaged with the course and teach you the Python fundamentals in an easy to follow manner</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copywriting &amp; Content Marketing Course: Be a PRO Copywriter</title>
      <link>/copywriting-content-marketing-course-be-a-pro-copywriter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/copywriting-content-marketing-course-be-a-pro-copywriter/</guid>
      <description>UPSKILL YOURSELF AND ENSURE YOU&#39;RE NEVER OUT OF WORK OR OUT OF CLIENTS, WITH THE CONTENT MARKETING &amp;amp; COPYWRITING COURSE 2021. LEARN EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO KNOW TO BECOME A PROFESSIONAL CONTENT CREATOR, AND START A NEW CAREER ONLINE, OR BOOST YOUR LOCAL OR E-COMMERCE BUSINESS.
&#34;I wanted to tell you that I have a job in a digital marketing company! I&#39;m working as a copywriter and account manager for a team of developers and graphic designers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copywriting: B2B Copywriting, Content Writing, Copy Writing</title>
      <link>/copywriting-b2b-copywriting-content-writing-copy-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/copywriting-b2b-copywriting-content-writing-copy-writing/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to get more customers in this groundbreaking, definitive course on B2B copywriting and content marketing. Master the art &amp;amp; science of copywriting to push people down your funnel to become active, paying customers, instead of just &#34;leads.&#34; Generate pipeline revenue and serious financial results instead of inflating vanity metrics, such as captured &#34;emails&#34; that never convert into paying customers. This is the ultimate course on B2B copywriting and content marketing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a Members Only Blog using PHP, MySQL, &amp; AJAX</title>
      <link>/create-a-members-only-blog-using-php-mysql-ajax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/create-a-members-only-blog-using-php-mysql-ajax/</guid>
      <description>This course offers a hands-on approach in learning how to develop web applications using PHP, MySQL, and AJAX. Students will develop a blog with MySQL database integration. The project aims to cover the following key concepts:
Creating Dynamic Web Pages in PHP
Creating a MySQL Database to store Member Data.
Creating PHP &amp;amp; AJAX Validated Member Registration Forms
Creating PHP &amp;amp; AJAX Validated Member Login Authentication
Working with Session Variables – Login/Logout Functionality</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Foundation</title>
      <link>/devops-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/devops-foundation/</guid>
      <description>If you are new to DevOps, this course will give you the basic information about DevOps, including key concepts and the terminologies. This course covers the DevOps Full Stack: People and Culture, Processes and Practices, Technology and Automation. People and Culture:
You will be able to summarize the cultural, structural, and technological barriers that IT faces, when attempting to deliver services at the right quality, speed, and cost, and why challenges are faced when implementing DevOps in today’s organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Calendar :  Virtual Assistant</title>
      <link>/google-calendar-virtual-assistant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/google-calendar-virtual-assistant/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Google Calendar: and help you if you are a virtual assistant I&#39;ll be your calendar coach! Learn everything you need to know about Google Calendar with this complete guide!

Managing your own appointments and calendars can be daunting and stressful if you are working as a virtual assistant. ! With Google Calendar and this course, you will learn how to use all the features available to provide very powerful calendar management services</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the Internet Works &amp; the Web Development Process</title>
      <link>/how-the-internet-works-the-web-development-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-the-internet-works-the-web-development-process/</guid>
      <description>This course explores how the internet works, including the composition and transmission of data packets over both Local and Wide Area Networks. We take a look at the HTTP and HTTPS protocols as applicable to client and server side communications - including DNS Lookups. This course will also teach students how email exchange works over SMTP and IMAP. The role of Network Ports and Firewalls are also introduced.The course comes complete with two bonus sections which offer a quick guide for aspiring Web Developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML, CSS, &amp; JavaScript - Certification Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>/html-css-javascript-certification-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/html-css-javascript-certification-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the HTML, CSS, &amp;amp; JavaScript - Certification Course for Beginners.
If you are interested in mastering the art of front-end development, look no further. This course is the complete beginners guide to developing cutting-edge web pages that are fully mobile responsive. The course branches into three sections. We start by exploring HTML5, students learn the composition of a web page and how a web browser interprets html code to display the visual elements of a page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML, JavaScript, &amp; Bootstrap - Certification Course</title>
      <link>/html-javascript-bootstrap-certification-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/html-javascript-bootstrap-certification-course/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the HTML, JavaScript, &amp;amp; Bootstrap – Certification Course for BeginnersThis course gives students the knowledge necessary to take their front-end development skills to the next level. This course, is meant for beginners who have little, to no experience with coding. We start right from the foundational concepts and work our way up to intermediate level topics. By the end of this course, students will be able to create stunning, mobile responsive web pages using the latest scripting languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM Big Data Engineer Certification 2021</title>
      <link>/ibm-big-data-engineer-certification-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ibm-big-data-engineer-certification-2021/</guid>
      <description>This certification is intended for IBM Big Data Engineers. The Big Data Engineer works directly with the Data Architect and hands-on Developers to convert the architect&#39;s Big Data vision and blueprint into a Big Data reality. The Data Engineer possesses a deep level of technical knowledge and experience across a wide array of products and technologies. A Data Engineer understands how to apply technologies to solve big data problems, and has the ability to build large-scale data processing systems for the enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improvvisazione Teatrale e Comica: dalla teoria alla pratica</title>
      <link>/improvvisazione-teatrale-e-comica-dalla-teoria-alla-pratica/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/improvvisazione-teatrale-e-comica-dalla-teoria-alla-pratica/</guid>
      <description>Cos&#39;è un&#39; improvvisazione? E se si chiama IMPROVVISAZIONE perché studiarla in un corso?
Perché sono state scritte tonnellate di libri a tal riguardo?
L&#39;improvvisazione è una vera e propria Arte e come tale necessita di studio, tecnica ed esperienza. 
Non si può improvvisare senza possedere le conoscenze adatte.
Esistono due differenti forme di improvvisazione, quella &#34;muta&#34; nella quale l&#39;unico strumento comunicativo è rappresentato dal corpo e quella &#34;parlata&#34; durante la quale voce(storytelling) e corpo agiscono all&#39;unisono, quest&#39;ultima è l&#39;improvvisazione di cui ti parlerò in questo corso.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Domain Names and Web Hosting - Quick Guide</title>
      <link>/introduction-to-domain-names-and-web-hosting-quick-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/introduction-to-domain-names-and-web-hosting-quick-guide/</guid>
      <description>Domain Names Section:
We provide an overview of the domain name registration process. This includes the role of registrars and TLD (Top Level Domain) administration by ICANN. ccTLD&#39;s (Country Code Top Level Domains) are also explored.
Students will gain hands-on experience with the registration process using popular domain registrars. We will provide a comparison of different registrars and register a sample domain name using GoDaddy. Other topics of discussion will include: domain name privacy and administration, auto-renewal, domain forwarding, and name server assignment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript &amp; jQuery - Certification Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>/javascript-jquery-certification-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/javascript-jquery-certification-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the JavaScript &amp;amp; jQuery – Certification Course for BeginnersThis course offers a comprehensive guide into the fundamentals of coding using JavaScript and jQuery. These powerful languages can be used to add animated, dynamic client-side functionality to any web page.The JavaScript section of the course takes students on a journey that starts right from the basics. This includes JavaScript placement, and embedding External JavaScript code. From there, we move into variable declaration and operators for performing arithmetic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NGINX, Apache, SSL Encryption - Certification Course</title>
      <link>/nginx-apache-ssl-encryption-certification-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nginx-apache-ssl-encryption-certification-course/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our latest course, which will guide you through the process of installing, securing, and configuring NGINX or Apache on an Ubuntu web server. You will also learn to encrypt all web traffic, using a Free SSL certificate from Let’s Encrypt.
APACHE Section:
This course begins with exploring the most widely used web server technology available, Apache. Statistics show that Apache is used to run over 65% of all web servers around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pharmacy Assistants In Canada Preparation Course</title>
      <link>/pharmacy-assistants-in-canada-preparation-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pharmacy-assistants-in-canada-preparation-course/</guid>
      <description>** Last updated on Aug 24 2021 **
**This course will also help US students in the clinical part as there are a lot of similarities**
** Your Certificate Will Be Available As Soon As You Finish The Course **
**We will mostly use Ontario, federal, and students insurances to empower your billing skills**
Are you looking for a career as a pharmacy assistant in Canada (especially in Ontario)? Are you a pharmacy assistant and would like to improve your skills and take your career to the next level?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMP® Practice Test: Project Management Professional 2021</title>
      <link>/pmp-practice-test-project-management-professional-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pmp-practice-test-project-management-professional-2021/</guid>
      <description>The PMP® certification is the most widely and globally recognized project management certification in 2021. It validates your experience and knowledge of Project Management. Unfortunately PMP® Exam content outline has changed in 2021, Hence old mock test preparations can not completely prepare you to take the challenge. This course can align your preparation to the new expectation of PMI from its students. Each practice test covers a deep understanding to carry out project management responsibilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical Bootcamp JWT Authentication with Java &amp; SpringBoot</title>
      <link>/practical-bootcamp-jwt-authentication-with-java-springboot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/practical-bootcamp-jwt-authentication-with-java-springboot/</guid>
      <description>JWT(Json web token) is a standard for securing API&#39;s in a Microservices architecture, using this standard we can secure API&#39;s built in any technology like Nodejs, Python, .NET etc but in this course we will building API&#39;s using Java and SpringBoot and than we will be securing them using JWT and Spring security, we will also use all the industry best practices and standards along the way.
We will start with learning concepts like:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management Essential Training</title>
      <link>/project-management-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project-management-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>Project management is a start-to-finish approach to getting things done and making projects more successful. It&#39;s a profession, but it&#39;s also a set of techniques that anyone can apply to achieve goals and manage project work more effectively. Project management can be used to guide small, simple projects as well as complex enterprise-wide initiatives.
In this course you&#39;ll be fascinated by how things work and how to make things work better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP C_THR12_65 Practice Tests</title>
      <link>/sap-c_thr12_65-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sap-c_thr12_65-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Preparing from the beginning of life we prepare ourselves for the challenges of taking the first step or speaking the first words.
In the current world, that is, in the present, it remains the same or you prepare for the exam or you may fail to waste time and money.
Practice tests offer mock questions where you can answer your questions if you are really prepared for the official exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SELL Like HELL: Facebook Ads for E-COMMERCE Ultimate MASTERY</title>
      <link>/sell-like-hell-facebook-ads-for-e-commerce-ultimate-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sell-like-hell-facebook-ads-for-e-commerce-ultimate-mastery/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Excellent Facebook Ads &amp;amp; Instagram Ads Course. Would highly recommend this course to someone who is looking to learn or for that matter even gain knowledge. No institute or a YouTube video teaches this in so much detail as much as Tomas. I haven’t come across so far a genuine course teaching material as much as you have designed. Thanks Tomas a ton.&#34; Ridhima
&#34;Best course for Facebook e-commerce ads. Really in depth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup a Virtual Web Server using Linode or Digital Ocean</title>
      <link>/setup-a-virtual-web-server-using-linode-or-digital-ocean/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/setup-a-virtual-web-server-using-linode-or-digital-ocean/</guid>
      <description>This course offers an in-depth, hands-on overview of setting up and configuring a production web server, using Linode or Digital Ocean. Virtual Cloud Servers have become the industry standard for hosting web applications of all sizes and complexity. This includes small static web pages, to dynamic, database driven web sites that handle thousands of simultaneous processes. Regardless of the project, virtual servers offer a solution that provides web developers a scalable infrastructure that can easily adapt to a changing environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Facebook Traffic Ads (Facebook CPC) Course 2021</title>
      <link>/the-complete-facebook-traffic-ads-facebook-cpc-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-facebook-traffic-ads-facebook-cpc-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Gain more clients, maximise sales, and push more traffic to your website with the most comprehensive and current Facebook Traffic and Marketing course out there - The Complete Facebook Traffic Ads (Facebook CPC) Course 2021!
&#34;I love Tom, he is the man, he really knows what he&#39;s talking about when it comes to Facebook marketing. A true expert in the field! Don&#39;t hesitate to take this course, because I promise you that you will not be disappointed!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Confluence Masterclass for Project Managers</title>
      <link>/atlassian-confluence-masterclass-for-project-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/atlassian-confluence-masterclass-for-project-managers/</guid>
      <description>Confluence is a powerful enterprise collaboration tool that brings people, knowledge, and ideas together in a shared workspace, so you can do your best work. Through this course &#34;Atlassian Confluence Masterclass&#34;, you will learn how to use Confluence to transform the way your team works.
This course is structured to guide you through all the key aspects of managing and using Confluence.
Whether you’re new to Confluence, training your teammates, or ready to take your Confluence skills to the next level, this guide covers everything from the basics to in-depth best practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate Exam SAA-C02</title>
      <link>/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-exam-saa-c02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-exam-saa-c02/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate Exam SAA-C02
The AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate (SAA-C02) examination is intended for individuals who perform in a solutions architect role. This exam validates an examinee’s ability to effectively demonstrate knowledge of how to architect and deploy secure and robust applications on AWS technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-104 Microsoft Azure Administrator Practice Exam july 2021</title>
      <link>/az-104-microsoft-azure-administrator-practice-exam-july-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/az-104-microsoft-azure-administrator-practice-exam-july-2021/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; FULLY UPDATED to the latest AZ-104 Microsoft Azure Administrator exam version july 2021
There are a lot of courses out there that are claiming that their courses are fully updated, but they&#39;re actually not! Our practice tests contain the latest additions on the new AZ-104 topics, the exam received an update in july 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-104 Microsoft Azure Administrator Practice Exams JUN21</title>
      <link>/az-104-microsoft-azure-administrator-practice-exams-jun21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/az-104-microsoft-azure-administrator-practice-exams-jun21/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; UPDATED to the latest AZ-104 Microsoft Azure Administrator exam JUN 2021
Microsoft&#39;s AZ-104 Microsoft Azure Administrator exam is one of the way to prove that you have a deep and thorough understanding &amp;amp; experience in Microsoft Azure. As you may aware, employers always look for latest certifications in the resume while filing up vacancies. Getting the Azure Administrator Associate certification is the ultimate proof of your expertise in Azure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-900 Microsoft Azure Fundamentals Exam - july 2021</title>
      <link>/az-900-microsoft-azure-fundamentals-exam-july-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/az-900-microsoft-azure-fundamentals-exam-july-2021/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;AZ-900 Microsoft Azure Fundamentals Exam - july 2021
Microsoft Azure Fundamentals is the first certification exam for Azure cloud. Through the completion of our three practice exams, you will gain all knowledge needed to successfully achieve your Azure qualification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-900 Microsoft Azure Fundamentals Practice Exams JUN2021</title>
      <link>/az-900-microsoft-azure-fundamentals-practice-exams-jun2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/az-900-microsoft-azure-fundamentals-practice-exams-jun2021/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; AZ-900 Microsoft Azure Fundamentals Practice Exams
The AZ-900 Microsoft Azure Fundamentals exam is intended for beginners who work with cloud-based solutions and services. Candidates should be able to demonstrate a fundamental knowledge of cloud concepts, Azure services, workloads, security, privacy, pricing, support, as well as networking, storage, compute, application support, and application development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CLF-C01  AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Practice Tests</title>
      <link>/clf-c01-aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/clf-c01-aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Get ready to validate your skills with the latest and most up-to-date practice exam from the AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner and become a Certified Professional now!
AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam (CLF-C01)
The AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner examination is intended for individuals who have the knowledge and skills necessary to effectively demonstrate an overall understanding of the AWS Cloud, independent of specific technical roles addressed by other AWS Certifications. The exam can be taken at a testing center or from the comfort and convenience of a home or office location as an online proctored exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Guide to Pinterest &amp; Pinterest Growth 2021</title>
      <link>/complete-guide-to-pinterest-pinterest-growth-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-guide-to-pinterest-pinterest-growth-2021/</guid>
      <description>Hey there, Nick Nyxson here.
Welcome to PinHeroes.
Only Pinterest course EVER to teach you how to grow your profile on Pinterest from 0 to 1 Million monthly viewers in just short few months.
Pinterest is one of the fastest-growing social media platforms and its main appeal is its unconventional way treat the content. It is an ONLY social media platform that Not just NOT RESTRICT&amp;nbsp;external content but actively encourages it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction into Facebook Marketing &amp; Facebook Advertising</title>
      <link>/introduction-into-facebook-marketing-facebook-advertising/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/introduction-into-facebook-marketing-facebook-advertising/</guid>
      <description>&#34;The BEST, authentic, great and very precise course on Facebook Marketing and Facebook Advertising. Though the course is just 10 hours, it covers the topics beyond anyone&#39;s expectations. I would rank this course #1 because the instructor Tomas takes the systematic and a very organized approach in training the students. I will enrol for another courses because it&#39;s JUST WORTH IT. The course brilliantly and generously covers the entire topic without biases or prejudice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness para desarrollar la inteligencia emocional</title>
      <link>/mindfulness-para-desarrollar-la-inteligencia-emocional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mindfulness-para-desarrollar-la-inteligencia-emocional/</guid>
      <description>Te enseño herramientas efectivas y sencillas de aplicar en tu rutina diaria, invirtiendo sólo entre 5 a 15 minutos al día tus emociones no serán más un obstáculo en la consecución de tus metas, tampoco volverás a sentir la culpa o vergüenza de tus impulsos y reacciones emocionales. 
Tu también puedes gozar de relaciones empáticas, satisfactorias y sin tantas fricciones. Poder solucionar de manera asertiva y consciente las diferencias con tus seres queridos, colegas, clientes y colaboradores es posible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income: 27 Ways to Earn Passive Income Online</title>
      <link>/passive-income-27-ways-to-earn-passive-income-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/passive-income-27-ways-to-earn-passive-income-online/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to earn money even while you are sleeping?
Do you want to earn money automatically once you&#39;ve set up the systems?
Then this is the right course for you.
I&amp;nbsp;have been earning passive income already for years and I have helped 1,000&#39;s of people worldwide to do the same through my YouTube channel, Udemy courses and blogs.
Earning passive income works in the following way (in a nutshell):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDE-GooglE Cloud Professional Data Engineer Practice tests</title>
      <link>/pde-google-cloud-professional-data-engineer-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pde-google-cloud-professional-data-engineer-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Description
This Google certified professional data engineer practice test 2021 is a sum of modules covering design systems that ingest large volume data, effective storage of data, efficient processing and analysis of data. The test series also includes questions that revolve arounds the utilization of tools for visualization, reporting and machine learning.
Post the practice test the applicants will have a sound knowledge of how to build, tune and monitor a high performance data system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Branding: Personal Brand Building | Fame &amp; Success!</title>
      <link>/personal-branding-personal-brand-building-fame-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/personal-branding-personal-brand-building-fame-success/</guid>
      <description>This is the definitive course on personal branding. My name is Dekker Fraser and I was a Global Brand Manager for Sony PlayStation. I have over 100,000 students on Udemy and I was a VP of Marketing for a Google accelerator startup. I was a college marketing instructor, and I studied brand management at the #1 business school for marketing. This is where the father of marketing himself, Philip Kotler, teaches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python And Flask Framework Complete Course</title>
      <link>/python-and-flask-framework-complete-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/python-and-flask-framework-complete-course/</guid>
      <description>This course is a depth introduction to fundamental python programming concepts.
Learn Python From Beginner To Advanced Level
 I’ve created thorough, extensive, but easy to follow content which you’ll easily understand and absorb.
 The course starts with the basics, including Python fundamentals, programming, and user interaction.

The curriculum is going to be very hands-on as we walk you from start to finish becoming a professional Python developer. We will start from the very beginning by teaching you Python basics and programming fundamentals, and then going into advanced topics and different career fields in Python so you can get real-life practice and be ready for the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantity Surveying With Rate Analysis And Take Off-Beginners</title>
      <link>/quantity-surveying-with-rate-analysis-and-take-off-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quantity-surveying-with-rate-analysis-and-take-off-beginners/</guid>
      <description>This course will help you to understand the roles and responsibilities of a Quantity Surveyor, the skills and educational qualifications required to start a career in Quantity Surveying, the basics of rate analysis and the required knowledge to take off quantities from construction drawings using two globally used software’s Bluebeam Revu and Planswift.

By the end of this course you will gain knowledge regarding the different element to be included while pricing your construction project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redação: Enem, vestibular, concurso.Teoria &#43; tira-dúvidas</title>
      <link>/reda%C3%A7%C3%A3o-enem-vestibular-concurso.teoria-tira-d%C3%BAvidas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reda%C3%A7%C3%A3o-enem-vestibular-concurso.teoria-tira-d%C3%BAvidas/</guid>
      <description>Se você já tem professor para avaliar suas redações, e não&amp;nbsp; precisa de exercícios de reforço, aqui você tem as quase 8&amp;nbsp;horas de aulas em vídeo do curso completo (disponível na plataforma Udemy) + tira-dúvidas ilimitado comigo!

Você vai descobrir como escrever dissertações de provas mais rápido, sem decorar regras ou fórmulas.
Se você trava ou fica em &#34;branco&#34;, veja o que te espera:
tipos de dissertação
como começar a redação sem travar</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP C_TSCM52_67 Practice Test</title>
      <link>/sap-c_tscm52_67-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sap-c_tscm52_67-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>Improve your score with hours of practice tests is the right way to test your knowledge with lifetime access to study anywhere.
Understanding the exam topics is one of the advantages of preparing for the official exam.
Find out more about the exam: C_TSCM52_67 - SAP Certified Application Associate - Acquisition with SAP ERP 6.0 EhP7
The SAP C_TSCM52_67 certification exam verifies that the candidate has adequate knowledge in the Purchasing area to meet the requirements of the consultant profile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP HANA C_HANATEC_12 Practice Tests</title>
      <link>/sap-hana-c_hanatec_12-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sap-hana-c_hanatec_12-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>In today&#39;s world, people need a source of study to prepare for life&#39;s new challenges.
Welcome to the practice tests for the exam: SAP C_HANATEC_12.
Our goal is to test your knowledge with questions and answers with the latest exam references, giving you the chance to pass the first attempt.
You have lifelong access to practice tests, meaning you can study from anywhere without hurrying to win this challenge.
Brief Details</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Engine Optimization Complete Specialization Course</title>
      <link>/search-engine-optimization-complete-specialization-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/search-engine-optimization-complete-specialization-course/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the World&#39;s best specialized SEO course ever. 
The course cover everything from theory to practical with case studies and examples. This is the only course in the world where you woll also learn about the technicalities of SEO and how to handle them. The content of this course is based on real world practices and checklists used by professionals in the SEO world.
You will learn about</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Lightroom Masterclass - Beginner to Expert</title>
      <link>/adobe-lightroom-masterclass-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/adobe-lightroom-masterclass-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Adobe Lightroom is a powerful, intuitive program used for enhancing, organizing, and editing your photos. Users can render enhancements on everything from smartphone photos to raw DSLR images. This course explores many of the exciting features this program offers. Take a look at just a brief summary of the course content below. Section 1: Introduction 
Students are provided with an overview of learning objectives and some of the key features that the course will explore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop CC Crash Course Learn Photoshop In Two Hour</title>
      <link>/adobe-photoshop-cc-crash-course-learn-photoshop-in-two-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/adobe-photoshop-cc-crash-course-learn-photoshop-in-two-hour/</guid>
      <description>Hi There, I am Stephen Koel Soren and I am a Graphics and Web Expert. This is a crash course for Adobe Photoshop and You will learn only the essential part that is really required for design in Photoshop within hour. You will learn from this course:
Color and Adjustment
Content-Aware &amp;amp; Cropping
Text Style
Shadow
Selection &amp;amp; Masking
Blur &amp;amp; Filters
Retouch
and many more.
This course is especially designed for beginner those who want to learn photoshop basic and essential part within a short time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop CC- Basic Photoshop training</title>
      <link>/adobe-photoshop-cc-basic-photoshop-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/adobe-photoshop-cc-basic-photoshop-training/</guid>
      <description>Learning the basics of Adobe Photoshop is definitely not easy, especially if you have no prior knowledge in this field. But, this course can teach you everything you need to know to start using photoshop and making your own projects with pictures that you take yourself or pictures that you have simply found on the internet. If you:
- Are a student and need to learn how to properly use Photoshop</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro CC Essential Video Editing Zero To Hero</title>
      <link>/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-essential-video-editing-zero-to-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-essential-video-editing-zero-to-hero/</guid>
      <description>Hi There,
My name is Stephen Koel Soren and I am a graphics and web expert. If you are absolute beginner or if you never open Adobe Premiere pro cc before than this is a perfect class for you. This is a beginner level class so so together me you we will learn Adobe Premiere pro from basic to advance. This is a project base class so you will be able to apply your learned skill in real time class project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Foundations of Python Programming | 2021 Training</title>
      <link>/advanced-foundations-of-python-programming-2021-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/advanced-foundations-of-python-programming-2021-training/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to the Advanced Foundations of Python Programming | 2021 Training Masterclass.
Learn the Advanced foundations of modern python programming with this powerful, deep, direct to the point and interactive training.
For each concept in this course, you&#39;ll master the theory then you&#39;ll&amp;nbsp; practice with many real examples.
Do you want to Advance your Python development career?
Do you want to be able to create real programs using the advanced concepts of Python?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced LinkedIn Advertising: LinkedIn Ads Advanced B2B</title>
      <link>/advanced-linkedin-advertising-linkedin-ads-advanced-b2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/advanced-linkedin-advertising-linkedin-ads-advanced-b2b/</guid>
      <description>This B2B LinkedIn advertising course builds on my previous one by showing you how to build more scalable full-funnel campaigns, instead of just focusing on the low-hanging fruit when it comes to lead generation. You will learn how to build an efficient lead generation campaign with the appropriate content. Learn from someone who has been doing LinkedIn advertising since 2011, has worked for companies of varying sizes (including the Fortune 100), and has a top-tier marketing MBA from Philip Kotler&#39;s school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Coach Fundamentos basado en Certtificacion CertiProf</title>
      <link>/agile-coach-fundamentos-basado-en-certtificacion-certiprof/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/agile-coach-fundamentos-basado-en-certtificacion-certiprof/</guid>
      <description>Este curso muestra aspectos básicos del rol de un Agile Coach.
Basado en el currículo académico desarrollado por CertiProf. No es una vision completa del impacto de un Agile Coach, pero si brinda todos los fundamentos requeridos para iniciar una carrera que considero nunca termina.
Ser un Agile Coach es un desafío y responsabilidad que debe mantener abierta la formación constante. Tener un mindset de aprendizaje constante.
Los portales de trabajo de todos los países muestran cifras de la necesidad de este rol, sus responsabilidades y sus ingresos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon EKS Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>/amazon-eks-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/amazon-eks-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to do use Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service but don&#39;t know where to start?	Would you like to make amazing Kubernetes applications in AWS Cloud or on-premise and bring your ideas to life?	Then Amazon EKS Ultimate Course is for you!	Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.	Amazon EKS is an in-demand skill in 2021.&amp;nbsp; The course begins with the basics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon PPC Masterclass - The Ultimate PPC Guide</title>
      <link>/amazon-ppc-masterclass-the-ultimate-ppc-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/amazon-ppc-masterclass-the-ultimate-ppc-guide/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling with Amazon&#39;s Sponsored Products ads but don&#39;t know where to start? Do your existing PPC campaigns get high aCos and/or low sales volume?&amp;nbsp; Then this course is designed for you!

I will show you the biggest mistakes I see when using Amazon&#39;s Sponsored Products and teach you how to properly set up and optimise and create your campaigns. 

After years of testing and spending literally tens of thousands of dollars I&#39;ve discovered highly profitable Amazon PPC campaigns that have gone on to generate tens of thousands of dollars in sales and PROFIT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American English Pronunciation for Beginners</title>
      <link>/american-english-pronunciation-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/american-english-pronunciation-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling with your English pronunciation? 
Do you have a strong accent when speaking English?

Do native speakers always ask you to repeat yourself?

Do you want to begin speaking with an American accent confidently?

Do you what tips and help with speaking with an American accent? 
I welcome you to this - “American English Pronunciation Training - course where I will patiently guide you through the basic techniques you need to pronounce English sounds correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App Marketing: Mobile App Marketing &amp; Growth Hacking</title>
      <link>/app-marketing-mobile-app-marketing-growth-hacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/app-marketing-mobile-app-marketing-growth-hacking/</guid>
      <description>This is the definitive course on app marketing to help with your go-to-market app launch. Please note that this is NOT just a course on app store optimization (ASO). This is a more comprehensive course on marketing your app in the market for maximum impact.
I led the mobile app marketing for a Google venture-backed startup (Series E) in Silicon Valley. In just four months, I increased downloads by 71% and mobile app revenue by 89%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arabic complete beginner course through (Byna Yadek)</title>
      <link>/arabic-complete-beginner-course-through-byna-yadek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/arabic-complete-beginner-course-through-byna-yadek/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I&#39;m Mr.Bakoor. I have been teaching Arabic for a while. I got students form All over the world. My respect for all of them. My students liked the way I teach because It&#39;s easy, it goes step by step, they easily understand and also show improvement,&amp;nbsp; I feel so happy when I my student telling me that they are really improving in Arabic, I hope to make Arabic teaching easier for everyone who think Learning Arabic is hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art Therapy for Men (Oxford Diploma)</title>
      <link>/art-therapy-for-men-oxford-diploma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/art-therapy-for-men-oxford-diploma/</guid>
      <description>Note: this course does not qualify the recipient to perform any form of therapy or counseling for any other person
This is an unusual course as it is designed to be of use/application to men in particular. Of course it is not &#39;exclusive&#39; just a slight bias. Studies are referenced where appropriate.
Please remember that this course includes:
a. the lectures themselves
b. the Q/A section - make full use of it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence in SEO (2021 Extreme Edition)</title>
      <link>/artificial-intelligence-in-seo-2021-extreme-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artificial-intelligence-in-seo-2021-extreme-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the ninth course in Term 1 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Looking for the word called &#34;Popularity&#34; to come to life? It&#39;s good to be heard, of course, and everything, but is that really the point? To be able to applaud and say, yeah... I had 1,000,000 visits last year to my website... that may be amazing, but why is website traffic important to your business or any business, for that matter?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Services for Solutions Architect Associate [2021]</title>
      <link>/aws-services-for-solutions-architect-associate-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aws-services-for-solutions-architect-associate-2021/</guid>
      <description>***UPDATE: New Content ALERT!!! Around 50+ video content added to the course!***

AWS is a public cloud and a pioneer in the cloud computing domain. Aws provides every kind of service model like IAAS, PAAS, and SAAS. In this course, I will discuss various cloud services provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS).
Here we will elaborate on the features of AWS services, their use cases, how to create those services, how to configure them, and how to integrate various services together to present a holistic cloud solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>B2B Lead Generation via Personalised Sales Videos &amp; LinkedIn</title>
      <link>/b2b-lead-generation-via-personalised-sales-videos-linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/b2b-lead-generation-via-personalised-sales-videos-linkedin/</guid>
      <description>Imagine if your B2B lead generation tactics were 20x MORE&amp;nbsp;EFFECTIVE than they are now.
This course can help make it happen…
Wonder Leads is an innovative new approach to business development. It centres on individually personalised sales videos delivered through LinkedIn, where it’s proved to be almost 20x more effective than cold calling at generating warm leads.
Based on the Axiom award-winning sales book (previous winners include Seth Godin, Tony Robbins &amp;amp; Peter Drucker), entrepreneur and champion for positive communication Dave Holloway reveals a step-by-step approach to effective social selling that anyone can follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Theory for Guitar</title>
      <link>/basic-theory-for-guitar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/basic-theory-for-guitar/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to your Music Theory for Guitarists Course!
Hi there! I&#39;m Jack, and I have been teaching music for many many years, and in all of that time, the main thing I have noticed that holds students back, whether they have played for months or for decades, is a lack of an understanding of the basics of music theory. So I&amp;nbsp;have created this course to address that issue so that students will have their fundamentals down and will therefore be able to continually improve without limit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become a Product Marketing Manager | Product Management</title>
      <link>/become-a-product-marketing-manager-product-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/become-a-product-marketing-manager-product-management/</guid>
      <description>Learn from an experienced Silicon Valley PMM with a top MBA
Learn how to become a product marketing manager from&amp;nbsp;someone with years of&amp;nbsp;experience in product marketing at small, medium, and large software companies including Sony.&amp;nbsp;Your lead instructor received his MBA from the top marketing school in the U.S. and works in the epicenter of product&amp;nbsp;marketing in San Francisco.&amp;nbsp;
New! Free access to the top-rated book Become a Product Marketing Manager (PDF version)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin 101 - Complete Intro to Bitcoin, Blockchain &amp; Crypto</title>
      <link>/bitcoin-101-complete-intro-to-bitcoin-blockchain-crypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bitcoin-101-complete-intro-to-bitcoin-blockchain-crypto/</guid>
      <description>In this course, we dive deep into one of the most revolutionary assets of all time... Bitcoin. We dig into how Bitcoin&#39;s underlying technology, blockchain work. With no technical knowledge required, you will learn how the blockchain works, and why it is being called the &#34;next generation of the internet.&#34; Next, we take a closer look at the fundamentals of Bitcoin, and what makes it the most important cryptocurrency in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/blockchain-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blockchain-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve not tried using Blockchain and invest the next generation currency, then today is the time to start!

Never before has there been an technology platform of this magnitude that will allow you to reach an audience of billions and rapidly grow your business online at next to zero cost!

Become The Ultimate Blockchain Master and join this course today to learn the same PROVEN success strategy Henry Zhang , the Crypto Currency expert and world-leading trader used to build this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blues &amp; Rock Theory for Guitar</title>
      <link>/blues-rock-theory-for-guitar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blues-rock-theory-for-guitar/</guid>
      <description>Now that we have worked our way through the basics of diatonic theory in our last course, that is to say, understanding major and minor scales and their harmonies, we’re ready to look at some styles that have strayed away from that system.
The most important influence on all the styles of popular music that break away from traditional European music, is Blues music- it doesn’t have to be your favorite thing to play or listen to, but whether you know it or not, there’s hardly a popular style in existence that doesn’t draw from it in some way or another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Branding &amp; Brand Management: Branding Strategy Brand Tactics</title>
      <link>/branding-brand-management-branding-strategy-brand-tactics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/branding-brand-management-branding-strategy-brand-tactics/</guid>
      <description>Top MBAs are expensive, time-consuming, and extremely difficult to get into. My goal with this course is to give you an MBA level of&amp;nbsp;understanding branding and brand management. Learn from a former Global Brand Manager at Sony PlayStation who studied brand management at the Kellogg School of Management and has helped countless startups with their branding. If you sell marketing services, this gives you a sophisticated edge over other marketers. If you’re a marketing manager, this gives you a strategic understanding of the role of branding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build Laravel Applications fast using blueprint</title>
      <link>/build-laravel-applications-fast-using-blueprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/build-laravel-applications-fast-using-blueprint/</guid>
      <description>What you&#39;ll learn
Initialization of a Laravel app using blueprint
Building blueprint yml file
Autocreation of migrations , models
Autocreation of Controllers , and actions
Autocreation of Mailable , Jobs , Events .. Change you whole way of thinking of Laravel application building
Configure your blueprint to work better for you
Increase development speed
Promote Laravel conventions
Move from your ERD to your fully-functioning Data Access Layer
Get rid of repetitive tasks and routine debugging process</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Repair - Auto Repair &amp; Tuning - Auto Technician Training</title>
      <link>/car-repair-auto-repair-tuning-auto-technician-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/car-repair-auto-repair-tuning-auto-technician-training/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
One of the things that I find most interesting about automotive technology is how it advances and changes. It is also interesting that ideas from many years ago often return to favour. In this course I have therefore concentrated on core technologies, in other words how the technology works, rather than giving too many examples from specific vehicles. However, I have included some examples of Formula 1 technology, arguably the pinnacle of automotive engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold Email Writing: Cold Emailing Cold Email Lead Generation</title>
      <link>/cold-email-writing-cold-emailing-cold-email-lead-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cold-email-writing-cold-emailing-cold-email-lead-generation/</guid>
      <description>Master high-performing cold emails and email marketing!
I’m going to teach you…
How I secured a meeting with the CEO and executive team of a $30 million business off just one single automated cold email template
How achieve open rates over 50% and boost your clicks and responses
How to change people’s minds using certain copywriting words
The six big tips for writing effective, persuasive cold emails
The BEST copywriting frameworks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Correction &amp; Grading with Adobe Premiere Pro 2021</title>
      <link>/color-correction-grading-with-adobe-premiere-pro-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/color-correction-grading-with-adobe-premiere-pro-2021/</guid>
      <description>This complete course will take you to the essentials of color correction with the Lumetri color tools inside Premiere Pro. You will learn different techniques while also understanding how color philosophy works. (Footage Included)
We&#39;ll fly together through this wonderful world of colors. And on the end you will be able to fix color issues and take your shots to a higher professional level.
What will I learn?
You will learn a complete essential training of color correction and grading in Premiere Pro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Grading and Video Editing with Davinci Resolve 17</title>
      <link>/color-grading-and-video-editing-with-davinci-resolve-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/color-grading-and-video-editing-with-davinci-resolve-17/</guid>
      <description>DaVinci Resolve 16&amp;nbsp; Beginners Course 
DaVinci Resolve 16 is a free professional video editing application used by professionals and amateurs. It’s easy and simple to use. It provides you with simple to use yet powerful tools to edit your videos and achieve high quality production.
This course is for beginners. You do not need any previous knowledge in DaVinci Resolve 17 or video editing experience.
You will dive straightaway into creating your first video and add music, graphics, text and couple of transitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combined Heat and Power (CHP) Cogeneration Fundamentals</title>
      <link>/combined-heat-and-power-chp-cogeneration-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/combined-heat-and-power-chp-cogeneration-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Combined Heat and Power (CHP) Cogeneration Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn all about the concept of CHP and cogeneration that are essential in working in the industry.

I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on cogeneration as well as how to apply it in the utility industry.

If you are currently a professional who are interested working with Cogeneration plants, you will find this course of great help to get the fundamental knowledge you need to kick start your professional career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Adobe Lightroom Megacourse: Beginner to Expert</title>
      <link>/complete-adobe-lightroom-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-adobe-lightroom-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to edit your own photos? Maybe you want to enhance a photo and show it off on social media, or perhaps you want to fix the imperfections in an otherwise perfect snapshot of your life. Whether you’re a casual photographer or hoping to make a career out of it, editing photos isn’t only for the pros. You can take any photo from drab to fab with just a few tweaks and adjustments - and we’re here to teach you how.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete CompTIA Network&#43; (N10-007) Video Training Series</title>
      <link>/complete-comptia-network-n10-007-video-training-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-comptia-network-n10-007-video-training-series/</guid>
      <description>** Get Ready to Crush Your CompTIA Network+ (N10-007) Exam **
Embark on (or continue) your IT certification journey with CompTIA’s Network+ certification. The Network+ certification acts as a “sampler platter” of networking, where you get to “taste test” a wide variety of technologies, like cloud, wireless, software defined networking, route/switch, security, troubleshooting, network management, and so many others.
Guiding you through each step of your journey is award-winning instructor and double CCIE (Cisco Certified Internetworking Expert) Kevin Wallace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Course of After Effects: Learn From an Expert</title>
      <link>/complete-course-of-after-effects-learn-from-an-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-course-of-after-effects-learn-from-an-expert/</guid>
      <description>Hi. This is Mohammad Fazel, motion designer and i have 10 years of experience in this field. I&#39;ll be glad to share my exprience in After Effects with you. in this course, I&#39;ll explore all capabilities that After Effects has in making Motion graphics and visual Effects.
after watching this course, you&#39;ll absolutely be ready to enter the world of motion graphics and visual effects.
you don&#39;t need any prior knowledge for this course and I&#39;ll teach you from introducing you to after effects to the point that you learn everything about the software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Digital Marketing Course for Local Businesses 2021</title>
      <link>/complete-digital-marketing-course-for-local-businesses-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-digital-marketing-course-for-local-businesses-2021/</guid>
      <description>&#34;This Digital Marketing Course is amazing. I have learned a lot of from this course. I like the explanation style of the teacher. So, please everyone join this course to change your life....&#34; Kamran
&#34;The complete content was brilliantly explained. Thank you.&#34; Riya
&#34;The course content is amazing. I have learned many new things, especially new tips and tricks in digital marketing. One thing I have to tell that the trainer is awesome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete French Course: Learn French for Beginners</title>
      <link>/complete-french-course-learn-french-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-french-course-learn-french-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to learn French? Dubbed the “language of love”, French is used by over 235 million speakers daily in over 54 countries. But why should you pick French out of all the languages you could be learning?
To start, France isn’t just one of the most beautiful countries in central Europe, but a global powerhouse with significant presence in the automobile, aircraft and chemical manufacturing, the electronic, machinery, metallurgy industries, as well as tourism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete General Chemistry 20&#43; hours of lectures &amp; examples</title>
      <link>/complete-general-chemistry-20-hours-of-lectures-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-general-chemistry-20-hours-of-lectures-examples/</guid>
      <description>Description:
General Chemistry is a basic course for a broad range of students from different fields of science and engineering. This course is designed to help you get a firm grasp over the most important topics in chemistry that you need to know in order to do great in your exams and classes. By the end of the course you’ll learn the principals and important concepts regarding matter, atoms, solutions, phases, chemical reactions, equilibrium, kinetics, acids and bases and so much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Introduction to Cybersecurity 2021</title>
      <link>/complete-introduction-to-cybersecurity-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-introduction-to-cybersecurity-2021/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Complete Introduction to Cybersecurity 2021. In this course, you will learn the fundamentals of I.T. while learning the working components of cybersecurity. No prior knowledge or skill is required. If you are a cybersecurity student, aspiring security professional, security enthusiast or someone intrigued to learn more about the industry, this course will provide a springboard for you to learn the basics. As a current cybersecurity student, I know exactly what type of questions, doubts, and thoughts you are experiencing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Inventory Management in Microsoft Excel &amp;TALLY ERP9</title>
      <link>/complete-inventory-management-in-microsoft-excel-tally-erp9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-inventory-management-in-microsoft-excel-tally-erp9/</guid>
      <description>Recent Student&#39;s Reviews

*** This course is well detailed in inventory management. I really learnt how to make practical use of excel, tally ERP9 and good inventory valuation (Williams Oguamah) ***

**Yes it is a good match for me. It will help me in my career path ( Dineo ) ***

*** it was awesome to learn &amp;amp; get insights from this course (Haritha.L) ***

*** Very Helpful (JULIUS IGNACIO)***</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete JAVASCRIPT with HTML5,CSS3 from zero to Expert-2021</title>
      <link>/complete-javascript-with-html5css3-from-zero-to-expert-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-javascript-with-html5css3-from-zero-to-expert-2021/</guid>
      <description>Want to learn Web Design &amp;amp; Web Development Skills? Then this is the RIGHT course For you! Many languages came and disappear but JavaScript is language that is enjoying a high run and demand in the programming world. The very first things you need to learn HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and JQuery to become a Web Developer and off-course some Web Design Guidelines. This course will exactly teach you all these New Skills to become a good Web Developer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Online Business Marketing Tool - Guide to Systeme</title>
      <link>/complete-online-business-marketing-tool-guide-to-systeme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-online-business-marketing-tool-guide-to-systeme/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Complete Online Business Marketing Tool - Guide to Systeme!
For a long time, marketers have had to piece together various tools and software tools in order to achieve their goals. But these days, marketers are constantly being confronted with new platforms, new startup companies, and old favorites that are constantly re-tooling themselves and shifting their strategies.
In this rapid-fire internet era of marketing, it can be hard for even the most seasoned professionals to keep up with everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Tamil Course: Learn Tamil for Beginners</title>
      <link>/complete-tamil-course-learn-tamil-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-tamil-course-learn-tamil-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to learn Tamil? As one of the oldest classical languages in the world, Tamil is spoken by over 70 million people. But why should you pick Tamil out of all the languages you could be learning?
To start, Tamil is the official language of Tamil Nadu, India’s fourth largest state, which has seen significant economic growth and foreign investment over the last decade. The state is a leading figure in several industries, such as automobile and auto-components, engineering, pharmaceuticals and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CompTIA Cloud&#43; CV0-002 Bootcamp Get Certified!</title>
      <link>/comptia-cloud-cv0-002-bootcamp-get-certified/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/comptia-cloud-cv0-002-bootcamp-get-certified/</guid>
      <description>Course comes with a 900+ page study guide with exam tips! Updated June 2020
This course is taught by a current CompTIA&amp;nbsp;SME&amp;nbsp;and CompTIA&amp;nbsp;Cloud Plus Train the Trainer.&amp;nbsp; 
This course is meant to provide you the baseline knowledge to pass the course and is meant for professionals that have IT&amp;nbsp;experience.&amp;nbsp; Get Certified promptly and efficiently.

The CompTIA Cloud+ certification is an internationally recognized validation of the knowledge required of IT practitioners working in cloud computing environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Creation &amp; Content Writing for B2B Content Marketing</title>
      <link>/content-creation-content-writing-for-b2b-content-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/content-creation-content-writing-for-b2b-content-marketing/</guid>
      <description>ATTENTION business-to-business writers and marketers!
Do you want to learn how to develop world-class B2B content from a former VP of Marketing with Fortune 100 experience, a top-tier MBA, and college-level teaching experience? Do you want to take your content writing and content creation to the next level? This is the course for you. This course goes into the details of B2B content writing &amp;amp; content creation using case studies and real-world examples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/content-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/content-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Content marketing is currently one of the biggest trends in digital marketing as a whole and is an area that many website owners and brands are investing in heavily right now thanks to the impressive returns that they are seeing.
But content marketing is a complex and broad term that encompasses a number of different strategies and activities.
In order for it to be successful, you need to have a good understanding of what it is, how it works and how you can best adapt it to work for your particular brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversion Rate Optimization CRO: B2B Conversion Rate CRO</title>
      <link>/conversion-rate-optimization-cro-b2b-conversion-rate-cro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/conversion-rate-optimization-cro-b2b-conversion-rate-cro/</guid>
      <description>Learn B2B (business-to-business) conversation rate optimization (conversion rate optimisation / CRO) to maximize leads and paying customers. Optimize the entire growth marketing funnel using tactical and strategic conversion maximization approaches from a top MBA with Fortune 100 experience and master&#39;s level analytics training. -&amp;gt; Real examples from my own experience in driving growth for companies of various sizes including Sony and a Google-accelerator startup
-&amp;gt; Advice from my colleagues who drove growth for top companies including LinkedIn and Sephora</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash Course on Civil Engineering and AutoCAD: Part 2</title>
      <link>/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-2/</guid>
      <description>&#34;An estimate for any construction work may be defined as the actual process of calculating the quantities and costs of the various items required in connection with the specialised project - whatsoever&#34;.
Before the start of the project for its execution, the owner should have full knowledge of the volume of work that is to be carried out. The tiny details can help him understand if the actual work can be completed within the proposed time frame and budget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash Course on Civil Engineering and AutoCAD: Part 3</title>
      <link>/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-3/</guid>
      <description>This incredible series-based crash course takes an amazing turn here in Part 3 as&amp;nbsp;&#34;New-age Environmental Engineering &amp;amp; Artificial Intelligence&#34; concepts are taught by Digital Marketing Legend &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34;&amp;nbsp;and Narmadha.M.
Environmental Engineering is a professional engineering discipline that takes advantage of specific scientific topics such as chemistry, biology, geography, geology, hydraulics, hydrology, microbiology, and mathematics to create solutions that will preserve and also improve the health of living organisms and increase environmental quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Criminology : Fundamentals of Criminal Psychology and Law</title>
      <link>/criminology-fundamentals-of-criminal-psychology-and-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/criminology-fundamentals-of-criminal-psychology-and-law/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
What is criminology?
Criminology is a branch of sociology, which traditionally examines human behavior, interaction, and organization. However, it also ties in research and concepts from other areas of study, such as philosophy, anthropology, biology, and psychology. Criminologists examine a broad range of topics related to crime. They are dedicated to studying not only the causes of crime but the social roots and impact as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Trading for Beginners 2021 (CLICK-BY-CLICK)</title>
      <link>/cryptocurrency-trading-for-beginners-2021-click-by-click/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cryptocurrency-trading-for-beginners-2021-click-by-click/</guid>
      <description>Cryptocurrencies may feel confusing if you are a complete beginner... Not anymore!
I&#39;ll show you how cryptocurrency trading works in a SIMPLE &amp;amp; EASY&amp;nbsp;way.
I&#39;ve educated over 350,000 people on Udemy and I&#39;d love to help you next.
After helping so many people, I&#39;ve realized that cryptocurrencies don&#39;t need to be complicated.
When you learn a few simple concepts, you&#39;re already ahead of 99.9% of the population. 1,000&#39;s of beginners have learned about Bitcoin &amp;amp; cryptocurrencies for the first time of their life through my Udemy &amp;amp; YouTube videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Analysis Real world use-cases- Hands on Python</title>
      <link>/data-analysis-real-world-use-cases-hands-on-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/data-analysis-real-world-use-cases-hands-on-python/</guid>
      <description>This is the first course that gives hands-on Data Analysis Projects using Python..


Can you start right now?
A frequently asked question of Python Beginners is: &#34;Do I need to become an expert in Python coding before I can start working on Data Analysis Projects?&#34;
The clear answer is: &#34;No!
You just require some Python Basics like data types, simple operations/operators, lists and numpy arrays that you can learn from my Free Python course &#39;Basics Of Python&#39;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Web- The complete Introduction to the hidden web</title>
      <link>/deep-web-the-complete-introduction-to-the-hidden-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/deep-web-the-complete-introduction-to-the-hidden-web/</guid>
      <description>Have you heard many times about the deep/dark web but you never knew what it is. Or you you have an Idea of what is it but you never visited this part of the web. Then this course for you. You will learn all the basics of the deep/dark and how to access this part of the web. At the end of the course, you will be able to use the TOR browser as your default browser and surf on all the parts of the Web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps - Introducción y Fundamentos no técnicos</title>
      <link>/devops-introducci%C3%B3n-y-fundamentos-no-t%C3%A9cnicos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/devops-introducci%C3%B3n-y-fundamentos-no-t%C3%A9cnicos/</guid>
      <description>DevOps Fundamentos 
*** BONUS *** Preparación Examen para DevOps Essentials Certification
Este curso le brindara conocimiento general y fundamental de lo que es DevOps y lo que no es DevOps.
No es un curso de uso de herramientas de software.&amp;nbsp;
No es un curso de implementación de entrega continua.
Este curso forma parte de la serie que he creado de &#34;alcanza la certificación&#34;. Este curso te brindara la posibilidad de entender la importancia de DevOps, un poco de mapeo con Scrum y otras técnicas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Differential Equations | Complete Differential Equations</title>
      <link>/differential-equations-complete-differential-equations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/differential-equations-complete-differential-equations/</guid>
      <description>Learn Differential Equation:
This course includes video lectures and text explanations of everything from differential equations and its applications, and it includes 7 quizzes (with video solutions!) and&amp;nbsp; for practice worksheet with extra practice problems, to help you test your understanding along the way. &#34;Differential Equations&#34; is arranged into the following sections:
Understanding of differential equations.
Order and degree of differential equations.
Formation of differential equation.
Variable separation method.
Substitution method of solution of differential equation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Forensics - Complete Digital Forensics Masterclass</title>
      <link>/digital-forensics-complete-digital-forensics-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/digital-forensics-complete-digital-forensics-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
Most comprehensive Digital Forensics Course, You will learn Depth understanding of how computers work and how to do digital forensics.
Upgrading every week 2021 Course Computer Forensics
Digital Forensics is defined as the process of preservation, identification, extraction, and documentation of computer evidence which can be used by the court of law. It is a science of finding evidence from digital media like a computer, mobile phone, server, or network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing Agency: Grow Your Digital Marketing Agency</title>
      <link>/digital-marketing-agency-grow-your-digital-marketing-agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/digital-marketing-agency-grow-your-digital-marketing-agency/</guid>
      <description>This is the ultimate course on growing your digital marketing agency &amp;amp; getting more clients. I worked for a digital marketing agency for 5 years. I also worked as an independent consultant. As a global marketing manager for Sony, I worked with some of the top marketing agencies in the world including Digitas, Mediacom, and Publicis. I taught college level digital marketing and I have an MBA from the top business school for marketing--the Kellogg School of Management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nomad Lifestyle: LIVE YOUR DREAM &amp; Travel the World</title>
      <link>/digital-nomad-lifestyle-live-your-dream-travel-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/digital-nomad-lifestyle-live-your-dream-travel-the-world/</guid>
      <description>IS IT POSSIBLE TO LIVE YOUR DREAM LIFE WITHOUT WORKING SO HARD? DOES IT HAVE TO TAKE SO MUCH EFFORT, STRESS, AND ENERGY TO HAVE A LIFE THAT DEEPLY FULFILS YOU? HONOR AND TRUST YOUR PROCESS, AND SURRENDER TO THE MAGIC OF LIFE!!! BEING A DIGITAL NOMAD MEANS LIVING LIFE 100% ON YOUR OWN TERMS!!!
From leaving behind the corporate life of a consistent and often capped salary, saying goodbye to cubicles, a regular work commute and the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digitale Produkte erfolgreich verkaufen mit Digistore 24</title>
      <link>/digitale-produkte-erfolgreich-verkaufen-mit-digistore-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/digitale-produkte-erfolgreich-verkaufen-mit-digistore-24/</guid>
      <description>Ich kann mich noch gut daran erinnern wie es war, meine ersten Online Produkte zu verkaufen.
Damals habe ich versucht, mit höherwertigen Kursen und Coachings Geld zu verdienen.
Allerdings hab ich damit gekämpft, ständig Rechnungen zu schreiben und den Überblick zu behalten.

So etwas frustriert und überfordert einen auf Dauer, und mir ging es genauso.
Dann ist etwas ziemlich Blödes passiert: Als ich mich nicht mehr um die Rechnungen (und auch Mahnungen) kümmern wollte, sind die Verkäufe natürlich eingebrochen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreaming Understand Dream Messages Remember Your Dreams 2020</title>
      <link>/dreaming-understand-dream-messages-remember-your-dreams-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dreaming-understand-dream-messages-remember-your-dreams-2020/</guid>
      <description>Dreaming Understand Dream Messages and Remember Your Dreams
5 Star Review 
I was able to use this information to sort through dreams....and understand what the dream was telling me after the hypnosis. I will keep coming back to the hypnosis sessions as I find them very helpful. I do admit I am not writing things down...but I am holding what I need to know in memory and mulling over what I am finding out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dropshipping Hurdles Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/dropshipping-hurdles-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dropshipping-hurdles-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>With drop shipping, most of the heavy-lifting has been done for you. In fact, not only is it one of the easiest business formats to get involved in, but it’s also one of the lowest-cost startup solutions you’ll ever find.
With little upfront work involved, you can build your very own ecommerce store within minutes, fully loaded with high-quality products that your customers will love.
This course will help you to ensure a smooth customer experience from start to finish, significantly reduce the number of returns, and make the process easier for both you and your buyers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurship - Ft. Matthew Rolnick of Yaymaker, Groupon</title>
      <link>/entrepreneurship-ft.-matthew-rolnick-of-yaymaker-groupon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/entrepreneurship-ft.-matthew-rolnick-of-yaymaker-groupon/</guid>
      <description>**Update**
This course includes an exclusive interview session with a seasoned business veteran - Matthew Rolnick. Matthew is currently the VP&amp;nbsp;of Sales at Yaymaker, and former Divisional Sales Manager at Groupon. His key accomplishments including generating over 10 million in sales at Groupon.
YouAccel recently had the opportunity to conduct a comprehensive Q&amp;amp;A style interview with Matthew Rolnick. The interview was conducted as part of an initiative to add valuable new content to YouAccel’s line up of Entrepreneurship and Freelancing courses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurship: Sales Training, Techniques and Methods</title>
      <link>/entrepreneurship-sales-training-techniques-and-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/entrepreneurship-sales-training-techniques-and-methods/</guid>
      <description>Entrepreneurship: Sales Training, Techniques and Methods
Have you tried to sell products and only failed, have you taken business in school and yet not able to learn how to get sales. Are you struggling with online sales and getting results?&amp;nbsp;If you answered yes to one or all of those questions then this class is right for you. I&amp;nbsp;created this class to help students just like yourself. Often I&amp;nbsp;am asked how you get all those sales, how is it done what are your secrets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethical Hacking for Beginners</title>
      <link>/ethical-hacking-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ethical-hacking-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>This course is for anyone interested in becoming an ethical hacker, no matter your current skill level. The curriculum is designed for absolute beginners interested in a career as a security professional, beginning with the absolute basics of penetration testing, and progressing to advanced topics and techniques. Get started today in your Ethical Hacking career.
The goal of ethical hacking is to find security vulnerabilities in an organization’s digital systems and networks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethical Hacking: Introduction to Exploits</title>
      <link>/ethical-hacking-introduction-to-exploits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ethical-hacking-introduction-to-exploits/</guid>
      <description>In a corner of the internet where there are no rules, there is a group of people who do not play by the rules. These are the hackers and crackers who cross lines and get away with it.
It&#39;s been around for a long time. There are entire generations of hackers that merely know how to utilize exploits; So what is an exploit?
In the security software industry, an exploit is a piece of software, a chunk of data, or a sequence of commands that takes advantage of a bug or vulnerability in order to cause unintended or unanticipated behavior to occur on computer software, hardware, or something electronic (usually computerized).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Face Recognition Web App with Machine Learning in Flask</title>
      <link>/face-recognition-web-app-with-machine-learning-in-flask/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/face-recognition-web-app-with-machine-learning-in-flask/</guid>
      <description>Face Recognition Web Project using Machine Learning in Flask Python
Face recognition is one of the most widely used in my application. If at all you want to develop and deploy the application on the web only knowledge of machine learning or deep learning is not enough. You also need to know the creation of pipeline architecture and call it from the client-side, HTTP request, and many more. While doing so you might face many challenges while developing the app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Ads B2B: Facebook Advertising&#43; Facebook Ads for B2B</title>
      <link>/facebook-ads-b2b-facebook-advertising-facebook-ads-for-b2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/facebook-ads-b2b-facebook-advertising-facebook-ads-for-b2b/</guid>
      <description>This is the ultimate course on business-to-business Facebook advertising!
I’ve been advertising on Facebook for over a decade. I was a VP of Marketing for a Google accelerator startup, a global marketing manager for Sony, and I’ve helped countless small businesses with digital advertising. I taught college-level digital marketing, and I studied digital marketing at the #1 ranked business school for marketing - the Kellogg School of Management. This is where the father of marketing, Philip Kotler, teaches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Page &amp; Facebook Ads Made as FUN: 10 DAYS Challenge</title>
      <link>/facebook-page-facebook-ads-made-as-fun-10-days-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/facebook-page-facebook-ads-made-as-fun-10-days-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Step by step Facebook ads &amp;amp; Instagram ads course for beginners (ready for ios 14.5+ restrictions) - Accept our 10 days challenge and learn how to set up Facebook business page &amp;amp; Facebook business manager. Install Facebook Pixel ready for iOS 14.5+ restrictions. Use Facebook Creator studio. Launch your first Facebook read ads &amp;amp; Facebook engagement campaigns. Generate leads with Facebook lead generation ads. This Facebook ads course includes essential info so you can prep for the Facebook Pixel API for iOS14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FPGA UART communication protocol series Vol1</title>
      <link>/fpga-uart-communication-protocol-series-vol1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fpga-uart-communication-protocol-series-vol1/</guid>
      <description>This Course was made by a professional electronic engineer specializes in FPGA !
This course is the first one on a series of courses about communication protocols.
In this course you will learn everything you need to know about UART
No prior communications protocol knowledge is needed - I will teach everything about serial communication and how to sample it, and about the issues we might have inside FPGA when trying to sample a signal from the outside world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fraud Analytics in Banking and Credit using Machine Learning</title>
      <link>/fraud-analytics-in-banking-and-credit-using-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fraud-analytics-in-banking-and-credit-using-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>In general, fraud can be defined as some illegal or criminal thing done by any person who intended to deceive in financial organizations or personal profit. So the processes of analyzing such illegitimate transactions done by anyone like buyer or customer are caught and only the legal transactions are allowed to be made. As fraud is increasing in day to day life so to analyze frauds that are occurring in the organizations or companies these frauds are analyzed using some quantitative science to understand the fraud, through BI (Business Intelligence), and then we have to develop effective fraud detection solutions through data science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Stack Mobile Application Development - Master Class</title>
      <link>/full-stack-mobile-application-development-master-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/full-stack-mobile-application-development-master-class/</guid>
      <description>There’s strong motivation for companies to find someone who can “do it all”. 
This Course explores the features of full-stack mobile development environments and covers several core native and hybrid mobile alternatives and the factors that influence the selection of each platform.
Full-stack mobile app development lies at the nexus of content and technology. Billions of people worldwide now use smartphones and tablets, which form the client side of the full-stack app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Futures Trading Mastery 2021 | FREE Top 45 Trading Signals!</title>
      <link>/futures-trading-mastery-2021-free-top-45-trading-signals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/futures-trading-mastery-2021-free-top-45-trading-signals/</guid>
      <description>My exclusive course teaches you how to start a successful futures trading business from scratch with zero experience. As one of the world’s 10 years veteran traders, I, Henry Zhang, will personally teach you the same proven strategy I used to build my trading empire from nothing.

Start a lucrative and sustainable trading business today with this complete A-Z guide designed to help everyone from beginners to existing traders looking to increase profits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics, GA4, GTM. How to improve your marketing?</title>
      <link>/google-analytics-ga4-gtm.-how-to-improve-your-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/google-analytics-ga4-gtm.-how-to-improve-your-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Description
Web analytics is the pulse of digital marketing. Everything is measured, and everything is measurable. With Google Analytics and a call tracking system, you can clearly understand who your client is, how to improve your site, and which traffic sources are the most beneficial for your business.
What will you learn in this course?
After completing this course, you will learn how to work with and get the most out of your web analytics data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growth Hacking &amp; Viral Marketing: #1 Strategy Growth Hacking</title>
      <link>/growth-hacking-viral-marketing-#1-strategy-growth-hacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/growth-hacking-viral-marketing-#1-strategy-growth-hacking/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to grow extremely quickly without a lot of money? Do you wish your marketing investments produced exponential growth instead of petty marginal gains? Do you feel there are better ways to grow than just copying competitors? Are you looking for HUGE wins and EXPLOSIVE growth hacking? This the course for you: the definitive guide to growth hacking!
This course is for truly ambitious entrepreneurs, marketers, and product managers who want to drive real IMPACT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacking Ético: Fundamentos de Rede e Ataques de Camada</title>
      <link>/hacking-%C3%A9tico-fundamentos-de-rede-e-ataques-de-camada/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hacking-%C3%A9tico-fundamentos-de-rede-e-ataques-de-camada/</guid>
      <description>Hola,
Bem-vindos ao curso de segurança cibernética “Segurança Cibernética: Fundamentos de Rede &amp;amp; Ataques de Camada de Rede“.
Para se tornar um Hacker Ético e aprender a hackear, o curso Fundamentos de Rede &amp;amp; Ataques de Camada de Rede é o começo perfeito para você. Este é um meio divertido porque a gente pode realmente olhar para os dados que vão nas redes como: como farejar a rede e coletar informações da rede.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Gain More Customers With Video Marketing</title>
      <link>/how-to-gain-more-customers-with-video-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-gain-more-customers-with-video-marketing/</guid>
      <description>In recent years, we can see the emergence of many websites on the Internet and even more intense competition between these sites. Everyone is trying to make their website better and more attractive than the competitor&#39;s, but still, everyone uses the same methods and tools to promote their business.
But many people forget about another very effective method, like video marketing, in which video is the main tool for promoting a business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Master Your Origin Challenge</title>
      <link>/how-to-master-your-origin-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-master-your-origin-challenge/</guid>
      <description>This course includes:
1 hours of on-demand video instruction
7 video sections
Over 30 downloadable exercises &amp;amp; resources
Downloadable book chapter
Full lifetime access
Access on mobile and TV
Certificate of completion

What you’ll learn:
Learn who and what you are and why.
Discover the “origin programming” done by your parents, etc. during your first 18 years of life.
Identify which of your traits and relationship characteristics come from your origin programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Stop Fear Spiritually</title>
      <link>/how-to-stop-fear-spiritually/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-stop-fear-spiritually/</guid>
      <description>Do you still allow fear to stop you from taking developmental steps?
If you have struggled to put that business idea that has been in your heart for many years&amp;nbsp;to work, then you&#39;re dwelling in the cage of fear.
&amp;nbsp;A wise man once said a child is born without fear except for the ones he&#39;s taught by society&amp;nbsp;as he grows up.
I want you to understand that everyone has the tendency to have fear but those who are great&amp;nbsp;achievers in our society have found a way to consistently kill it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermediate Python Immersive Training | Boost your career</title>
      <link>/intermediate-python-immersive-training-boost-your-career/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/intermediate-python-immersive-training-boost-your-career/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to The Intermediate Python Immersive Training | Boost your career
In this course, you will learn in depth the most important Python language topics for the intermediate level.
Once you have completed this course, you will be able to use all these techniques, which we will list in detail.
There is a wonderful feature in this course, as it explains in important detail all you need in these topics in a direct and practical way that saves you valuable time and effort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview Success</title>
      <link>/interview-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/interview-success/</guid>
      <description>This course is for anyone wanting to do better at Job interviews and successfully get a Job offer in the career you want!
Created by practising Recruitment professionals with decades of experience in Business and Executive Recruitment from both Corporate leadership and Recruitment Agency backgrounds, we know what interviewers are looking for and what it takes to stand out - the competition is tougher than ever and we will help you shine!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Biomedical Engineering - Nanodevices RAHBME282</title>
      <link>/intro-to-biomedical-engineering-nanodevices-rahbme282/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/intro-to-biomedical-engineering-nanodevices-rahbme282/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Nanodevices course, brought to you by Rahsoft. In this course we will be going over the basics and fundamentals of nanodevices and nanosensors, as well as in-depth examples and practice problems to give you a better understanding of the field. The course is taught by Dennis Fer, a Biomedical Engineering Instructor at Rahsoft, and the course advisor is Ahsan Ghoncheh, the Co-Founder and Technical Advisor at Rahsoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Domain Names &amp; Web Hosting(Free Domain Name)</title>
      <link>/introduction-to-domain-names-web-hostingfree-domain-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/introduction-to-domain-names-web-hostingfree-domain-name/</guid>
      <description>Domain Names Section:
We provide an overview of the domain name registration process. This includes the role of registrars and TLD (Top Level Domain) administration by ICANN. ccTLD&#39;s (Country Code Top Level Domains) are also explored.
Students will gain hands-on experience with the registration process using popular domain registrars such as GoDaddy/Namecheap. We will provide a comparison of different registrars and register a sample domain name using GoDaddy/Namecheap. Other topics of discussion will include: domain name privacy and administration, auto-renewal, domain forwarding, and name server assignment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Heat Transfer Engineering - RAHHT1 Rahsoft</title>
      <link>/introduction-to-heat-transfer-engineering-rahht1-rahsoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/introduction-to-heat-transfer-engineering-rahht1-rahsoft/</guid>
      <description>Heat Transfer is one of the principle courses for all the university students who study in one of the branches of chemical engineering, mechanical engineering or materials engineering. This course which is placed at the beginning semesters of bachelor programs, is offered in two separate courses as heat transfer 1 &amp;amp; 2 each credited as 3 units. Having a full grasp over the concepts of heat transfer and fully understand the mechanisms of heat transfer in different situations is a must for any students studying the fields mentioned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japanese for French speakers : katakana</title>
      <link>/japanese-for-french-speakers-katakana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/japanese-for-french-speakers-katakana/</guid>
      <description>C&#39;est un cours complet pour apprendre tous les katakana, l&#39;alphabet de base japonais qui est utilisé pour écrire certaines catégories de mots tels que les mots étrangers ou les onomatopées. Grâce à des photos, des illustrations animées, une bande-son et des sous-titres en français, vous apprendrez facilement à lire le tableau entier des 46 katakana, à les prononcer parfaitement et à les écrire dans le bon ordre. Vous ne serez pas ennuyés, car à la fin de chaque section vous pourrez vérifier vos progrès avec des quiz amusants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Programming: Complete Beginner to Advanced</title>
      <link>/java-programming-complete-beginner-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/java-programming-complete-beginner-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to learn real world programming skills that will help you get your first java programming job?
Java is one of the most popular programming languages used to create Web applications and platforms. It was designed for flexibility, allowing developers to write code that would run on any machine.
So it’s your time now to take advantage of a loads of jobs and freelance opportunities that are available for java programmers out there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Android Hacking For Beginners</title>
      <link>/learn-android-hacking-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-android-hacking-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>We will use msfvenom for creating a payload and save it as an apk file. After generating the payload, we need to setup a listener to Metasploit framework. Once the target downloads and installs the malicious apk then, an attacker can easily get back a meterpreter session on Metasploit. An attacker needs to do some social engineering to install apk on the victim’s mobile device.
in this course we gonna learn different kind of lauching attacks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Basic HTML, CSS &amp; Javascript (Typescript) with Vue</title>
      <link>/learn-basic-html-css-javascript-typescript-with-vue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-basic-html-css-javascript-typescript-with-vue/</guid>
      <description>If you&#39;re tired of long courses and just want to learn basic web development this course is for you.

We focus on teaching you only what you need to know and keeping the videos short. The main focus of this course is to teach the basics of HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, and Vue JS. By the end of this course, you should be able to create a basic website, understand how styling a website works and how to get data from a server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Basics of Adobe Photoshop CC 2021 for Beginners</title>
      <link>/learn-basics-of-adobe-photoshop-cc-2021-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-basics-of-adobe-photoshop-cc-2021-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Want to learn Photoshop but don’t know where to start from?
This course is well designed and prepared to make you a decent Photoshop user. All the course contents and examples are wisely chosen and each chapter is explained using the step-by-step method to better fit your needs. The initial chapters are basics and further chapters are explained in more details without making things overcomplicated. To help you follow along with the lectures, exercise files are included in each chapter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Carnatic Flute | Annamacharya Keerthanams</title>
      <link>/learn-carnatic-flute-annamacharya-keerthanams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-carnatic-flute-annamacharya-keerthanams/</guid>
      <description>Tallapaka Annamacharya (also popularly known as Annamayya)(22 May 1408 – 4 April 1503) was a 15th-century Hindu saint and the earliest known Indian musician to compose songs called sankirtanas in praise of the Lord Venkateswara, a form of Vishnu.The musical form of the keertana songs that he composed, which are still popular among Carnatic music concert artists, have strongly influenced the structure of Carnatic music compositions. Annamacharya is remembered for his saintly life, and is honoured as a great devotee of Vishnu by devotees and saintly singers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Carnatic Flute | Intermediate Level | Varnams Volume 5</title>
      <link>/learn-carnatic-flute-intermediate-level-varnams-volume-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-carnatic-flute-intermediate-level-varnams-volume-5/</guid>
      <description>Varṇam is a type of composition in the Carnatic music system consisting of short metric pieces which encapsulate the main features (patterns of notes) of a raga.Varnams capture the raga bhavam, ranjaka prayogas visesha sancharas, etc. Dhatu and Janta prayogas (phrase usage) are usually part of a Varnam. Understanding of these aspects is key to developing manodharma sangeetham (ie., improvisation aspects of Carnatic music such as raga aalapana, swara kalpana, neraval etc)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn HTML5 In-Depth - With Real-World Examples</title>
      <link>/learn-html5-in-depth-with-real-world-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-html5-in-depth-with-real-world-examples/</guid>
      <description>HTML is the main markup language for web pages. 
HTML elements are the basic building-blocks of web pages. 
Learning HTML is your first step to become a web developer. 
HTML concepts will help you learn other web development technologies faster.

In this course you will learn how to create web pages using HTML5.

Which is foundation for web development.

You will learn HTML5 elements including images, videos, lists, tables, forms, Iframes and much more with Real-world Examples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Microsoft Publisher | Complete Microsoft Publisher</title>
      <link>/learn-microsoft-publisher-complete-microsoft-publisher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-microsoft-publisher-complete-microsoft-publisher/</guid>
      <description>Learn the Microsoft Publisher Designing Skills By joining this Complete Microsoft Publisher Training Course.
Microsoft Publisher is one of the Products of Microsoft Office. Microsoft Publisher interface looks very much like other Microsoft office products as Microsoft Word but it is extensively used for designing. Microsoft Publisher is used for different design work. Microsoft Publisher can be used for advertisements design, certificate design, newsletter design, flyer or brochure design, banner design, business card design, or letterhead design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Unity Shaders from Scratch</title>
      <link>/learn-unity-shaders-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-unity-shaders-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>In this course we&#39;re going to look at Unity ShaderLab and the HLSL shading language to create amazing shaders. Maybe you are
a developer struggling to bring to life a particular game feature because it needs a custom shader.
a developer who always wanted to create custom shaders but was too scared to start. a developer wanting to add some custom post-processing effects to your 3d renders.
Unity ShaderLab is how you create custom shaders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Money Online With Digital Product Launch</title>
      <link>/make-money-online-with-digital-product-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/make-money-online-with-digital-product-launch/</guid>
      <description>take this 9 Days Journey with me to create, craft and launch your digital course product and program. start selling Instantly.

Do you want to overcome your all financial problems? and start your business online?
Have you always sought to create and launch a digital product but stuck with the process?
Are you having a hard time doing it as it requires a huge Investment, Time and Energy?
Would you prefer a better, Simpler, Easier and Faster way to launch your digital product or program?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management Consulting Essential Training</title>
      <link>/management-consulting-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/management-consulting-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>**Updated for 2021!**
Imagine you could learn the techniques taught by the world’s top consulting firms such as McKinsey and BCG without ever working at a firm! What if you could put yourself in a position to earn a six-figure salary, not to mention maximize the efficiency of any business interests you have, all from the comfort of your own home?
Management consulting involves identifying and suggesting important changes to what a company does and how they do it—developing a working strategic plan and guiding its execution with optimum effectiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management Consulting Skills Mastery</title>
      <link>/management-consulting-skills-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/management-consulting-skills-mastery/</guid>
      <description>**Updated for 2021!**
The most complete course available on management consultant. 8+hours of videos, activities, templates, case studies, articles and more.
Everything you need to know about management consulting tools and techniques from problem solving to presentation skills, from corporate strategic analysis to financial analysis.
Learn management consulting skills step-by-step. Real life consulting projects, business cases, and templates included. Learn by doing!
Management consulting involves identifying and suggesting important changes to what a company does and how they do it—developing a working strategic plan and guiding its execution with optimum effectiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Python With NumPy For Data Science &amp; Machine Learning</title>
      <link>/master-python-with-numpy-for-data-science-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/master-python-with-numpy-for-data-science-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>Hi, welcome to the &#39;NumPy For Data Science &amp;amp; Machine Learning&#39; course. This forms the basis for everything else. The central object in Numpy is the Numpy array, on which you can do various operations. We know that the matrix and arrays play an important role in numerical computation and data analysis. Pandas and other ML or AI tools need tabular or array-like data to work efficiently, so using NumPy in Pandas and ML packages can reduce the time and improve the performance of the data computation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Reporting Automation with Google Sheets</title>
      <link>/master-reporting-automation-with-google-sheets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/master-reporting-automation-with-google-sheets/</guid>
      <description>Learn to solve any business modeling task you might ever experience!
Have you ever felt that you&#39;re regularly repeating some tasks in Google Sheets or Excel?
Have you ever thought about the time you would save if you would automate those tasks?

All the work you&#39;re doing in a repetitive manner in Google Sheets or Excel could be automated.&amp;nbsp;It requires no coding skills, add-ons, or special tools - all you need to know is how to execute advanced formula combinations that will do all the automation for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master the Modes on Guitar</title>
      <link>/master-the-modes-on-guitar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/master-the-modes-on-guitar/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to your course on Mastering the Modes! This can be a difficult and confusing topic, but not to worry! By the time you&#39;re through, you will the have the modes totally mastered!&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
Before you get going, it is best if you have already gone through my course on Basic Theory for Guitar, as that gives you the foundation to tackle the modes, but if you have a strong grasp of all the Major and Minor scales and all their associated chords, you should be good to go, and if not, no worries, my previous course is super fun as well!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matemáticas desde aritmética a cálculo con Python</title>
      <link>/matem%C3%A1ticas-desde-aritm%C3%A9tica-a-c%C3%A1lculo-con-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/matem%C3%A1ticas-desde-aritm%C3%A9tica-a-c%C3%A1lculo-con-python/</guid>
      <description>En este curso te enseñaré a usar Python como una herramienta para resolver problemas de matemáticas desde la aritmética hasta el cálculo diferencial e integral. Además de que te enseñaré a usar este lenguaje de manera muy básica. Siempre he dicho que lo mejor de un curso es ir al grano, por lo que te ayudaré a hacer ejercicios matemáticos directamente con las herramientas de Google Colaborative que nos permitirán programar en Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mathematics &amp; Statistics for Machine Learning</title>
      <link>/mathematics-statistics-for-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mathematics-statistics-for-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;This course doesn&#39;t cover programming related to AI but helps you to build a strong foundation in math &amp;amp; statistics needed for AI&amp;gt;
The trainer of this course is an AI expert and he has observed that many students and young professionals make the mistake of learning machine learning without understanding the core concepts in maths and statistics. This course will help to address that gap in a big way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MatPlotLib for Python Developers - Advanced</title>
      <link>/matplotlib-for-python-developers-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/matplotlib-for-python-developers-advanced/</guid>
      <description>We will be covering all the advanced level concepts in the course by the virtue of the sample questions which have been included to help the trainees on getting a precise view of the topics. You will get to learn about all the advanced-level topics and will also learn how to leverage them to draft solutions for plotting-based problems. Once you are done with this unit, you will be able to work proficiently with all the aspects of Matplotlib.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel - Learn MS EXCEL For DATA Analysis</title>
      <link>/microsoft-excel-learn-ms-excel-for-data-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/microsoft-excel-learn-ms-excel-for-data-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Whether you are interested in learning
- Different ways of how to properly use Microsoft Excel
- Learn the basics of Data Analysis
- Learn how to create different Excel Apps
- Just grow your Knowledge about this amazing Microsoft App
Or any other reason, this course is definitely for you. The way this class have been designed was to offer to the student an easy way to learn Microsoft Excel and the basics of Data analysis at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern JavaScript for React JS - ES6.</title>
      <link>/modern-javascript-for-react-js-es6./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/modern-javascript-for-react-js-es6./</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to extend your knowledge in Javascript programming by learning the concepts of modern javascript - ES6?
If you want to start your journey to become a React or Angular developer, then this is the perfect course for you. What&#39;s this course about?
This course is specifically designed for those who want to get a quick start with Modern Javascript, especially ES6 concepts. It covers all the basic concepts of ES6: how the javascript has evolved, how to use its latest features that come under ES6 topics, what is babel, and how it is used to compile the ES6 code to make it browser compatible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern React JS Hooks e Context com a Edição Mais Recente</title>
      <link>/modern-react-js-hooks-e-context-com-a-edi%C3%A7%C3%A3o-mais-recente/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/modern-react-js-hooks-e-context-com-a-edi%C3%A7%C3%A3o-mais-recente/</guid>
      <description>Olá,
Bem-vindo ao Curso Modern React JS Hooks e Context com a Edição Mais Recente.
Você quer aprender React JS, mas não tem experiência alguma? Nosso curso React JS Hooks e Context é perfeito para você começar. Neste curso, desenvolvemos o curso React JS para fornecer tudo o que você precisa aprender para dominar o Hooks e Context.

Neste curso, mostraremos tudo o que você precisa saber para dominar o web development usando ReactJS, fornecendo um conhecimento poderoso por meio de uma mistura de diagramas e da criação de um aplicativo simples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nanotechnology Fundamentals - Most comperehensive NANOTECH</title>
      <link>/nanotechnology-fundamentals-most-comperehensive-nanotech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nanotechnology-fundamentals-most-comperehensive-nanotech/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
Nanotechnology is a field of research and innovation concerned with building &#39;things&#39; - generally, materials and devices - on the scale of atoms and molecules. A nanometre is one-billionth of a metre: ten times the diameter of a hydrogen atom. The diameter of a human hair is, on average, 80,000 nanometres. At such scales, the ordinary rules of physics and chemistry no longer apply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NodeJs: Build The Complete E-Commerce Web API [2021]</title>
      <link>/nodejs-build-the-complete-e-commerce-web-api-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nodejs-build-the-complete-e-commerce-web-api-2021/</guid>
      <description>What is Node.js?
Node.js, or Node, is a runtime environment for executing JavaScript code outside of a browser. It is ideal for building highly-scalable, data-intensive backend services (APIs) that power your client’s apps (web or mobile apps).

Why Should learn Node?
Node is great for prototyping and agile development as well as building super fast and highly scalable apps; Companies like Uber and PayPal use Node in production to build applications because it requires fewer people and less code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Object Oriented Programming in C&#43;&#43;  &amp;  Interview Preparation</title>
      <link>/object-oriented-programming-in-c-interview-preparation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/object-oriented-programming-in-c-interview-preparation/</guid>
      <description>Classroom like learning, Detailed Explanation of Question, Top Frequently Asked Questions
Concepts of C++ programming are made very simple and easy.

Curriculum:
Introduction
Why Object Oriented Programming
Example of OOP
Member Function and Member Variable
Access Specifiers
Characteristics&amp;nbsp; Of OOP Top Frequently Asked Interview Question - Part 1
Top Frequently Asked Interview Question - Part 2
Top Frequently Asked Interview Question - Part 3

Topics Covered in Questions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul: A Biography: Small Group Edition</title>
      <link>/paul-a-biography-small-group-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/paul-a-biography-small-group-edition/</guid>
      <description>N. T. Wright&#39;s definitive biography of Paul reveals the apostle&#39;s lasting role in Christian history as an inventor of new paradigms for how we understand Jesus and what he accomplished. Wright celebrates Paul’s stature as one of the most effective and influential intellectuals in human history, while shedding fresh light on his writings, thoughts, and ideas. Consider these remarkable facts: Paul&#39;s writing occupy less than 90 pages in a modern translation yet they have, page per page, generated more sermons, books, monographs, and journal articles than any other writings from the ancient world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PowerPoint: Basics For Work &amp; Studies</title>
      <link>/powerpoint-basics-for-work-studies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/powerpoint-basics-for-work-studies/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the PowerPoint Basics course. If you are a student, a teacher or an office worker no matter what your position or job is PowerPoint is one software that everyone needs to know nowadays and most people use the software without knowing the basics of the software that makes it easy tasks difficult and makes less time-consuming tasks time consuming and results in sitting in front of the computer for more then necessary hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing Strategies Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/pricing-strategies-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pricing-strategies-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Your price structure plays an important role in your ability to convert a prospect into a loyal customer, but assigning value to your offer goes well beyond that. Positioning your business so that it is geared towards a tight market is equally important.
Doing this will help you better tailor your offers so they meet market expectations, but it will make it easier for you to create a powerful marketing message that sets you apart from the competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Launch: How to Go to Market Product Marketing Plan</title>
      <link>/product-launch-how-to-go-to-market-product-marketing-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/product-launch-how-to-go-to-market-product-marketing-plan/</guid>
      <description>Create a breakthrough go-to-market product marketing plan in just a few days ... using this 7-step formula!
“Going to market is just the process of convincing people that your new way is better than the status quo.”
In 3,2,1…product launch, Dekker Fraser and Spencer Grover offer marketing professionals and entrepreneurs proven and cutting-edge guidance for launching new products and getting ready to go-to-market, employing the latest marketing tactics emerging from Silicon Valley and the foundational thinking from top business schools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Development Using JAVA for Beginners - 2021</title>
      <link>/project-development-using-java-for-beginners-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project-development-using-java-for-beginners-2021/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to learn real world programming skills that will help you get your first java programming job?
Java is one of the most popular programming languages used to create Web applications and platforms. It was designed for flexibility, allowing developers to write code that would run on any machine.
So it’s your time now to take advantage of a loads of jobs and freelance opportunities that are available for java programmers out there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python 3 Master Course for 2021</title>
      <link>/python-3-master-course-for-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/python-3-master-course-for-2021/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to Master Python?&amp;nbsp; Then this is the course for you where I will take you from complete beginner to Advanced Python Programmer.&amp;nbsp; Let me walk you through a detailed step by step process that will help you accomplish your goals and have fun learning on the way we will cover the following in detail:

Introduction
Documentation
What is Python
Getting Started with Python Documentation
Cover Summary of Python Beginner&#39;s Documentation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Bootcamp 2021 Build 15 working Applications and Games</title>
      <link>/python-bootcamp-2021-build-15-working-applications-and-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/python-bootcamp-2021-build-15-working-applications-and-games/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of getting videos and lectures on just python basics and syntaxes or just strucked in college studies and hello world program. so I guess you have to give a try to this course this course is designed after analysing what a student need to study python. After analysing what they required and what they want in a course, how they can easily start any course but didn&#39;t able to finish it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Complete Course For Python Beginners</title>
      <link>/python-complete-course-for-python-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/python-complete-course-for-python-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Learn Python From Beginner To Advanced Level
 I’ve created thorough, extensive, but easy to follow content which you’ll easily understand and absorb.
 The course starts with the basics, including Python fundamentals, programming, and user interaction.

The curriculum is going to be very hands-on as we walk you from start to finish becoming a professional Python developer. We will start from the very beginning by teaching you Python basics and programming fundamentals, and then going into advanced topics and different career fields in Python so you can get real-life practice and be ready for the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Demonstrations For Practice Course</title>
      <link>/python-demonstrations-for-practice-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/python-demonstrations-for-practice-course/</guid>
      <description>Learn Python From Beginner To Advanced Level By Demonstrations
The course is created thorough, extensive, but easy to follow content which you’ll easily understand and absorb.
 The course starts with the basics, including Python fundamentals, programming, and user interaction.

The curriculum is going to be very hands-on as we walk you from start to finish becoming a professional Python developer. We will start from the very beginning by teaching you Python basics and programming fundamentals, and then going into advanced topics and different career fields in Python so you can get real-life practice and be ready for the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python for beginners - Learn all the basics of python</title>
      <link>/python-for-beginners-learn-all-the-basics-of-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/python-for-beginners-learn-all-the-basics-of-python/</guid>
      <description>Programming can sometimes be very hard to learn especially if you have no experience in this field. But, this course have everything that you need to be able to start your programming career or improve your programming skills by learning all the basis of python. If you :
- Are in school and want to learn how to program in python
- Need to learn this programming language for work</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python-Introduction to Data Science and Machine learning A-Z</title>
      <link>/python-introduction-to-data-science-and-machine-learning-a-z/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/python-introduction-to-data-science-and-machine-learning-a-z/</guid>
      <description>Learning how to program in Python is not always easy especially if you want to use it for Data science. Indeed, there are many of different tools that have to be learned to be able to properly use Python for Data science and machine learning and each of those tools is not always easy to learn. But, this course will give all the basics you need no matter for what objective you want to use it so if you :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quadratic Equations &amp; Quadratic Expression</title>
      <link>/quadratic-equations-quadratic-expression/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quadratic-equations-quadratic-expression/</guid>
      <description>Learn Quadratic Equations and Functions:
This 7 lessons course includes video lectures and text explanations of everything from quadratic equations and functions, and it includes 7 quizzes (with video solutions!) and&amp;nbsp; for practice worksheet with extra practice problems, to help you test your understanding along the way. &#34;Quadratic equations and expression&#34; is arranged into the following sections:
Basic concept of quadratic Equation
Solving a quadratic equation by different method
How many ways are there to solve a quadratic equation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Online vs Xero Accounting Software</title>
      <link>/quickbooks-online-vs-xero-accounting-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quickbooks-online-vs-xero-accounting-software/</guid>
      <description>This course will compare two leading online accounting software applications, QuickBooks Online and Xero, in a step by step format.
This is a comprehensive accounting course.
We will discuss the purchasing options and the best tools to learn these accounting software packages at the lowest cost.
Learners will understand how to set up a new company file in each software package.
The course will demonstrate how to navigate each software package and how to generate, analyze, and customize common financial reports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Engineering, Debugging and Malware Analysis - 2021</title>
      <link>/reverse-engineering-debugging-and-malware-analysis-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reverse-engineering-debugging-and-malware-analysis-2021/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
Breaking something down and putting it back together is a process that helps people understand how things were made.
 A person would be able to redo and reproduce an origami by unfolding it first. Knowing how cars work requires understanding each major and minor mechanical part and their purposes. The complex nature of the human anatomy requires people to understand each and every part of the body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopify Bootcamp: Increase Your Sales and Conversion rate</title>
      <link>/shopify-bootcamp-increase-your-sales-and-conversion-rate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/shopify-bootcamp-increase-your-sales-and-conversion-rate/</guid>
      <description>​Learning how to work with Shopify is not always easy and can sometimes be very complicated espescially if you never worked with this program before. This is why this course have been created and is here to help you achieve your goals and teach you everything you need to know in order to increase your conversion rate on shopify. If you:
- Have just started out with shopify and don&#39;t know what app to use</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopify Guide: Start your own clothing brand with Shopify</title>
      <link>/shopify-guide-start-your-own-clothing-brand-with-shopify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/shopify-guide-start-your-own-clothing-brand-with-shopify/</guid>
      <description>Starting out your first online business is not always easy especially if you have no knowledge about this topic. If you also want your business to be in the clothing industry it&#39;s even more complicated. Indeed, this is why this is why this course have been designed and this is exactly what you need to stat out in the business world online. If you:
- Are interested by the clothing industry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopify guide: The complete shopify store creation course</title>
      <link>/shopify-guide-the-complete-shopify-store-creation-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/shopify-guide-the-complete-shopify-store-creation-course/</guid>
      <description>Launching your first business is definitely not an easy task, especially if you are launching an online business and you have no prior knowledge about this topic. Also, learning by yourself without a course is not always an easy task because it&#39;s not always easy to filter good information from bad information online. This is why this course have been created. Indeed, this course will teach you all the basics of starting an online store to sell different products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slack Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>/slack-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/slack-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to do project management but don&#39;t know where to start?	Would you like to make amazing projects and apps and bring your ideas to life?	Then Slack Ultimate Course is for you!	Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Slack is an in-demand skill in 2021.&amp;nbsp; The course begins with the basics. We&#39;ll Cover everything you need to know about Slack from scratch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SnapChat Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/snapchat-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/snapchat-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Uncover the secrets to creating extremely successful marketing campaigns on Snapchat!
Snapchat is pretty much the hottest thing going these days, especially among the younger millennial crowd. The site allows users to send “Snaps”, which are pictures or videos, to their followers. These Snaps disappear after a short period of time, giving users the (somewhat false) sense that anything they do won’t last forever.
Snapchat can actually be extremely useful for your business, especially if you market to the younger crowd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Marketing B2B: Proven Social Media Marketing</title>
      <link>/social-media-marketing-b2b-proven-social-media-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/social-media-marketing-b2b-proven-social-media-marketing/</guid>
      <description>This is the ultimate course on business-to-business social media marketing. I’ve been doing B2B marketing on social media platforms like LinkedIn and Facebook for over a decade. I was a Vice President of Marketing for a Google accelerator startup, and I was a Global Marketing Manager for Sony. I also held numerous positions helping small startups with their social media marketing.
I taught college-level digital marketing, and I studied digital marketing and B2B marketing at the Kellogg School of Management, the #1-ranked business school for marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Marketing on Autopilot with Missinglettr</title>
      <link>/social-media-marketing-on-autopilot-with-missinglettr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/social-media-marketing-on-autopilot-with-missinglettr/</guid>
      <description>Did you know? The technique of automating social media activities in order to improve the results generated from social media channels is known as social media automation. It saves time and effort spent on administering social platforms, communicating with prospects, and increasing brand exposure for marketers.&amp;nbsp;Let&#39;s now ask you a quick question.
Have you ever dreamt of automating your social media campaigns with a magical platform that creates, schedules and provides reports of branded social media content while you&#39;re busy doing something else?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social media marketing strategy 2021. Launch your SMM!</title>
      <link>/social-media-marketing-strategy-2021.-launch-your-smm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/social-media-marketing-strategy-2021.-launch-your-smm/</guid>
      <description>What is social media marketing and its role in modern society?
Social media marketing is the use and management of different social media platforms to promote your brand, products, and services. It is a great tool to communicate with your existing customers and reach new ones. Social media marketing helps you drive traffic to your website, increase sales, build engagement and customer loyalty.
The use of social media is a fast-growing global trend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storytelling Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/storytelling-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/storytelling-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Story telling can be a powerful component in a marketing strategy. It can be the driving force behind developing, and more importantly, establishing a brand that connects and resonates with your target audience.
It’s also the easiest way to express emotions and illustrate your commitment to providing value.
There’s nothing more powerful than a carefully crafted story that fulfills the needs of your core market.
In this special course, you will learn top story-telling methods, how to best use these strategies and how you can use storytelling to strengthen your brand or launch a new one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systems Thinking: Enterprise Wide Change Fundamentals</title>
      <link>/systems-thinking-enterprise-wide-change-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/systems-thinking-enterprise-wide-change-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Systems Thinking: Enterprise Wide Change Fundamentals Course is a comprehensive video course where you can learn all about the fundamental knowledge about Systems Thinking that are essential in conducting changes in business.

I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on System Thinking as well as how to apply it in the business world. Learning Systems Thinking allows you to have solid understanding of how corporations work and allows you to effectively deploy enterprise wide changes in a strategic manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talento Humano 3.0 analizando lo nuevo de recursos humanos</title>
      <link>/talento-humano-3.0-analizando-lo-nuevo-de-recursos-humanos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talento-humano-3.0-analizando-lo-nuevo-de-recursos-humanos/</guid>
      <description>Las ciencias administrativas han desarrollado importantes investigaciones sobre los individuos y grupos en las organizaciones, que quizás pareciera un tema nuevo. Por tanto, al referirse al Talento Humano se hace mención a ese recurso importante desde una concepción más actualizada considerando los cambios y avances en la sociedad del siglo XXI, con matices más específicos dentro de una organización social. Como resultado, se han presentado diversas posiciones y conceptos, en relación a ese individuo con características muy concretas y complejas que interactúa en una organización bien sea pública, privada, pequeña mediana o gran empresa, pero que algunos gerentes parecieran no valorar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tax &amp; Adjusting Entry Year-End Accounting Excel Worksheet</title>
      <link>/tax-adjusting-entry-year-end-accounting-excel-worksheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tax-adjusting-entry-year-end-accounting-excel-worksheet/</guid>
      <description>Create a new Excel worksheet from scratch to be used in the adjusting and tax entry process. 
This course is most beneficial to tax preparers and public accountants who enter adjusting entries but is also useful to anybody in accounting. Similar Excel worksheets to the ones we will construct can be useful for analyzing many areas of accounting, and the Excel skills learned in creating them are also very applicable both inside accounting and outside of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 150 Most Important Irregular Verbs in English. Volume 1</title>
      <link>/the-150-most-important-irregular-verbs-in-english.-volume-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-150-most-important-irregular-verbs-in-english.-volume-1/</guid>
      <description>Support available in: English 
Spanish 
French

I can&#39;t wait to share with you this exciting English course based on Irregular Verbs. 
Do you feel unsure about the right conjugation when you try use irregular verbs in every day conversation?
Are you frustrated of having to memorize unending word lists? 
Then this course is for you. 
It is not a secret that Irregular Verbs are hard to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Brain Training Course - Neuroplasticity -</title>
      <link>/the-complete-brain-training-course-neuroplasticity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-brain-training-course-neuroplasticity/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Brain Training Course - Neuroplasticity -
Brain Training for the Modern Smart Phone Era! You Can Train Your Brain to Think More Clearly and Creatively
Brain training is essential if you want do you live up to your full potential as a human being. Your brain is your most important organ, therefore it is essential that you train it for peak performance.
Like it or not, every single day your brain is being trained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Dart Learning Guide</title>
      <link>/the-complete-dart-learning-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-dart-learning-guide/</guid>
      <description>تم الانتهاء من تحديث دورة الدارت
التحديثات شملت:
١- تحديث الاكواد المكتوبة في الدورة لتعمل على اخر اصدار في الدارت بدون مشاكل.
٢- تم توسيع دورة الدرات باضافة قسم كامل للبرمجة الغير متزامنة (Asynchronous Programming) لتتضمن شرح مواضيع (Future, Stream, Async/Await, get Api, File system)
٣- أضافة شرح لدوال الفلترة او التصفية (where, indexWhere, map, any, وغيرهم)
٤- أضافة مشروع تطبيقي في نهاية الدورة.
٥- أضافة شرح مفصل لمفهوم ال null safety والتحديثات الجديدة مثل required وال late.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete eBay Dropshipping University</title>
      <link>/the-complete-ebay-dropshipping-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-ebay-dropshipping-university/</guid>
      <description>Akın Yılmaz is Founde r&amp;amp; Ceo of OKYANUSI. After coming UK, he had nothing but books, so he decided to sell them and now he is running with his e-commerce empire. Akin Yilmaz also helps his customers to grow their business with a team of 50 people on digitalmarketing. com. At the same time, Akın Yılmaz’s helping young people to grow their own businesses by telling his experiences and stories to more than 10000 students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Java Game Development Course for 2021</title>
      <link>/the-complete-java-game-development-course-for-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-java-game-development-course-for-2021/</guid>
      <description>Learn JAVA by developing fun games from scratch.&amp;nbsp; This course is for everyone who has desire to learn JAVA. The game complexity increases with every section and you will be able to rise your knowledge throughout the course. You will develop amazing games and you will see how JAVA works moving things on screen and objects interaction. You will also create and import pictures used in the games and get familiar with creating randomly movable enemies, animating the game characters and playing music while playing the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Law Of Attraction Course Updated for the 2020s</title>
      <link>/the-complete-law-of-attraction-course-updated-for-the-2020s/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-law-of-attraction-course-updated-for-the-2020s/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Law Of Attraction Course Updated for the 2020s
Master the Law of Attraction - Become Your Own Best Law of Attraction Coach - Great Life Manifestation Attract Success
You can obtain mastery of the Law of Attraction. You may have seen the movie or read the book, but this course will teach you in a systematic way how to re-condition your brain, completely, into an abundance-creating being.
TJ Walker dives deep into the secrets of the Law of Attraction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Short Course on Ripple Cryptocurrency</title>
      <link>/the-complete-short-course-on-ripple-cryptocurrency/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-short-course-on-ripple-cryptocurrency/</guid>
      <description>*** Course access&amp;nbsp;includes&amp;nbsp;quizzes &amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;homework exercises, 1-on-1 instructor support&amp;nbsp;(Ripple Cryptocurrency) and&amp;nbsp;LIFETIME&amp;nbsp;access! ***
Hear why this is one of the TOP-NOTCH&amp;nbsp;Ripple Cryptocurrency course&amp;nbsp;on Udemy:
Very informative indeed! Last lecture on Ripple charts was very helpful. Thanks.
-Raghbir Bhullar
I enjoyed learning about a different cryptocurrency than Bitcoin, but I would have liked more information on buying and selling Ripple. The instructor explained how to open accounts on two platforms. What is the difference between the two?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Solidity Course  - Blockchain - Zero to Expert</title>
      <link>/the-complete-solidity-course-blockchain-zero-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-solidity-course-blockchain-zero-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Solidity is the most popular blockchain language in the world designed to build DApplications (Smart Contracts). It powers Ethereum and there is an in demand exponential growth of high-paying jobs all over the world which is changing the way we conduct business.
Learning Solidity can be likened to learning web development languages years ago - You are very much ahead of the game starting today -and that&#39;s why you want to learn Solidity too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Miraculous Faith</title>
      <link>/the-miraculous-faith/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-miraculous-faith/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling to overcome a problem or a challenge in your life, business, or marriage? Do you want simple-to-understand and easy-to-apply descriptions or explanations of the Christian faith that will help you solve those nagging problems in your life, business, or marriage?
If those questions apply to you, then this course, ‘The Miraculous Faith: Principles of Christian Faith Manifestation: How to make miracles through faith’ is just the right one for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Python Developer Essentials 2021 Immersive Bootcamp</title>
      <link>/the-python-developer-essentials-2021-immersive-bootcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-python-developer-essentials-2021-immersive-bootcamp/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to The Python Developer Essentials 2021 Immersive Bootcamp
Learn the skills you need to become a Professional Certified Python Developer with this Complete Training Course.
You&#39;ll become a Certified Python Developer and Coding Rockstar in no time. This course covers all the following concepts theoretically and practically:
How to Program with Modern Python
The clean Python code
The core Python concepts needed to become A Dev Professional</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Python Programming A-Z Definitive Diploma in 2021</title>
      <link>/the-python-programming-a-z-definitive-diploma-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-python-programming-a-z-definitive-diploma-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>Hi, Welcome to The Python Programming A-Z Definitive Diploma in 2021.
Your complete Guide to Python Programming.
Almost Python is currently used for everything in Software Engineering.
Although it is very easy to learn, but, it is very useful and powerful.
Its fields are so many, and by learning python, it will be very easy for you to get higher Jobs in the largest companies such as Google, Dropbox, Spotify and many more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Python Programming Comprehensive Bootcamp</title>
      <link>/the-python-programming-comprehensive-bootcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-python-programming-comprehensive-bootcamp/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to The Python Programming Comprehensive Bootcamp.
In this Complete Bootcamp, we’ll teach you everything you need to know to become a Professional Python developer.
Variables, Representing Data Types, and using Computational Power.
Data Structure for data organization, management and storage formatting.
Practical Flow control and Iterable aspects.
Building software by composing pure functions process.
Object-Oriented Programming model to organize software design.
Application containers and Handling all files.
Playing with Exception events and analyzing Errors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Python Programming For Everyone Immersive Training</title>
      <link>/the-python-programming-for-everyone-immersive-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-python-programming-for-everyone-immersive-training/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to The Python Programming For Everyone Immersive Training Course for Beginners.
This Immersive Masterclass covers all the essential&amp;nbsp;topics to become a Professional Python developer from the ground up Topics like: variables, data types, Strings, data structures,&amp;nbsp; functional programming, different types of modules, files handling, object-oriented programming and many more.
You&#39;ll get A demonstration of each point in this training and an explanation of all theoretical and practical aspects in an easy way and in an easy language for anyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Series Analysis Real World Projects in Python</title>
      <link>/time-series-analysis-real-world-projects-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/time-series-analysis-real-world-projects-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to land a top-paying job in Data Science , AI &amp;amp; Time Series Analysis &amp;amp; Forecasting?
Or are you a seasoned AI practitioner who want to take your career to the next level?
Or are you an aspiring data scientist who wants to get Hands-on&amp;nbsp; Data Science and Time Series Analysis?

If the answer is yes to any of these questions, then this course is for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Driving Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/traffic-driving-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/traffic-driving-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>You’ve likely heard about the power of viral sharing. When enough people share content and it goes viral, the traffic is virtually unstoppable.
And it’s targeted, FREE traffic!
When you inject viral sharing into your sales copy or funnel, you’ll immediately maximize exposure with very little work involved. Instead of spending hours setting up traffic campaigns and ads on social media networks, you motivate your visitors into doing all the work for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Academic Writing course: Research &#43; Essay Writing!</title>
      <link>/ultimate-academic-writing-course-research-essay-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ultimate-academic-writing-course-research-essay-writing/</guid>
      <description>This course is specially developed for students who need the essential knowledge to prepare them for writing and defending their thesis/dissertation in an efficient and effective manner. I have created 17&amp;nbsp;lectures that cover all facets of thesis writing in&amp;nbsp;one and a half&amp;nbsp;hour!
Summary
I will start with the end in mind; how is your thesis evaluated? Based on this central question I explain my formula of success and take you by the hand from topic selection all the way up to successful thesis defence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Beginner Guide to Streamlabs OBS (OBS)</title>
      <link>/ultimate-beginner-guide-to-streamlabs-obs-obs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ultimate-beginner-guide-to-streamlabs-obs-obs/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Ultimate Beginner Guide to Streamlabs OBS (OBS)!
Nick Nyxson here, Your Instructor for this course.
In this course, you will learn how to start using&amp;nbsp; Streamlabs OBS which is live streaming software made by Streamlabs and is a modified version of Open Broadcaster Software (OBS).
In this course You Will Learn:
What is SLOBS (Streamlabs OBS);
How Streamlabs OBS is any different from OBS Studio;
Streamlabs OBS Settings Walkthrough;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valutazione delle Prestazioni</title>
      <link>/valutazione-delle-prestazioni/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/valutazione-delle-prestazioni/</guid>
      <description>Lavori in un’Azienda e vuoi saperne di più sulla Valutazione?
Lavori presso le Risorse Umane (HR) e vuoi approfondire una tua competenza tecnica?
Vuoi sapere cos’è nel dettaglio il Sistema della Valutazione delle Prestazioni?? Qual è il suo scopo?? Le modalità di attuazione dalla sua iniziale fase di progettazione??

Bene!! Sei nel posto giusto…anzi…nell’aula virtuale giusta.
In questo corso ti parlerò di tutte le fasi della Valutazione delle Prestazioni, di chi sono gli Attori interessati e coinvolti, della differenza tra i diversi modelli da usare, delle variabili da tenere sempre in considerazione quando si ha a che fare con il capitale umano (non siamo dei Robot e tutto va adattato e modellato in base a determinati fattori) motivo per cui è importantissimo iniziare con un’ottima progettazione dettagliata della comunicazione del Sistema nonché verificare la situazione attuale dell’impresa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Editing with Adobe Premiere Pro CC 2021 for Beginners</title>
      <link>/video-editing-with-adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2021-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/video-editing-with-adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2021-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Start your Video Editing Career with Premiere Pro CC 2021 and create professional productions for Film, TV and Youtube!
Adobe Premiere Pro is the best video editing program you can use &amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;it&#39;s so compatible with the Adobe family which a great plus for the program and makes your workflow easy and productive. Premiere Pro is used by professionals internationally&amp;nbsp;for every type of production &amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;it could seem overwhelming and hard when you open it for first time but with this course within an hour you will able to do Creative video editing !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VIVADO Xilinx FPGA -Learn From The Beginning (&#43;PCIe project)</title>
      <link>/vivado-xilinx-fpga-learn-from-the-beginning-pcie-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vivado-xilinx-fpga-learn-from-the-beginning-pcie-project/</guid>
      <description>In this course you will learn how to use VIVADO tool to develop Xilinx FPGAs.
As it&#39;s easy for you to understand, working as an FPGA developer is the most profitable job in the Hardware development industry. And by now, it is a profession with great demand in every big company: Apple, Microsoft, Intel, Amazon, Google and many others!
If you want to work as an FPGA developer or just to know how to design an FPGA this is the course for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Development with Bootstrap, Python &amp; Django</title>
      <link>/web-development-with-bootstrap-python-django/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/web-development-with-bootstrap-python-django/</guid>
      <description>Hello there, Welcome to Web Development with Bootstrap, Python &amp;amp; Django course.
This course will be your gateway to learn web design with blank HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap files with a step-by-step approach.&amp;nbsp; We can assure you that only this course will enough for you to learn web development from scratch to intermediate. Then you will learn Python Programming step-by-step. I made Python 3 programming simple and easy with exercises, challenges, and lots of real-life examples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Command Line (cmd) &amp; Batch Script Management</title>
      <link>/windows-command-line-cmd-batch-script-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/windows-command-line-cmd-batch-script-management/</guid>
      <description>One of the many tools that administrators use on a daily basis is the Windows Command Line / Prompt. Over this course, you&#39;ll learn the following skills, which are often used in the real world:

* How to create, rename, move and delete files and directories.
* The different types of file systems and how to navigate between directories
*&amp;nbsp;Setting the date and time on your PC using the date, time and tzutil commands</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireshark: Packet Analysis and Ethical Hacking: Core Skills</title>
      <link>/wireshark-packet-analysis-and-ethical-hacking-core-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/wireshark-packet-analysis-and-ethical-hacking-core-skills/</guid>
      <description>Learn Wireshark practically. Wireshark pcapng files provided so you can practice while you learn! There is so much to learn in this course:
- Capture Telnet, FTP, TFTP, HTTP passwords. - Replay VoIP conversations. - Capture routing protocol (OSPF) authentication passwords.
- Troubleshoot network issues.
- Free software.
- Free downloadable pcapng files.
- Answer quiz questions.
The course is very practical. You can practice while you learn!
Learn how to analyze and interpret network protocols and leverage Wireshark for what it was originally intended: Deep Packet Inspection and network analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Marketing 2021: Strategies and Growth</title>
      <link>/youtube-marketing-2021-strategies-and-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/youtube-marketing-2021-strategies-and-growth/</guid>
      <description>When you take this course, we will start you from an idea that you want to do YouTube video marketing and we will end with you crafting a professional YouTube channel as well as a strategy for how you will use it.&amp;nbsp;
Boomy and Lara are both internet marketing professionals committed to helping guide you with videos demonstrating the best and the worst in YouTube. We wanted this to be a course that you could watch while you work on your own channel, so it may take longer then the hour of video content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner 500 Practice Exam Questions</title>
      <link>/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-500-practice-exam-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-500-practice-exam-questions/</guid>
      <description>Want to test your exam readiness for the Amazon AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner AND feel confident to pass your AWS exam first time? Then these ultimate AWS Cloud Practitioner exam questions are for you! These 6 practice tests reflect the difficulty of the Amazon Web Services exam questions and are the most similar to the real AWS exam experience available on Udemy as demonstrated by the fantastic student reviews from over 500,000 students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Developer Associate Exam Training 2021 [NEW]</title>
      <link>/aws-certified-developer-associate-exam-training-2021-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aws-certified-developer-associate-exam-training-2021-new/</guid>
      <description>This popular AWS Developer Associate Training for the AWS Certified Developer Associate certification exam (DVA-C01) is packed with over 28 hours of comprehensive video lessons, hands-on labs, full-length practice exam simulation, quizzes and exam-crams. With our mixture of in-depth theory, architectural diagrams and hands-on training, you&#39;ll learn how to architect and build applications on Amazon Web Services, fully preparing you for the AWS Developer Certification exam. With this complete Udemy AWS Developer training course, you have everything you need to comfortably pass the AWS Developer Certification exam at the first attempt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate - 2021 [SAA-C02]</title>
      <link>/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-2021-saa-c02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-2021-saa-c02/</guid>
      <description>This Ultimate Exam Training for the AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate is packed with comprehensive video lessons, guided hands-on labs, a full-length practice exam, 3 hours exam-cram lectures and 90&amp;nbsp;Quiz questions! If you are looking to confidently pass your AWS Solutions Architect certification exam first time AND learn how to build the best solution architecture on Amazon Web Services - then this AWS Certification course is for you!
This AWS Training covers 70% of what you need to know for the AWS Certified SysOps Administrator Associate and AWS Certified Developer Associate Exams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate: Complete Course</title>
      <link>/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-complete-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-complete-course/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the AWS Certified Solutions Architect Complete Course!
Where you’re going to learn how to get started with AWS as a solutions architect so you can pass the exam and officially get certified.
I want to congratulate you for making the decision to get certified as a solutions architect.
In this practical, hands-on course our main objective is to give you education not just to understand the ins and outs of AWS, but also to learn exactly how you can apply what you learn to real world scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Solutions Architect Professional SAP-C01 2021</title>
      <link>/aws-certified-solutions-architect-professional-sap-c01-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aws-certified-solutions-architect-professional-sap-c01-2021/</guid>
      <description>This is the year to pass your AWS&amp;nbsp;Certified Solutions Architect Professional exam!&amp;nbsp;Get access to the most comprehensive and well-delivered course for this exam anywhere on the Internet. This AWS&amp;nbsp;Solutions Architect professional certification course will have you sailing through the AWS&amp;nbsp;exam with confidence. Delivered using visual animations, architectural diagrams, and hands-on exercises this course will have you covered - whatever your preferred learning style.
This course is for you if you:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Python Course : from Beginner to Intermediate</title>
      <link>/complete-python-course-from-beginner-to-intermediate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-python-course-from-beginner-to-intermediate/</guid>
      <description>Looking to mater Python for your job or as a career enhancement?
Python is the most widely used programming language on the planet. In the United States, the average pay for a Python developer is $116k. That&#39;s almost $30k more than the competition!

Python is utilized by large corporations like as Google, Facebook, Dropbox, Reddit, Spotify, Quora, and others.

Its clear and beautiful syntax appeals to mathematicians, scientists, engineers, and developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Governmental Accounting 200 Capital Projects &amp; Debt Service</title>
      <link>/governmental-accounting-200-capital-projects-debt-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/governmental-accounting-200-capital-projects-debt-service/</guid>
      <description>The course will focus on larger capital projects and the use of a capital project fund and debt service fund to track them.
We will cover governmental accounting objective, which will be a review from governmental accounting 100.
The course will discuss what capital assets are and how they are recorded in governmental accounting, comparing governmental accounting to for-profit accounting.
Students will learn to record transactions for the issuance of bonds used to finance capital projects, recording transactions at the government-wide level and in the capital project fund, debts service fund, and general fund.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management Consulting Presentation Essential Training</title>
      <link>/management-consulting-presentation-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/management-consulting-presentation-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>In today&#39;s job market, you are only as good as your presentation skills. As the competition for high-level consulting and management positions becomes increasingly cutthroat, you need a powerful way to make your message stand out from the rest.
My name is John Burress and I&#39;m excited to introduce you to the McKinsey presentation system. During my time as a corporate strategist, I&#39;ve used McKinsey presentations to significantly grow many leading businesses using the same techniques you&#39;ll learn under my instruction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not-for-Profit Accounting-Charities, Colleges, &amp; Health Care</title>
      <link>/not-for-profit-accounting-charities-colleges-health-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/not-for-profit-accounting-charities-colleges-health-care/</guid>
      <description>Not for Profit Accounting-Charities, Colleges, &amp;amp; Health Care will cover accounting principles related to not for profit organizations.
Our concentration will be on nongovernmental not-for-profit organizations. However, we will discuss the differences between nongovernmental not for profit organization and governmental not-for-profit organizations. We will also discuss accounting concepts for both governmental and nongovernmental organizations related to health care and colleges.
The course will start by introducing what a not for profit organization is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partnership Accounting</title>
      <link>/partnership-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partnership-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Partnership accounting will cover accounting topics related to a partnership form of business entity.
This partnership course will focus on the accounting issues that are different in a partnership as compared to other types of entities like a sole proprietorship or corporations. As we focus on the differences, we always want to keep in mind the similarities in accounting for different business entities. Most of what we have learned about the double entry accounting system and day to day accounting transactions in prior courses will remain the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PNL: Conversación transformacional &amp; Negociación efectiva</title>
      <link>/pnl-conversaci%C3%B3n-transformacional-negociaci%C3%B3n-efectiva/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pnl-conversaci%C3%B3n-transformacional-negociaci%C3%B3n-efectiva/</guid>
      <description>Los seres humanos hemos concebido la idea de que existen variables que están fuera de la gestión individual, por tal motivo se ha exteriorizado la responsabilidad de aquellos pilares transformándonos en víctima de factores externos configurados en paradigmas (política, economía, ciencia y religión) encarnados en autoridades dueñas de conocimientos, reglas y mandamientos que han configurado las estructuras mentales por las cuales construimos nuestras experiencias y realidades.
Sin embargo, gracias a la era de la información y a consecuencia de la conectividad producida por el mismo fenómeno, estamos comenzando a cambiar la percepción del tiempo y el conocimiento desde un paradigma lineal e inamovible a otro holístico y constituidos por millares de posibilidades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python And Django Framework For Beginners Complete Course</title>
      <link>/python-and-django-framework-for-beginners-complete-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/python-and-django-framework-for-beginners-complete-course/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Learn Python From Scratch
 I’ve created thorough, extensive, but easy to follow content which you’ll easily understand and absorb.
 The course starts with the basics, including Python fundamentals, programming, and user interaction.

The curriculum is going to be very hands-on as we walk you from start to finish becoming a professional Python developer. We will start from the very beginning by teaching you Python basics and programming fundamentals, and then going into advanced topics and different career fields in Python so you can get real-life practice and be ready for the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Online-Bookkeeping Business-Easy Way</title>
      <link>/quickbooks-online-bookkeeping-business-easy-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quickbooks-online-bookkeeping-business-easy-way/</guid>
      <description>QuickBooks Online bookkeeping business designed for small business clients or small businesses who want a simple cash basis format for entering data.&amp;nbsp; 
This course is designed for bookkeepers and is also useful for small business owners who want a simple system for entering financial data into QuickBooks for financial planning and year-end tax preparation. 
The bookkeeping system we discuss will also describe the relationship between the bookkeeper, the business, and the year-end tax and financial statement preparers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Pro-Business &amp; Personal-One QuickBooks File</title>
      <link>/quickbooks-pro-business-personal-one-quickbooks-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quickbooks-pro-business-personal-one-quickbooks-file/</guid>
      <description>Both business and personal financial, bookkeeping, and tax information in one QuickBooks file using class tracking. 
This course will demonstrate how to use the class tracking feature in QuickBooks Pro Desktop 2019, applying the feature to tracking both business and personal financial information in one QuickBooks file. 
Note that tracking both business and personal data in one QuickBooks file will not be the best option for many businesses but is a good option for small businesses who want one location to track and analyze financial data and generate financial reports that can be used for tax preparation, budgeting, and business planning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Python Modules to Create AI Projects For Beginners</title>
      <link>/some-python-modules-to-create-ai-projects-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/some-python-modules-to-create-ai-projects-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>In this course, we are going to cover some python modules which help us to make AI projects like J.A.R.V.I.S, Face recognition, Face detection, etc. In my next course i will show you how to create J.A.R.V.I.S .python is high level interpreted&amp;nbsp; language, in this project we are going to use python 3.6 Ratings: 3.29/5
Enrollments: 52297
Coupon Code: LETS_DO_IT
Current Price: FREE
Enroll NOW: Enroll now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Content Marketing Quiz (2021 Edition)</title>
      <link>/the-ultimate-content-marketing-quiz-2021-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-ultimate-content-marketing-quiz-2021-edition/</guid>
      <description>Content is truly termed as &#34;The King&#34;.
&#39;Content marketers always say that with our clients we want to build close, trusting relationships&#39;. But how many of our respected personal relationships are marked by a lack of feeling? The best way to create those genuinely meaningful relationships we all want to have with our clients is to concentrate on making stories more personally resonant, situationally important, and emotionally intelligent. Greater empathy is the real key to every goal - we have (as content marketers, and as people).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Search Engine Optimization (SEO) Quiz 2021</title>
      <link>/the-ultimate-search-engine-optimization-seo-quiz-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-ultimate-search-engine-optimization-seo-quiz-2021/</guid>
      <description>We all know that search engine optimization (SEO) is the art and science of getting pages to rank higher in search engines like Google,&amp;nbsp;Bing,&amp;nbsp;Duckduckgo etc. Since search is one of the main ways people discover online content, ranking higher in search engines can lead to an increase in website traffic. SEO has two key objectives. The first is to help you understand what online users are looking for - so that you can create high-quality content to serve their purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate WordPress Quiz for Beginners and Advanced Users</title>
      <link>/the-ultimate-wordpress-quiz-for-beginners-and-advanced-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-ultimate-wordpress-quiz-for-beginners-and-advanced-users/</guid>
      <description>WordPress has surely come a long way since it was first released long back&amp;nbsp; — so too do the WordPress numbers (stats, basically) that serve to characterize this popular tech platform. Because of its user-friendly interface, WordPress users can easily publish their content on the Internet - meaning it simplifies the website building efforts of designers and developers using the platform. A significant segment of the WordPress user community needs to learn more about the platform so that they can not only publish content but also design, customize, and manipulate their WordPress themes to make their websites look amazing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Development Masterclass - Complete Certificate Course</title>
      <link>/web-development-masterclass-complete-certificate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/web-development-masterclass-complete-certificate-course/</guid>
      <description>This course is fully compatible with the latest versions of Ubuntu (20.04 LTS, 18.04 LTS). You can also continue using 14.04 LTS or 16.04 LTS if you prefer, as the content is compatible with all versions.
This course offers a comprehensive look into the entire web development process - from local server configuration using WAMP and MAMP (Apache, MySQL, PHP)&amp;nbsp;to production deployment using the latest web technologies including: LAMP Stack (Linux, Apache, PHP and MySQL) for Ubuntu, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, XML, and AJAX.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner - Complete NEW Course 2021</title>
      <link>/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-complete-new-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 12:19:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-complete-new-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>100%&amp;nbsp;UPDATED in&amp;nbsp;MAY&amp;nbsp;2021:&amp;nbsp;This AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner training course has just been completely updated with 100% new content for May 2021! The course is packed with comprehensive video lessons, hands-on labs, practice exam questions, quizzes and exam-crams! If you are new to Amazon Web Services / Cloud Computing and looking to confidently pass your AWS Cloud Practitioner Certification Exam first time - then this value-packed AWS&amp;nbsp;training course is for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Command Line Terminal Basic for Beginners (In Hindi)</title>
      <link>/linux-command-line-terminal-basic-for-beginners-in-hindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 12:19:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/linux-command-line-terminal-basic-for-beginners-in-hindi/</guid>
      <description>Become an effective Linux user and advance your Career. Learning the Linux Command Line will take you FAR!


Learn to appreciate the power of the Linux command line.

Understand the structure of the Linux File System.

Learn how to navigate your Linux File System using few simple commands!

Learn how to create, modify, and process files.

यह पाठ्यक्रम आईटी पेशेवरों या ऐसे लोगों के लिए लक्षित है जो लिनक्स से परिचित होना चाहते हैं। और यह दर्शकों को वह जानकारी देने के लिए है जो उन्हें कमांड-लाइन के साथ आरंभ करने के लिए जानना आवश्यक है और इसकी मदद से Linux manage कैसे करें।</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence in App Creation: Beginners Edition</title>
      <link>/artificial-intelligence-in-app-creation-beginners-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artificial-intelligence-in-app-creation-beginners-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the sixth course in Term 2 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Today, Artificial Intelligence (AI), Machine Learning, and Deep Learning technologies are used in diverse fields as part of the daily life of large organizations across the globe. The rapid speed of AI growth demonstrates that it is a groundbreaking technology designed to transform the way people use devices and conduct business: achievements in unmanned aerial vehicles, the ability to beat people in chess and sporting games, automated customer service, and analytical systems - of course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate Practice Exams</title>
      <link>/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-practice-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-practice-exams/</guid>
      <description>Want to test your exam readiness for the Amazon AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate AND feel confident to pass your AWS certification exam first time? Then these ultimate AWS Solutions Architect Associate practice exams are for you! These 6 practice tests reflect the difficulty of the Amazon Web Services exam questions and are the most similar to the real AWS exam experience available on Udemy as demonstrated by the fantastic student reviews from over 500,000 students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified SysOps Administrator Associate Practice Exams</title>
      <link>/aws-certified-sysops-administrator-associate-practice-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aws-certified-sysops-administrator-associate-practice-exams/</guid>
      <description>Want to maximize your chances of passing your AWS Certified SysOps Administrator Associate exam first time?&amp;nbsp;Then these brand-new AWS SysOps Administrator Associate practice exams are for you! These 3 sets of AWS&amp;nbsp;practice tests (with 65 practice questions each) reflect the difficulty of the Amazon Web Services exam questions and are the most similar to the real AWS certification exam experience available on Udemy. With this AWS Certification Training course, you&#39;ll know when you are ready to take your AWS Certified SysOps certification exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Intelligence using Tableau</title>
      <link>/business-intelligence-using-tableau/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/business-intelligence-using-tableau/</guid>
      <description>This course focuses on how business intelligence in Tableau uses business analytics tools that make it easy to combine data from multiple sources, analyze and visualize information. It helps trainees in making more informed and better decisions to guide the business. After the completion of the course trainee will be through with all the concepts of business intelligence and Tableau.
The objective of this course is to assist the folks in running a business strategically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cursillo Excel Básico</title>
      <link>/cursillo-excel-b%C3%A1sico/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cursillo-excel-b%C3%A1sico/</guid>
      <description>Curso de Bolsillo Excel que lo puedes llevar a todo lado. Tocaremos los temas más fundamentales pero a la vez indispensables cuando usamos Excel. Diseñado para todos aquellos que están empezando con esta poderosa herramienta. - Primero lo primero: En el primero video te cuento cuáles son los puntos a tratar. Luego, pasaremos al contenido principal del curso.&amp;nbsp; - Abordaremos Atajos y Truquitos para ya a empezar a sentir qué tan fácil resulta trabajar con la interfaz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring VirBELA 3D University Campus (2021 Edition)</title>
      <link>/exploring-virbela-3d-university-campus-2021-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/exploring-virbela-3d-university-campus-2021-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the eighth course in Term 3 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Did you know?&amp;nbsp;Virtual worlds are simulated environments accessed by multiple users through an online interface or software. Virtual worlds integrate two things which can be intrinsic to human nature; social connectivity and creativeness.
Human beings are a social species that require verbal exchange to thrive and we are constantly seeking opportunities for interaction, expression and validation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managerial Accounting / Cost Accounting</title>
      <link>/managerial-accounting-/-cost-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/managerial-accounting-/-cost-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Comprehensive managerial and cost accounting course. Topics include:
· Job order costing
· Process costing
· Cost volume profit analysis
· Master Budgets
· Flexible Budgets
· Responsibility accounting
· Relevant costs
· Time value of money
This course will go into detail about each topic. We will include”
· Practice Excel files with both an answer tab and a practice tab
· Lecture PDF files that can be downloaded and reviewed without internet access</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support Us</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2021 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>You can support us by the following:
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
