<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Humanities on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/humanities/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Humanities on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/humanities/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Write Dreamy, Heartfelt, Soulful Poetry - Creative Writing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/write-dreamy-heartfelt-soulful-poetry-creative-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/write-dreamy-heartfelt-soulful-poetry-creative-writing/</guid>
      <description>Learn to write dreamy and imaginative poetry that inspires readers and takes them to new worlds.
Create beauty with your writing and give the gift of inspiration to others.
What you will learn
We&#39;ll start with poetry basics like similes, rhyming, metaphors, and building imagery. We will also explore the brain science of what makes people feel certain feelings. We&#39;ll combine the science with philosophy to help you understand what goes on in the mind of a reader or listener.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/for-ukraine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/for-ukraine/</guid>
      <description>All the revenue received by me (the Instructor!) from sales of this course will go to help those in Ukraine/fleeing from Ukraine. Not &#39;profit&#39; but REVENUE. The Videographer/Videoeditor has waived all fees too. This course is about the war in Ukraine. It is divided into five main sections:
Relevance - each lecture explains how this course is RELEVANT to you if you study....(range of subjects)
Truth - we look at how &#39;truth&#39; has suffered in this war</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Método Completo de Escritura de Novela Psicológica</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/m%C3%A9todo-completo-de-escritura-de-novela-psicol%C3%B3gica/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/m%C3%A9todo-completo-de-escritura-de-novela-psicol%C3%B3gica/</guid>
      <description>Hola querido/a escritor/a:
Si estás leyendo estas líneas significa que John ha muerto y ha escapado a Francia con nuestros ahorros!!!
Obviamente, si estás leyendo esto es porque estás buscando aprender a escribir una novela, o ya tienes una idea y te falta un poquito de ayuda para ponerla a andar. Siempre es necesario un signo que nos indique el camino. En este caso, este curso te indicará el camino correcto.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Book of Jonah: Insightful Overview &amp; Life Applications</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-book-of-jonah-insightful-overview-life-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-book-of-jonah-insightful-overview-life-applications/</guid>
      <description>Contrary to popular misrepresentation, this minor prophetic book is not about the great or big fish. It is the great big God.
The God who shows, love, mercy and compassion even in the of events that cry for justice. It is about God and His immanent activities on the earth.
In this we see Jonah fleeing his mission (chapters 1–2)
We see him purporting to give up on his and take to flight (1:1–3)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book of Romans: By Apostle Paul &amp; 16 Life Changing Lessons!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/book-of-romans-by-apostle-paul-16-life-changing-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 15:08:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/book-of-romans-by-apostle-paul-16-life-changing-lessons/</guid>
      <description>----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Apart from the Book of Revelations, The Epistle to the Romans has made some of the most significant contributions into our Christian walk today. Beginning with Chapter #1, Paul uses the local knowledge of &#34;Power&#34; as the instrument to illustrate the &#34;The Gospel as the Power to save&#34; He makes it known that everyone needs the unmerited favour of God - Grace. No one is excluded. The Gentiles for their worship of the created things and the Jews for their inability to fulfill the law they have used to judge others!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Thessalonians - Summary &amp; Life Lessons For Todays Living</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2-thessalonians-summary-life-lessons-for-todays-living/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 19:27:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2-thessalonians-summary-life-lessons-for-todays-living/</guid>
      <description>Paul wrote this letter shortly after the return of Timothy&#39;s account of how the newly found Church was emerging. He was able to deduct that certain issues identified in the first letter were still prevalent. In some cases, the scenarios have gotten worse.
One strong opposition identified was a letter supposed to have been written by Paul in which was claimed that the 2nd Coming had already taken place! Such a rumor ignited the confusion and fear responsible for idleness within this body of Christ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book of Nehemiah - How To Develop The Leader In You!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/book-of-nehemiah-how-to-develop-the-leader-in-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 18:10:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/book-of-nehemiah-how-to-develop-the-leader-in-you/</guid>
      <description>----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
It is almost impossible to discuss &#34;Leadership&#34; from a Christian perspective without delving into the Book of Nehemiah. In my view this is the only Bible Book that details the highest concentration of Leadership Traits.
In today&#39;s world the subject focus of this books reminds us of God&#39;s intention when he made man; created communities and established societies. In a nutshell the success of the entire world rests on God and those who open themselves to His form of Leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book of Ezra - How To Enjoy The Prophetic Word Spoken On You</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/book-of-ezra-how-to-enjoy-the-prophetic-word-spoken-on-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/book-of-ezra-how-to-enjoy-the-prophetic-word-spoken-on-you/</guid>
      <description>----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
The Book of Ezra Old Testament is tightly linked to at least 8 other Books of the Bible. It is almost impossible to fully grasp how the Children of Israel experienced their restoration without reading and understanding Ezra. Bible scholars tell us that it is probable Ezra the Priest wrote the Books of 1 and 2 Chronicles, Ezra as well as Nehemiah. This Book chronicles the returns and rebuilding of Jerusalem as well as providing the New Testament Believer with tried and tested principles that we can apply to our lives today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bible: 2 Timothy - 7 Lessons We Can Learn For Today!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bible-2-timothy-7-lessons-we-can-learn-for-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 18:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bible-2-timothy-7-lessons-we-can-learn-for-today/</guid>
      <description>The Book of 2 Timothy illustrates profound truths about:
God&#39;s desire for man The end of man
End times prophesy
Paul&#39;s future
Ministry succession
Hope
Loyalty
Weakness
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Whether one of your favorite scriptures is about God giving us the spirit of power, of love and of self discipline or I have fought the good fight, I have finished the race and I have kept the faith; the book of 2 Timothy includes the above and also abounds with much more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bible: Titus - 7 Lessons We Can Learn For Today!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bible-titus-7-lessons-we-can-learn-for-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 15:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bible-titus-7-lessons-we-can-learn-for-today/</guid>
      <description>Review From Other Books Book of 2 Peter
&#34;I had read Book 2 Peter after your teaching. Thank you. I wish that I could read the rest of the books in Bible thoroughly in future&#34;. - Cynthia Josephine
Book of Philippians! The instructor has a notable passion for sharing the Book of Philippians! (All the Books of the Bible) That passion drew me to seriously consider his engaging presentation. The instructor challenged me to see myself through the eyes of my Lord and Savior - not the eyes of the world!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Corinthians: 13 Life Changing Lessons</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2-corinthians-13-life-changing-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 21:08:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2-corinthians-13-life-changing-lessons/</guid>
      <description>&#34;A few days before completing this course I visited my auto mechanic for a minor repair. Shortly after parking, a reckless lorry driver smashed into it.! I was completely upset because he tried to cover up the incident by not reporting himself. We had to trail through 4 hours of videotape to identify the culprit.
Whilst mauling over the situation I directed my thoughts to Romans 8 and considered that this will work together for my good somehow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Churches &amp; NGO/Charity Can Generate More Income Streams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-churches-ngo/charity-can-generate-more-income-streams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 22:20:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-churches-ngo/charity-can-generate-more-income-streams/</guid>
      <description>If you answer to any of the above two questions is yes - then join this course. In this no-fluff actionable course I will reveal to you how you, your organization can start generating additional streams of income for your Charity, NGO, Church, or Social Enterprise.
I will give you ideas and suggestions that will reveal the untapped opportunities that you can use to start generating income for your organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gospel of Mark: Experience God&#39;s Life Changing Word Today!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gospel-of-mark-experience-gods-life-changing-word-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 18:19:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gospel-of-mark-experience-gods-life-changing-word-today/</guid>
      <description>Recent Review from a previous course:
&#34;I enjoyed this concise course on the Second Book of Timothy. The instructor does an excellent job of choosing what lessons to discuss and on making the lessons apply to your life.&#34; - Bob Klug &#34;I have heard our instructor before and he is excellent.&#34; - Florence Taber-Brown
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Said to be the first of the written Gospels; this 16 Chapter book pens a compelling pacy account of the actions, sayings and experiences of our Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colossians - 4 Life Lessons - For Effective Transformation!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/colossians-4-life-lessons-for-effective-transformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 13:19:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/colossians-4-life-lessons-for-effective-transformation/</guid>
      <description>In this set of videos, I have given some verse by verse exposition however the focus is on how the lessons from the Bible can be applied to your daily life. It is surely a deeper dive into the book and you will get a sense of what the Holy Spirit requires you to do with what you have learned or received or heard or seen.
I believe the lessons are very informative and simplistic, for anyone whether with advanced Bible knowledge or a new Believer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galatians - 6 Life Lessons - For Effective Transformation!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/galatians-6-life-lessons-for-effective-transformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 13:19:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/galatians-6-life-lessons-for-effective-transformation/</guid>
      <description>This Pauline letter was written to address the verbal plague that was spreading through the Church. It advocated that what Jesus did on the cross was not good enough without circumcision. Hence Paul&#39;s responses were stern and yet with an unusual depth of Old Testament revelations. As an example, Paul used the story of Ishmael mocking Isaac in the book of Genesis (21v9) to explain the manner the Jewish believers were persecuting the gentile believers at that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gospel of Luke: For Growth In Your Relationship With God!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gospel-of-luke-for-growth-in-your-relationship-with-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 13:19:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gospel-of-luke-for-growth-in-your-relationship-with-god/</guid>
      <description>Recent Review from a previous course:
&#34;Yes, it was a great course and is very helpful for Christians&#34; - Isha Singhal &#34;I enjoyed this concise course on the Second Book of Timothy. The instructor does an excellent job of choosing what lessons to discuss and on making the lessons apply to your life.&#34; - Bob Klug &#34;It helped me to summarize Mark and use the information in teaching&#34;.- Florence Taber-Brown</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bible: A Survey Of Systematic Theology - Part One</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-bible-a-survey-of-systematic-theology-part-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 21:51:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-bible-a-survey-of-systematic-theology-part-one/</guid>
      <description>This is a Bible Institute level course in systematic theology. We cover the major doctrines of the Bible. This course presents classic theology from a literal and normal approach to the Bible. Key Bible passages are taught to show the relationship of important teachings to one another. There are fifty-two chapters in the book. The book is presented throughout several courses. This is the first course in the series. Content covered in this first course includes the Bible, inspiration, revelation and the Trinity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bible: Philippians - 7 Lessons We Can Learn For Today!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bible-philippians-7-lessons-we-can-learn-for-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 17:04:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bible-philippians-7-lessons-we-can-learn-for-today/</guid>
      <description>Review - Book of Philippians 5 Star Rating
Student: Matt Hayes
The instructor has a notable passion for sharing the Book of Philippians! (All the Books of the Bible) That passion drew me to seriously consider his engaging presentation. The instructor challenged me to see myself through the eyes of my Lord and Savior - not the eyes of the world! I learned many valuable teachings about the Book of Philippians by taking this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corso Completo di Scrittura Comica - Parte Seconda</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-completo-di-scrittura-comica-parte-seconda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-completo-di-scrittura-comica-parte-seconda/</guid>
      <description>In questo corso, rivolto sia ai professionisti che ai semplici appassionati, ti insegnerò come poter diventare un ottimo autore comico nei più rinomati campi dello spettacolo. Ti spiegherò, passo dopo passo, le differenti fasi dello scrivere comico partendo dall&#39;idea iniziale e dallo sviluppo di un tema fino ad approdare alla fase dell’organizzazione del materiale e la costruzione dei personaggi. Quando si ha a che fare con la scrittura comica è necessario tener sempre a mente e in piena considerazione fattori come il pubblico, lo stile e il linguaggio in perenne trasformazione, i meccanismi chiave che muovono la grande macchina della comicità.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art Legends in Art History</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/art-legends-in-art-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/art-legends-in-art-history/</guid>
      <description>We are using an ancient and proven technique in teaching you about art history. We are using storytelling. During ancient times, wise people spread the tales of the past to anyone who would listen. The art of storytelling is lost in the education space of today. We have made it our mission to teach our students about the masters of the art world, the art movements, and art history by telling stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking for College Students: Become a Great Speaker</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-for-college-students-become-a-great-speaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 12:19:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-for-college-students-become-a-great-speaker/</guid>
      <description>Imagine speaking to a classroom or even an auditorium full of students knowing that everyone understands you, remembers your key messages and feels you are a confident speaker. Wouldn&#39;t it be great to know that you can speak to any sized audience and that you will always come across your very best? In this Public Speaking for College Students course you will learn the following: *How to speak with confidence inside and outside the classroom *How to avoid the common speaking blunders made by most other college students *How to rehearse important presentations on video *How to make fellow students and adults remember your messages This course is delivered primarily through spoken lecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrivere un Dialogo - Scrittura Creativa Vol. 3</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/scrivere-un-dialogo-scrittura-creativa-vol.-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 18:00:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/scrivere-un-dialogo-scrittura-creativa-vol.-3/</guid>
      <description>Ciao! In questo corso ti spiegherò come poter approcciare, nel migliore dei modi, alla composizione di un’ ottima sequenza dialogica e all’importanza che essa assume all’interno di un racconto, un romanzo o qualsivoglia opera di carattere narrativo. Considera che tra i motivi del “Blocco della pagina bianca&#34; di molti scrittori alle prime armi vi è proprio il senso di inadeguatezza o incapacità nell’affrontare la scrittura dei dialoghi e ti renderai conto che ovviare eliminando gli stessi dialoghi non rappresenta affatto una soluzione effettiva.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Il Personaggio - Scrittura Creativa Vol. 5</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/il-personaggio-scrittura-creativa-vol.-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 09:03:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/il-personaggio-scrittura-creativa-vol.-5/</guid>
      <description>Come nasce l&#39;idea per un personaggio narrativo?
A chi o a cosa ispirarsi?
Dall&#39;idea di un determinato personaggio come si giunge poi al suo inserimento in un preciso contesto narrativo?
Come rivestire uno o più personaggi di credibilità??
Queste sono solo alcune delle domande che affiorano nella mente di uno scrittore quando decide di cimentarsi nella scrittura di un &#39;opera narrativa, a prescindere dal genere che deciderà di seguire o adottare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul: A Biography: Small Group Edition</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/paul-a-biography-small-group-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/paul-a-biography-small-group-edition/</guid>
      <description>N. T. Wright&#39;s definitive biography of Paul reveals the apostle&#39;s lasting role in Christian history as an inventor of new paradigms for how we understand Jesus and what he accomplished. Wright celebrates Paul’s stature as one of the most effective and influential intellectuals in human history, while shedding fresh light on his writings, thoughts, and ideas. Consider these remarkable facts: Paul&#39;s writing occupy less than 90 pages in a modern translation yet they have, page per page, generated more sermons, books, monographs, and journal articles than any other writings from the ancient world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
