<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Humanities on </title>
    <link>/tags/humanities/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Humanities on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 23:49:51 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/humanities/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Il Personaggio - Scrittura Creativa Vol. 5</title>
      <link>/il-personaggio-scrittura-creativa-vol.-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 23:49:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/il-personaggio-scrittura-creativa-vol.-5/</guid>
      <description>Come nasce l&#39;idea per un personaggio narrativo?
A chi o a cosa ispirarsi?
Dall&#39;idea di un determinato personaggio come si giunge poi al suo inserimento in un preciso contesto narrativo?
Come rivestire uno o più personaggi di credibilità??
Queste sono solo alcune delle domande che affiorano nella mente di uno scrittore quando decide di cimentarsi nella scrittura di un &#39;opera narrativa, a prescindere dal genere che deciderà di seguire o adottare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul: A Biography: Small Group Edition</title>
      <link>/paul-a-biography-small-group-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/paul-a-biography-small-group-edition/</guid>
      <description>N. T. Wright&#39;s definitive biography of Paul reveals the apostle&#39;s lasting role in Christian history as an inventor of new paradigms for how we understand Jesus and what he accomplished. Wright celebrates Paul’s stature as one of the most effective and influential intellectuals in human history, while shedding fresh light on his writings, thoughts, and ideas. Consider these remarkable facts: Paul&#39;s writing occupy less than 90 pages in a modern translation yet they have, page per page, generated more sermons, books, monographs, and journal articles than any other writings from the ancient world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
