<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Humanities on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/humanities/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Humanities on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/humanities/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Corso Completo di Scrittura Comica - Parte Seconda</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/corso-completo-di-scrittura-comica-parte-seconda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/corso-completo-di-scrittura-comica-parte-seconda/</guid>
      <description>In questo corso, rivolto sia ai professionisti che ai semplici appassionati, ti insegnerò come poter diventare un ottimo autore comico nei più rinomati campi dello spettacolo. Ti spiegherò, passo dopo passo, le differenti fasi dello scrivere comico partendo dall&#39;idea iniziale e dallo sviluppo di un tema fino ad approdare alla fase dell’organizzazione del materiale e la costruzione dei personaggi. Quando si ha a che fare con la scrittura comica è necessario tener sempre a mente e in piena considerazione fattori come il pubblico, lo stile e il linguaggio in perenne trasformazione, i meccanismi chiave che muovono la grande macchina della comicità.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art Legends in Art History</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/art-legends-in-art-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/art-legends-in-art-history/</guid>
      <description>We are using an ancient and proven technique in teaching you about art history. We are using storytelling. During ancient times, wise people spread the tales of the past to anyone who would listen. The art of storytelling is lost in the education space of today. We have made it our mission to teach our students about the masters of the art world, the art movements, and art history by telling stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking for College Students: Become a Great Speaker</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-for-college-students-become-a-great-speaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 12:19:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-for-college-students-become-a-great-speaker/</guid>
      <description>Imagine speaking to a classroom or even an auditorium full of students knowing that everyone understands you, remembers your key messages and feels you are a confident speaker. Wouldn&#39;t it be great to know that you can speak to any sized audience and that you will always come across your very best?  In this Public Speaking for College Students course you will learn the following:  *How to speak with confidence inside and outside the classroom  *How to avoid the common speaking blunders made by most other college students  *How to rehearse important presentations on video  *How to make fellow students and adults remember your messages  This course is delivered primarily through spoken lecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrivere un Dialogo - Scrittura Creativa Vol. 3</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/scrivere-un-dialogo-scrittura-creativa-vol.-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 18:00:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/scrivere-un-dialogo-scrittura-creativa-vol.-3/</guid>
      <description>Ciao! 
 In questo corso ti spiegherò come poter approcciare, nel migliore dei modi, alla composizione di un’ ottima sequenza dialogica e all’importanza che essa assume all’interno di un racconto, un romanzo o qualsivoglia opera di carattere narrativo. Considera che tra i motivi del “Blocco della pagina bianca&#34; di molti scrittori alle prime armi vi è proprio il senso di inadeguatezza o incapacità nell’affrontare la scrittura dei dialoghi e ti renderai conto che ovviare eliminando gli stessi dialoghi non rappresenta affatto una soluzione effettiva.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Il Personaggio - Scrittura Creativa Vol. 5</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/il-personaggio-scrittura-creativa-vol.-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 09:03:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/il-personaggio-scrittura-creativa-vol.-5/</guid>
      <description>Come nasce l&#39;idea per un personaggio narrativo?
A chi o a cosa ispirarsi?
Dall&#39;idea di un determinato personaggio come si giunge poi al suo inserimento in un preciso contesto narrativo?
Come rivestire uno o più personaggi di credibilità??
Queste sono solo alcune delle domande che affiorano nella mente di uno scrittore quando decide di cimentarsi nella scrittura di un &#39;opera narrativa, a prescindere dal genere che deciderà di seguire o adottare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul: A Biography: Small Group Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/paul-a-biography-small-group-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/paul-a-biography-small-group-edition/</guid>
      <description>N. T. Wright&#39;s definitive biography of Paul reveals the apostle&#39;s lasting role in Christian history as an inventor of new paradigms for how we understand Jesus and what he accomplished. Wright celebrates Paul’s stature as one of the most effective and influential intellectuals in human history, while shedding fresh light on his writings, thoughts, and ideas. Consider these remarkable facts: Paul&#39;s writing occupy less than 90 pages in a modern translation yet they have, page per page, generated more sermons, books, monographs, and journal articles than any other writings from the ancient world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
