<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fitness on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/fitness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fitness on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/fitness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Functional Fitness Training – Easy Way To Get Shape At Home</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/functional-fitness-training-easy-way-to-get-shape-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/functional-fitness-training-easy-way-to-get-shape-at-home/</guid>
      <description>In this online functional fitness course you will learn how to get in shape gently, without killing yourself. This functional fitness course will be your guide, teaching you simple ways to feel and look better than you have in years without grunting, sweating and straining. If you want to get in shape, but don’t want to be a gym rat, this is the perfect fitness course for you.
This functional fitness course teaches you how to tone stretch muscles to give yourself the shape, strength, balance and movement of somebody years younger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kettlebell Fitness Training – Easy Way To Maximum Fitness</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/kettlebell-fitness-training-easy-way-to-maximum-fitness/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/kettlebell-fitness-training-easy-way-to-maximum-fitness/</guid>
      <description>In this online kettlebell Fitness video training course you will learn how tone up &amp;amp; burn fat the way the top pros teach it. Consider this video course to be your “Personal Trainer” guiding you to the most effective methods for fat burning, muscle building, toning and strength.
Kettlebell Fitness training has 5 main benefits: 1) Tones the muscles &amp;amp; problem areas 2) Greatly improves strength &amp;amp; endurance 3) Can help you build muscle 4) Improves balance &amp;amp; stability 5) Hits muscles other exercises miss!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muscle Building - How To Workout For Increasing Muscle Mass</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/muscle-building-how-to-workout-for-increasing-muscle-mass/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/muscle-building-how-to-workout-for-increasing-muscle-mass/</guid>
      <description>In This Muscle Building Course You Will Learn How The Pros Teach People How To Pack On Muscle Fast. This Course Is Not Medical Advice ... But Is Based On Scientific Research &amp;amp; Principles That Are Known To Get Results Fast! Having These Tools &amp;amp; Strategies Will Make Gaining Muscle So Much Easier, Dramatically Increasing The Results You Get &amp;amp; Helping You Achieve Your Goals In Less Time.
In This Online Muscle Building Course For Men &amp;amp; Women You Will Learn How To Build Muscle And Strength The Way The Top Pros Teach It.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Fitness &amp; Health Masterclass - 21 Courses in 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-fitness-health-masterclass-21-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-fitness-health-masterclass-21-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>If You Only Buy ONE Course This Year … It GOT To Be This One!
With over 22 hours of video content, downloadable resources and bonuses - this is one of the most comprehensive fitness &amp;amp; health masterclass available!
You&#39;ll also get access to:
Lifetime Access to course updates
Fast &amp;amp; Friendly Support in the Q&amp;amp;A section
Udemy Certificate of Completion Ready for Download
To make sure you find the information you are looking for the easiest, we have divided our Masterclass to 21 main sections:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tai Chi Chen Style 38 Form -to Sharp Mind &amp; Physical Fitness</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tai-chi-chen-style-38-form-to-sharp-mind-physical-fitness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/tai-chi-chen-style-38-form-to-sharp-mind-physical-fitness/</guid>
      <description>In this courses, I will show you through breath control exercise and Tai Chi Skill to regain the peace of mind. Tai Chi Chen Style 38 Forms (陈式38式太极拳) combines the most of the postures from Chen Style Traditional 74 Forms, cut repeating movements. Comparing with Basic Tai Chi Chen Style 22 Forms and the commonly seen Tai Chi Yang Style, Tai Chi Chen Style 38 Forms keep the kicking, jumping and leaping movements which will apply in fighting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
