<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Compliance on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/compliance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Compliance on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/compliance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Money Laundering Concepts: AML, KYC and Compliance</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/anti-money-laundering-concepts-aml-kyc-and-compliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/anti-money-laundering-concepts-aml-kyc-and-compliance/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the course on Anti-Money Laundering (AML), where you will learn about the key issues faced by financial institutions today: Money Laundering and Terrorist Financing. This course will educate you on Money Laundering and Terrorist Financing laws, Know Your Customer, Customer Due Diligence, Economic Sanctions and Politically Exposed Persons. This is a comprehensive course that captures all relevant concepts required for training employees of an organization.
We will start the course by understanding the term Money Laundering and will then cover the process &amp;amp; impact of the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of Fraud Prevention and Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-fraud-prevention-and-monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-fraud-prevention-and-monitoring/</guid>
      <description>WHY FRAUD PREVENTION?
Understanding how fraud is committed - and especially how it&#39;s prevented - is not easy.
There are countless techniques to take into account. Perpetrators can be of different types and use different approaches.
For anyone aiming to know more about fraud prevention - whether as a fraud monitoring professional, a payments professional, or any other type of professional that wants to master the theory and practice of fraud prevention, finding the right information is crucial.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
