<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Growth Hacking on </title>
    <link>/tags/growth-hacking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Growth Hacking on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 17:46:02 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/growth-hacking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Growth Hacking &amp; Viral Marketing: #1 Strategy Growth Hacking</title>
      <link>/growth-hacking-viral-marketing-#1-strategy-growth-hacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 17:46:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/growth-hacking-viral-marketing-#1-strategy-growth-hacking/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to grow extremely quickly without a lot of money? Do you wish your marketing investments produced exponential growth instead of petty marginal gains? Do you feel there are better ways to grow than just copying competitors? Are you looking for HUGE wins and EXPLOSIVE growth hacking? This the course for you: the definitive guide to growth hacking!
This course is for truly ambitious entrepreneurs, marketers, and product managers who want to drive real IMPACT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App Marketing: Mobile App Marketing &amp; Growth Hacking</title>
      <link>/app-marketing-mobile-app-marketing-growth-hacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/app-marketing-mobile-app-marketing-growth-hacking/</guid>
      <description>This is the definitive course on app marketing to help with your go-to-market app launch. Please note that this is NOT just a course on app store optimization (ASO). This is a more comprehensive course on marketing your app in the market for maximum impact.
I led the mobile app marketing for a Google venture-backed startup (Series E) in Silicon Valley. In just four months, I increased downloads by 71% and mobile app revenue by 89%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence in SEO (2021 Extreme Edition)</title>
      <link>/artificial-intelligence-in-seo-2021-extreme-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artificial-intelligence-in-seo-2021-extreme-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the ninth course in Term 1 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Looking for the word called &#34;Popularity&#34; to come to life? It&#39;s good to be heard, of course, and everything, but is that really the point? To be able to applaud and say, yeah... I had 1,000,000 visits last year to my website... that may be amazing, but why is website traffic important to your business or any business, for that matter?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
