<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arts &amp; Crafts on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/arts-crafts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Arts &amp; Crafts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/arts-crafts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>#1 Embellishments Course for Acrylic Pouring &amp; Painting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/#1-embellishments-course-for-acrylic-pouring-painting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/#1-embellishments-course-for-acrylic-pouring-painting/</guid>
      <description>IS THIS FOR YOU?
If you are interested in embellishing your Acrylic Paint Pouring &amp;amp; Fluid Art and want to try it for yourself.
Or, you’ve already started and are finding that it’s not quite as easy as it appears on some of the videos you&#39;ve seen.
Or, are doing OK but want to broaden your knowledge and embellishment skills......
THEN THIS IS THE PERFECT TRAINING COURSE FOR YOU
This unique training course will guide you through every step of the way to embellish your very own fluid art masterpieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Portrait Drawing Techniques- Beginners and Advanced</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basic-portrait-drawing-techniques-beginners-and-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basic-portrait-drawing-techniques-beginners-and-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the &#34;Basic portrait sketching techniques for beginners&#34; course. This course teaches you how to easily create a portrait sketch from the very first basics. This tutorial in simple and beginner language will help you a lot in learning this style of painting. This course does not require any previous knowledge and if you are only a little interested in painting and have talent, with the help of this course you can easily create beautiful portraits because we have tried to teach you all the steps , step by step.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn to Draw Illustrated Creatures From Simple Shapes</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-to-draw-illustrated-creatures-from-simple-shapes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 21:50:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-to-draw-illustrated-creatures-from-simple-shapes/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover all the steps to create creatures from the depths of your imagination, and turn them into vibrant creatures, in three easy processes.
You will learn from a professional artist with over 10 years of experience.
You will get to watch every step and you will learn invaluable advice that will help you achieve your artistic goals, even if you have never picked up a pencil before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Pencil Drawing and Shading</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-pencil-drawing-and-shading/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 20:40:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-pencil-drawing-and-shading/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the “Ultimate Pencil Drawing and Shading from Beginner to Advanced Level” course!
This course has been created to teach you all the drawing techniques you need from beginner to advanced level. Never drawn pencil artworks before? That’s exactly why the first lesson of the course starts right at the beginning with an introduction to pencil drawing to teach you about pencil pressure, pencil layering and light to dark gradients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watercolor Portrait in Cellulose Paper</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/watercolor-portrait-in-cellulose-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:10:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/watercolor-portrait-in-cellulose-paper/</guid>
      <description>What you will learn
Learn how to paint a portrait using cellulose paper in watercolor.
How to block-in a drawing portrait drawing.
How to fine tune proportions and measurements.
How to mix skin tones in watercolor.
Insights on how to visualize volume and form.
Understand the main differences of cellulose and cotton watercolor paper.
Problem-solve issues that arise with cellulose watercolor paper.
Requirements
Basic understanding of watercolor and drawing would be helpful</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Çektiğiniz Fotoğrafları Yağlıboya Resme Dönüştürün !</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%C3%A7ekti%C4%9Finiz-foto%C4%9Fraflar%C4%B1-ya%C4%9Fl%C4%B1boya-resme-d%C3%B6n%C3%BC%C5%9Ft%C3%BCr%C3%BCn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 16:32:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%C3%A7ekti%C4%9Finiz-foto%C4%9Fraflar%C4%B1-ya%C4%9Fl%C4%B1boya-resme-d%C3%B6n%C3%BC%C5%9Ft%C3%BCr%C3%BCn/</guid>
      <description>Merhabalar !
Yeni başlayan ve resim yeteneğini ileri seviyelere taşımak isteyen herkes için hazırladığımız kursumuzun temel amacı ; yağlıboya resim teknikleri öğretmek. Ayrıca hepimizin o çok sevdiği , güzel mekanlarda çektiğimiz fotoğrafları tuval üzerine nasıl aktarabiliriz ? Nasıl yağlıboya sanat eserleri haline getirebiliriz ? Bu kursumuzda öğrencilerimize tasarım yapmayı ve uygulamak için ne tür teknikler kullanılacağını öğretmekteyiz. İyi bir gözlem ve analiz ile gördükleri bir fotoğrafı yorumlayarak yapacakları resmin nereden başlayıp nerede sonlanacağına dair bir fikirlerinin ve güvenlerinin oluşmasını hedeflemekteyiz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>رسم شجرة بدون اوراق بألوان الخشب - English Subtitled</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%B1%D8%B3%D9%85-%D8%B4%D8%AC%D8%B1%D8%A9-%D8%A8%D8%AF%D9%88%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%82-%D8%A8%D8%A3%D9%84%D9%88%D8%A7%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AE%D8%B4%D8%A8-english-subtitled/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%B1%D8%B3%D9%85-%D8%B4%D8%AC%D8%B1%D8%A9-%D8%A8%D8%AF%D9%88%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%82-%D8%A8%D8%A3%D9%84%D9%88%D8%A7%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AE%D8%B4%D8%A8-english-subtitled/</guid>
      <description>أهلا بكم في الفيديو التعليمي لرسم رسم شجرة بدون أوراق بألوان الخشب. حرصت في هذا الفيديو أن تبدأ من المستوي صفر وذلك لما يحتويه الفيديو من شقين، الأول هو رسم الشجرة حيث انها من الأشياء الهامة جدا في خيال كل رسام وفنان وثانيا وهي طريقة التعامل مع ألوان الخشب، لاظهار امكانياتها وقدرتها على التعبير بجرأة لرسم الأشجار
كان هدفي بهذه الدورة الاحساس بالمتعة في التعامل مع ألوان الخشب, وذلك بناء علي تكنيك مبسط وسهل, ولهذا قمت برسم للهيكل الأساسي (الساق والاغصان الكبيرة) للشجرة، ثم الأغصان الصغيرة لها, ثم التفاصيل الخاصة الصغيرة حتي تصل الي رسمها باحتراف, مع الأخذ في الاعتبار تأثير الإضاءة على رسم عناصر الشجرة من مناطق مضاءة واخري مظللة, مع ذكر الأخطاء الشائعة اثناء عملية الرسم.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
