<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meditation on </title>
    <link>/tags/meditation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meditation on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/meditation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Meditation For Beginners</title>
      <link>/meditation-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/meditation-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Meditation is one of the most powerful things that you can do, as a human being. It trains you to be in control of you mind and your emotions, in ways that you never knew were possible. It allows you to be happy just to be alive, even in the most difficult of circumstances; even when you&#39;re injured, or suffering a loss, stressed out at work, overwhelmed, depressed or anxious. It allows you to find the basic happiness of being alive, and that pervades everything else, so that you can deal with everything else much better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditation Masterclass</title>
      <link>/meditation-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/meditation-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you&#39;ll learn meditations from all around the world, from mindfulness to zen to breath-work, chakras, Tibetan bowls, and everything in between.
This course is for anyone who&#39;s interested in meditation, from n00bs to zen masters alike; no matter what your level of experience, you can gain a lot from exploring this course. By the end, you&#39;ll have experience with over a dozen different styles of meditation.
This course is accredited by The Meditation Organization as a Certified Teacher Training Course -- AMC (Accredited Meditation Course) #39283 -- so once you receive your diploma at the end of this course, you&#39;ll be able to teach meditation to others as well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
