<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meditation on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/meditation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meditation on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/meditation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Meditation For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/meditation-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/meditation-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Meditation is one of the most powerful things that you can do, as a human being. It trains you to be in control of you mind and your emotions, in ways that you never knew were possible. It allows you to be happy just to be alive, even in the most difficult of circumstances; even when you&#39;re injured, or suffering a loss, stressed out at work, overwhelmed, depressed or anxious. It allows you to find the basic happiness of being alive, and that pervades everything else, so that you can deal with everything else much better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditation Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/meditation-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/meditation-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you&#39;ll learn meditations from all around the world, from mindfulness to zen to breath-work, chakras, Tibetan bowls, and everything in between.
This course is for anyone who&#39;s interested in meditation, from n00bs to zen masters alike; no matter what your level of experience, you can gain a lot from exploring this course. By the end, you&#39;ll have experience with over a dozen different styles of meditation.
This course is accredited by The Meditation Organization as a Certified Teacher Training Course -- AMC (Accredited Meditation Course) #39283 -- so once you receive your diploma at the end of this course, you&#39;ll be able to teach meditation to others as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mediation Made Simple: Learn how to Calm your Mind</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/mediation-made-simple-learn-how-to-calm-your-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 11:41:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/mediation-made-simple-learn-how-to-calm-your-mind/</guid>
      <description>Do you find it difficult to calm your mind?
Do you feel that you are a slave to your thoughts?
Do you want to overcome overthinking, anxiety, or constant rumination?
Change is available more quickly than you can imagine. It just requires you to take that first step...
In this short course, we start from the very beginning. We learn what meditation is, why we shouldn’t fear the practice and we understand what the real benefits are of mediation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditation For Beginners with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/meditation-for-beginners-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 12:19:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/meditation-for-beginners-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>Meditation for Beginners with MRS JOY is designed to provide emotional and mental health skills through the practice of meditation, to help people all over the world to learn this essential self-regulation tool, so they can improve their lives for the better. It&#39;s also an additional tool for those supporting friends and loved ones that are passing through stress and hard times at the moment. 
Meditation is important for each one of us, as a healthy habit for a successful lifestyle, free of stress and its symptoms, like anxiety and depression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fully Accredited Certification in Mindfulness Practice</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fully-accredited-certification-in-mindfulness-practice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fully-accredited-certification-in-mindfulness-practice/</guid>
      <description>This course is designed, keeping in mind that you don&#39;t have any prior knowledge and understanding of Mindfulness/ Mindfulness Meditation. So we have completely avoided medical jargon and have simplified it for you.
This course will cover Mindfulness/ Mindfulness Meditation as a whole and enable you to use the methods and techniques.
The accredited certification will be provided by India&#39;s leading CPD provider.
 Ratings: 4.85/5
Enrollments: 643
Coupon Code: TOTAL-OFF</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heal From Within - 14 Guided Meditations with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/heal-from-within-14-guided-meditations-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:42:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/heal-from-within-14-guided-meditations-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>Embrace The Power Of Guided Meditation
Let The Healing Begin

Experts advise that most of the population suffers from some form of dysfunction and issues…

According to eNotAlone...
&#34;In the United States today, more people come from dysfunctional families than healthy families. It is estimated that approximately 70 to 80 percent come from dysfunctional families.&#34;

According to DoSomething…
&#34;About 20% of teens will experience depression before they reach adulthood.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
