<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Graphic Design &amp; Illustration on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/graphic-design-illustration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Graphic Design &amp; Illustration on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/graphic-design-illustration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Graphic Design Certification &#43; Live Class</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-certification--live-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-certification--live-class/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the incredible series-based course &#34;Graphic Design Certification - Legendary Edition&#34;.
We know that design helps us understand the world better, and its patterns allow us to keep up with the times. You should always be conscious of the latest trends in graphic design, whether you are a designer, developer, or a newbie. This course is a testament to the latest trends in the field of graphic design, this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Create a Professional Presentation in PowerPoint</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-create-a-professional-presentation-in-powerpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-create-a-professional-presentation-in-powerpoint/</guid>
      <description>Dear PEOPLE from all over the WORLD!
We are Anton and Natalia, founders of NeitDesign, and we specialize in PowerPoint presentations. We started creating presentations in 2015 and now we are Top Rated Seller on Fiverr and Fiverr PRO in Presentation Design. However, we must confess - we also made MISTAKES. And, these mistakes cost us time and money. What we mean is when we began our career, we received huge number of REVISION requests from our clients who wanted to make their presentations look PERFECT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advance logo design course: Bear mascot shape design</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advance-logo-design-course-bear-mascot-shape-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advance-logo-design-course-bear-mascot-shape-design/</guid>
      <description>***** Learn mascot logo design: Professional bear mascot logo design quickly and step by step *****
Learn mascot bear logo design in adobe illustrator step and step very easy way. If you are familiar with adobe illustrator then this course is for you. I will mostly use the Pen tool to draw shapes and some other tools but you can also use Adobe Photoshop if you have basic knowledge of it but I prefer adobe illustrator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Basics of Adobe Photoshop CC 2022 for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-basics-of-adobe-photoshop-cc-2022-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-basics-of-adobe-photoshop-cc-2022-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Want to learn Photoshop but don’t know where to start from?
This course is well designed and prepared to make you a decent Photoshop user. All the course contents and examples are wisely chosen and each chapter is explained using the step-by-step method to better fit your needs. The initial chapters are basics and further chapters are explained in more details without making things overcomplicated. To help you follow along with the lectures, exercise files are included in each chapter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Clip Studio Paint Megacourse: Beginner to Expert</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-clip-studio-paint-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-clip-studio-paint-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Learn digital art with Clip Studio Paint!
Design like a pro!
Have you ever wanted to get into digital art? In today’s world, we see it everywhere - from book covers, to movie posters, fanart and bespoke custom illustrations. Whether you’re an aspiring artist eager to create original and fan content, or an experienced artist looking to expand from traditional into digital media, the possibilities when painting digitally are endless. Even someone who’s never picked up a stylus before can learn the skills and start creating beautiful pieces of art - and we’re here to teach you how.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Design A Great Movie Poster That Works</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-design-a-great-movie-poster-that-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-design-a-great-movie-poster-that-works/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m an independent filmmaker and I know the importance of good looking poster for a film. Especially for independent films. Let me say the way it is, your movie poster is the deciding factor for the audience when deciding what to watch. As simple as that. It&#39;s beyond important. Imagine getting home from work, getting comfortable on a sofa in front of your tv, and scrolling through hundreds of tv shows and movies deciding what to watch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Design a STAND-OUT social media content in Canva.</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-design-a-stand-out-social-media-content-in-canva./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:11:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-design-a-stand-out-social-media-content-in-canva./</guid>
      <description>Have you been stuck in creating your own graphics for social media, but don’t know how to begin? Have you researched graphic design tutorials online only to find that they never cover what you&#39;re really looking for? I know that sometimes designing can be frustrating! It takes a lot of a hard time to create custom graphics yourself, especially when you’re just starting out with no previous experience. I’ve been there too… Spending countless hours online searching for the right tutorial - but always coming up short.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Illustrator 2022 Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-illustrator-2022-ultimate-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-illustrator-2022-ultimate-guide/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone and welcome to Adobe Illustrator 2022 Ultimate Guide.
In this video, we&#39;re going to go over an in-depth overview of what we&#39;re going to be learning throughout this course.
So let&#39;s jump into it.
So in Section two, we&#39;re going to talk about Adobe Creative Cloud 2022 plans and pricing.
So we&#39;ll cover individuals, business students and teachers and schools, universities.
Then we&#39;ll talk about how to set up a free creative cloud account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe InDesign 2022 Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-indesign-2022-ultimate-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-indesign-2022-ultimate-guide/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone and welcome to Adobe InDesign 2022 Ultimate Guide.
In this video, we&#39;re going to go over a course overview of what we&#39;re going to be learning throughout the course.
So in Section two, we&#39;re going to talk about Adobe Creative Cloud plans.
So we&#39;ll cover individuals, business students and teachers and schools and universities.
Then we&#39;ll talk about how to use Adobe Creative Cloud Web to install Adobe InDesign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphic Designing for People with Autism, Dyslexia etc</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-designing-for-people-with-autism-dyslexia-etc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-designing-for-people-with-autism-dyslexia-etc/</guid>
      <description>Here, this Digital Tech training course is part of a series of various other classes made Specifically for Special Needs People.
The Special Needs people are mainly those who are Autistic, Dyslexic, having Down Syndrome, Asperger’s, Cerebral Palsy and various others.
They are are known to have exceptional talents, which only need to be uncovered. However, once their hidden talents are tapped, they are capable of producing wonders.
Unfortunately, they are rarely given fair chances i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multimedia and Graphic designing Course for Special Needs</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/multimedia-and-graphic-designing-course-for-special-needs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/multimedia-and-graphic-designing-course-for-special-needs/</guid>
      <description>This Digital Tech training course is part of a series of various other classes made Specifically for Special Needs People.
The Special Needs people are mainly those who are Autistic, Dyslexic, having Down Syndrome, Asperger’s, Cerebral Palsy and various others.
The Special Needs people are known to have exceptional talents, which only need to be uncovered. However, once their hidden talents are tapped, they are capable of producing wonders.
Unfortunately, they are rarely given fair chances i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aprende Photoshop en 18 días</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprende-photoshop-en-18-d%C3%ADas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprende-photoshop-en-18-d%C3%ADas/</guid>
      <description>En este curso aprenderás a conocer desde CERO todas las herramientas de PHOTOSHOP CC 2017 - 2018, además conocerás algunos filtros, fusiones de capas y otras herramientas; además podrás realizar ejercicios prácticos donde aplicaras todas las herramientas aprendidas; podrás aprender de forma rápida y cómoda; y realizar ejercicios en el horario que mejor que convenga, ¿Qué esperas, aceptas el reto? únete al mejor curso de Photoshop y aprende a utilizar el software desde CERO en solo 18 días.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Incredible Visual Graphics with Canva (2022 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-incredible-visual-graphics-with-canva-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-incredible-visual-graphics-with-canva-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Create Incredible Visual Graphics with Canva (2022 Edition)&#34;.
So, you&#39;re looking for an online course that will train you on Canva - the superb graphic design tool, very easily?
You&#39;ve come to the right place, my passionate learner. Look no further.
Welcome, my name is Srinidhi Ranganathan. My fans fondly call me &#34;Digital Marketing Legend&#34;. Teaming up with Saranya and Stefi, we have now put this course together to help people just like you quickly master Canva.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence Photo Colorisation Tools (2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-photo-colorisation-tools-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-photo-colorisation-tools-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Artificial Intelligence Photo Colorisation Tools (2022)&#34;.
Colours are a vital part of how stories are told through photography and we know this. Now, it&#39;s high time to bring new life to old photos by automatically applying colour to them with the power of Artificial Intelligence (AI) tools.
This 2022 mind-blowing and incredible course focussed on &#34;Artificial Intelligence Photo Colorisation Tools&#34; created by Digital Marketing Legend &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34; teaches you how to leverage Deep Learning to the maximum use in order for colourizing Black and white photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art Of Drawing Cartoon Comic Strips [NEW]</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-art-of-drawing-cartoon-comic-strips-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-art-of-drawing-cartoon-comic-strips-new/</guid>
      <description>NOW IS THE MOMENT Updated - 18/10/2021
Learn to communicate your ideas through visual Art.
More and More film companies employ Graphic artists and Cartoonist for their Animations.
Here is Your Opportunity
Do You Want To Be a Creative?
Join Thousands of students learn how to Draw &amp;amp; Create cartoon Comic Strips.
This Masterclass is the Compilation 0f 13 years of my Life&#39;s Learning &amp;amp; Pesronal experience on the Subject of Drawing Cartoons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Revit Guide - Model a Modern Multistory Building</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-revit-guide-model-a-modern-multistory-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-revit-guide-model-a-modern-multistory-building/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Revit Guide is your course for perfecting your BIM and Revit design and collaboration skills.
Revit is a complex program with lots of levers. To learn the most, you need to fundamentals while also learning industry workflows. In this comprehensive course, you will learn how to use Revit to plan, model and develop a project based on actual Architectural designs, so you can perfect your skill for your next team project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe InDesign. Aprende a maquetar de manera profesional</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-indesign.-aprende-a-maquetar-de-manera-profesional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 20:40:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-indesign.-aprende-a-maquetar-de-manera-profesional/</guid>
      <description>Adobe InDesign es un software de diseño, utilizado para la maquetación de cualquier documento, ya sean periódicos, revistas, libros o cualquier material de publicación que se nos ocurra. Es un programa fácil de comprender y dinámico. Nos permite diseñar y maquetar de una manera ágil y creativa incluyendo elementos como títulos, textos, imágenes e incluso enlaces para su visualización posterior en páginas web. También nos permite configurar nuestras propias plantillas, crear hojas de estilo para automatizar parámetros como la fuente, el tamaño, el color, etc… y otros muchos accesos directos para acelerar el proceso de diseño y hacer la vida del maquetador un poco más sencilla.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art Of Drawing The Face | Beginner&#39;s Course (NEW) 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-art-of-drawing-the-face-beginners-course-new-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 13:36:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-art-of-drawing-the-face-beginners-course-new-2022/</guid>
      <description>Learn How to Draw Anyone, Anytime!
••• VERY EASY •••
Realistic Drawing Course
Imagine Moment; that you could Draw your Friends, the Face of the one you Love, Your Family Members.
Imagine you could Draw just anyone and you made them so happy each time.
Imagine the Joy and Fulfilment.
DRAWING IS A Basic Instinct; We are all born with.
Many People think that Drawing is Hard but The Truth is that Drawing is a Skill and with the right knowledge and Practice, You can master the Art of Drawing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create an animated promo video in PowerPoint</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-create-an-animated-promo-video-in-powerpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 15:08:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-create-an-animated-promo-video-in-powerpoint/</guid>
      <description>After you complete this course, you will get to know and practice:
major tools and techniques of PowerPoint. Even if you never worked in PowerPoint before, we will explain step by step, so you will not have any complications. It will help you to create professional presentations by yourself.
PowerPoint hotkeys. To optimize working process and increase speed, we will use hotkeys. We will explain how they work and how to use them, and by the end of the course you will easily use them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New illustration Painting - Digital Photoshop Drawing Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/new-illustration-painting-digital-photoshop-drawing-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:57:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/new-illustration-painting-digital-photoshop-drawing-course/</guid>
      <description>In 2021, about 40,000 students have learned this &#39;Guochao&#39; illustration course in China. Just come and join them to see what you can create.
What is &#39;Guochao&#39; illustration style?
There are many kinds of Chinese style illustration, &#39;Guochao&#39; is one of them. &#39;Guochao&#39; means based on the Chinese traditional culture background, adding some modern fashion elements. It is also the illustration style mainly introduced in this course.
This course has 4 parts (total 11 lessons) with downloadable resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop CC- Basic Photoshop training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-cc-basic-photoshop-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:10:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-cc-basic-photoshop-training/</guid>
      <description>Learning the basics of Adobe Photoshop is definitely not easy, especially if you have no prior knowledge in this field. But, this course can teach you everything you need to know to start using photoshop and making your own projects with pictures that you take yourself or pictures that you have simply found on the internet. If you:
- Are a student and need to learn how to properly use Photoshop</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Adobe Photoshop CC Course With Advance Training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/professional-adobe-photoshop-cc-course-with-advance-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:10:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/professional-adobe-photoshop-cc-course-with-advance-training/</guid>
      <description>A professional photoshop course with advance photoshop training where a student will learn about selection and masking, how to design logo, t-shirt, business card, resume, mug, bottle, calendar, cover, gif, along with that student will learn how to earn money by graphics designing work, retouching, advance use of photoshop tools etc. It’s a professional photoshop course specially for graphics designers and before enrol this course you must have knowledge about basic photoshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop CC Fundamentals and Essentials Training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-cc-fundamentals-and-essentials-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-cc-fundamentals-and-essentials-training/</guid>
      <description>Hi There, I am Stephen Koel Soren and I am a Graphics and Web Expert. If you are a beginner and looking to learn photoshop from scratch then this course will help you to learn Adobe Photoshop Professionally. For learning graphics design and photoshop retouching from beginner to advanced this course can be a lighthouse for you. You can learn from this course about Photoshop Layer, Color and Adjustment, Photoshop Color Correction, Shape and Symbol, Content-Aware &amp;amp; Cropping, Photoshop Text Style, Gradient Stroke &amp;amp; Bevel, Shadow, Blending, Selection, Photoshop Masking, Blur &amp;amp; Filters, Transform, Warp &amp;amp; Distort, Clipping Mask, Retouch, Photoshop Retouching, Effect Of Visual Style, Brush, Export, Earning Money With Graphics Design Work, Advance Tool and many more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Figma Basics Super Easy Crash Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/figma-basics-super-easy-crash-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/figma-basics-super-easy-crash-course/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Figma Basics Super Easy Crash Course. Figma is an interface design application that runs in the browser—but it’s actually much more than that. I would go so far as to say it’s probably the best application for team-based collaborative design projects. If you are new to Figma or Designing as a whole then this is the right place for you.
Figma is a collaborative web-based editing and design interface tool that offers a web API, plus- it’s free!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Drawing Cartoon : Baby Viking 2.0 (NEW)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-art-of-drawing-cartoon-baby-viking-2.0-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-art-of-drawing-cartoon-baby-viking-2.0-new/</guid>
      <description>Have you been laughed at and told you&#39;re not creative?
Do you want to learn how to draw professional colored Cartoon Characters straight from your imagination to impress your &#34;Talented&#34; Friends and Family?
Give me a moment of your time and I will show you how to draw and edit your own colored Cartoon Character from your imagination.
My name is T.S Amachree and I am a Cartoonist. This Masterclass is an improved version with a never before seen Step- by - Step Guide for Drawing A Cartoon Character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cartoon Drawing Course : Angry Mom Driving in Traffic</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cartoon-drawing-course-angry-mom-driving-in-traffic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 21:27:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cartoon-drawing-course-angry-mom-driving-in-traffic/</guid>
      <description>This course will help you with the knoweldge on How to Draw and Color Cartoons, with these simplified and easy to follow techniques to enable you become a Professional Cartoonist.
Created by a Amazing Cartoonist ( over 10 years Experience) T.S Amachree to help you Draw and Color Amazing Cartoons Straight from Your Imagination even with your little experience in Drawing.
What You&#39;ll Learn
How to Draw &amp;amp; Color A Cartoon School Bus</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Express your Stories with Cartoons</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-express-your-stories-with-cartoons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 13:34:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-express-your-stories-with-cartoons/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED VERSION 21/10/2021
Are you Creative with Stories but You Don&#39;t really Know how to bring it to life visually? This Course is for you.
Hello; I&#39;m T.S Amachree and I&#39;m a Professional Cartoonist.
In this detailed Cartoon Comic Series Course; I will be sharing with you my knowledge &amp;amp; secrets in Drawing and Developing Cartoon Comic series from your Imagination.
This course will teach you easy yet powerful techniques and tricks to help you create amazing Comic Series that will impress your friends and family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-Shirt Design Masterclass In Photoshop | Sell Your T-Shirt</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/t-shirt-design-masterclass-in-photoshop-sell-your-t-shirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 13:12:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/t-shirt-design-masterclass-in-photoshop-sell-your-t-shirt/</guid>
      <description>In this course you will learn How to create or design your own custom T-Shirt In Photoshop. This course is for Intermediate skill levels, so you will find this course easy to follow if you have basic photoshop knowledge. You will learn how to design a fire fighter tshirt, how to design hero soldier or I’d rather die like a man than live like a coward tagline design, how to design a wanted black and white tshirt, how design a lumberjack tshirt using only with elements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Cartoon Drawing  Course :  a Kid driving a Car</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/simple-cartoon-drawing-course-a-kid-driving-a-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 13:12:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/simple-cartoon-drawing-course-a-kid-driving-a-car/</guid>
      <description>Drawing a Car can be very complicated when editing the transparent windShield; in this masterclass, i will teach you a simple technique to achieve Transparent Glasses using aKid in His Toy Car. This is a Real Time Step-By Step Process of the entire Drawing and Editing using Photoshop.
Hello I&#39;m T.S Amachree, I have been a Cartoonist for more than 13 years and I have upgraded my techniques over the years; I love deeply sharing my Knoweldge and Experience with you, How I Draw and Color My Cartoon Characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canva: Certificação Designer Gráfico Profissional | 2022 |</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/canva-certifica%C3%A7%C3%A3o-designer-gr%C3%A1fico-profissional-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 13:18:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/canva-certifica%C3%A7%C3%A3o-designer-gr%C3%A1fico-profissional-2022/</guid>
      <description>Olá! Seja bem vind@ ao curso mais completo de Canva 2022 aqui da plataforma! Muito prazer, eu sou o professor Rafael Galvão, sou designer gráfico a mais de 3 anos e tenho mais de 8 milhões de visualizações em todos os meus projetos! Já desenvolvi trabalhos para pequenas, médias e grandes empresas e Universidades no Brasil e no exterior! Vou compartilhar contigo no curso por meio de uma metodologia de fácil compreensão várias dicas estratégicas para o desenvolvimento dos seus projetos do absoluto zero até o mercado!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Der ultimative Adobe Photoshop CC Wekzeuge Kurs [2021]</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/der-ultimative-adobe-photoshop-cc-wekzeuge-kurs-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:46:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/der-ultimative-adobe-photoshop-cc-wekzeuge-kurs-2021/</guid>
      <description>Info zu dem Kurs
In diesem ultimativen Adobe Photoshop CC Werkzeuge Kurs auf deutsch lernst Du nicht nur die Einstellungen aller Werkzeuge kennen, sondern ich werde Dir auch noch ein paar Anwendungsbeispiele zeigen, die man als Designer oder Fotograf für Grafiken und Fotobearbeitung ganz gut gebrauchen kann. Ganz egal ob Webdesigner, Mediendesigner, Logodesigner, Grafikdesigner, Künstler, Fotograf, Freelancer oder einfacher Hobby Photoshopper in diesem Kurs ist für jeden etwas dabei! Zusätzlich werde ich Dir neben den Werkzeugen auch noch zeigen wo Du kostenlose Pinsel und Schriftarten herunterladen kannst und ich werde Dir auch die Mischmodis, Pinseleinstellungen, den Farbwähler, auswählen + maskieren und die Kopierquellen beibringen, daher diese Punkte auch alle mit den Photoshop Werkzeugen zusammenhängen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Nothing To Pro: Business Card Design With Photoshop CC</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/from-nothing-to-pro-business-card-design-with-photoshop-cc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 09:53:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/from-nothing-to-pro-business-card-design-with-photoshop-cc/</guid>
      <description>From Nothing To Pro: Business Card Design With Photoshop CC Graphics Design Theory In this course, I&#39;m going to be doing a really practical and comprehensive dive into photoshop business card design for you going through every single aspect of the graphics design theory I used all round.
When you are done learning, there&#39;s a bonus class which takes you by the hand and show you how to make side income designing business card for brands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop 2021 Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-2021-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-2021-basics/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Design but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Designs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Photoshop 2021 Basics is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Design is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building designs like an expert with Adobe Photoshop 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Создание бизнес презентации в PowerPoint с нуля</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D1%81%D0%BE%D0%B7%D0%B4%D0%B0%D0%BD%D0%B8%D0%B5-%D0%B1%D0%B8%D0%B7%D0%BD%D0%B5%D1%81-%D0%BF%D1%80%D0%B5%D0%B7%D0%B5%D0%BD%D1%82%D0%B0%D1%86%D0%B8%D0%B8-%D0%B2-powerpoint-%D1%81-%D0%BD%D1%83%D0%BB%D1%8F/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D1%81%D0%BE%D0%B7%D0%B4%D0%B0%D0%BD%D0%B8%D0%B5-%D0%B1%D0%B8%D0%B7%D0%BD%D0%B5%D1%81-%D0%BF%D1%80%D0%B5%D0%B7%D0%B5%D0%BD%D1%82%D0%B0%D1%86%D0%B8%D0%B8-%D0%B2-powerpoint-%D1%81-%D0%BD%D1%83%D0%BB%D1%8F/</guid>
      <description>Курс &#34;Создание бизнес презентации в PowerPoint с нуля&#34; состоит из 10 основных лекций, каждая из которых посвящена созданию 1 из 10 слайдов. Опыт показывает, что 10-12 слайдов – это оптимальный размер бизнес-презентации. Помимо лекций, к курсу прилагается папка с исходными файлами, чтобы облегчить Вам поиск необходимых для дизайна иконок и фото.
Также к курсу прилагаются 7 бонусных видео и домашние задания, разработанные к каждой теме. В них я делюсь секретами профессионального дизайнера, даю советы и вдохновляю Вас на лучшие результаты.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income: Beginners Design &amp; Print on demand</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/passive-income-beginners-design-print-on-demand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/passive-income-beginners-design-print-on-demand/</guid>
      <description>This is an awesome Photoshop course that teaches you how to use this program from a complete beginner to create a design and selling option for it. Even if you&#39;ve never touched Photoshop in your life. I can teach you how to design like a pro. I have also added a few tips &amp;amp; tricks that I learned over the years. This course is like no other course on the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become Professional Social Media Visual Designer | Canva</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/become-professional-social-media-visual-designer-canva/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/become-professional-social-media-visual-designer-canva/</guid>
      <description>Canva helps you to professionally prepare many images such as social media posts, logos, posters, presentations, invitations, cards, advertisements from your phone, tablet or computer. Every design has some rules, of course, but it depends on the imagination on the basis of design ability. Canva gives you exactly this support. You don&#39;t need to have miracle design knowledge to use Canva. All you have to do is use your imagination and with the support of us, effortlessly pour all this into the design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphic Design: Side Hustle to Self-Employed</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-side-hustle-to-self-employed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-side-hustle-to-self-employed/</guid>
      <description>Are you thinking about going full-time as a freelancer in graphic design?
Even if you are just ramping up your freelance life after hours, this class will give you a bunch of tools and tips that will set you up for success!
It&#39;s a huge endeavor to get a business off the ground - especially if the business is in creative production ( like graphic design, 3D modeling, illustration, etc). Not only are you responsible for your day-to-day deliverables, but you also have to market yourself, bill clients, network, and so much more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphic Design - Biding For Online Work 101</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-biding-for-online-work-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 10:06:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-biding-for-online-work-101/</guid>
      <description>eBook Included in Class!
There are lots of ways to build your portfolio, meet new clients and make money with graphic design. One of those avenues is online bid-for-work websites like Upwork. These sites let you upload your portfolio, check out job listings, and offer a bid to do the work based on the client&#39;s description of the job they need to be done. Seems easy enough? Not always!
If you are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photoshop Challenge</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/photoshop-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 21:40:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/photoshop-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Adobe Photoshop es el programa más potente del mercado para la transformación, retoque y reparación de imágenes digitales, así como para la elaboración de todo tipo de creatividades.
Este curso pretende ser un curso diferente. Aprenderemos jugando! A través de 9 ejercicios, 9 retos de una dificultad creciente, este curso nos proporcionará todas las habilidades necesarias para tener un conocimiento profundo de las herramientas más importantes de Adobe Photoshop. Se trata de un curso eminentemente práctico en donde se proponen 10 ejercicios para que el alumno los realice primero por si solo antes de ver el video y ponga a prueba sus conocimientos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Adobe Photoshop CC Masterclass Basics To Advanced</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-adobe-photoshop-cc-masterclass-basics-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-adobe-photoshop-cc-masterclass-basics-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Learn Adobe Photoshop CC From Scratch &amp;amp; Ultimate Photoshop Masterclass Course For Newbie. If you are a beginner and looking to learn photoshop from scratch then this course will help you to learn Adobe Photoshop Professionally. For learning graphics design and photoshop retouching from beginner to advanced this course can be a lighthouse for you. You can learn from this course about Photoshop Layer, Color and Adjustment, Photoshop Color Correction, Shape and Symbol, Content-Aware &amp;amp; Cropping, Photoshop Text Style, Gradient Stroke &amp;amp; Bevel, Shadow, Blending, Selection, Photoshop Masking, Blur &amp;amp; Filters, Transform, Warp &amp;amp; Distort, Clipping Mask, Retouch, Photoshop Retouching, Effect Of Visual Style, Brush, Export, Earning Money With Graphics Design Work, Advance Tool and many more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphic Design - Passive Income Downloads &amp; Self Publishing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-passive-income-downloads-self-publishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 10:48:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-passive-income-downloads-self-publishing/</guid>
      <description>-- Updated 6/28/21, remixed audio on all lessons --
So what is the deal with selling downloads and print-on-demand (AKA Self Publishing)? The answers are in this class!
It doesn&#39;t matter how far along you are in your creative arts business, how old you are, how extensive your portfolio is - setting up downloads NOW creates passive future income for years to come. PLUS I show you how you can use them NOW as your own marketing tools while having the same items pull double duty as passive income streams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All In One Adobe Photoshop Essential Course For Everyone</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/all-in-one-adobe-photoshop-essential-course-for-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 13:19:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/all-in-one-adobe-photoshop-essential-course-for-everyone/</guid>
      <description>In this course you will Learn 7 Types Important Work Of Adobe Photoshop With Step-By-Step Video Tutorial for your brand or business or for your personal use!
· This course is actually for anyone because this course provides 7 Essential practical projects
· Do you want to create your own social media graphics, business card, logo or something but you have no idea that how to use Photoshop or don&#39;t know where to begin?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphic Design - Bulletproof Freelance Business</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-bulletproof-freelance-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:16:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-bulletproof-freelance-business/</guid>
      <description>Creating the graphics is only one part of the job!
There is so much more that goes on behind the scenes that can eat into your design time - and PROFITS - if you don’t have your business model set up to protect you and create a transparent and open designer/client relationship at the same time.
Running a small business always has a fair share of the unexpected. Things happen outside the usual ‘get hired - do the design - get paid’ operations that can slow you down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop CC Crash Course Learn Photoshop In Two Hour</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-cc-crash-course-learn-photoshop-in-two-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-cc-crash-course-learn-photoshop-in-two-hour/</guid>
      <description>Hi There, I am Stephen Koel Soren and I am a Graphics and Web Expert. This is a crash course for Adobe Photoshop and You will learn only the essential part that is really required for design in Photoshop within hour. You will learn from this course:
Color and Adjustment
Content-Aware &amp;amp; Cropping
Text Style
Shadow
Selection &amp;amp; Masking
Blur &amp;amp; Filters
Retouch
and many more.
This course is especially designed for beginner those who want to learn photoshop basic and essential part within a short time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Course of After Effects: Learn From an Expert</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-course-of-after-effects-learn-from-an-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-course-of-after-effects-learn-from-an-expert/</guid>
      <description>Hi. This is Mohammad Fazel, motion designer and i have 10 years of experience in this field. I&#39;ll be glad to share my exprience in After Effects with you. in this course, I&#39;ll explore all capabilities that After Effects has in making Motion graphics and visual Effects.
after watching this course, you&#39;ll absolutely be ready to enter the world of motion graphics and visual effects.
you don&#39;t need any prior knowledge for this course and I&#39;ll teach you from introducing you to after effects to the point that you learn everything about the software.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
