<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Photography &amp; Video on </title>
    <link>/tags/photography-video/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Photography &amp; Video on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 09:14:03 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/photography-video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pictures and Videos colorization by Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>/pictures-and-videos-colorization-by-artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 09:14:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pictures-and-videos-colorization-by-artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>How Apocalypse series and videos have been colorized?
Can we colorize all old movies such as Charli Chaplin, laurel and hardy, and so on .......

Revive the history 

 Hello and Welcome to our course .... First Automated Colorization and Color grading course in the WORLD!
This course presents amazing techniques to colorize and upscale any noisy old black and Wight pictures, frames or videos based on artificial intelligence, machine learning, and deep learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Architectural, Night &amp; HDR Photography</title>
      <link>/mastering-architectural-night-hdr-photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 16:04:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mastering-architectural-night-hdr-photography/</guid>
      <description>Architectural photography is one of the important branches of photography. In this course, you will learn how to shoot architectural photos, process them, and important tips &amp;amp; tricks.  There are many ways to shoot architecture photography and the method you choose will be based on how your images will be used. Are they for a realtor, a home builder, a commercial developer, or maybe an architect? Depending on who you are shooting for will depend on how you approach the photography and this course covers many methods that can be applied to each type of client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Guide to InVideo and InVideo Video Creation</title>
      <link>/complete-guide-to-invideo-and-invideo-video-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 18:00:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-guide-to-invideo-and-invideo-video-creation/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Complete Guide to InVideo and InVideo Video Creation!
The only course you will need to start with InVideo, one of the best online video creators and editors on the market. With InVideo you can create short-form and long-form content for any social media platform, including Instagram, YouTube, TikTok, Facebook, Pinterest, and many more. In addition to all that you are also able to transform your blog posts into full-length videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Adobe Lightroom Megacourse: Beginner to Expert</title>
      <link>/complete-adobe-lightroom-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 13:19:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-adobe-lightroom-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to edit your own photos? Maybe you want to enhance a photo and show it off on social media, or perhaps you want to fix the imperfections in an otherwise perfect snapshot of your life. Whether you’re a casual photographer or hoping to make a career out of it, editing photos isn’t only for the pros. You can take any photo from drab to fab with just a few tweaks and adjustments - and we’re here to teach you how.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Lightroom Masterclass - Beginner to Expert</title>
      <link>/adobe-lightroom-masterclass-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 20:22:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/adobe-lightroom-masterclass-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Adobe Lightroom is a powerful, intuitive program used for enhancing, organizing, and editing your photos. Users can render enhancements on everything from smartphone photos to raw DSLR images. This course explores many of the exciting features this program offers. Take a look at just a brief summary of the course content below. Section 1: Introduction Students are provided with an overview of learning objectives and some of the key features that the course will explore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Academy - The Complete 2021 Guide Beginner to Pro</title>
      <link>/youtube-academy-the-complete-2021-guide-beginner-to-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 20:22:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/youtube-academy-the-complete-2021-guide-beginner-to-pro/</guid>
      <description>Everything you need to know from discovering what to make your channel about, planning, branding, filming, equipment; how to upload; how to use the best tags and titles to get more views, how to get more subscribers, get monitized; what makes the most money; and how to review your analytics to grow. The complete guide from A-Z for everything you need to know, all in one place for YouTube. Become a YouTube creator today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Colorization -  Colorize Old Photos Using a Free Tool</title>
      <link>/photo-colorization-colorize-old-photos-using-a-free-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 12:05:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/photo-colorization-colorize-old-photos-using-a-free-tool/</guid>
      <description>Want to give life to your old black &amp;amp; white photographs?

Then it&#39;s time for you to learn Photo Colorization!

In the span of one hour, you will learn a quick &amp;amp; simple method of coloring black &amp;amp; white images. Best of all, you will be using a free tool so you don&#39;t have to make any investment (other than your time of course). You just need to focus your time in quickly learning on how colorize old photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Grading and Video Editing with Davinci Resolve 17</title>
      <link>/color-grading-and-video-editing-with-davinci-resolve-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 10:31:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/color-grading-and-video-editing-with-davinci-resolve-17/</guid>
      <description>DaVinci Resolve 16 Beginners Course 
DaVinci Resolve 16 is a free professional video editing application used by professionals and amateurs. It’s easy and simple to use. It provides you with simple to use yet powerful tools to edit your videos and achieve high quality production.
This course is for beginners. You do not need any previous knowledge in DaVinci Resolve 17 or video editing experience.
You will dive straightaway into creating your first video and add music, graphics, text and couple of transitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Lightroom For Beginners : Complete Photo/Image Editing</title>
      <link>/adobe-lightroom-for-beginners-complete-photo/image-editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/adobe-lightroom-for-beginners-complete-photo/image-editing/</guid>
      <description>=== students&#39; reviews&#39; regarding this course ===
&#34;This course is great for Lightroom beginners. Although I do have some experience with Lightroom, I needed a course like this because of its simplicity and details covered. All the modules covered are important for any editing process. Would recommend this to every photographer out there starting out. Thank you for the course!&#34; -- Ansh Agrawal
&#34;It was informative and interactive&#34; -- Bamidele Joshua</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Correction &amp; Grading with Adobe Premiere Pro 2021</title>
      <link>/color-correction-grading-with-adobe-premiere-pro-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/color-correction-grading-with-adobe-premiere-pro-2021/</guid>
      <description>This complete course will take you to the essentials of color correction with the Lumetri color tools inside Premiere Pro. You will learn different techniques while also understanding how color philosophy works. (Footage Included)
We&#39;ll fly together through this wonderful world of colors. And on the end you will be able to fix color issues and take your shots to a higher professional level.
What will I learn?
You will learn a complete essential training of color correction and grading in Premiere Pro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Editing with Adobe Premiere Pro CC 2021 for Beginners</title>
      <link>/video-editing-with-adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2021-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/video-editing-with-adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2021-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Start your Video Editing Career with Premiere Pro CC 2021 and create professional productions for Film, TV and Youtube!
Adobe Premiere Pro is the best video editing program you can use &amp;amp; it&#39;s so compatible with the Adobe family which a great plus for the program and makes your workflow easy and productive. Premiere Pro is used by professionals internationally for every type of production &amp;amp; it could seem overwhelming and hard when you open it for first time but with this course within an hour you will able to do Creative video editing !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Photography Masterclass: 4 courses in 1</title>
      <link>/complete-photography-masterclass-4-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-photography-masterclass-4-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>----- Our students reviews regarding this course ------
&#34;fantastic o am learn a lot from this lecture.. I always think i know a lot about photography but when i follow this course which is so easy to understant.. now i feel i know nothing... thanks for the explanations&#34; -- Eva
&#34;It&#39;s good and straight to the point.. and covers a lot of basic aspects you might need in photography and photo editing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro 2021 Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>/adobe-premiere-pro-2021-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:42:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/adobe-premiere-pro-2021-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Edit Video but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Videos and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Premiere Pro 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Video Editing is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start Editing Videos like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Editing In Adobe Premiere Pro Mega Pack 5 Courses In 1</title>
      <link>/video-editing-in-adobe-premiere-pro-mega-pack-5-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:42:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/video-editing-in-adobe-premiere-pro-mega-pack-5-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>90% OFF for 1 month USE COUPON CODE : EARLYBIRD90 Video editing is one of the most demanding and lucrative skills of 21st century . From mobile screens , social media to theater every sector requires video editing in some form or other . Hence learning the industry standard software are a must . In this course you will learn video editing using adobe premiere pro with practical examples . And follow along pattern ensures that all changes will happen in front of your eyes .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Graphics Design and Video Editing Masterclass</title>
      <link>/complete-graphics-design-and-video-editing-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-graphics-design-and-video-editing-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Hi There,
My name is Stephen Koel Soren and I am a graphics and web expert. This is a combo course for learning adobe premiere pro cc and adobe photoshop for learning video editing and graphics design. If you are absolute beginner or if you never open Adobe Premiere pro cc and Adobe Photoshop cc before than this is a perfect class for you. This is a beginner level class so so together me you we will learn Adobe Premiere pro and Photoshop from basic to advance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GIMP 2.10 für Anfänger - Grundkurs für jeden Einsteiger!</title>
      <link>/gimp-2.10-f%C3%BCr-anf%C3%A4nger-grundkurs-f%C3%BCr-jeden-einsteiger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gimp-2.10-f%C3%BCr-anf%C3%A4nger-grundkurs-f%C3%BCr-jeden-einsteiger/</guid>
      <description>Das GNU Image Manipulation Program (GIMP) ist eine kostenlose, Photoshop ähnliche Bildbearbeitungssoftware welche Windows, Max OS und Linux unterstützt.
Okay, aber warum nutzt es dann nicht jeder?
Selbst mit Zugriff auf viele GNU + Youtube-Tutorials ist das GIMP-Programm immer noch eine schwer zu erlernende Software.
Bis jetzt...
Mit meinem GIMP 2.10 für Anfänger - Grundkurs für jeden Einsteiger! lernt jeder, innerhalb von nur 3 Stunden, mit GIMP umzugehen und danach sein Projekt zu bearbeiten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Earn from Photography: Absolute Beginners Guide</title>
      <link>/how-to-earn-from-photography-absolute-beginners-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-earn-from-photography-absolute-beginners-guide/</guid>
      <description>=== Students&#39; Reviews&#39; Regarding This Course ===
&#34;i enjoyed the course, very educative and straight to the point.&#34; -- Muhammad Kabir Musa &#34;This course was simple and easy to listen. There are a few tips I&#39;ve not thought of when looking to earn money with photography. The bonus section was good variety as it showed some tips to editing photos. This is definitely a beginner&#39;s guide and is quite basic.&#34; -- Jessica Lam</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portrait Photography for Absolute Beginners</title>
      <link>/portrait-photography-for-absolute-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portrait-photography-for-absolute-beginners/</guid>
      <description>=== students reviews regarding this course ===
&#34;This course really helps me to improve my photography knowledge and I would like to thanks all of those who help this to be a success.&#34; -- Wijekoon
&#34;so far the course is about what i really want to learn especially about basic portrait photography. i learn a lot of new things from this course&#34; - Fadila
&#34;Good for an absolute beginner. If you have just bought a DSLR camera and don&#39;t know anything about photography, it&#39;s good way to get your feet wet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro CC Essential Video Editing Zero To Hero</title>
      <link>/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-essential-video-editing-zero-to-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-essential-video-editing-zero-to-hero/</guid>
      <description>Hi There,
My name is Stephen Koel Soren and I am a graphics and web expert. If you are absolute beginner or if you never open Adobe Premiere pro cc before than this is a perfect class for you. This is a beginner level class so so together me you we will learn Adobe Premiere pro from basic to advance. This is a project base class so you will be able to apply your learned skill in real time class project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
