<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Photography &amp; Video on </title>
    <link>/tags/photography-video/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Photography &amp; Video on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/photography-video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Portrait Photography for Absolute Beginners</title>
      <link>/portrait-photography-for-absolute-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portrait-photography-for-absolute-beginners/</guid>
      <description>=== students reviews regarding this course ===
&#34;This course really helps me to improve my photography knowledge and I would like to thanks all of those who help this to be a success.&#34; -- Wijekoon
&#34;so far the course is about what i really want to learn especially about basic portrait photography. i learn a lot of new things from this course&#34; - Fadila
&#34;Good for an absolute beginner. If you have just bought a DSLR camera and don&#39;t know anything about photography, it&#39;s good way to get your feet wet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Lightroom Masterclass - Beginner to Expert</title>
      <link>/adobe-lightroom-masterclass-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/adobe-lightroom-masterclass-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Adobe Lightroom is a powerful, intuitive program used for enhancing, organizing, and editing your photos. Users can render enhancements on everything from smartphone photos to raw DSLR images. This course explores many of the exciting features this program offers. Take a look at just a brief summary of the course content below. Section 1: Introduction 
Students are provided with an overview of learning objectives and some of the key features that the course will explore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro CC Essential Video Editing Zero To Hero</title>
      <link>/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-essential-video-editing-zero-to-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-essential-video-editing-zero-to-hero/</guid>
      <description>Hi There,
My name is Stephen Koel Soren and I am a graphics and web expert. If you are absolute beginner or if you never open Adobe Premiere pro cc before than this is a perfect class for you. This is a beginner level class so so together me you we will learn Adobe Premiere pro from basic to advance. This is a project base class so you will be able to apply your learned skill in real time class project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Correction &amp; Grading with Adobe Premiere Pro 2021</title>
      <link>/color-correction-grading-with-adobe-premiere-pro-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/color-correction-grading-with-adobe-premiere-pro-2021/</guid>
      <description>This complete course will take you to the essentials of color correction with the Lumetri color tools inside Premiere Pro. You will learn different techniques while also understanding how color philosophy works. (Footage Included)
We&#39;ll fly together through this wonderful world of colors. And on the end you will be able to fix color issues and take your shots to a higher professional level.
What will I learn?
You will learn a complete essential training of color correction and grading in Premiere Pro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Grading and Video Editing with Davinci Resolve 17</title>
      <link>/color-grading-and-video-editing-with-davinci-resolve-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/color-grading-and-video-editing-with-davinci-resolve-17/</guid>
      <description>DaVinci Resolve 16&amp;nbsp; Beginners Course 
DaVinci Resolve 16 is a free professional video editing application used by professionals and amateurs. It’s easy and simple to use. It provides you with simple to use yet powerful tools to edit your videos and achieve high quality production.
This course is for beginners. You do not need any previous knowledge in DaVinci Resolve 17 or video editing experience.
You will dive straightaway into creating your first video and add music, graphics, text and couple of transitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Adobe Lightroom Megacourse: Beginner to Expert</title>
      <link>/complete-adobe-lightroom-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-adobe-lightroom-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to edit your own photos? Maybe you want to enhance a photo and show it off on social media, or perhaps you want to fix the imperfections in an otherwise perfect snapshot of your life. Whether you’re a casual photographer or hoping to make a career out of it, editing photos isn’t only for the pros. You can take any photo from drab to fab with just a few tweaks and adjustments - and we’re here to teach you how.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Editing with Adobe Premiere Pro CC 2021 for Beginners</title>
      <link>/video-editing-with-adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2021-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/video-editing-with-adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2021-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Start your Video Editing Career with Premiere Pro CC 2021 and create professional productions for Film, TV and Youtube!
Adobe Premiere Pro is the best video editing program you can use &amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;it&#39;s so compatible with the Adobe family which a great plus for the program and makes your workflow easy and productive. Premiere Pro is used by professionals internationally&amp;nbsp;for every type of production &amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;it could seem overwhelming and hard when you open it for first time but with this course within an hour you will able to do Creative video editing !</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
