<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Photography &amp; Video on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/photography-video/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Photography &amp; Video on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/photography-video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Videoscribe Whiteboard Animations : MasterClass With Project</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/videoscribe-whiteboard-animations-masterclass-with-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/videoscribe-whiteboard-animations-masterclass-with-project/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our Videoscribe Whiteboard Animations: MasterClass With Project course!
This course is designed for VideoScribe v3.7, to ensure you are using the most up-to-date version we recommend updating your app from your Sparkol account page.
My name is Chetan Pujari. I’ve been creating videos and teaching courses on how to get the most out of VideoScribe for over 5 years.
In this course, I’ve captured our top hints and tips so you can quickly learn how easy it is to create engaging whiteboard animation videos using VideoScribe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filmora 11/X/9:  Zero to Hero in Video Editing (2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/filmora-11/x/9-zero-to-hero-in-video-editing-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/filmora-11/x/9-zero-to-hero-in-video-editing-2022/</guid>
      <description>Who Is This For?
This course was made for YouTubers, filmmakers, Vloggers, professional video editors, who want to edit for others like freelance. Content creators for YouTube and social media often want a simplified workflow, and Filmora certainly provides that kind of editing experience. But does that mean it’s something experienced editors should ignore? Not necessarily. Filmora9 does not have the features of professional software like Premiere, Final Cut, Media Composer, or Resolve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create awesome videos from text using Pictory</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-awesome-videos-from-text-using-pictory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-awesome-videos-from-text-using-pictory/</guid>
      <description>In the creation and grading of visual or video content and brand stories, artificial intelligence and machine learning have become increasingly useful nowadays.
Can Artificial Intelligence (AI) help in video creation?
The answer is a big &#34;Yes&#34;. You can use AI to generate a video from your script or blog post content within minutes thanks to a powerful new-age tool that has emerged called &#34;Pictory&#34;. In this mind-blowing online training course on Udemy titled &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical Photography for Absolute Beginners: 9 Courses in 1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/practical-photography-for-absolute-beginners-9-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/practical-photography-for-absolute-beginners-9-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>=== Students reviews on this course ===
&#34;I had a great love for this course. Through this photography course, I learned so many new things that I never heard of. The teaching method is very simple and beautiful which can be learned easily by anyone.&#34; -- Naveen Yes
&#34;Awesome all are understanding and point to point&#34; -- Naman Verma
&#34;It was great course. I now have a better understanding as to which camera to purchase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Correction &amp; Grading with Adobe Premiere Pro 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/color-correction-grading-with-adobe-premiere-pro-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/color-correction-grading-with-adobe-premiere-pro-2022/</guid>
      <description>This complete course will take you to the essentials of color correction with the Lumetri color tools inside Premiere Pro. You will learn different techniques while also understanding how color philosophy works. (Footage Included)
We&#39;ll fly together through this wonderful world of colors. And on the end you will be able to fix color issues and take your shots to a higher professional level.
What will I learn?
You will learn a complete essential training of color correction and grading in Premiere Pro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Editing with Adobe Premiere Pro CC 2022 for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-editing-with-adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2022-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-editing-with-adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2022-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Start your Video Editing Career with Premiere Pro CC 2022 and create professional productions for Film, TV and Youtube!!
Adobe Premiere Pro is the best video editing program you can use &amp;amp; it&#39;s so compatible with the Adobe family which a great plus for the program and makes your workflow easy and productive. Premiere Pro is used by professionals internationally for every type of production &amp;amp; it could seem overwhelming and hard when you open it for first time but with this course within an hour you will able to do Creative video editing !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Color Grading and Video Editing with Davinci Resolve 17</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/color-grading-and-video-editing-with-davinci-resolve-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/color-grading-and-video-editing-with-davinci-resolve-17/</guid>
      <description>DaVinci Resolve 16 Beginners Course DaVinci Resolve 16 is a free professional video editing application used by professionals and amateurs. It’s easy and simple to use. It provides you with simple to use yet powerful tools to edit your videos and achieve high quality production.
This course is for beginners. You do not need any previous knowledge in DaVinci Resolve 17 or video editing experience.
You will dive straightaway into creating your first video and add music, graphics, text and couple of transitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Lightroom For Beginners : Complete Photo/Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-lightroom-for-beginners-complete-photo/image-editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:33:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-lightroom-for-beginners-complete-photo/image-editing/</guid>
      <description>=== students&#39; reviews&#39; regarding this course ===
&#34;This course is great for Lightroom beginners. Although I do have some experience with Lightroom, I needed a course like this because of its simplicity and details covered. All the modules covered are important for any editing process. Would recommend this to every photographer out there starting out. Thank you for the course!&#34; -- Ansh Agrawal
&#34;It was informative and interactive&#34; -- Bamidele Joshua</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being Independent Movie Director</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/being-independent-movie-director/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/being-independent-movie-director/</guid>
      <description>We all know how hard it is to become a film director. We all know the saying that only one in a million makes it. To put it simply, the moment you will decide to become a movie director your life won&#39;t be the same anymore. Quite literally. You&#39;ll need to go above and beyond not only to make your films but also to maintain that life you&#39;re living. Being a movie director comes with enormous outside pressure, risks, challenges, and constant obstacles that you will have to battle on daily basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Edit A Feature Film By Yourself</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-edit-a-feature-film-by-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-edit-a-feature-film-by-yourself/</guid>
      <description>By independent director, producer and screenwriter Hank Orion. In this course we will dive deep into editing tips and techniques for independent films. From raw footage to final master and more. We will talk about stuff they don&#39;t teach you at film school. Some of the topics we will cover in this course are:
Preparing Your Footage To Edit
Importing Files To Premiere Pro
Creating Closing Credits Roll
Creating Film Opening Sequence</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Make Independent Feature Film On A Budget</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-make-independent-feature-film-on-a-budget/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-make-independent-feature-film-on-a-budget/</guid>
      <description>I never went to film school, I had to learn everything I know about filmmaking by making mistakes, on my own. And I will never regret I chose that route. Because for the past five years of my life I learned how to not just be a better filmmaker, but also how to make feature films by myself without relying on other people, make films with whatever equipment I have at my disposal be it an expensive cinema camera, an iPhone or even a GoPro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Produce A Low Budget Independent Feature Film!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-produce-a-low-budget-independent-feature-film/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-produce-a-low-budget-independent-feature-film/</guid>
      <description>When I was younger and decided to become a filmmaker I decided to come to London and study film at the university. Six months into my course I quit university when I realized that the information provided there was not sufficient for me to make a film. I was young, broke, and all I had was a dream, all I needed was the information and guidance.
As times changed, I had to adapt to constantly changing technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro 2022 Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-2022-ultimate-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-2022-ultimate-guide/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone and welcome to Adobe Premiere Pro 2022 Ultimate Guide.
In this video, we&#39;re going to go over a course overview of what we&#39;re going to be learning throughout the course.
So in Section two, we&#39;re going to be covering creative cloud plans.
So we&#39;ll cover individuals, business students and teachers and schools and universities.
Then we&#39;ll learn how to set up a free creative cloud account.
Next, we&#39;ll work on Adobe Creative Cloud Web and learn how to install Adobe Premiere Pro 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movavi Video Editor Guide - Video Editing for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/movavi-video-editor-guide-video-editing-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/movavi-video-editor-guide-video-editing-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Imagine being able to edit videos like a pro. Imagine editing them with only two clicks, no need for overlays, transitions or music. Video editing is kind of complicated. Or is it?
Movavi video editor is a simple and powerful video editing software that will make your video magic happen. It can be used to edit and convert videos, create 3D effects, stabilize shaky footage, add audio tracks to your video, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Earn from Photography: Absolute Beginners Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-earn-from-photography-absolute-beginners-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-earn-from-photography-absolute-beginners-guide/</guid>
      <description>=== Students&#39; Reviews&#39; Regarding This Course ===
&#34;i enjoyed the course, very educative and straight to the point.&#34; -- Muhammad Kabir Musa &#34;This course was simple and easy to listen. There are a few tips I&#39;ve not thought of when looking to earn money with photography. The bonus section was good variety as it showed some tips to editing photos. This is definitely a beginner&#39;s guide and is quite basic.&#34; -- Jessica Lam</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Editing Mastery With Camtasia In Hindi/Urdu 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-editing-mastery-with-camtasia-in-hindi/urdu-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 20:12:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-editing-mastery-with-camtasia-in-hindi/urdu-2022/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to learn Camtasia to edit your videos like a pro and produce professional videos for your courses or a youtube channel or social media. (All my Udemy courses are edited on this software &amp;amp; I am showing how I do it) I have recorded/edited thousands of hours of videos in Camtasia and you will learn from my experience where you only need to spend only 2 hours of your life to master this software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portrait Photography for Absolute Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/portrait-photography-for-absolute-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/portrait-photography-for-absolute-beginners/</guid>
      <description>=== students reviews regarding this course ===
&#34;This course really helps me to improve my photography knowledge and I would like to thanks all of those who help this to be a success.&#34; -- Wijekoon
&#34;so far the course is about what i really want to learn especially about basic portrait photography. i learn a lot of new things from this course&#34; - Fadila
&#34;Good for an absolute beginner. If you have just bought a DSLR camera and don&#39;t know anything about photography, it&#39;s good way to get your feet wet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Beautiful Photo and Video Slideshows with Animoto</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-beautiful-photo-and-video-slideshows-with-animoto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-beautiful-photo-and-video-slideshows-with-animoto/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this superb and impressive Udemy course focussed on &#34;Create Beautiful Photo and Video Slideshows with Animoto&#34; in 2022.
Take charge and learn quick, amazing and easy methods for creating and editing powerful web and social media promo videos like a professional in the fastest time possible with the power of Animoto.
Whether you are an entrepreneur, employee, content creator, teacher, author, or social media enthusiast, over the last few years it has become extremely important and of course - CRUCIAL to know how to do a little bit of everything online, including how to make your brand stand out with videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to VLOG 2022 : Complete Beginners Course &#43;YouTube</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-vlog-2022-complete-beginners-course-youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 20:03:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-vlog-2022-complete-beginners-course-youtube/</guid>
      <description>This course has everything you need to know about vlogging, from a current vlogger! How to film; plan a video, what&#39;s needed in a successful video, come with me filming and editing as well as all the extras of how to create a YouTube channel and your branding.
I have my own channel, i&#39;ve had two actually and I am constantly testing what works and what doesn&#39;t online, trends, video styles, lengths to see which are more successful, which get more views, subscribers and make more money for my channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Architectural, Night &amp; HDR Photography</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mastering-architectural-night-hdr-photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 20:40:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mastering-architectural-night-hdr-photography/</guid>
      <description>Architectural photography is one of the important branches of photography. In this course, you will learn how to shoot architectural photos, process them, and important tips &amp;amp; tricks. There are many ways to shoot architecture photography and the method you choose will be based on how your images will be used. Are they for a realtor, a home builder, a commercial developer, or maybe an architect? Depending on who you are shooting for will depend on how you approach the photography and this course covers many methods that can be applied to each type of client.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Lightroom Masterclass - Beginner to Expert</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-lightroom-masterclass-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 15:08:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-lightroom-masterclass-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Adobe Lightroom is a powerful, intuitive program used for enhancing, organizing, and editing your photos. Users can render enhancements on everything from smartphone photos to raw DSLR images. This course explores many of the exciting features this program offers. Take a look at just a brief summary of the course content below. Section 1: Introduction Students are provided with an overview of learning objectives and some of the key features that the course will explore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro CC 2022: Video Editing for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2022-video-editing-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 15:08:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2022-video-editing-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>This course is a one-stop shop that has everything you need to become a confident editor inside Premiere Pro.
If you&#39;ve taken a quick look at Adobe Premiere Pro and are completely overwhelmed by the features and have no clue how to start editing your first video, you have come to the right course.
In this complete guide to the Adobe Premiere Pro video editing course, you&#39;ll not only learn all of the editing tools available in Premiere Pro but also how to edit with the mindset of a professional editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DaVinci Resolve 17: Video editing course for beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/davinci-resolve-17-video-editing-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 15:08:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/davinci-resolve-17-video-editing-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>In this course I&#39;ll teach you how to use DaVinci Resolve. In this course I included only the most important and main tools from DaVinci, to teach anyone (you need 0 experience) how to edit a good video. I guess you&#39;ll learn the most on your own, but first you need to know how to use such a magical tool as DaVinci, that&#39;s what I&#39;m going to teach you in this course (from making simple cuts to transitions / visual effects and even color grading) all of that in this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro CC Essential Video Editing Zero To Hero</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-essential-video-editing-zero-to-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 20:40:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-essential-video-editing-zero-to-hero/</guid>
      <description>Hi There,
My name is Stephen Koel Soren and I am a graphics and web expert. If you are absolute beginner or if you never open Adobe Premiere pro cc before than this is a perfect class for you. This is a beginner level class so so together me you we will learn Adobe Premiere pro from basic to advance. This is a project base class so you will be able to apply your learned skill in real time class project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wedding Photography Complete Guide For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/wedding-photography-complete-guide-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/wedding-photography-complete-guide-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to start a career or business in Wedding Photography? Do you enjoy capturing moments in a lifetime? Then you have come to the right place. In this course we will show you how we take photos at a wedding, How we freeze that moment in time and make it accessible for the couple forever.
Wedding Photography has become an in demand skill. Weddings nowadays are not complete without wedding photographers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro 2022 Projects</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-2022-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-2022-projects/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Edit Video but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Videos and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Premiere Pro 2022 Projects is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Video Editing is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start Editing Videos like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TikTok pop-up editing tool----CapCut</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tiktok-pop-up-editing-tool----capcut/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 21:29:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tiktok-pop-up-editing-tool----capcut/</guid>
      <description>In this video editing course you will learn how to edit videos from raw clips to TikTok pop-up videos.we have covered all main features of TikTok&#39;s pop-up video editing like cutting, trimming, transitions, enhancing, speed up and so on.
What can you expect learning our course?
1,Master CapCut and be CONFIDENT Editing Your Own TikTok Videos
2,Edit an entire video from beginning to end, using the simplest and most practical technique</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aprende Photoshop de 0 a 100</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprende-photoshop-de-0-a-100/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprende-photoshop-de-0-a-100/</guid>
      <description>Bienvenido al curso de photoshop de 0 a 100 sin rodeos. Aprenderás a tocar todas las areas del software con ejemplos directos y que prácticas, area de las selecciones, transformaciones, pinceles, retoques fotográficos y aspectos avanzados de las capas como son las capas de ajuste y los blending modes. Que es photoshop??:
Adobe Photoshop es un editor de fotografías desarrollado por Adobe Systems Incorporated. Usado principalmente para el retoque de fotografías y gráficos, su nombre en español significa &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get 5 Million Free Images and Videos for Commercial Use</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/get-5-million-free-images-and-videos-for-commercial-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/get-5-million-free-images-and-videos-for-commercial-use/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the sixth course in Term 3 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Everybody loves free photos and videos, for sure and this is a huge requirement in the marketing industry. This mind-blowing yet innovative course focuses on &#34;Get 5 Million Free Images and Videos for Commercial Use&#34; and is created by Digital Marketing Legend Srinidhi Ranganathan with the help of Civil Engineering MasterMind Saranya Srinidhi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro CC 2017 - The Complete Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2017-the-complete-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 10:44:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2017-the-complete-guide/</guid>
      <description>Why Learn Premiere Pro?
Premiere Pro is one of the leading video editing software applications. It is an important application to know how to use for anyone wanting to work in television, video or film industries. Learning Premiere Pro is also useful for those editing video as a hobby or for personal use, as it can be used to create videos ranging from highly professional using high-definition footage to more basic videos captured with a camera phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures and Videos colorization by Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pictures-and-videos-colorization-by-artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 14:54:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pictures-and-videos-colorization-by-artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>How Apocalypse series and videos have been colorized?
Can we colorize all old movies such as Charli Chaplin, laurel and hardy, and so on .......
Revive the history Hello and Welcome to our course .... First Automated Colorization and Color grading course in the WORLD!
This course presents amazing techniques to colorize and upscale any noisy old black and Wight pictures, frames or videos based on artificial intelligence, machine learning, and deep learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Photography : 21 Courses in 1 [Beginner to Expert]</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-photography-21-courses-in-1-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 16:23:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-photography-21-courses-in-1-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Our students&#39; reviews regarding this course --
&#34;This course has been broken down to explain some difficult photography lingo and setting into plain easy to understand English and the teacher goes nice and slow so you don&#39;t feel bombarded with tons of info at once!&#34; -- Christi Guimar
&#34;I found this course really helpful and I learned more about some of the technical aspects that will help me improve my photography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagram Photo: Make Your Instagram Look Pretty in 5 Steps</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/instagram-photo-make-your-instagram-look-pretty-in-5-steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/instagram-photo-make-your-instagram-look-pretty-in-5-steps/</guid>
      <description>If you are into beautiful photos – you’re in a right place. Here we will talk about everything you need to make a truly pretty Instagram profile (Instagram Photography). And this time it won’t be someone else you so frequently see on Instagram, this is going to be you!
This is a great opportunity to learn why do these bloggers and those cafés have really pretty profiles (Instagram Photography) and also learn how to make one!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videoscribe Whiteboard Animations Masterclass for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/videoscribe-whiteboard-animations-masterclass-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 15:38:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/videoscribe-whiteboard-animations-masterclass-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome guys my name is Anwer Khan and I will be your instructor throughout this course. In this course, I will talk straight to the point. Therefore, we will cover more in less time. Videoscribe for Beginners course!
VideoScribe is software for creating whiteboard animations automatically. In order to use videoscribe you don&#39;t need any graphic designing skills. Videoscribe is easy to learn, quick and inexpensive. You can create great animated videos in no time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Streamlabs OBS von A bis Z der exklusive Komplettkurs</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/streamlabs-obs-von-a-bis-z-der-exklusive-komplettkurs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:36:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/streamlabs-obs-von-a-bis-z-der-exklusive-komplettkurs/</guid>
      <description>Über mich
Mein Name ist Andreas und ich befasse mich seit ca. 3 Jahren aktiv mit Streamlabs OBS. Ich habe mich sehr intensiv mit der Streaming Software auseinander gesetzt und vielen anderen auch schon erfolgreich geholfen Streamlabs OBS einzurichten. Meine Erfahrungen mit der Stream Plattform Twitch ist auch ziemlich hoch, weil ich auch selber Twitch Streamer bin und die Szene aktiv verfolge. Genau deswegen kenne ich auch die größten Probleme und die meist gestellten Fragen, die in diesem Kurs alle abgedeckt werden mit 115 Lektionen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Guide to InVideo and InVideo Video Creation</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-guide-to-invideo-and-invideo-video-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-guide-to-invideo-and-invideo-video-creation/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Complete Guide to InVideo and InVideo Video Creation!
The only course you will need to start with InVideo, one of the best online video creators and editors on the market. With InVideo you can create short-form and long-form content for any social media platform, including Instagram, YouTube, TikTok, Facebook, Pinterest, and many more. In addition to all that you are also able to transform your blog posts into full-length videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Editing In Adobe Premiere Pro Mega Pack 5 Courses In 1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-editing-in-adobe-premiere-pro-mega-pack-5-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-editing-in-adobe-premiere-pro-mega-pack-5-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>90% OFF for 1 month USE COUPON CODE : EARLYBIRD90 Video editing is one of the most demanding and lucrative skills of 21st century . From mobile screens , social media to theater every sector requires video editing in some form or other . Hence learning the industry standard software are a must . In this course you will learn video editing using adobe premiere pro with practical examples . And follow along pattern ensures that all changes will happen in front of your eyes .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Adobe Lightroom Megacourse: Beginner to Expert</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-adobe-lightroom-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-adobe-lightroom-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to edit your own photos? Maybe you want to enhance a photo and show it off on social media, or perhaps you want to fix the imperfections in an otherwise perfect snapshot of your life. Whether you’re a casual photographer or hoping to make a career out of it, editing photos isn’t only for the pros. You can take any photo from drab to fab with just a few tweaks and adjustments - and we’re here to teach you how.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals Of Photography</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentals-of-photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentals-of-photography/</guid>
      <description>If you just bought a DSLR, a mirrorless or just a point and shoot camera, and are wondering what the next step should be, enrol in the most comprehensive course to learn the basics and fundamentals of photography with World Photographers Club.
Learn everything about your camera, which lenses are good for you, basic concepts like shutter speed, aperture, ISO, white balance, focal length, and more, and see how they affect your photography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Academy - The Complete 2021 Guide Beginner to Pro</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-academy-the-complete-2021-guide-beginner-to-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 20:22:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-academy-the-complete-2021-guide-beginner-to-pro/</guid>
      <description>Everything you need to know from discovering what to make your channel about, planning, branding, filming, equipment; how to upload; how to use the best tags and titles to get more views, how to get more subscribers, get monitized; what makes the most money; and how to review your analytics to grow. The complete guide from A-Z for everything you need to know, all in one place for YouTube. Become a YouTube creator today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Colorization -  Colorize Old Photos Using a Free Tool</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/photo-colorization-colorize-old-photos-using-a-free-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 12:05:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/photo-colorization-colorize-old-photos-using-a-free-tool/</guid>
      <description>Want to give life to your old black &amp;amp; white photographs?
Then it&#39;s time for you to learn Photo Colorization!
In the span of one hour, you will learn a quick &amp;amp; simple method of coloring black &amp;amp; white images. Best of all, you will be using a free tool so you don&#39;t have to make any investment (other than your time of course). You just need to focus your time in quickly learning on how colorize old photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Photography Masterclass: 4 courses in 1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-photography-masterclass-4-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-photography-masterclass-4-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>----- Our students reviews regarding this course ------
&#34;fantastic o am learn a lot from this lecture.. I always think i know a lot about photography but when i follow this course which is so easy to understant.. now i feel i know nothing... thanks for the explanations&#34; -- Eva
&#34;It&#39;s good and straight to the point.. and covers a lot of basic aspects you might need in photography and photo editing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Graphics Design and Video Editing Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-graphics-design-and-video-editing-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-graphics-design-and-video-editing-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Hi There,
My name is Stephen Koel Soren and I am a graphics and web expert. This is a combo course for learning adobe premiere pro cc and adobe photoshop for learning video editing and graphics design. If you are absolute beginner or if you never open Adobe Premiere pro cc and Adobe Photoshop cc before than this is a perfect class for you. This is a beginner level class so so together me you we will learn Adobe Premiere pro and Photoshop from basic to advance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GIMP 2.10 für Anfänger - Grundkurs für jeden Einsteiger!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gimp-2.10-f%C3%BCr-anf%C3%A4nger-grundkurs-f%C3%BCr-jeden-einsteiger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gimp-2.10-f%C3%BCr-anf%C3%A4nger-grundkurs-f%C3%BCr-jeden-einsteiger/</guid>
      <description>Das GNU Image Manipulation Program (GIMP) ist eine kostenlose, Photoshop ähnliche Bildbearbeitungssoftware welche Windows, Max OS und Linux unterstützt.
Okay, aber warum nutzt es dann nicht jeder?
Selbst mit Zugriff auf viele GNU + Youtube-Tutorials ist das GIMP-Programm immer noch eine schwer zu erlernende Software.
Bis jetzt...
Mit meinem GIMP 2.10 für Anfänger - Grundkurs für jeden Einsteiger! lernt jeder, innerhalb von nur 3 Stunden, mit GIMP umzugehen und danach sein Projekt zu bearbeiten.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
