<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Communication on </title>
    <link>/tags/communication/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Communication on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 13:19:24 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/communication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Persuasive Writing Ft. Two Forbes Contributors &amp; Copywriters</title>
      <link>/persuasive-writing-ft.-two-forbes-contributors-copywriters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 13:19:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/persuasive-writing-ft.-two-forbes-contributors-copywriters/</guid>
      <description>What has the power to spark revolutions, empower people, express thoughts, emotions, love, hate, and fear, and is only bound by the limits of our imagination? – Words. Words are undoubtedly one of the most powerful tools that mankind possesses. However, mastering the art of articulating thoughts into meaningful written expressions, is no simple undertaking. If done correctly, words can be used as a mechanism of persuasion. Words can be used to further career goals, relationships, business goals, and just about any other facet of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management Consulting Presentation Essential Training</title>
      <link>/management-consulting-presentation-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/management-consulting-presentation-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>In today&#39;s job market, you are only as good as your presentation skills. As the competition for high-level consulting and management positions becomes increasingly cutthroat, you need a powerful way to make your message stand out from the rest.
My name is John Burress and I&#39;m excited to introduce you to the McKinsey presentation system. During my time as a corporate strategist, I&#39;ve used McKinsey presentations to significantly grow many leading businesses using the same techniques you&#39;ll learn under my instruction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Steps Into Public Speaking</title>
      <link>/first-steps-into-public-speaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:28:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/first-steps-into-public-speaking/</guid>
      <description>First Steps into Public Speaking
Do you get nervous when presenting at company meetings?
Do you find it hard to make conversation at gatherings and social events?
Do you lock up in awkward social situations?
If so, this course is just for you!
It’s aimed at anybody who wants to improve their speaking skills in informal or formal situations.
We’ll give you the confidence and the skills to interact with others, and to speak in front of small or large groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Culture</title>
      <link>/business-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/business-culture/</guid>
      <description>About The Course
In a world of ever-lowering employee engagement levels, ever-reducing staff retention levels and ever-increasing levels of staff turnover, combined with higher levels of employee expectations, the need for a culture that creates, supports and enables committed, motivated and effective people has never been so crucial.
This course takes you through proven processes to establish and embed the culture you want to live and the behaviours you want to see from your people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
