<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Communication on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/communication/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Communication on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/communication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mastering The Interview</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/mastering-the-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/mastering-the-interview/</guid>
      <description>The interview is one of the key elements of the job search process.
As with any skill, we can get better at it with preparation and practice. So in this course, you will explore how to prepare for an interview and become familiar with the types of questions to expect, as well as the questions you should think about asking.
Some people are natural at selling themselves to hiring managers. Others aren’t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEO &amp; Copywriting Course as PROJECT &amp; FUN: 40 DAYS Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/seo-copywriting-course-as-project-fun-40-days-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/seo-copywriting-course-as-project-fun-40-days-challenge/</guid>
      <description>SEO, local SEO, copywriting, WordPress website creation &amp;amp; content marketing course made as PROJECT &amp;amp; FUN. Please, accept our 30 days challenge. Enjoy animations, over my shoulder explanations, screen recordings, assignments &amp;amp; interactive quizzes. Learn everything you need to know to become a professional SEO, local SEO, copywriting &amp;amp; WordPress websites consultant, and start a new career online, land your dream job, or boost your local or e-commerce business.
You’ll achieve mastery FAST with our 3-part FAST LEARN course structure - Join over 600,000+ satisfied students by enrolling and enjoy THE EASIEST WAY TO GO FROM BEGINNER TO PRO:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conflict Resolution for Co-Workers</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/conflict-resolution-for-co-workers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/conflict-resolution-for-co-workers/</guid>
      <description>CO-WORKERS OR CONFLICT WORKERS?
Many people believe that conflicts, in the corporate world, are a rare occasion.
In fact, they are a lot more common than you would think.
They can occur with managers, subordinates, co-workers, or even external stakeholders such as clients or partners.
Naturally, they can occur due to a variety of reasons, from personal issues to business problems, and they can range in severity.
But one thing is for sure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Persuasive Writing Ft. Two Forbes Contributors &amp; Copywriters</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/persuasive-writing-ft.-two-forbes-contributors-copywriters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/persuasive-writing-ft.-two-forbes-contributors-copywriters/</guid>
      <description>What has the power to spark revolutions, empower people, express thoughts, emotions, love, hate, and fear, and is only bound by the limits of our imagination? – Words. Words are undoubtedly one of the most powerful tools that mankind possesses. However, mastering the art of articulating thoughts into meaningful written expressions, is no simple undertaking. If done correctly, words can be used as a mechanism of persuasion. Words can be used to further career goals, relationships, business goals, and just about any other facet of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified LinkedIn Marketing Professional | CPD Accredited</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/certified-linkedin-marketing-professional-cpd-accredited/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/certified-linkedin-marketing-professional-cpd-accredited/</guid>
      <description>Two LinkedIn Marketing Certificates for the Price of One! Finish your Udemy course and Contact us to get your Continuing Professional Development (CPD) Certificate! Check out &#34;This is How You Earn Your CPD Accrdeited Certificate!&#34; Lecture for more information!

LinkedIn Marketing has become the most popular method for success-hungry marketers to make the most from their promoting efforts. If not given sufficient importance to, it can prove disastrous for your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Steps Into Public Speaking</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/first-steps-into-public-speaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/first-steps-into-public-speaking/</guid>
      <description>First Steps into Public Speaking
Do you get nervous when presenting at company meetings?
Do you find it hard to make conversation at gatherings and social events?
Do you lock up in awkward social situations?
If so, this course is just for you!
It’s aimed at anybody who wants to improve their speaking skills in informal or formal situations.
We’ll give you the confidence and the skills to interact with others, and to speak in front of small or large groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management Consulting Presentation Essential Training</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/management-consulting-presentation-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/management-consulting-presentation-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>In today&#39;s job market, you are only as good as your presentation skills. As the competition for high-level consulting and management positions becomes increasingly cutthroat, you need a powerful way to make your message stand out from the rest.
My name is John Burress and I&#39;m excited to introduce you to the McKinsey presentation system. During my time as a corporate strategist, I&#39;ve used McKinsey presentations to significantly grow many leading businesses using the same techniques you&#39;ll learn under my instruction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Culture</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/business-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/business-culture/</guid>
      <description>About The Course
In a world of ever-lowering employee engagement levels, ever-reducing staff retention levels and ever-increasing levels of staff turnover, combined with higher levels of employee expectations, the need for a culture that creates, supports and enables committed, motivated and effective people has never been so crucial.
This course takes you through proven processes to establish and embed the culture you want to live and the behaviours you want to see from your people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
