<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Communication on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/communication/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Communication on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/communication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Speakers 3.0 | Aprendiendo hablar en público</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/speakers-3.0-aprendiendo-hablar-en-p%C3%BAblico/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/speakers-3.0-aprendiendo-hablar-en-p%C3%BAblico/</guid>
      <description>Es muy probable que haya existido la oratoria, de una forma u otra, desde que hay personas. Pero la mayoría de los expertos en oratoria que se dedican a hablar en público en la comunicación empresarial, remontan los orígenes de la oratoria moderna a la antigua Grecia y Roma.
Por supuesto, esas sociedades no tenían presentaciones de diapositivas, pero sí tenían la necesidad de hablar en público. Por ello, desarrollaron métodos para hacerlo que todavía se estudian hoy en día.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEO &amp; Copywriting Course as Project &amp; Fun: 45 Days Challenge</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/seo-copywriting-course-as-project-fun-45-days-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:33:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/seo-copywriting-course-as-project-fun-45-days-challenge/</guid>
      <description>SEO, Local SEO, Copywriting, Wordpress Website Creation &amp;amp; Content Marketing Course Made As Project &amp;amp; Fun. Accept our 45 days challenge. Enjoy animations, over my shoulder explanations, screen recordings, assignments &amp;amp; interactive quizzes. Learn everything you need to know to become a professional SEO, local SEO, copywriting &amp;amp; WordPress websites consultant, and start a new career online, land your dream job, or boost your local or e-commerce business.
&#34;Very detailed with the enlightening information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Steps Into Public Speaking</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/first-steps-into-public-speaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/first-steps-into-public-speaking/</guid>
      <description>First Steps into Public Speaking
Do you get nervous when presenting at company meetings?
Do you find it hard to make conversation at gatherings and social events?
Do you lock up in awkward social situations?
If so, this course is just for you!
It’s aimed at anybody who wants to improve their speaking skills in informal or formal situations.
We’ll give you the confidence and the skills to interact with others, and to speak in front of small or large groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investing Presentations-Deliver an IPO Roadshow Presentation</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/investing-presentations-deliver-an-ipo-roadshow-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/investing-presentations-deliver-an-ipo-roadshow-presentation/</guid>
      <description>Investing Presentations. Imagine that every time you deliver your IPO road show presentation, investors are nodding their heads with understanding and agreement on your key points. Wouldn&#39;t it be nice to know that investors will perceive you as confident, competent and that they fully understand why your business has great potential upside? In this Investing Presentations: How to Deliver an IPO Road Show Presentation course you will learn the following: * How to avoid the most common blunders that plague IPO road show presentations * How to make your legal and investment banking team happy, and still give an interesting presentation * How to deal with boring slides and lots of data * How to engage and connect with your investor audience This Investing Presentations course is delivered primarily through spoken lecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation Skills -Deliver an Excellent Ceremonial Speech</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/presentation-skills-deliver-an-excellent-ceremonial-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 20:12:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/presentation-skills-deliver-an-excellent-ceremonial-speech/</guid>
      <description>Presentation Skills. Imagine yourself giving a ceremonial speech and you are the epitome of confidence, class and dignity. Wouldn&#39;t it be great to know that your next ceremonial speech will be delivered without a hitch? In this How to Deliver a Ceremonial Speech course, you will learn the following: * How to read an oath in front of people * How to control emotions on an emotional day * How to speak with confidence and dignity using excellent Presentation Skills</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking: You Can Speak to Large Audiences</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-you-can-speak-to-large-audiences/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 20:12:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-you-can-speak-to-large-audiences/</guid>
      <description>Public Speaking - Imagine yourself speaking confidently and authoritatively to hundred or even thousands of people in the audience. Wouldn&#39;t t be great to know you can speak to 1000 people just as easily and as confidently as when you speak to one person? In this How to Speak to Large Audiences Public Speaking course, you will learn the following: * How to appear relaxed and confident, even if you shaking on the inside * How to avoid the common mistakes most people make when they are speaking to a large audience * How to move around the stage effectively * How to be clearly understood and remembered This Public Speaking course is delivered primarily through spoken lectures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Body Language in the Workplace</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/body-language-in-the-workplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:16:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/body-language-in-the-workplace/</guid>
      <description>Body language in the workplace has never been more important, more complicated or more confusing. TJ Walker, a world-class presentation skills and body language expert to executives around the world, is here to guide you on how to handle yourself(and your body) in every workplace situation. Body Language in the Workplace 2018 reflects the modern reality that executives and workers need to convey comfort and authority not just in face-to-face meetings and presentations, but also in on-demand and live video communications on Skype, Facetime, YouTube, Zoom, WebEx and other platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Negotiation A-Z™: Inside Secrets from a Master Negotiator</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/negotiation-a-z-inside-secrets-from-a-master-negotiator/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:15:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/negotiation-a-z-inside-secrets-from-a-master-negotiator/</guid>
      <description>**Course Updated - April 2022**
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; COURSE REGULARLY UPDATED: NEW TIPS, MORE LESSONS &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; CERTIFIED COACH, SPEAKER AND TRAINER &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; OVER 180,000 STUDENTS IN TOTAL &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
How important is the need of negotiating? Does it impact your life and your money? Well, all that I would say is, “If you can’t negotiate effectively with people, you shouldn’t buy/sell anything for more than a few dollars.”
The reason I say this is because regardless of the type of work we do, knowing how to negotiate effectively can greatly impact our success and our satisfaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Proofreading Course: Editing and Proofreading</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-proofreading-course-editing-and-proofreading/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:15:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-proofreading-course-editing-and-proofreading/</guid>
      <description>Is it a big deal to have typos in your cover letter? YES, it is!Should you pay more attention to detail? Absolutely.Have you ever been lost in translation, couldn&#39;t see the tree for the forest!?
Then, this is the place for you. Do not mix up proofreading with editing (Copy editing).
Study to be the editor too. Develop an eye for details.
Understand the context and act accordingly.
Proofreading is the ultimate stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Write Like a Boss -Business Writing Skills for Corporates</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/write-like-a-boss-business-writing-skills-for-corporates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 16:17:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/write-like-a-boss-business-writing-skills-for-corporates/</guid>
      <description>The term business writing refers to memorandums, reports, proposals, emails, and other forms of writing used in organizations to communicate with internal or external audiences. • Business writers write to get work done. Writing like a boss means writing like a leader. Companies want leaders with power skills like written communication, email writing techniques and persuasion -- and these are the skills you&#39;ll learn about in this course!
Good writing skills in business have always been important, but in today’s age of technology, they are even more so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Account Management: A Beginner&#39;s Guide to Client Relations</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/account-management-a-beginners-guide-to-client-relations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 22:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/account-management-a-beginners-guide-to-client-relations/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever considered becoming a key account manager? Account managers develop long-term, strategic partnerships with a company&#39;s biggest (i.e., most important) customers. From closing sales and fostering relationships to strategic planning and cross-functional leadership, this position requires a diverse set of talents. Whether you&#39;re a salesperson searching for a new challenge or an account manager eager to take on bigger clientele, there&#39;s a job for you.
In this course, we&#39;ll define account manager competencies, show examples of popular skills, and offer advice on how to improve them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview Essentials - Master Your Interview Essentials Now</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/interview-essentials-master-your-interview-essentials-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 19:14:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/interview-essentials-master-your-interview-essentials-now/</guid>
      <description>Interview Essentials - Master Your Interview Essentials NowInterview Essentials To Help You Land the Job - Sell Yourself Into a Great Job with Strong Interview Essentials
If you want to get a new job, change careers, earn more money, enhance your status, and prestige, then you must excel in your job interview. This course will give you the tools and confidence to be great in your job interview. You&#39;ll learn how to tell the story of your achievements both on the job in and in your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creare Video - Impara a parlare davanti alla telecamera</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/creare-video-impara-a-parlare-davanti-alla-telecamera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 12:48:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/creare-video-impara-a-parlare-davanti-alla-telecamera/</guid>
      <description>Livello: principiante
Hai presente quando proviamo a registrare dei video e poi non ci piacciono? Oppure ci blocchiamo continuamente e non riusciamo a concludere una registrazione?
Che tu non abbiamo mai provato a registrare dei video o sei alle prime armi ti sarà sicuramente capitato di trovari in difficoltà nel parlare davanti alla telecamera. Il punto è che possiamo invece creare dei video a basso costo col tuo cellulare e distinguerci nella nostra comunicazione.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified LinkedIn Marketing Professional | CPD Accredited</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-linkedin-marketing-professional-cpd-accredited/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 15:38:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-linkedin-marketing-professional-cpd-accredited/</guid>
      <description>Two LinkedIn Marketing Certificates for the Price of One! Finish your Udemy course and Contact us to get your Continuing Professional Development (CPD) Certificate! Check out &#34;This is How You Earn Your CPD Accrdeited Certificate!&#34; Lecture for more information!
LinkedIn Marketing has become the most popular method for success-hungry marketers to make the most from their promoting efforts. If not given sufficient importance to, it can prove disastrous for your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking Emergency! Ace the Speech With Little Prep</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-emergency-ace-the-speech-with-little-prep/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-emergency-ace-the-speech-with-little-prep/</guid>
      <description>Public Speaking. Imagine standing up to give a presentation to an important audience knowing that you will look comfortable, confident and relaxed. And you know that your audience will understand you and remember all of your key points. And you did all this even though you procrastinated until the very last hour before you gave the speech.
You can give a great speech that looked like you worked on it for weeks, even though you waited until an hour before you spoke to begin preparing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remote Speaking - Pro Speaking Skills in The Coronavirus Era</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/remote-speaking-pro-speaking-skills-in-the-coronavirus-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/remote-speaking-pro-speaking-skills-in-the-coronavirus-era/</guid>
      <description>***Updated to reflect changing market conditions based on Coronavirus adaptations. Presentation Skills now need to be virtual. Imagine being able to give a keynote speech to hundreds or even thousands of key players in your industry, without having to leave your home or office. You can now deliver keynote speech, live, though Skype and other online services to conventions and audiences in other cities and continents. In this How to Give a Virtual Keynote Speech Presentation Skills course you will learn the following: *How to prepare for the technical aspects of delivering a virtual speech *How to speak to an audience you can&#39;t see *How to look comfortable, confident and relaxed when speaking virtually *How to use engage your audience and host This Presentation Skills course is delivered primarily through spoken lecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Persuasive Writing Ft. Two Forbes Contributors &amp; Copywriters</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/persuasive-writing-ft.-two-forbes-contributors-copywriters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/persuasive-writing-ft.-two-forbes-contributors-copywriters/</guid>
      <description>What has the power to spark revolutions, empower people, express thoughts, emotions, love, hate, and fear, and is only bound by the limits of our imagination? – Words. Words are undoubtedly one of the most powerful tools that mankind possesses. However, mastering the art of articulating thoughts into meaningful written expressions, is no simple undertaking. If done correctly, words can be used as a mechanism of persuasion. Words can be used to further career goals, relationships, business goals, and just about any other facet of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management Consulting Presentation Essential Training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/management-consulting-presentation-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/management-consulting-presentation-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>In today&#39;s job market, you are only as good as your presentation skills. As the competition for high-level consulting and management positions becomes increasingly cutthroat, you need a powerful way to make your message stand out from the rest.
My name is John Burress and I&#39;m excited to introduce you to the McKinsey presentation system. During my time as a corporate strategist, I&#39;ve used McKinsey presentations to significantly grow many leading businesses using the same techniques you&#39;ll learn under my instruction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storytelling: You Can learn to Tell Stories Effectively</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/storytelling-you-can-learn-to-tell-stories-effectively/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/storytelling-you-can-learn-to-tell-stories-effectively/</guid>
      <description>Storytelling is the essential ingredient in all successful speakers. Imagine yourself in front of a crowd and the audience is sitting on the edge of their seats, listening to ever detail of your story. You can become a master storyteller.
Storytelling-How to Tell Stories In this &#34;How to Tell Stories&#34; Storytelling course you will learn all the necessary elements of selecting, developing and telling stories when delivering speeches, presentations and other business-related talks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conflict Resolution for Co-Workers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/conflict-resolution-for-co-workers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/conflict-resolution-for-co-workers/</guid>
      <description>CO-WORKERS OR CONFLICT WORKERS?
Many people believe that conflicts, in the corporate world, are a rare occasion.
In fact, they are a lot more common than you would think.
They can occur with managers, subordinates, co-workers, or even external stakeholders such as clients or partners.
Naturally, they can occur due to a variety of reasons, from personal issues to business problems, and they can range in severity.
But one thing is for sure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Culture</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/business-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/business-culture/</guid>
      <description>About The Course
In a world of ever-lowering employee engagement levels, ever-reducing staff retention levels and ever-increasing levels of staff turnover, combined with higher levels of employee expectations, the need for a culture that creates, supports and enables committed, motivated and effective people has never been so crucial.
This course takes you through proven processes to establish and embed the culture you want to live and the behaviours you want to see from your people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
