<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lifestyle on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/lifestyle/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lifestyle on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:52:12 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/lifestyle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hypnosis for to visit Past life or lives Guided Hypnosis</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/hypnosis-for-to-visit-past-life-or-lives-guided-hypnosis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:52:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/hypnosis-for-to-visit-past-life-or-lives-guided-hypnosis/</guid>
      <description>5 Star Review 
Great course and appreciated the bonus, feel good lecture. Instructor is easy to listen to and very good at what he does. Thank you for offering your course which has saved me many hundreds of dollars as well as my precious time from having to schedule the allotted time with a therapist. Very comfortable watching as my time allowed and going through these sessions in the privacy of my home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decluttering - Complete Organizing Home, Office, Life Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/decluttering-complete-organizing-home-office-life-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/decluttering-complete-organizing-home-office-life-course/</guid>
      <description>Decluttering - Complete Organizing Home, Office, Life Course
Decluttering Your Life - Organization, Home Improvement, Minimalist Lifestyle, and Computer Organization Techniques
You can declutter your life and start to enjoy your home, office, car and surroundings on your own terms. Your clutter no longer has to fill up your space and your life.
Decluttering can seem so overwhelming that it just seems too hard to ever start. This course will make it easy for you to start Decluttering today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypnosis to overcome Dentist fear guided hypnosis program</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/hypnosis-to-overcome-dentist-fear-guided-hypnosis-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 20:22:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/hypnosis-to-overcome-dentist-fear-guided-hypnosis-program/</guid>
      <description>Hypnosis to overcome Dentist fear guided hypnosis program has beed created to simulate a therapy visit with me 
Learn to change how you feel about the dentist If the thoughts of going for a dental appointment to your dentist have had you feeling anxious this course is just right for you. Because you will be using natures gift of hypnosis and being able to be hypnotized to change your thoughts and reactions to going to the dentist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poker Mastery - Get The Mental Edge in Your Poker Game</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/poker-mastery-get-the-mental-edge-in-your-poker-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 13:08:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/poker-mastery-get-the-mental-edge-in-your-poker-game/</guid>
      <description>Poker Mastery - Get The Mental Edge in Your Poker Game
5 Star Reviews
Great course learnt a lot and would highly recommend Alan Kirwan’s course
Robert Glass
The course is relaxing and easy to follow
Patrick
Good course for me.
Ning Yu
Hypnosis for Poker inner game mastery Guided Hypnosis was created to help you achieve your goals by simulating a private hypnosis session with me.
This hypnosis course will help you Learn why everyone knows Poker is not just a game of skill and a sprinkling of good luck but a mental game and a game of self control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Sourdough Bread Baking - Levels 1, 2, 3 and 4!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-sourdough-bread-baking-levels-1-2-3-and-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-sourdough-bread-baking-levels-1-2-3-and-4/</guid>
      <description>**New Courses just added as of 2/19/21** Learn how Wheat Germ can improve the flavor of your Sourdough Bread. The new updates in the Sourdough Bread Baking demonstrate more advanced techniques and recipes. Make sure to check them out today!
Complete Sourdough Bread Baking Course – Bake Your Own Homemade Bread Today – Bread Baking Sourdough at Home – San Francisco Sourdough Bread Baking
Imagine waking up in the morning with the fresh smell of sourdough bread baking that you cooked out of your own oven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oracle or Tarot Cards? Quick Start Guide: Choosing Your Deck</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/oracle-or-tarot-cards-quick-start-guide-choosing-your-deck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/oracle-or-tarot-cards-quick-start-guide-choosing-your-deck/</guid>
      <description>Upon completion of this course, you will be able to select the Oracle or Tarot card deck that will be your partner in giving accurate readings that flow with ease. You will know the difference between Oracle and Tarot cards and figure out which one fits your style and finally you’ll learn where to buy your new deck.
Choosing your card deck is the first step on a fun, magical and often amazing journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Antike Astrologie 2</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/antike-astrologie-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/antike-astrologie-2/</guid>
      <description>Dieser Kurs baut auf seiem Vorgänger Antike Astrologie 1 auf und erweitert die erste gelernte Technik mit der Methode der Elementarherrscher. Kannst du mit der Technik des Herrschers des Aszendenten (Kurs 1 ) das Generelle Lebenesthema bestimmen, so geht es hier um eine erste Timing - Technik.
Du erfährst wie du 3 grundlegende Planeten ermittelst und diese anschließend evaluierst. Dadurch wird das Leben des Horoskopstellers in 2 Hälften geteilt, die jeweils von den 3 Elementarherrscheerplaneten unterstützt werden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreaming Understand Dream Messages Remember Your Dreams 2020</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/dreaming-understand-dream-messages-remember-your-dreams-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/dreaming-understand-dream-messages-remember-your-dreams-2020/</guid>
      <description>Dreaming Understand Dream Messages and Remember Your Dreams
5 Star Review 
I was able to use this information to sort through dreams....and understand what the dream was telling me after the hypnosis. I will keep coming back to the hypnosis sessions as I find them very helpful. I do admit I am not writing things down...but I am holding what I need to know in memory and mulling over what I am finding out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Law Of Attraction Course Updated for the 2020s</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-law-of-attraction-course-updated-for-the-2020s/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-law-of-attraction-course-updated-for-the-2020s/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Law Of Attraction Course Updated for the 2020s
Master the Law of Attraction - Become Your Own Best Law of Attraction Coach - Great Life Manifestation Attract Success
You can obtain mastery of the Law of Attraction. You may have seen the movie or read the book, but this course will teach you in a systematic way how to re-condition your brain, completely, into an abundance-creating being.
TJ Walker dives deep into the secrets of the Law of Attraction.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
