<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lifestyle on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/lifestyle/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lifestyle on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/lifestyle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Positive Transformation Hypnotherapy | Certificate Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/positive-transformation-hypnotherapy-certificate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/positive-transformation-hypnotherapy-certificate-course/</guid>
      <description>Positive Transformation Hypnotherapy | Certificate Course
Hello everyone! I&#39;d like to welcome you to this course I created that is a complete guide for anyone who wants to learn the art of hypnotherapy, &amp;amp; use it to help induce positive mind shifts that last! I always wanted to be able to help the people around me but to do so I had to be able to help myself. This is what positive mind hypnotherapy did for me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reiki Secrets Revealed: Complete 30-Hour Certification Class</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/reiki-secrets-revealed-complete-30-hour-certification-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/reiki-secrets-revealed-complete-30-hour-certification-class/</guid>
      <description>✨✨The Complete 30+ Hour Reiki Certification: Secrets from A-Z includes over 30 hours of video lectures, including hand-drawn images of each of the Reiki symbols. Most of this course content is entirely original, with a brand-new approach to never-before-seen uses of Reiki. this is one of the most in-depth, longest, and comprehensive Reiki course you will find on the platform✨✨
Update April 2022: Thanks to student contributions, we now have an additional Reiki Handbook that is over 20,000 words long!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Oil Cooking Recipes - Eat Healthy! Live Strong!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/no-oil-cooking-recipes-eat-healthy-live-strong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/no-oil-cooking-recipes-eat-healthy-live-strong/</guid>
      <description>**Course Updated - June 2022**
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; COURSE REGULARLY UPDATED: NEW TIPS, MORE LESSONS &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; CERTIFIED COACH, SPEAKER AND TRAINER &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; OVER 180,000 STUDENTS IN TOTAL &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
Life is all about compromises, right?
Well, if you think you can ignore your bad eating habits just because you exercise regularly, think again. Unfortunately, spending an hour of rigorous exercise in the gym for a greasy double cheeseburger or relying on a good metabolism to take the place of healthy eating habits completely misses the point of living a healthy lifestyle…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#1 Embellishments Course for Acrylic Pouring &amp; Painting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/#1-embellishments-course-for-acrylic-pouring-painting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/#1-embellishments-course-for-acrylic-pouring-painting/</guid>
      <description>IS THIS FOR YOU?
If you are interested in embellishing your Acrylic Paint Pouring &amp;amp; Fluid Art and want to try it for yourself.
Or, you’ve already started and are finding that it’s not quite as easy as it appears on some of the videos you&#39;ve seen.
Or, are doing OK but want to broaden your knowledge and embellishment skills......
THEN THIS IS THE PERFECT TRAINING COURSE FOR YOU
This unique training course will guide you through every step of the way to embellish your very own fluid art masterpieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Portrait Drawing Techniques- Beginners and Advanced</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basic-portrait-drawing-techniques-beginners-and-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basic-portrait-drawing-techniques-beginners-and-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the &#34;Basic portrait sketching techniques for beginners&#34; course. This course teaches you how to easily create a portrait sketch from the very first basics. This tutorial in simple and beginner language will help you a lot in learning this style of painting. This course does not require any previous knowledge and if you are only a little interested in painting and have talent, with the help of this course you can easily create beautiful portraits because we have tried to teach you all the steps , step by step.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soundwave Healing | Solfeggio Frequency Certificate Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/soundwave-healing-solfeggio-frequency-certificate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/soundwave-healing-solfeggio-frequency-certificate-course/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Soundwave Healing!
This is an incredible short &amp;amp; sweet course on understanding all 10 of the healing frequencies that can be used in conjunction with sound therapy! This includes &amp;amp; covers the original 6 solfeggio frequencies and was made for all people who want to learn how to heal with sound waves &amp;amp; solfeggio frequencies. In this Soundwave Healing course, you will receive 10 x 10 min pure sound meditations on all of the healing frequencies (174hz - 963hz) that will be downloadable and available for commercial use in the course!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>39 Travel Tips to Make Your Travel More Enjoyable - 1 Hour</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/39-travel-tips-to-make-your-travel-more-enjoyable-1-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/39-travel-tips-to-make-your-travel-more-enjoyable-1-hour/</guid>
      <description>39 Travel Tips to Make Your Travel More Enjoyable - 1 HourTravel Tips To Help You Enjoy All Your Business and Personal Travel and Vacations - Practical and Usable Travel Tips
You can travel the globe with fewer hassles and more enjoyment. When you follow the right travel tips, you can avoid the headaches that ruin travel experiences for so many other people.
Instructor TJ Walker is a savvy and experienced world traveler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn to Draw Illustrated Creatures From Simple Shapes</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-to-draw-illustrated-creatures-from-simple-shapes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 21:50:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-to-draw-illustrated-creatures-from-simple-shapes/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover all the steps to create creatures from the depths of your imagination, and turn them into vibrant creatures, in three easy processes.
You will learn from a professional artist with over 10 years of experience.
You will get to watch every step and you will learn invaluable advice that will help you achieve your artistic goals, even if you have never picked up a pencil before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Law Of Attraction Course Updated for the 2020s</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-law-of-attraction-course-updated-for-the-2020s/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:30:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-law-of-attraction-course-updated-for-the-2020s/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Law Of Attraction Course Updated for the 2020sMaster the Law of Attraction - Become Your Own Best Law of Attraction Coach - Great Life Manifestation Attract Success
You can obtain mastery of the Law of Attraction. You may have seen the movie or read the book, but this course will systematically teach you how to re-condition your brain, completely, into an abundance-creating being.
TJ Walker dives deep into the secrets of the Law of Attraction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Pie Baking Course: Bake a Pie for Every Season</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-pie-baking-course-bake-a-pie-for-every-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 20:40:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-pie-baking-course-bake-a-pie-for-every-season/</guid>
      <description>We decided to bring you &#34;The Ultimate Pie Baking Course: Bake a Pie for Every Season&#34; because we once fell in love with baking pies, and felt that mixing some flavors together was so magical and beautiful, so we had to share this course with you so you can also enjoy preparing and baking pies yourself, at your home, using very simple tools and ingredients.
You can enjoy the pies we have for you, with your loved ones on any season and occasion around the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Pencil Drawing and Shading</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-pencil-drawing-and-shading/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 20:40:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-pencil-drawing-and-shading/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the “Ultimate Pencil Drawing and Shading from Beginner to Advanced Level” course!
This course has been created to teach you all the drawing techniques you need from beginner to advanced level. Never drawn pencil artworks before? That’s exactly why the first lesson of the course starts right at the beginning with an introduction to pencil drawing to teach you about pencil pressure, pencil layering and light to dark gradients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watercolor Portrait in Cellulose Paper</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/watercolor-portrait-in-cellulose-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:10:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/watercolor-portrait-in-cellulose-paper/</guid>
      <description>What you will learn
Learn how to paint a portrait using cellulose paper in watercolor.
How to block-in a drawing portrait drawing.
How to fine tune proportions and measurements.
How to mix skin tones in watercolor.
Insights on how to visualize volume and form.
Understand the main differences of cellulose and cotton watercolor paper.
Problem-solve issues that arise with cellulose watercolor paper.
Requirements
Basic understanding of watercolor and drawing would be helpful</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minimalist Lifestyle - Complete Course - Decluttering Life</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/minimalist-lifestyle-complete-course-decluttering-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:15:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/minimalist-lifestyle-complete-course-decluttering-life/</guid>
      <description>Minimalist Lifestyle - Complete Course - Decluttering Life
Learn Minimalism for your home, office and life. Minimalist interior design for all facets of your life and career
You can live a healthy, calm, and relaxing minimalist lifestyle. Imagine everything in your home is clean, beautiful, and devoid of clutter. Your possessions are beautiful. Your life is filled with purpose because you are no longer wasting time managing all of your stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angel Card Reading 2022 - Transformational Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/angel-card-reading-2022-transformational-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 18:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/angel-card-reading-2022-transformational-course/</guid>
      <description>The Angels of Heaven invite you to join this transformational course, where you will learn how to tap into their higher vibrational wisdom through the power of one simple tool: Angel Cards!
Whether you want to learn how to channel guidance from the heavenly realm for yourself or for others, this course is for you.
You will enjoy a complete guide on Angel Card Readings: Including: learning spreads from beginner to advanced, getting to know 19 Archangels, tapping into your intuition for your highest good, and much more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISTQB Agile Tester Extension training for 2022 &#43; 400 QUIZ</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/istqb-agile-tester-extension-training-for-2022--400-quiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 13:47:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/istqb-agile-tester-extension-training-for-2022--400-quiz/</guid>
      <description>Complete training package(only course which provides this)
ISTQB Agile Training + Reference book+ Topic wise Quiz + Chapter Wise Quiz + NOTES : COMPLETE PACKAGE
This course will help you to clear ISTQB Foundation level Agile Tester Extension Testing ,
First few video are provided for free, you can watch them to check the quality of the course.
we have maintained the same quality through the course. Highlights of the course:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2022 Commercial Driver’s License Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2022-commercial-drivers-license-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 21:20:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2022-commercial-drivers-license-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Commercial Driver’s License Practice Test
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily
Endorsements on your Commercial Driver’s License open you up to many more Truck Job Opportunities. However, getting these endorsements isn’t easy, as some require background checks and/or an additional skills test. The written test can be the biggest hurdle since it’s the part over which you have the most control. Below is a list of the different CDL Practice Tests that we offer, as well as the accompanying endorsement information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreaming Understand Dream Messages Remember Your Dreams 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/dreaming-understand-dream-messages-remember-your-dreams-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 12:48:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/dreaming-understand-dream-messages-remember-your-dreams-2022/</guid>
      <description>Dreaming Understand Dream Messages and Remember Your Dreams in 2022
5 Star Review I was able to use this information to sort through dreams....and understand what the dream was telling me after the hypnosis. I will keep coming back to the hypnosis sessions as I find them very helpful. I do admit I am not writing things down...but I am holding what I need to know in memory and mulling over what I am finding out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nomads and Expats: Moving to Mexico</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-nomads-and-expats-moving-to-mexico/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 12:27:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-nomads-and-expats-moving-to-mexico/</guid>
      <description>In this course you will learn how to travel in Mexico and live there (if you choose to do so), for long periods. You will learn the basics about immigration, crime and violence, the ease of living in Mexico, what to expect when going to the doctor or dentist, how to take care of your health, what it takes to rent an apartment or house, the cost of transportation, cell phone usage, using the Internet, electricity, gas, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Çektiğiniz Fotoğrafları Yağlıboya Resme Dönüştürün !</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%C3%A7ekti%C4%9Finiz-foto%C4%9Fraflar%C4%B1-ya%C4%9Fl%C4%B1boya-resme-d%C3%B6n%C3%BC%C5%9Ft%C3%BCr%C3%BCn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 16:32:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%C3%A7ekti%C4%9Finiz-foto%C4%9Fraflar%C4%B1-ya%C4%9Fl%C4%B1boya-resme-d%C3%B6n%C3%BC%C5%9Ft%C3%BCr%C3%BCn/</guid>
      <description>Merhabalar !
Yeni başlayan ve resim yeteneğini ileri seviyelere taşımak isteyen herkes için hazırladığımız kursumuzun temel amacı ; yağlıboya resim teknikleri öğretmek. Ayrıca hepimizin o çok sevdiği , güzel mekanlarda çektiğimiz fotoğrafları tuval üzerine nasıl aktarabiliriz ? Nasıl yağlıboya sanat eserleri haline getirebiliriz ? Bu kursumuzda öğrencilerimize tasarım yapmayı ve uygulamak için ne tür teknikler kullanılacağını öğretmekteyiz. İyi bir gözlem ve analiz ile gördükleri bir fotoğrafı yorumlayarak yapacakları resmin nereden başlayıp nerede sonlanacağına dair bir fikirlerinin ve güvenlerinin oluşmasını hedeflemekteyiz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kundalini Reiki 1-2-3-master teacher (all in one course)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kundalini-reiki-1-2-3-master-teacher-all-in-one-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 14:59:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kundalini-reiki-1-2-3-master-teacher-all-in-one-course/</guid>
      <description>KUNDALINI REIKI (1-2-3 MASTER TRAINING)
You will learn how to use Universal Life Force Energy Kundalini Reiki to heal yourself, your friends, family, pets, other people, animals, objects and even situations! You will learn how to take care of your mind, body, and spirit, as well as attracting loving energy and abundance into your life.
====== INCLUDED ======
This course includes all levels of Kundalini Reiki including Master. This course is all digital, which means you can go as slow or as fast as you want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obsession - with healthy eating</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/obsession-with-healthy-eating/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 13:13:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/obsession-with-healthy-eating/</guid>
      <description>Notice: Please do NOT enrol on this course on impulse, thinking you might watch it later. Maybe show an interest on impulse, yes, but before you enrol, watch the Preview videos, read the Course Description and then make a decision. If you then enrol then please start the course as soon as possible. Watch the lectures, look at the workbooks and join in the discussions. Joining my courses is a serious business and I want you to get the most out of your study – but I also want you to enjoy the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>رسم شجرة بدون اوراق بألوان الخشب - English Subtitled</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%B1%D8%B3%D9%85-%D8%B4%D8%AC%D8%B1%D8%A9-%D8%A8%D8%AF%D9%88%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%82-%D8%A8%D8%A3%D9%84%D9%88%D8%A7%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AE%D8%B4%D8%A8-english-subtitled/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%B1%D8%B3%D9%85-%D8%B4%D8%AC%D8%B1%D8%A9-%D8%A8%D8%AF%D9%88%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%82-%D8%A8%D8%A3%D9%84%D9%88%D8%A7%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AE%D8%B4%D8%A8-english-subtitled/</guid>
      <description>أهلا بكم في الفيديو التعليمي لرسم رسم شجرة بدون أوراق بألوان الخشب. حرصت في هذا الفيديو أن تبدأ من المستوي صفر وذلك لما يحتويه الفيديو من شقين، الأول هو رسم الشجرة حيث انها من الأشياء الهامة جدا في خيال كل رسام وفنان وثانيا وهي طريقة التعامل مع ألوان الخشب، لاظهار امكانياتها وقدرتها على التعبير بجرأة لرسم الأشجار
كان هدفي بهذه الدورة الاحساس بالمتعة في التعامل مع ألوان الخشب, وذلك بناء علي تكنيك مبسط وسهل, ولهذا قمت برسم للهيكل الأساسي (الساق والاغصان الكبيرة) للشجرة، ثم الأغصان الصغيرة لها, ثم التفاصيل الخاصة الصغيرة حتي تصل الي رسمها باحتراف, مع الأخذ في الاعتبار تأثير الإضاءة على رسم عناصر الشجرة من مناطق مضاءة واخري مظللة, مع ذكر الأخطاء الشائعة اثناء عملية الرسم.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Antike Astrologie 1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/antike-astrologie-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/antike-astrologie-1/</guid>
      <description>In diesem Kurs lernst du die Grundlagen der hellenistischen- römischen Astrologie. 2000 Jahre alte Prognostische Techniken werden seit ca. 20 Jahren wiederbelebt. Hier geb ich dir das Werkzeug in die Hand, damit du selbst bei dir die erste Technik anwenden kannst um in deinem Horoskop deine Lebensaufgabe zu erkennen: Die verrät dir der Herrscher deines Aszendenten - der Kurios
Ratings: 4.44/5
Enrollments: 5227
Coupon Code: 4F1A00CB61BB30F66882
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proven Travel Hacks for Southeast Asia</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/proven-travel-hacks-for-southeast-asia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/proven-travel-hacks-for-southeast-asia/</guid>
      <description>Ricky Shetty and Scott Paton take you on a journey throughout SE Asian countries like, Indonesia, Singapore, Malaysia, Thailand and the Philippines. Seasoned travellers, they share their favourite travel hacks for each country.
You&#39;ll learn the best ways to get around, where to stay, what foods to make sure you sample and much more!
Discover:
The best places to visit
How to travel safely
What food you must try
The countries discussed are:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypnosis for to visit Past life or lives Guided Hypnosis</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hypnosis-for-to-visit-past-life-or-lives-guided-hypnosis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:52:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hypnosis-for-to-visit-past-life-or-lives-guided-hypnosis/</guid>
      <description>5 Star Review Great course and appreciated the bonus, feel good lecture. Instructor is easy to listen to and very good at what he does. Thank you for offering your course which has saved me many hundreds of dollars as well as my precious time from having to schedule the allotted time with a therapist. Very comfortable watching as my time allowed and going through these sessions in the privacy of my home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decluttering - Complete Organizing Home, Office, Life Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/decluttering-complete-organizing-home-office-life-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/decluttering-complete-organizing-home-office-life-course/</guid>
      <description>Decluttering - Complete Organizing Home, Office, Life Course
Decluttering Your Life - Organization, Home Improvement, Minimalist Lifestyle, and Computer Organization Techniques
You can declutter your life and start to enjoy your home, office, car and surroundings on your own terms. Your clutter no longer has to fill up your space and your life.
Decluttering can seem so overwhelming that it just seems too hard to ever start. This course will make it easy for you to start Decluttering today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypnosis to overcome Dentist fear guided hypnosis program</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hypnosis-to-overcome-dentist-fear-guided-hypnosis-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 20:22:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hypnosis-to-overcome-dentist-fear-guided-hypnosis-program/</guid>
      <description>Hypnosis to overcome Dentist fear guided hypnosis program has beed created to simulate a therapy visit with me Learn to change how you feel about the dentist If the thoughts of going for a dental appointment to your dentist have had you feeling anxious this course is just right for you. Because you will be using natures gift of hypnosis and being able to be hypnotized to change your thoughts and reactions to going to the dentist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poker Mastery - Get The Mental Edge in Your Poker Game</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/poker-mastery-get-the-mental-edge-in-your-poker-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 13:08:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/poker-mastery-get-the-mental-edge-in-your-poker-game/</guid>
      <description>Poker Mastery - Get The Mental Edge in Your Poker Game
5 Star Reviews
Great course learnt a lot and would highly recommend Alan Kirwan’s course
Robert Glass
The course is relaxing and easy to follow
Patrick
Good course for me.
Ning Yu
Hypnosis for Poker inner game mastery Guided Hypnosis was created to help you achieve your goals by simulating a private hypnosis session with me.
This hypnosis course will help you Learn why everyone knows Poker is not just a game of skill and a sprinkling of good luck but a mental game and a game of self control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Sourdough Bread Baking - Levels 1, 2, 3 and 4!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-sourdough-bread-baking-levels-1-2-3-and-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-sourdough-bread-baking-levels-1-2-3-and-4/</guid>
      <description>**New Courses just added as of 2/19/21** Learn how Wheat Germ can improve the flavor of your Sourdough Bread. The new updates in the Sourdough Bread Baking demonstrate more advanced techniques and recipes. Make sure to check them out today!
Complete Sourdough Bread Baking Course – Bake Your Own Homemade Bread Today – Bread Baking Sourdough at Home – San Francisco Sourdough Bread Baking
Imagine waking up in the morning with the fresh smell of sourdough bread baking that you cooked out of your own oven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oracle or Tarot Cards? Quick Start Guide: Choosing Your Deck</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/oracle-or-tarot-cards-quick-start-guide-choosing-your-deck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/oracle-or-tarot-cards-quick-start-guide-choosing-your-deck/</guid>
      <description>Upon completion of this course, you will be able to select the Oracle or Tarot card deck that will be your partner in giving accurate readings that flow with ease. You will know the difference between Oracle and Tarot cards and figure out which one fits your style and finally you’ll learn where to buy your new deck.
Choosing your card deck is the first step on a fun, magical and often amazing journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Antike Astrologie 2</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/antike-astrologie-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/antike-astrologie-2/</guid>
      <description>Dieser Kurs baut auf seiem Vorgänger Antike Astrologie 1 auf und erweitert die erste gelernte Technik mit der Methode der Elementarherrscher. Kannst du mit der Technik des Herrschers des Aszendenten (Kurs 1 ) das Generelle Lebenesthema bestimmen, so geht es hier um eine erste Timing - Technik.
Du erfährst wie du 3 grundlegende Planeten ermittelst und diese anschließend evaluierst. Dadurch wird das Leben des Horoskopstellers in 2 Hälften geteilt, die jeweils von den 3 Elementarherrscheerplaneten unterstützt werden.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
