<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Teacher Training on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/teacher-training/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Teacher Training on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/teacher-training/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Workshops und Seminare professionell vorbereiten und leiten</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/workshops-und-seminare-professionell-vorbereiten-und-leiten/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/workshops-und-seminare-professionell-vorbereiten-und-leiten/</guid>
      <description>Dieser Kurs hilft dir bei der Vorbereitung, Leitung und Durchführung eines professionellen Workshops.
Freue dich auf glückliche und zufriedene Teilnehmer, ebenso wie gut zahlende Kunden! Es ist kein Geheimnis, dass Workshops eine großartige Möglichkeit sind, Menschen zusammenzubringen, um Wissen und Erfahrung auszutauschen. Aber was ist, wenn du nicht weisst, wie du sie organisieren sollst? Oder was, wenn du befürchtest, dass dir die Zeit ausgeht oder du nicht in der Lage bist, alle Teilnehmer bei der Stange zu halten?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TESOL and TPRS Course (For Language Teachers)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tesol-and-tprs-course-for-language-teachers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tesol-and-tprs-course-for-language-teachers/</guid>
      <description>Although uneducated parents can teach a languge to their children, how can educated teachers not teach a foreign language? In this course, you will learn how to teach a languge with a contemporary method but ancient.
In ancient times, people used to travel by horses or camels but then they invented cars and began to go everywhere with them. Today, we use planes. There is no doubt that cars are faster than horses, but planes are the fastest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops - systemisch konzipieren und gestalten</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/workshops-systemisch-konzipieren-und-gestalten/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/workshops-systemisch-konzipieren-und-gestalten/</guid>
      <description>Würden Sie gerne Ihre Fähigkeiten als (zukünftige) Führungskraft hinsichtlich Vorträge und Workshops verbessern? Dieser Kurs ist mit dem systemischen Ansatz am neuesten Stand und gibt Ihnen das notwendige Hintergrundwissen, damit Sie mit Ihren eigenen Projekten gleich durchstarten können.
Zielgruppe sind (zukünftige) Führungskräfte, Projektleiter/innen, Personen mit Leitungsfunktionen oder einfach alle Menschen mit Verantwortung im Job.
Ich habe sowohl wissenschaftliche Inhalte als auch meine eigene Erfahrungen als Trainer, Coach und Führungskraft in diesen Lektionen eingebaut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Google Classroom Course: Teaching Google Classroom</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-google-classroom-course-teaching-google-classroom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 16:38:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-google-classroom-course-teaching-google-classroom/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Google Classroom Course: Teaching Google Classroom: Become a Master At Teaching Google Classroom - Teaching Online with Google Classroom - Google Certified Educator
Recent Updates:
How do I record my screen recording video?
Added 3 videos guide for new Google Classroom update 1. Environment 2. Invite by URL 3. Return Once All with 1 click Added Lecture on How You Can Do Math in Google Classroom Using Docs and Math Type How to Keep Your Devices Secure Complete Guide of Making and Keeping Passwords that You Haven&#39;t Heard Of!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teacher Training - How to Teach Online - Remote Teaching 1Hr</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/teacher-training-how-to-teach-online-remote-teaching-1hr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 20:10:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/teacher-training-how-to-teach-online-remote-teaching-1hr/</guid>
      <description>(Please note this is a beginner course designed to be completed in less than one hour for classroom teachers who are looking to become more comfortable and confident teaching online.)
Online Teacher Training
The Coronavirus has changed the world. Teachers who have spent a lifetime teaching students in the classroom must now learn (quickly!) how to teach students online and in virtual classrooms.
This course is designed for busy, stressed teachers who are battling numerous crises at the moment and don&#39;t have time for a 1-3 day course on online teacher training.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publish Simple Videos For a Living - Skillshare Earnings</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/publish-simple-videos-for-a-living-skillshare-earnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/publish-simple-videos-for-a-living-skillshare-earnings/</guid>
      <description>**Our 80,000+ satisfied students and our countless 5-star reviews are no accident.** We practice what we preach ! At QualiWave, we want to share only the best content that helped us expanding in the past and still growing exponentially in the future! Let us help you to make 2020 YOUR best year ever!
PLEASE WATCH THE PROMO VIDEO FOR PROOF OF INCOME Hey,
If you&#39;ve been following me for a while then you know I run multiple six figure businesses, all of them having one thing in common: video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Record Your Screen Like A Pro: Create Sellable HD Videos!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/record-your-screen-like-a-pro-create-sellable-hd-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 12:41:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/record-your-screen-like-a-pro-create-sellable-hd-videos/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to know how to create high-quality video content? Would you like to finally start getting involved with Udemy, Youtube, or any other video-sharing network? Can you follow the easy instructions I will lay down for you to master the art of screencast production in no time at all? That&#39;s what I thought! Let me help you! In this course, I will teach you which free software to use, and how you can use them to shorten your learning curve and start creating video content right away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABC de ventas</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/abc-de-ventas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 23:02:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/abc-de-ventas/</guid>
      <description>El clásico proceso de venta se ha visto afectado por la introducción de internet en nuestras vidas como soporte para la toma de decisiones en la compra, es más, a día de hoy podemos hablar de un cambio radical no en cada una de las fases del proceso sino en cómo se realizan esas fases.
Para simplificar el esquema del proceso de venta, las fases fundamentales dentro de las cuales habría que diferenciar otras.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Scrum Training, Scrum Master Certification</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-scrum-training-scrum-master-certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-scrum-training-scrum-master-certification/</guid>
      <description>Agile Scrum Training, Scrum Master Certification Prep, Tests
Set yourself apart with the first and only official professional certification program for Agile Scrum Training, Scrum Master Certification Prep, Tests.
ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator is for the engineers and developper to validate their Agile Scrum Training, Scrum Master Certification Prep, Tests
Practice tests are designed by experts to simulate the real exam scenario. The questions are based on the exam syllabus outlined by official documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMI-PBA certification for Business Analyst</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pmi-pba-certification-for-business-analyst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pmi-pba-certification-for-business-analyst/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to take the Microsoft PMI-PBA certification for Business Analyst Analyzing and Visualizing Data with Microsoft Power BI exam?
properly balanced based on the exam domains just like you will get in the official exam. . In addition, after taking the exam you can review your answers compared against the correct answers including comprehensive explanations of each question, links to documentation and articles, the correct and incorrect answer options</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/servicenow-certified-system-administrator/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/servicenow-certified-system-administrator/</guid>
      <description>Docker Certified Associate - Practice Exams
Set yourself apart with the first and only official professional certification program for ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator.
ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator is for the engineers and developper to validate their ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator
Practice tests are designed by experts to simulate the real exam scenario. The questions are based on the exam syllabus outlined by official documentation. The questions that appear in each practice test are unique and not repeated in other practice tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AutoCAD Course l كورس الاوتوكاد</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/autocad-course-l-%D9%83%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%B3-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%88%D8%AA%D9%88%D9%83%D8%A7%D8%AF/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/autocad-course-l-%D9%83%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%B3-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%88%D8%AA%D9%88%D9%83%D8%A7%D8%AF/</guid>
      <description>كورس الاوتوكاد كورس هنتعلم فيه مع بعض اهم الاسس اللي لازم تكون عارفها عن الاوتوكاد
هنتعلم مع بعض اوامر الرسم المختلفة وكذالك اوامر التعديل المختلفة
زي Filet , Extend , Scale , Alignment , Divide , match , hatch ,text , offset , move , rotate , mirror , Block and Explode سنتعرف على الاوامر الهامة داخل برنامج الاوتوكاد الذى لا غنى عنه فى اى تصميم او رسومات بانواعها والذى ايضاً فى حاجه له مع برامج اخرى لتوصيل الفكرة وتنفيذها بسهولة .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corso completo di Teatro per bambini 4-6 anni</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-completo-di-teatro-per-bambini-4-6-anni/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:16:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-completo-di-teatro-per-bambini-4-6-anni/</guid>
      <description>In questo corso spiegherò come poter gestire un gruppo di bambini dai 4 ai 6 anni facendo loro praticare, in modo ludico ma nello stesso tempo costruttivo e creativo, attività teatrali volte alla conoscenza di elementi fondamentali per la suddetta fascia d&#39;età. Gli scopi di un laboratorio teatrale destinato ai più piccini sono svariati tra cui: 1. Favorire la socializzazione; 2. Superare eventuali timidezze; 3. Coordinare l&#39;attività motoria; 4. Acquisire la conoscenza delle figure geometriche nello spazio; 5.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
