<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Other Health &amp; Fitness on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/other-health-fitness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Other Health &amp; Fitness on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/other-health-fitness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>virology 4 you</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/virology-4-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/virology-4-you/</guid>
      <description>in scientific fiction and reality virus is a June premiere virus was the most mysterious subject in medicine bacterial filter discovery electron microscope we unveil this mystery in this course we speak about history of discovery virus structure virus classifications virus multiplication virus pathogenesis zoonosis some important viruses hepatitis
Rabies is a vaccine preventable, zoonotic, viral disease. Once clinical symptoms appear, rabies is. Vaccinating dogs is the most
cost effective strategy for preventing rabies in people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deciphering Multi Orgasmic Man – Important Prior Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/deciphering-multi-orgasmic-man-important-prior-knowledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/deciphering-multi-orgasmic-man-important-prior-knowledge/</guid>
      <description>Normally it is thought that sex education courses are only for young people, but in this case, Tantric and Taoist knowledge teach us that: The older a person is; his body will naturally transform into Orgasmic! So men and women between 30 and 70 years of age are going to be the biggest beneficiaries.
According to Eastern wisdom, the orgasmic capacity must be taken advantage of! And the first step that men must take is to understand what &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction To Swedish Body Massage</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-swedish-body-massage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-swedish-body-massage/</guid>
      <description>This course is aimed at assisting you on your journey to become a massage therapist. If you don&#39;t know where to start, this IS FOR YOU. You will learn all the theory you need before you can begin your practical lessons. As a student of Body massage, I was perplexed when I enrolled in school and was taught massage theory. I thought I was simply going to be taught practical lessons but after my lessons, i understood why learning the theory was essential before we explored practical lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work from home; work at work...or play?</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/work-from-home-work-at-work...or-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 22:00:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/work-from-home-work-at-work...or-play/</guid>
      <description>This course is in two sections:
Working from home
Working at work
In the first section we go through various ways - using Art Therapy - self-care can be practised at home to reduce stress, help focus and improve overall wellbeing. This includes visualisations as well as Art Therapy exercises.
In the second section we go through a series of games that can be played at work. These will remove tension but BEWARE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Counseling clients with Insomnia to Sleep Better</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/counseling-clients-with-insomnia-to-sleep-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 22:30:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/counseling-clients-with-insomnia-to-sleep-better/</guid>
      <description>Counselling clients with Insomnia to Sleep Better
Overcome Insomnia &amp;amp; common sleep problems by understanding the principles of deep sleep, habits and lifestyle choices
You may have difficulty sleeping or you may have difficulty shutting off your mind when you want to sleep. If your sleep problems have led to trouble during the day, such as difficulty with everyday activities, or if they cause you to distress then this course is for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Massaggio Decontratturante Vol1 &#43; Vol2: Test di Valutazione</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/massaggio-decontratturante-vol1--vol2-test-di-valutazione/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 14:59:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/massaggio-decontratturante-vol1--vol2-test-di-valutazione/</guid>
      <description>Ok..hai seguito i miei corsi oppure sei già un massaggiatore esperto...
Ma se ti chiedessi la differenza tra muscolo e tendine? Dove si trova l&#39;organo tendine del Golgi e a cosa serve?
Sapresti rispondermi a menadito o ci stai ancora pensando? Sei pronto per metterti alla prova? Con questo test di 100 domande avrai modo di testare le conoscenze acquisite durante i miei corsi di massaggio decontratturante. Avrai la possibilità di annotare e approfondire nuovi aspetti che nelle lezioni frontali possono sfuggire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Massaggio Decontratturante: schiena, spalle, collo.</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/massaggio-decontratturante-schiena-spalle-collo./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 01:45:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/massaggio-decontratturante-schiena-spalle-collo./</guid>
      <description>Hai problemi con la cervicale e vorresti capirne qualcosa in più sul funzionamento del tuo stesso corpo?
Sei un allenatore e vorresti contribuire al benessere della tua squadra?
Pratichi già massaggi e vorresti ampliare le tue conoscenze??
Sei un appassionato e di massaggi??
Bene!!! Sei nell&#39;aula virtuale giusta!
In questo corso spiegherò dalla A alla Z tutto ciò che c&#39;è da sapere per poter effettuare un ottimo massaggio decontratturante agli arti superiori.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
