<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travel on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travel on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>39 Travel Tips to Make Your Travel More Enjoyable - 1 Hour</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/39-travel-tips-to-make-your-travel-more-enjoyable-1-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/39-travel-tips-to-make-your-travel-more-enjoyable-1-hour/</guid>
      <description>39 Travel Tips to Make Your Travel More Enjoyable - 1 HourTravel Tips To Help You Enjoy All Your Business and Personal Travel and Vacations - Practical and Usable Travel Tips
You can travel the globe with fewer hassles and more enjoyment. When you follow the right travel tips, you can avoid the headaches that ruin travel experiences for so many other people.
Instructor TJ Walker is a savvy and experienced world traveler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2022 Commercial Driver’s License Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2022-commercial-drivers-license-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 21:20:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2022-commercial-drivers-license-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Commercial Driver’s License Practice Test
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily
Endorsements on your Commercial Driver’s License open you up to many more Truck Job Opportunities. However, getting these endorsements isn’t easy, as some require background checks and/or an additional skills test. The written test can be the biggest hurdle since it’s the part over which you have the most control. Below is a list of the different CDL Practice Tests that we offer, as well as the accompanying endorsement information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nomads and Expats: Moving to Mexico</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-nomads-and-expats-moving-to-mexico/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 12:27:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-nomads-and-expats-moving-to-mexico/</guid>
      <description>In this course you will learn how to travel in Mexico and live there (if you choose to do so), for long periods. You will learn the basics about immigration, crime and violence, the ease of living in Mexico, what to expect when going to the doctor or dentist, how to take care of your health, what it takes to rent an apartment or house, the cost of transportation, cell phone usage, using the Internet, electricity, gas, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proven Travel Hacks for Southeast Asia</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/proven-travel-hacks-for-southeast-asia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/proven-travel-hacks-for-southeast-asia/</guid>
      <description>Ricky Shetty and Scott Paton take you on a journey throughout SE Asian countries like, Indonesia, Singapore, Malaysia, Thailand and the Philippines. Seasoned travellers, they share their favourite travel hacks for each country.
You&#39;ll learn the best ways to get around, where to stay, what foods to make sure you sample and much more!
Discover:
The best places to visit
How to travel safely
What food you must try
The countries discussed are:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
