<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project Management on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/project-management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project Management on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/project-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Confluence Masterclass for Project Managers</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/atlassian-confluence-masterclass-for-project-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/atlassian-confluence-masterclass-for-project-managers/</guid>
      <description>Confluence is a powerful enterprise collaboration tool that brings people, knowledge, and ideas together in a shared workspace, so you can do your best work. Through this course &#34;Atlassian Confluence Masterclass&#34;, you will learn how to use Confluence to transform the way your team works.
This course is structured to guide you through all the key aspects of managing and using Confluence.
Whether you’re new to Confluence, training your teammates, or ready to take your Confluence skills to the next level, this guide covers everything from the basics to in-depth best practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management Essentials: A practical approach</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/project-management-essentials-a-practical-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/project-management-essentials-a-practical-approach/</guid>
      <description>PROJECTS ARE EVERYWHERE!!
Are you confused about Project Management and do you think you will benefit from learning the most important aspects of project management? This course will set you on course and will allow you to PROGRESS at work whether you are from the business or part of technical team. This course could also enlighten you to start a potential NEW CAREER as Project Manager.
After attending this course you will - Get an edge by understanding what few people know about Project Management</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>دورة إدارة المشاريع الاحترافية بالعربي PMP Prep. Arabic</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/%D8%AF%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%A9-%D8%A5%D8%AF%D8%A7%D8%B1%D8%A9-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D8%B4%D8%A7%D8%B1%D9%8A%D8%B9-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81%D9%8A%D8%A9-%D8%A8%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B9%D8%B1%D8%A8%D9%8A-pmp-prep.-arabic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/%D8%AF%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%A9-%D8%A5%D8%AF%D8%A7%D8%B1%D8%A9-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D8%B4%D8%A7%D8%B1%D9%8A%D8%B9-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81%D9%8A%D8%A9-%D8%A8%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B9%D8%B1%D8%A8%D9%8A-pmp-prep.-arabic/</guid>
      <description>تحديث هام: هناك إصدار أحدث من الكتاب وهو الإصدار السادس, هذا الكورس معتمد على الإصدار الخامس, بالرغم من أن الاختلافات ليست كبيرة ولكن إذا أردتم التقدم للامتحان فيفضل حضور كورس آخر يعتمد على الإصدار السادس. وحتى تحديث هذا الكورس للإصدار الجديد سأبقيه مجاناً.

تحديث هام 2: غيّر موقع يوديمي سياسيته بخصوص الكورسات المجانية وأوقف إعطاء شهادات الحضور لها, للأسف هذا الكورس لم يعد يزود شهادة حضور ما دام مجانياً.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HVAC Ductwork Quantity Take off for Quantity Surveyors</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/hvac-ductwork-quantity-take-off-for-quantity-surveyors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 10:00:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/hvac-ductwork-quantity-take-off-for-quantity-surveyors/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this course on HVAC Duct Quantity Take off.
HVAC stands for Heating, Cooling, Air Conditioning. It forms a part of MEP Services.
Ducts are used as a medium for transmission of air from the equipment&#39;s to different rooms in a building.
Accurate estimation of DUCT quantities is critical for an effective cost management of a construction project. In this course you will understand how to take off the HVAC duct quantity using different unit of measurements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Project Management: Agile, Scrum, Kanban &amp; XP</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/agile-project-management-agile-scrum-kanban-xp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/agile-project-management-agile-scrum-kanban-xp/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Course on Agile Project Management!
Software industry is going crazy on agile methods. It is rapidly becoming the choice for software development where requirements are unpredictable or is expected to change over time. This course will help you explore how working on an Agile project has benefits for your development team, your end users, and your organization as a whole.
Here is a list of the topics we will cover in this course:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contracts Management in Construction Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/contracts-management-in-construction-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/contracts-management-in-construction-projects/</guid>
      <description>Every construction project is bound by a Contract. Proper Contract Management plays a major role in the effective management of your construction projects. Adhering to all the Contractual obligations, the terms and conditions can save both cost and time. There are a few standard Contract Forms that is followed in a Construction project mainly FIDIC (International Federation of Consulting Engineers), NRM (New Rules of Measurement), JCT (The Joint Contracts Tribunal). The procedures to commence work, the documents required at each stage of the project, variation procedures, payment terms, basis for termination and suspension of works by either parties, completion of work, roles and responsibilities of all the stake holders and their staffs, dispute resolution methods, Arbitration procedures etc are all mentioned in the contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Stories for Agile Scrum&#43;Product Owner&#43;Business Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/user-stories-for-agile-scrum-product-owner-business-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/user-stories-for-agile-scrum-product-owner-business-analysis/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Scrum Open, Professional Scrum™, Professional Scrum Master™, PSM, PSM I, PSM 1, etc. is the protected brand of Scrum . org. Our course and practice exams are neither endorsed by nor affiliated with Scrum . org.&#34;
Three reasons to TAKE THIS COURSE right now!
The unique reasons for taking this course are:
Complete, Concise, Confident Overview of User Stories - I cover all of the theory and give you examples of how the theory is used in industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management: Cost &amp; Schedule Monitoring using EVM</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/project-management-cost-schedule-monitoring-using-evm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 11:17:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/project-management-cost-schedule-monitoring-using-evm/</guid>
      <description>The course will help you understand the basic concepts of Earned Value Management which is one of the most important technique for effective Project Management.
By the end of this course you will learn the key terms of Earned Value Management, their definitions and the various formulas used to analyze whether the project is getting executed on track with respect to cost and schedule.
The course lets you understand the concept of Budget, Planned Value, Earned Value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Project 2019 Course for beginners to advanced</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-project-2019-course-for-beginners-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-project-2019-course-for-beginners-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Our objective is to present you the course in a easiest way, make you feel it is easy to use, easy to grasp, easy to learn and easy to implement in your project management goals.
 This course is developed keeping in considerations about growing requirements and aspirations of students, mid-professionals, young-professionals in learning the project management skills. The planning is pre-requisite before starting any meaningful project nowadays for all kind of industries such as construction, software and manufacturing sectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Business Productivity Training Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/best-business-productivity-training-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/best-business-productivity-training-course/</guid>
      <description>In This Online Course You Will Learn About The Major Productivity Challenges Facing Companies Today … These Challenges Can Make Or Break A Businesses. This Amazing Online Training Will Give Your Business Or Career An Unfair Advantage Against The Competition.
In This Productivity Training Course You Will Discover Specific Tools, Strategies And Techniques To Beat These Challenges. By Learning How To Think Like A Top Producer … You Can Make Massive Advances In Your Business Or Career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantity Surveying Templates for Effective Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quantity-surveying-templates-for-effective-cost-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quantity-surveying-templates-for-effective-cost-management/</guid>
      <description>This course explains the different Quantity Surveying templates created by me for effective post contract cost management.
You can download these templates and use it in your professional life.
By the end of this course, you will learn the below :
Prepare a perfect payment application summary for the interim payment applications.
Able to properly track both the inward and outward payments specific to the project.
Efficiently monitor and update the variations and claims status of the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAPM  Practice Tests: 3 Real CAPM Exams (UPDATED JULY 2021)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/capm-practice-tests-3-real-capm-exams-updated-july-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/capm-practice-tests-3-real-capm-exams-updated-july-2021/</guid>
      <description>PMI&#39;s Certified Associate in Project Management (CAPM) is an entry-level certification for project practitioners, designed for those with less experience.
The CAPM Certification tests an individual’s knowledge of the Project Management Body of Knowledge (PMBOK® Guide).
Overview of the CAPM Certification 
The CAPM certification offers recognition to practitioners who are interested in or are just starting a career in project management, as well as project team members who wish to demonstrate their project management knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMP Practice Test Exam 2021-PMBOK6</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pmp-practice-test-exam-2021-pmbok6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pmp-practice-test-exam-2021-pmbok6/</guid>
      <description>In the Practice Tests for PMP, you&#39;ll be challenged with 560 PMP practice exam questions based on the PMBOK Guide, sixth edition. These question have been collated to emulate the PMP exam and are based on the PMP exam objectives as provided by PMI and are current keeping in mind the current updates to the PMP exam in 2021.
This course has been updated to reflect the new PMP Exam domains</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 PMP Mock Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-pmp-mock-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-pmp-mock-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>These mock tests are specially created to assist PMP® aspirants to get familiar with the new 2021 PMP® Exam format and test their understanding of the PMP® Exam syllabus.
After taking these prep tests, you will get a clear idea about your readiness for the real exam and you will be able to identify and focus on your weakness points. This preparation course includes a sum of 380 questions to make sure you’ll be able to face all possibilities and scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Level PMP Mock Questions</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/advanced-level-pmp-mock-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/advanced-level-pmp-mock-questions/</guid>
      <description>2021 Advanced PMP Exam Simulator: Boost your confidence and proficiency before taking the PMP certification exam.

This course offers a simulation of the updated 2021 PMP exam, providing 180 highly realistic mock questions to help you test your understanding of project management knowledge areas &amp;amp; approaches.

These practice tests were created to prepare you for the real PMP Exam, identifying any knowledge gaps and clearing any hard-to-understand concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management Essential Training</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/project-management-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/project-management-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>Project management is a start-to-finish approach to getting things done and making projects more successful. It&#39;s a profession, but it&#39;s also a set of techniques that anyone can apply to achieve goals and manage project work more effectively. Project management can be used to guide small, simple projects as well as complex enterprise-wide initiatives.
In this course you&#39;ll be fascinated by how things work and how to make things work better.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
