<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project Management on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/project-management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project Management on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/project-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Agile Scrum Master Training : Case Studies and Confessions</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-scrum-master-training-case-studies-and-confessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-scrum-master-training-case-studies-and-confessions/</guid>
      <description>THIS COURSE HAS BEEN DESIGNED TO SAVE YOU HUNDREDS IF NOT THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS ON AGILE SCRUM CASE STUDIES CONTINUOUS IMPROVEMENT TRAINING AS A Scrum Master, Project Manager, Product Owner or Team Member
Three reasons to TAKE THIS COURSE right now!
The unique reasons for taking this course are:
Complete, Concise, Confident Overview of Scrum using short stories and case studies - I cover the theory and give you examples of how the theory is used in industry in each case study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum Certification Course 2022 (Based on Scrum Guide 2020)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/scrum-certification-course-2022-based-on-scrum-guide-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/scrum-certification-course-2022-based-on-scrum-guide-2020/</guid>
      <description>Are you preparing for your Scrum certification and need to listen to the Official Scrum Guide 2020? Then this, is the right course.
Are you a software developer looking for your first job? You&#39;ll need to understand Scrum and you&#39;ll get that here.
Are you a program manager trying to move from traditional project management to agile project management? The latest Scrum principles taught in this course will help you do that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PO Academy I - Product Owner Role, Craft, Skills and Tools</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/po-academy-i-product-owner-role-craft-skills-and-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/po-academy-i-product-owner-role-craft-skills-and-tools/</guid>
      <description>Product Owner is a relatively new, yet very hot role with rapidly growing demand. According to Glassdoor the median salary of a Product Owner is $107,368 in US. Whether you are already stepping into this role, or are only considering to become a PO in the near future, this course is for you.
After completing this course you will develop a good understanding of the role (who Product Owners are and what they do), the craft (what constitutes the majority of their day to day work), the skills and the tools you need to master in order to be successful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Crash Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-crash-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-crash-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>In this course, we will learn everything about Agile methodologies, we will learn about agile values &amp;amp; principles, then talk about agile roles like scrum master &amp;amp; product owner, then we will talk about the most famous methodologies like Scrum, Kanban, and Extreme programming. Also, we will talk about agile ceremonies like Daily Stand-up meeting, retrospective meeting, and Sprint review. We will learn about writing user stories &amp;amp; acceptance criteria. We will talk about planning for Agile projects using planning poker activity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Project Management Certification Prep&#43;Agile Scrum&#43;Jira</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-project-management-certification-prep-agile-scrum-jira/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-project-management-certification-prep-agile-scrum-jira/</guid>
      <description>Three reasons to TAKE THIS COURSE right now! The unique reasons for taking this course are: Complete, Concise, Confident Overview of Agile project management - You will be confident that you have a complete overview of Agile project management as the founders intended it, because I only teach accurately based on the Agile Manifesto and Agile Principles. Gain confidence and get your Agile Certificate - I teach you everything you need to know to gain confidence then award you a certificate of completion without going into a class room or spending 1000s of Dollars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management Essential Training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-management-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-management-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>Project management is a start-to-finish approach to getting things done and making projects more successful. It&#39;s a profession, but it&#39;s also a set of techniques that anyone can apply to achieve goals and manage project work more effectively. Project management can be used to guide small, simple projects as well as complex enterprise-wide initiatives.
In this course you&#39;ll be fascinated by how things work and how to make things work better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum Fundamentals for Scrum Master and Agile Projects</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/scrum-fundamentals-for-scrum-master-and-agile-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/scrum-fundamentals-for-scrum-master-and-agile-projects/</guid>
      <description>This course provides a comprehensive overview of the Scrum framework for agile project management. You’ll learn the basics of Scrum and the Scrum lifecycle, how to organize a Scrum team and set up a project, and how to implement a Scrum, from releases and sprints to enterprise transformation. This course is for anyone involved in product delivery using the Scrum framework. It is particularly beneficial for those people within an organization accountable for getting the most out of Scrum, including Scrum Masters, managers, and Scrum Team members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brilliant StartUp - Liderazgo para jóvenes profesionales</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/brilliant-startup-liderazgo-para-j%C3%B3venes-profesionales/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/brilliant-startup-liderazgo-para-j%C3%B3venes-profesionales/</guid>
      <description>Hace dos o tres años atrás pensaba que me hubiese gustado que me enseñen cuando era joven profesional y con eso hubiese potenciado mi carrera como profesional. Como aprenderlos durante el recorrido, cambio mi forma de gestionar, problemas, personas, equipos y transformaciones. Son esas cosas que nos van transformando un poquito todos los días.
En el curso verán las 12 herramientas dividas en 4 módulos, en total son 14 vídeos de entre 7-10 minutos don de le contare, historias, experiencias, conocimientos, tips y consejos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMI Scheduling Professional (PMI-SP)® Pro Tests Simulator</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pmi-scheduling-professional-pmi-sp-pro-tests-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pmi-scheduling-professional-pmi-sp-pro-tests-simulator/</guid>
      <description>2022 PMI Scheduling Professional (PMI-SP)® Pro Tests Simulator Most common questions for PMI Scheduling Professional (PMI-SP)® The Project Management Institute (PMI) ® offers a professional credential for project schedulers, known as the PMI Scheduling Professional (PMI-SP)®. PMI&#39;s professional credentialing examination development processes stand apart from other project management certification examination development practices. PMI serves more than three million professionals including over 650,000 members in 213 countries and territories around the world, with 303 chapters and 14,000 volunteers serving local members in over 180 countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management Professional [PMP] Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-management-professional-pmp-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-management-professional-pmp-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>2022 Project Management Professional [PMP] Practice Tests
Boost your Salary !
Top PMP Exam Questions with detailed Answers; Real PMP simulator Project Management Professional (PMP) is an internationally recognized professional designation offered by the Project Management Institute (PMI). As of 31 July 2020, there are 1,036,367 active PMP-certified individuals and 314 chartered chapters across 214 countries and territories worldwide.
The exam is one of eight credentials offered by PMI and is based on the PMI Project Management Body of Knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash Course: Project Management Fundamentals [Earn 6 PDUs]</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crash-course-project-management-fundamentals-earn-6-pdus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crash-course-project-management-fundamentals-earn-6-pdus/</guid>
      <description>Looking to get into one of the fastest growing professions in the modern world or just to brush up on your fundamental knowledge? Either way, this course is for you.
Project management is growing at an immense rate, that despite the job market uncertainties brought about by the 4th industrial revolution. The Project Management Institute (PMI), probably the most recognized authority on project management worldwide, estimates that job growth in the project management industry will be a staggering 33% or 22 million jobs by 2027.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practice Exam - PMI-SP® : PMI Scheduling Professional 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/practice-exam-pmi-sp-pmi-scheduling-professional-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/practice-exam-pmi-sp-pmi-scheduling-professional-2022/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED to the new PMI-SP Exam version!
Are you ready for this learning journey ? let&#39;s go !!
Why taking this practice exams ?
You can retake the exams as many times as you want
This is a huge original question bank
You get support from instructors if you have questions
30-days money-back guarantee if you&#39;re not satisfied
What you will get?
Fresh and updated material
Questions and Answers in Practice Mode</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management Professional (PMP) Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-management-professional-pmp-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:33:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-management-professional-pmp-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>The Project Management Professional (PMP)® is the world&#39;s leading project management certification. Now including predictive, agile and hybrid approaches, the PMP® proves project leadership experience and expertise in any way of working. It supercharges careers for project leaders across industries and helps organizations find the people they need to work smarter and perform better.
Research indicates that employers will need to fill nearly 2.2 million new project-oriented roles each year through 2027.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change Management: Make the Change!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/change-management-make-the-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/change-management-make-the-change/</guid>
      <description>We all live in times of constant change - personally and professionally. That&#39;s not a bad thing but not everyone is always ready to change. Having worked in many engineering projects and having lived in various countries, I have lots of first hand experience managing personal and professional change projects. I created this training because it would have helped me a lot and spared me some mistakes (believe me!) if I had had a hands on training for change management when I started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PBA Exam Prep Professional in Business Analysis 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pba-exam-prep-professional-in-business-analysis-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pba-exam-prep-professional-in-business-analysis-2022/</guid>
      <description>[january 2022 Updated]: Latest exam questions added.
Get Ready To Prepare Like You’ve Never Prepared Before!!!
Finally! Pass Professional in Business Analysis (PMI-PBA) – Associate Exam in just 3 days with a 100% money-back guarantee.
Preparing for your PMI-PBA Certified certification, assess your knowledge of topics on the exam with these practice test questions.
The purpose of this Practice Question Set is to help you pass the Certified of PMI-PBA Professional in Business Analysis – Associate exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanban Metrics for Agile teams: Measure &amp; Improve Flow</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kanban-metrics-for-agile-teams-measure-improve-flow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kanban-metrics-for-agile-teams-measure-improve-flow/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the course on Kanban Flow Metrics!
About Kanban Flow Metrics
In order to build successful &amp;amp; productive teams, establishing a stable workflow is important. A stable workflow helps your organization to deliver the product faster and with greater customer value. But how can you measure the success rate of your workflow and improve it?
The answer is simple - with statistically significant data. And it is therefore essential to track the right metrics in order to make meaningful tweaks to your Kanban workflow and setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantity Surveyor&#39;s Guide for Pre-Contracts Management</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quantity-surveyors-guide-for-pre-contracts-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quantity-surveyors-guide-for-pre-contracts-management/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this course on Quantity Surveyor&#39;s Guide for Pre-Contracts Management.
Quantity Surveyor&#39;s play an important role during the Pre Contracts Stage of any project. During this stage, if proper management of works are done, then once the execution stage of the project begins, the chances of the project getting successfully completed is very high.
By the end of this course, you will learn the following:
Different Tender Documents involved in a Construction Project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Confluence A-Z: Confluence for New Users</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/atlassian-confluence-a-z-confluence-for-new-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 13:36:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/atlassian-confluence-a-z-confluence-for-new-users/</guid>
      <description>Confluence is a powerful enterprise collaboration tool that brings people, knowledge, and ideas together in a shared workspace, so you can do your best work. Through this course &#34;Atlassian Confluence Masterclass&#34;, you will learn how to use Confluence to transform the way your team works.
This course is structured to guide you through all the key aspects of managing and using Confluence.
Whether you’re new to Confluence, training your teammates, or ready to take your Confluence skills to the next level, this guide covers everything from the basics to in-depth best practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management: Becoming a &#39;Successful Project manager&#39;</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-management-becoming-a-successful-project-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 13:36:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-management-becoming-a-successful-project-manager/</guid>
      <description>If you are starting out, you may be wondering: what are the most important Project Management concepts that you need to understand? That’s what you will learn in this Course.
Project Management is not only a fabulous discipline for building a career around, it is one of the most valuable life-skills you can acquire.
We have selected the topics based on the suggestions of Experts in the PM field. So, as course focuses mainly on, delivering the core content on Management techniques which is easily understandable by all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management: Cost &amp; Schedule Monitoring using EVM</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-management-cost-schedule-monitoring-using-evm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 15:08:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-management-cost-schedule-monitoring-using-evm/</guid>
      <description>The course will help you understand the basic concepts of Earned Value Management which is one of the most important technique for effective Project Management.
By the end of this course you will learn the key terms of Earned Value Management, their definitions and the various formulas used to analyze whether the project is getting executed on track with respect to cost and schedule.
The course lets you understand the concept of Budget, Planned Value, Earned Value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Root Cause Analysis: 5 Whys Diagram</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/root-cause-analysis-5-whys-diagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/root-cause-analysis-5-whys-diagram/</guid>
      <description>The 5 Whys Diagram is one of the most important root cause analysis tools there is. Understanding its purpose and knowing how and when to deploy it is a skill highly in demand in today&#39;s market. Whether you are an employee, manager or business owner, having the ability to identify a problem, discover its root cause and act to fix it quickly is crucial. The deployment of this tool can lead to large scale error reduction, process improvement and even financial savings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects Cost Management, Estimating, Budgeting and Control.</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/projects-cost-management-estimating-budgeting-and-control./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 20:40:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/projects-cost-management-estimating-budgeting-and-control./</guid>
      <description>This course consist of two parts. The fist part is a theoretical explanation based on the cost management chapter from PMBOK (the book that is used for PMP certificate) and the second part is a practical example about how to apply the theoretical part..
Both parts talk about three main topics:
How to estimate costs for activities in the project, which also include:
Types of Costs
Estimating costs tools and techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantity Surveying Templates for Effective Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quantity-surveying-templates-for-effective-cost-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 20:40:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quantity-surveying-templates-for-effective-cost-management/</guid>
      <description>This course explains the different Quantity Surveying templates created by me for effective post contract cost management.
You can download these templates and use it in your professional life.
By the end of this course, you will learn the below :
Prepare a perfect payment application summary for the interim payment applications.
Able to properly track both the inward and outward payments specific to the project.
Efficiently monitor and update the variations and claims status of the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basics of Agile</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basics-of-agile/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basics-of-agile/</guid>
      <description>You will learn Agile principles, values, approaches, &amp;amp; mindset to help organizations make changes faster and with less expense. This course will not only teach you the fundamentals of Agile to help you develop the adaptive mindset, but it will also break down the most popular Agile frameworks such as Scrum.
Here is what you will receive with your enrollment:
High-quality video lectures that explain the different terms and concepts with real world examples and applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management Course: Project Monitoring, Control &amp; EVM</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-management-course-project-monitoring-control-evm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-management-course-project-monitoring-control-evm/</guid>
      <description>Project management is an extremely intricate field and requires you to have knowledge in several technical areas of expertise. The 5 process groups ranging from project initiation to project closure are all very important pieces of the overall puzzle and you will need to master them all to distinguish yourself as one of the best project managers. Depending on who you talk to, they may have different ideas on which of the process groups should be considered more or less important than the others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management Crash Course in 60 Minutes</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-management-crash-course-in-60-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:10:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-management-crash-course-in-60-minutes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Project Management Crash Course.
This course is designed to help you for your practical day to day project management, to improve your project management knowledge, skills and to enhance your career by understanding and opting for best suited project management certification for you.
- You will learn the basic concepts of Project management to understand difference between a project and operations, classification of projects, programme and portfolio and the understanding of project management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contracts Management in Construction Projects</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/contracts-management-in-construction-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/contracts-management-in-construction-projects/</guid>
      <description>Every construction project is bound by a Contract. Proper Contract Management plays a major role in the effective management of your construction projects. Adhering to all the Contractual obligations, the terms and conditions can save both cost and time. There are a few standard Contract Forms that is followed in a Construction project mainly FIDIC (International Federation of Consulting Engineers), NRM (New Rules of Measurement), JCT (The Joint Contracts Tribunal). The procedures to commence work, the documents required at each stage of the project, variation procedures, payment terms, basis for termination and suspension of works by either parties, completion of work, roles and responsibilities of all the stake holders and their staffs, dispute resolution methods, Arbitration procedures etc are all mentioned in the contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn the ESSENTIAL concepts of Project Management in 2 hrs</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-the-essential-concepts-of-project-management-in-2-hrs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-the-essential-concepts-of-project-management-in-2-hrs/</guid>
      <description>PROJECTS ARE EVERYWHERE!!
Are you confused about Project Management and do you think you will benefit from learning the most important aspects of project management? This course will set you on course and will allow you to PROGRESS at work whether you are from the business or part of technical team. This course could also enlighten you to start a potential NEW CAREER as Project Manager.
After attending this course you will - Get an edge by understanding what few people know about Project Management</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SIMULADOR PMP 2022 GUIA preguntas Examen Vol II</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/simulador-pmp-2022-guia-preguntas-examen-vol-ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/simulador-pmp-2022-guia-preguntas-examen-vol-ii/</guid>
      <description>PMP corresponde a las siglas de Project Management Professional (Profesional en Dirección de Proyectos) y hace referencia a una certificación que garantiza que una persona tiene conocimientos y experiencia en la gestión de proyectos. Lo emite el Instituto de la Gestión de Proyectos —PMI, por sus siglas en inglés— de Pensilvania (Estados Unidos).
El simulador incluye preguntas de opción múltiple y múltiples respuestas, tal como es el nuevo formato del examen desde enero del año 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum Certification 2022 &#43;Scrum Master&#43; Agile Scrum Training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/scrum-certification-2022-scrum-master-agile-scrum-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 21:27:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/scrum-certification-2022-scrum-master-agile-scrum-training/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Scrum Open, Professional Scrum™, Professional Scrum Master™, PSM, PSM I, PSM 1, etc. is the protected brand of Scrum . org. Our course and practice exams are neither endorsed by nor affiliated with Scrum . org.&#34; Three reasons to TAKE THIS COURSE right now! The unique reasons for taking this course are: Complete, Concise, Confident Overview of Scrum - You will be confident that you have learned Scrum as the founders intended because I only teach accurately from the rule-book of Scrum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flowchart mapping</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/flowchart-mapping/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 20:10:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/flowchart-mapping/</guid>
      <description>Being able to map a flowchart is something highly in demand in today’s world. If you’re an employee, your manager wants to see how much more value you can bring to your role – and being able to map out your key processes for a variety of purposes is one way you can do this. If you’re a business owner, it is crucial you know exactly what is going on in each and every process that makes up your organisation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Project Management: Agile, Scrum, Kanban &amp; XP</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-project-management-agile-scrum-kanban-xp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-project-management-agile-scrum-kanban-xp/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Course on Agile Project Management!
Software industry is going crazy on agile methods. It is rapidly becoming the choice for software development where requirements are unpredictable or is expected to change over time. This course will help you explore how working on an Agile project has benefits for your development team, your end users, and your organization as a whole.
Here is a list of the topics we will cover in this course:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Kanban | Project Management | Certify | Board &amp; Card</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-kanban-project-management-certify-board-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 19:15:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-kanban-project-management-certify-board-card/</guid>
      <description>Please note that this course and practice exams are neither endorsed by, nor in partnership, nor affiliated with Scrum org or any other Kanban Certification agency.
Welcome to the complete Course on KANBAN. Around 35+ video lectures
Numerous Reading material and real world based activities to explain Kanban concepts in detail
External Resources to show real world examples
Multiple Quizzes for Kanban concepts
Kanban Practice Test based on various certification exams</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Project Management | Agile Delivery | Agile Teams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-project-management-agile-delivery-agile-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 19:15:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-project-management-agile-delivery-agile-teams/</guid>
      <description>If you are looking to learn Agile Project Management Concept, you have landed at the right place.
The use of Agile methodologies is growing at an incredible rate, the basic way we do traditional plan-driven project management hasn&#39;t changed significantly since the 1950&#39;s and 1960&#39;s and the rate of technology change today is making a pure plan-driven approach very cumbersome and impractical to implement in many real-world situations. ****************************************REVIEW FOR THE COURSE ************************</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Construction Estimating Quantity Takeoff Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/construction-estimating-quantity-takeoff-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 19:15:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/construction-estimating-quantity-takeoff-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Construction Estimating Quantity Takeoff Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn industry specific knowledge about construction estimation.
I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on how to master the art of quantity takeoff.
If you are a professional who are interested to work as an estimator for construction projects or just got a job in the construction industry, you will find this course of great help to get the fundamental knowledge you need to kick start your professional career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2022 PMI Scheduling Professional (PMI-SP) Be PRO Planner</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2022-pmi-scheduling-professional-pmi-sp-be-pro-planner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2022-pmi-scheduling-professional-pmi-sp-be-pro-planner/</guid>
      <description>PMI Scheduling Professional (PMI-SP) Be PRO Planner
Get Ready to be PMI Scheduling Professional (PMI-SP) based on American project management institute PMI
The Project Management Institute (PMI) ® offers a professional credential for project schedulers, known as the PMI Scheduling Professional (PMI-SP)®. PMI&#39;s professional credentialing examination development processes stand apart from other project management certification examination development practices.
To be qualified for this certification, you need to have a four-year degree and 3,500 hours of project scheduling experience, which is around 2 years of experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOP Risk Management Professional (PMI-RMP) Questions</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/top-risk-management-professional-pmi-rmp-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/top-risk-management-professional-pmi-rmp-questions/</guid>
      <description>TOP Risk Management Professional (PMI-RMP) Questions
PMI RMP Preparation with UPDATED UNIQUE questions and detailed answers
Boost your salary and Career
The PMI Risk Management Professional (PMI-RMP)® highlights your ability to identify and assess project risks, mitigate threats and capitalize on opportunities. In this capacity, you enhance and protect the needs of your organization.
Gaining distinction as a PMI-RMP® sets you apart from other professionals and brings credit to your organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Kanban Organised: From To-Do To Done With Kanban Boards</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/get-kanban-organised-from-to-do-to-done-with-kanban-boards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/get-kanban-organised-from-to-do-to-done-with-kanban-boards/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Great course. I have been using Jira board to drive delivery of projects at work and never thought to apply this in my personal life. Since I set it up two weeks ago, I am more organized. I can easy add tasks onto the backlog and decide what needs to be done next and what can go into upcoming sprints. Thanks Peter.&#34; - Simangele S.
&#34;The course provides step by step guidance on how to use a Kanban board.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lean Six Sigma White Belt: Certification</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lean-six-sigma-white-belt-certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 21:10:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lean-six-sigma-white-belt-certification/</guid>
      <description>Lean Six Sigma is an extremely powerful methodology, capable of saving organisations vast amounts of money and time. Having the skills, knowledge and understanding given by Lean Six Sigma is increasingly important in todays workplace. Organisations want their employees and consultants to know how to make processes more efficient, how to increase the quality of products and how to save time and money that can ultimately be reinvested back into the organisation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HVAC Ductwork Quantity Take off for Quantity Surveyors</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hvac-ductwork-quantity-take-off-for-quantity-surveyors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 09:09:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hvac-ductwork-quantity-take-off-for-quantity-surveyors/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this course on HVAC Duct Quantity Take off.
HVAC stands for Heating, Cooling, Air Conditioning. It forms a part of MEP Services.
Ducts are used as a medium for transmission of air from the equipment&#39;s to different rooms in a building.
Accurate estimation of DUCT quantities is critical for an effective cost management of a construction project. In this course you will understand how to take off the HVAC duct quantity using different unit of measurements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMP Mock Test Exam : Get Ready for PMP Certification.</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pmp-mock-test-exam-get-ready-for-pmp-certification./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 12:24:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pmp-mock-test-exam-get-ready-for-pmp-certification./</guid>
      <description>Hi to all the aspirants of the PMP Exam, in this mock series you will go through a lot of questions that will help you prepare for the quality scenario-based questions and problems that you might have encountered, practiced, and solved while preparing for the PMP exam.
In order to be prepared for the PMP exam, you have to familiarize yourself with the Exam and for that you need to test your limits and know where you stand, while solving the exam questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basecamp can help you organise and delegate your projects.</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basecamp-can-help-you-organise-and-delegate-your-projects./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:37:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basecamp-can-help-you-organise-and-delegate-your-projects./</guid>
      <description>Do you want to complete tasks more quickly and with less frustration while still ensuring high-quality results?
If you answered yes, I have some good news for you... In a nutshell, &#34;Basecamp.&#34;
Basecamp is the best project management platform for internet entrepreneurs ever created.
With over 2 million customers, the company has built one of the internet&#39;s oldest and longest-surviving businesses.
They began as a web design firm and have evolved into the market leader in project management software over the course of 18 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Run Your Business From The Cloud</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-run-your-business-from-the-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 12:41:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-run-your-business-from-the-cloud/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;ve probably heard the term &#34;Cloud&#34; thrown around online.
Did you know that running everything in the cloud can help you save both time and resources?
Cloud computing has now become the norm. You no longer need to invest in multiple supercomputers or high-end servers.
Everything can be done straight from the cloud, and everyone can have access to it.
There’s no way around this fact, and soon you’ll come to that realization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Il Corso Fondamentale di Project Management</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/il-corso-fondamentale-di-project-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 18:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/il-corso-fondamentale-di-project-management/</guid>
      <description>Questo corso di Project Management è nato per trasmetterti tutte le conoscenze e le tecniche fondamentali da applicare direttamente sul campo.
Dalla farmaceutica alle no-profit, dall&#39;ingegneria aerospaziale al marketing digitale si avviano progetti, e per ognuno di essi serve il Project Manager per gestirlo.
Migliora la tua carriera con nuovi orizzonti, metti in risalto le tue doti rispetto a tutti gli altri.
Se ti piace vedere le cose sia nel loro insieme e sia nei dettagli singoli, potresti essere un Project Manager perfetto.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanban: Agile Kanban Productivity &amp; Efficiency&#43;Agile Scrum</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kanban-agile-kanban-productivity-efficiency-agile-scrum/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 13:37:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kanban-agile-kanban-productivity-efficiency-agile-scrum/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Scrum Open, Professional Scrum™, Professional Scrum Master™, PSM, PSM I, PSM 1, etc. is the protected brand of Scrum . org. Our course and practice exams are neither endorsed by nor affiliated with Scrum . org.&#34;
Three reasons to TAKE THIS COURSE right now!
The unique reasons for taking this course are:
Complete, Concise, Confident Overview of Kanban - I cover the theory and give you examples of how the theory is used in industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Scrum Advanced Software Development&#43;Program Management</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-scrum-advanced-software-development-program-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 17:12:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-scrum-advanced-software-development-program-management/</guid>
      <description>THIS COURSE HAS BEEN DESIGNED TO SAVE YOU HUNDREDS IF NOT THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS ON ADVANCED SCRUM TRAINING AS A SCRUM MASTER, PROGRAM MANAGER, TEAM MEMBER, OR PRODUCT OWNER.
&#34;Scrum Open, Professional Scrum™, Professional Scrum Master™, PSM, PSM I, PSM 1, etc. is the protected brand of Scrum . org. Our course and practice exams are neither endorsed by nor affiliated with Scrum . org.&#34;
Three reasons to TAKE THIS COURSE right now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2022 NEW PMBOK 6th Version of Agile PMI-PMP Exam PMP</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2022-new-pmbok-6th-version-of-agile-pmi-pmp-exam-pmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 17:51:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2022-new-pmbok-6th-version-of-agile-pmi-pmp-exam-pmp/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Agile PMP EXAM SIMULATOR 2022
NEW PMBOK 6th
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily
This New REAL LATEST VERSION EXAMS 200 Q and A Exam aligns to the new PMP 2021 Exam Content Outline
Project Management Professional PMP is an internationally recognized professional designation offered by the Project Management Institute PMI . Project Management Professional PMP boosts your career and salary. PMP increases your opportunities for TOP management positions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Story Mapping Workshop - Scrum Product Owner</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/user-story-mapping-workshop-scrum-product-owner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 17:51:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/user-story-mapping-workshop-scrum-product-owner/</guid>
      <description>About this class
Did you realize how difficult is to visualize the product as a whole when working with a typical Flat Product Backlog?
A solution is User Story Mapping. A user story map is a simple idea, is about arranging user stories into a helpful shape. User Story mapping is used by top companies of any industry to visualize goals with activities and agree fast on how to achieve them with minimum versions of the product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified Associate in Project Management (CAPM) Simulator</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-associate-in-project-management-capm-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-associate-in-project-management-capm-simulator/</guid>
      <description>Certified Associate in Project Management (CAPM)
REAL practical SIMULATOR for Certified Associate in Project Management (CAPM)
To earn your Certified Associate in Project Management (CAPM)® certification, you need to meet the experience or education requirements, and pass the CAPM examination, a 150-question exam.
Regardless of how advanced your project experience or education might be, you should still prepare vigorously for the exam.
Successful CAPM candidates typically use multiple study aids — including courses, self-study and study groups — and will spend many hours to prepare, so make sure you leave yourself plenty of preparation time before you take the exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrum Ceremonies Simplified</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/scrum-ceremonies-simplified/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 13:01:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/scrum-ceremonies-simplified/</guid>
      <description>This is a crash course to learn how to facilitate Scrum ceremonies effectively with the help of best practices, gamification, and tips. By the end of this course, you will learn all about how to participate and facilitate below:
Backlog Refinement
Sprint Planning
Daily Standup
Sprint Review
Sprint Retrospective
Note: If you have already enrolled in my other course, &#34;Applying Scrum&#34;, you need not enroll in this one.
This course will set a strong foundation for Scrum Masters, Product Owners, and Engineers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Stories for Agile Scrum&#43;Product Owner&#43;Business Analysis</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/user-stories-for-agile-scrum-product-owner-business-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 20:57:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/user-stories-for-agile-scrum-product-owner-business-analysis/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Scrum Open, Professional Scrum™, Professional Scrum Master™, PSM, PSM I, PSM 1, etc. is the protected brand of Scrum . org. Our course and practice exams are neither endorsed by nor affiliated with Scrum . org.&#34;
Three reasons to TAKE THIS COURSE right now!
The unique reasons for taking this course are:
Complete, Concise, Confident Overview of User Stories - I cover all of the theory and give you examples of how the theory is used in industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management: Deliver on Time &#43; Scrum Project Delivery</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-management-deliver-on-time--scrum-project-delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-management-deliver-on-time--scrum-project-delivery/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Scrum Open, Professional Scrum™, Professional Scrum Master™, PSM, PSM I, PSM 1, etc. is the protected brand of Scrum . org. Our course and practice exams are neither endorsed by nor affiliated with Scrum . org.&#34;
Three reasons to TAKE THIS COURSE right now!
The unique reasons for taking this course are:
Complete, Concise, Confident Overview of Project Delivery &amp;amp; Meeting Deadlines using agile scrum - I cover the theory and give you examples of how the theory is used in industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAFe® Agilist | Leading SAFe® Test papers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/safe-agilist-leading-safe-test-papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/safe-agilist-leading-safe-test-papers/</guid>
      <description>Scaled Agile, Inc is a protected Brand. These practice tests are neither endorsed by nor affiliated with Scaled Agile, Inc. The questions are created based on the material for the exam and help students identify weak areas to improve upon for the actual exam.
This course contains 6 practice tests each containing 45 questions just like the real &#34;Leading SAFe®&#34; exam required to get SAFe® Agilist&#34; certificate. These tests will help you pass SAFe® Agilist 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>دورة إدارة المشاريع الاحترافية بالعربي PMP Prep. Arabic</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%AF%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%A9-%D8%A5%D8%AF%D8%A7%D8%B1%D8%A9-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D8%B4%D8%A7%D8%B1%D9%8A%D8%B9-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81%D9%8A%D8%A9-%D8%A8%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B9%D8%B1%D8%A8%D9%8A-pmp-prep.-arabic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%AF%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%A9-%D8%A5%D8%AF%D8%A7%D8%B1%D8%A9-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D8%B4%D8%A7%D8%B1%D9%8A%D8%B9-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81%D9%8A%D8%A9-%D8%A8%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B9%D8%B1%D8%A8%D9%8A-pmp-prep.-arabic/</guid>
      <description>تحديث هام: هناك إصدار أحدث من الكتاب وهو الإصدار السادس, هذا الكورس معتمد على الإصدار الخامس, بالرغم من أن الاختلافات ليست كبيرة ولكن إذا أردتم التقدم للامتحان فيفضل حضور كورس آخر يعتمد على الإصدار السادس. وحتى تحديث هذا الكورس للإصدار الجديد سأبقيه مجاناً.
تحديث هام 2: غيّر موقع يوديمي سياسيته بخصوص الكورسات المجانية وأوقف إعطاء شهادات الحضور لها, للأسف هذا الكورس لم يعد يزود شهادة حضور ما دام مجانياً.
تحديث 3: بإمكانك الحصول على الكورس مجاناً, فقط أرسل إيميل بذلك هنا</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Project 2019 Course for beginners to advanced</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-project-2019-course-for-beginners-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-project-2019-course-for-beginners-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Our objective is to present you the course in a easiest way, make you feel it is easy to use, easy to grasp, easy to learn and easy to implement in your project management goals.
This course is developed keeping in considerations about growing requirements and aspirations of students, mid-professionals, young-professionals in learning the project management skills. The planning is pre-requisite before starting any meaningful project nowadays for all kind of industries such as construction, software and manufacturing sectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Business Productivity Training Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/best-business-productivity-training-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/best-business-productivity-training-course/</guid>
      <description>In This Online Course You Will Learn About The Major Productivity Challenges Facing Companies Today … These Challenges Can Make Or Break A Businesses. This Amazing Online Training Will Give Your Business Or Career An Unfair Advantage Against The Competition.
In This Productivity Training Course You Will Discover Specific Tools, Strategies And Techniques To Beat These Challenges. By Learning How To Think Like A Top Producer … You Can Make Massive Advances In Your Business Or Career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAPM  Practice Tests: 3 Real CAPM Exams (UPDATED JULY 2021)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/capm-practice-tests-3-real-capm-exams-updated-july-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/capm-practice-tests-3-real-capm-exams-updated-july-2021/</guid>
      <description>PMI&#39;s Certified Associate in Project Management (CAPM) is an entry-level certification for project practitioners, designed for those with less experience.
The CAPM Certification tests an individual’s knowledge of the Project Management Body of Knowledge (PMBOK® Guide).
Overview of the CAPM Certification The CAPM certification offers recognition to practitioners who are interested in or are just starting a career in project management, as well as project team members who wish to demonstrate their project management knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMP Practice Test Exam 2021-PMBOK6</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pmp-practice-test-exam-2021-pmbok6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pmp-practice-test-exam-2021-pmbok6/</guid>
      <description>In the Practice Tests for PMP, you&#39;ll be challenged with 560 PMP practice exam questions based on the PMBOK Guide, sixth edition. These question have been collated to emulate the PMP exam and are based on the PMP exam objectives as provided by PMI and are current keeping in mind the current updates to the PMP exam in 2021.
This course has been updated to reflect the new PMP Exam domains</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 PMP Mock Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2021-pmp-mock-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2021-pmp-mock-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>These mock tests are specially created to assist PMP® aspirants to get familiar with the new 2021 PMP® Exam format and test their understanding of the PMP® Exam syllabus.
After taking these prep tests, you will get a clear idea about your readiness for the real exam and you will be able to identify and focus on your weakness points. This preparation course includes a sum of 380 questions to make sure you’ll be able to face all possibilities and scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Level PMP Mock Questions</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-level-pmp-mock-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-level-pmp-mock-questions/</guid>
      <description>2021 Advanced PMP Exam Simulator: Boost your confidence and proficiency before taking the PMP certification exam.
This course offers a simulation of the updated 2021 PMP exam, providing 180 highly realistic mock questions to help you test your understanding of project management knowledge areas &amp;amp; approaches.
These practice tests were created to prepare you for the real PMP Exam, identifying any knowledge gaps and clearing any hard-to-understand concepts.
This simulator is broken down into 3 parts to mimic the real-exam experience, which suggests a 10-minute break after each set of 60 questions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
