<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mental Health on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/mental-health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mental Health on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/mental-health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kick Out Depression -Complete Treatment 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kick-out-depression-complete-treatment-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kick-out-depression-complete-treatment-2022/</guid>
      <description>Depression (major depressive disorder) is a common and serious medical illness that negatively affects how you feel, think, and act. Fortunately, it is also treatable. Depression causes feelings of sadness and/or a loss of interest in activities you once enjoyed. It can lead to various emotional and physical problems and decrease your ability to function at work and home.
You will learn in this course:-
1. About Depression.
2. How Depression affects your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBT and Nutrition Ultimate Certification Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cbt-and-nutrition-ultimate-certification-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cbt-and-nutrition-ultimate-certification-course/</guid>
      <description>Research in the medical and behavioural sciences and information about cognitive behavioural therapy and pharmacological treatments for mental disorders is rapidly changing. Furthermore, medical and health concerns are unique to each individual and require individual attention and care.
Cognitive-behavioural therapy (CBT) holds a unique status in the field of mental health – CBT is effective for many psychological problems, is relatively brief, and is well received by individuals
A large volume of research has been published regarding CBT, including a number of well-designed studies involving people in “real world” clinical settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBT: Complete psychotherapy Certificate Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cbt-complete-psychotherapy-certificate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cbt-complete-psychotherapy-certificate-course/</guid>
      <description>CBT is an intensive, short-term, problem-oriented approach. It was designed to be quick, practical and goal-oriented and to provide people with long-term skills to keep them healthy. The focus of cbt is on the problems that come up in a person’s day-to-day life. cbt helps people to look at how they interpret and evaluate what is happening around them and the effects these perceptions have on their emotional experience.
Childhood experiences and events, while not the focus of cbt, may also be reviewed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overcome Depression with Cognitive Behavioural Therapy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/overcome-depression-with-cognitive-behavioural-therapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/overcome-depression-with-cognitive-behavioural-therapy/</guid>
      <description>Deal with your Depression and Live a More Fulfilled Life
264 million people around the world suffer from major depression. Depression is fully treatable and people can recover from it and live fulfilling lives.
Does this sound like you?
I feel drained of my physical and mental energy
I’m no longer interested in things I used to enjoy
My body weight has increased/decreased rapidly
My sleep pattern has changed - I’m not sleeping enough/I’m sleeping more than usual</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stress Management - 1-Hour Intro Course - Reduce Stress Now</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/stress-management-1-hour-intro-course-reduce-stress-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/stress-management-1-hour-intro-course-reduce-stress-now/</guid>
      <description>Stress Management - 1-Hour Intro Course - Reduce Stress NowStress Management Strategies to Improves Your Quality of Life Now - Mindfulness - Anxiety Management - Resilience
You can manage your stress today. Stop going through life in a stressful, harried and hurried manner.
Best selling personal development course creator TJ Walker takes you through the fastest and easiest steps to regain control of your life and to reduce harmful stress. Some stress is unavoidable, but you can eliminate needless stress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become Depression Counselor - Major Depressive Disorder</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/become-depression-counselor-major-depressive-disorder/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 22:42:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/become-depression-counselor-major-depressive-disorder/</guid>
      <description>Become Depression Counsellor - Major Depressive Disorder
Depression Counseling made Simpler and Effective - MDD
Provide Effective Depression Counseling to Clients with MDD. A result-oriented approach to improve your counselling skill
In this course, I share the unique insights that I have learned through my years in counselling depressive clients. Knowledge builds upon the knowledge, so it is always a good idea to learn from other mental health professionals. I share useful analogies, mindset shifts, tools &amp;amp; techniques in this course that you can directly use in your counselling sessions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Yourself Up For Sustainable Sobriety</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/setting-yourself-up-for-sustainable-sobriety/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/setting-yourself-up-for-sustainable-sobriety/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people can decide to quit drinking but maintaining sobriety is another story. If you&#39;ve struggled with the recovery roller coaster of quitting, relapsing, cutting back, and relapsing more times than you remember then you&#39;re not alone. It&#39;s incredibly difficult to stay sober when we don&#39;t have the tools or our mindset is in the dumps after our battle with addiction. This course is here to guide you on your path to recovery so you can build a solid foundation to keep you on your feet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art Therapy for Men (Oxford Diploma)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/art-therapy-for-men-oxford-diploma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/art-therapy-for-men-oxford-diploma/</guid>
      <description>Note: this course does not qualify the recipient to perform any form of therapy or counseling for any other person
This is an unusual course as it is designed to be of use/application to men in particular. Of course it is not &#39;exclusive&#39; just a slight bias. Studies are referenced where appropriate.
Please remember that this course includes:
a. the lectures themselves
b. the Q/A section - make full use of it!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
