<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Happiness on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/happiness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Happiness on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/happiness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Clarity Compass: Finding &amp; Following my Unique Purpose</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/my-clarity-compass-finding-following-my-unique-purpose/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/my-clarity-compass-finding-following-my-unique-purpose/</guid>
      <description>Do you feel frustrated because you outgrew your current situation and are so ready for a change but don’t know where to start? You’re struggling to figure out what you really desire to pursue next in life because you’re overwhelmed &amp;amp; procrastinating any decision because you’re stuck overthinking?
Then this is for you.
My Clarity Compass is a bite sized video online course that will help you to reflect on what you really want in life, what makes you happy &amp;amp; to make a decision with confidence on what you want to pursue next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brain Computer Interfacing via spiking neuromorphic networks</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/brain-computer-interfacing-via-spiking-neuromorphic-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/brain-computer-interfacing-via-spiking-neuromorphic-networks/</guid>
      <description>This exciting course contains two parts. The first part introduces you to the fundamentals of brain functioning prior to Brain-Computer Interfacing in the second part.
The first part of the course aims to provide students with an introduction to the core ideas of the brain involving inculcating happiness and well-being to manage stress, anxiety, and depression. Further acquainting them with the significance of positive thinking, courage, and determination, the meaning of life, gratitude, and compassion in life in the first part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Daily Joy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-daily-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 20:40:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-daily-joy/</guid>
      <description>I’m a strong believer that your day is your life. Yet so many people feel stuck and frustrated living their days on repeat and doing the same things. And I used to be one of those people!
For years I felt trapped because my days were all the same, and my routine left me bored and unfulfilled. I had had enough and I decided I wasn&#39;t going to live my life on repeat anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 10 Laws for Personal Success - The Complete Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-10-laws-for-personal-success-the-complete-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 16:26:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-10-laws-for-personal-success-the-complete-course/</guid>
      <description>The 10 Laws for Personal Success - The Complete Course
Personal success...it can be yours. You can achieve your goals in life, have a great career, build strong relationships, and live your life‘s purpose. Nobody was born with personal success; it is a function of applying skills in a systematic way throughout life.
TJ Walker is one of the top personal development trainers in the world and coaches people on the elements of personal success, personal development, and personal transformation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Happiness Course: Become Happier Now!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-happiness-course-become-happier-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:15:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-happiness-course-become-happier-now/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Happiness Course: Become Happier Now!Happiness Can Be Yours! Learn Happiness Habits to Build Your Personal Success and Enhance Personal Development Today
Your happiness can be chosen. You only get one life, why not make the most of it and learn how to be happy on a daily basis?
Negative habits practiced on a daily basis create but unhappy, unfulfilled life. The positive habits practiced on a daily basis will create a happy life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Steps To Permanent Happiness</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/10-steps-to-permanent-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/10-steps-to-permanent-happiness/</guid>
      <description>This is a lifetime journey that we will take together. I will be your teacher, guide, psychologist, motivator and friend.
To be truly happy we need to learn and understand why we are unhappy, what is happiness and how we can achieve it. We have different types of happiness, but here we are going to be focused on permanent happiness.
For permanent happiness, we have to make changes in our minds and soul.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
