<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Religion &amp; Spirituality on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/religion-spirituality/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Religion &amp; Spirituality on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/religion-spirituality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Certified Diploma Course In Ancestral Healing Level-1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-diploma-course-in-ancestral-healing-level-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-diploma-course-in-ancestral-healing-level-1/</guid>
      <description>Namaskar,
Welcome To Vidya Retreat.
This is our exclusive certified course, which is completely designed by famous Author Dr. Himani. She owns the copyright of this course. Kindly write us in inbox only to get a personal certificate, not in Q &amp;amp; A section. Every 30 days we issue all certificates. Ancestral healing is the procedure of exposing and healing acquired wounds and traumas passed down by our ancestors. Anybody investigating their heritage will discover both positives and negatives that go through the bloodlines from one generation to the next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Manifestation - 12 Universal Laws</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-manifestation-12-universal-laws/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 12:41:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-manifestation-12-universal-laws/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling to manifest your goals? Are you unclear about how the law of attraction works? Do you feel like you&#39;re doing everything right but still not getting the results you want? What if I told you that you are manifesting, but not what you want?
That&#39;s because you may be unaware of the 12 universal laws that govern the universe. These laws operate in tandem with the law of attraction and affect your ability to manifest certain desires.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bible: 7 Lessons From The Book Of Jude Plus The Why..</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bible-7-lessons-from-the-book-of-jude-plus-the-why../</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 15:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bible-7-lessons-from-the-book-of-jude-plus-the-why../</guid>
      <description>The Book of Jude is one of the shortest books of the New Testament. Written by the brother of our Lord Jesus and the brother of James; the book appears just before the book of Revelation in our bibles. Its size must not be mistaken for its potency - small in size yet packs a very big punch. Although the book mirrors much of the content in 2 Peter it provides many unique features of its own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Corinthians: 16 Life Changing Lessons</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/1-corinthians-16-life-changing-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 17:47:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/1-corinthians-16-life-changing-lessons/</guid>
      <description>How To Win: If there was a Book in the Bible that illustrates how a Christian should live in an overtly worldly setting, then 1 Corinthians speaks volumes and offers numerous tactics to help us navigate such terrain.
After starting the Church (Acts 18) the people continued many of their worldly practices alongside their Christian walk. There was division, selfishness, promiscuity, immorality on one side, and extreme living - abstinence from marriage, food, etc on the other side of the spectrum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Stop Fear Spiritually</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-stop-fear-spiritually/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-stop-fear-spiritually/</guid>
      <description>Do you still allow fear to stop you from taking developmental steps?
If you have struggled to put that business idea that has been in your heart for many years&amp;nbsp;to work, then you&#39;re dwelling in the cage of fear.
&amp;nbsp;A wise man once said a child is born without fear except for the ones he&#39;s taught by society&amp;nbsp;as he grows up.
I want you to understand that everyone has the tendency to have fear but those who are great&amp;nbsp;achievers in our society have found a way to consistently kill it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Miraculous Faith</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-miraculous-faith/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-miraculous-faith/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling to overcome a problem or a challenge in your life, business, or marriage? Do you want simple-to-understand and easy-to-apply descriptions or explanations of the Christian faith that will help you solve those nagging problems in your life, business, or marriage?
If those questions apply to you, then this course, ‘The Miraculous Faith: Principles of Christian Faith Manifestation: How to make miracles through faith’ is just the right one for you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
