<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Online Education on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/online-education/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Online Education on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:35:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/online-education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Udemy bootcamp: How to create a STUNNING course Unofficial</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/udemy-bootcamp-how-to-create-a-stunning-course-unofficial/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:35:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/udemy-bootcamp-how-to-create-a-stunning-course-unofficial/</guid>
      <description>Let&#39;s start with the basics, right now you are a person that surely has something to offer, a certain knowledge that you have and that you think you will be able to teach. By creating this course my main objective was to help you by giving you all the tips thats I used to create online content on different plateforms. So if you are someone that is ready to start with udemy and creat your own content this course is for you !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adli Bilişim/Dijital Kursu</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/adli-bili%C5%9Fim/dijital-kursu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:47:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/adli-bili%C5%9Fim/dijital-kursu/</guid>
      <description>Günümüzün dijital dünyasında önemli bir konu olan siber dünya ile ilgili hukuki ve kanuni, ama öncesindeki süreçte de önemli bir yer teşkil ederek üzerinde bilimsel ve pratik çalışmalar yapılmaya ihtiyaç duyulan adli Dijital Bilişim, bu kursta detaylarıyla incelenerek, kursu takip edenler için hem pratikte, günlük yaşamda, hem de mesleki anlamda önemli yeterlilik bilgileri ve tecrübeleri vermektedir.
Bu kurs, Adli Bilişim ile ilgili temel ve genel bilgileri içermektedir. Dersler, akıcı ve anlaşılır bir şekilde olup, her düzeyden başlayabileceğiniz şekilde tasarlanmıştır.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10X Amazon Ebay Dropshipping Fba Wholesale 2021 Para Kazanma</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/10x-amazon-ebay-dropshipping-fba-wholesale-2021-para-kazanma/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/10x-amazon-ebay-dropshipping-fba-wholesale-2021-para-kazanma/</guid>
      <description>2021 yılında hala ticarete başlamadıysan bu kurs tam sana göre. Ben Akın Yılmaz, takım arkadaşlarımla beraber sizlerin ticaretinizi geliştirmenizi ve internet üzerinden gelir elde edebilmeniz için sizlere Udemy üzerinden Ücretisiz eğitimler hazırlıyoruz. Temel ticaret mantığını anlamak ve kendinizi e-ticaret alanında geliştirmek için lütfen bu kursa ve Akın Yılmaz kanalına göz atın. Buralarda sahip olmasını isteyeceğiniz çok kıymetli bilgiler var. Ve siz bu bilgileri edinmelisiniz. Artık kendi paranızı kazanma vaktiniz geldi. Tek yapmanız gereken aksiyon alıp artık başlamak ve ticaretinizi geliştirmek.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Digital Marketing</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-digital-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 13:08:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-digital-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Dear Students,
Are you Preparing for Interview in Digital Marketing? Don’t be stressed, Take our Digital Marketing quiz and prepare yourself for the Interview.
With this Digital Marketing Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and tricks to solve Digital Marketing based questions. Here you will get Digital Marketing based MCQ for your next Job or Exam.
In Digital Marketing Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Knowledge in the field of Digital Marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High School Organic Chemistry 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/high-school-organic-chemistry-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/high-school-organic-chemistry-1/</guid>
      <description>Chemistry is fun when you learn from the best tutors. At Go2uni, we present you “High School Organic Chemistry 1”. We start from the basics and take a deep dive with clear examples and exercises to ensure every concept is understood.
Go2uni presents seasoned tutors with years of experience to offer you &#34;High School Organic Chemistry 1&#34;, the organic chemistry course you need to ace your exams.
This course will demystify Chemistry with tonnes of examples, work through exercises and take-home exercises.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
