<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Memory &amp; Study Skills on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/memory-study-skills/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Memory &amp; Study Skills on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/memory-study-skills/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Memory: 3 Ways of Memorising Like a Spy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/memory-3-ways-of-memorising-like-a-spy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/memory-3-ways-of-memorising-like-a-spy/</guid>
      <description>Our brain is really stubborn at times. It doesn’t want to remember certain things, it doesn’t want to cope with the fact that you just have to remember certain information. Lucky us – this problem can be solved.
This course is about Memory, about memorizing like a spy, so that’s exactly what we are going to do. We are going to learn how to Memory like a spy. Spies have to remember a lot, their life depends on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find your Unique Memory Personality – Intro to Online Test</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/find-your-unique-memory-personality-intro-to-online-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 21:29:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/find-your-unique-memory-personality-intro-to-online-test/</guid>
      <description>Do you know your Unique Memory Personality?
Do you know how you personally learn and remember the easiest and fastest way?
Do you know which of our 12 Secret Memory Languages works best for you?
This course is for you if you are busy and want a fast introduction to your Memory Personality. If you want the advanced Master Class search on Udemy &#34;Next-Generation Memory, Learning &amp;amp; Communication Improvement&#34;.
Hi, I’m Dan Agervig Hansen; Educational &amp;amp; Corporate trainer and coach for 25 years, 3x Best-Selling Author, and creator of the Memory Personality Typology and the 12 Secret Languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Memory Athlete&#39;s Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-memory-athletes-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 23:34:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-memory-athletes-guide/</guid>
      <description>This course will take you through the wonderful world of memory improvement, introducing you to the challenges that memory athletes face, the methods they use, what their memory workouts look like, and how you can become a practitioner of the memory sport yourself.
It is a practical and useful guide for anyone who wants to explore the world of this sport and learn the advanced techniques used by memory athletes to achieve amazing performance with their minds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management 4 Tweens &amp; Teens</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-4-tweens-teens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 12:24:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-4-tweens-teens/</guid>
      <description>In this class students will learn time management skills that will aid them to be much more productive and to minimize stress (if not eliminate it) around schoolwork, and chores. They will leave this course having learned how to manage their time effectively, no longer entertaining distractions, cutting out multitasking and procrastination. Students will learn how to manage their planners, to be organized, how to prioritize, to be strategic and consistent, and to re-frame their perspective regarding chores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neuroplasticity: Teach Your Brain  To Work 3 Times Faster</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/neuroplasticity-teach-your-brain-to-work-3-times-faster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/neuroplasticity-teach-your-brain-to-work-3-times-faster/</guid>
      <description>If you have never imagined what living life on autopilot is, this may be because you are going all autopilot and not realizing it. Being conscious about our lives is the least we can do to actually live the better life.
So, what does neuroplasticity have to do with it? Pretty easy. Neuroplasticity helps our brain to get out of the ‘comfort zone’, of sorts. It helps us learn new things, thus expanding our brain broad and wide for everything new the world can offer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
