<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investing &amp; Trading on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/investing-trading/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Investing &amp; Trading on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/investing-trading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Forex- learn to trade forex by yourself</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-forex-learn-to-trade-forex-by-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-forex-learn-to-trade-forex-by-yourself/</guid>
      <description>The financial markets are not very easy to handle and to trade. The Forex market is the biggest of those with more than 2 trillion dollars exchanged on a daily basis. But, there is a way to make profit out of all those transaction with forex trading and this is the goal of this course. Indeed, if you :
- Are someone who is interested in forex trading but never actually started</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Der große Börsenhandel Ratgeber: Investieren leicht gemacht</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/der-gro%C3%9Fe-b%C3%B6rsenhandel-ratgeber-investieren-leicht-gemacht/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/der-gro%C3%9Fe-b%C3%B6rsenhandel-ratgeber-investieren-leicht-gemacht/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Eine Investition in Wissen bringt die besten Zinsen.&#34; - Benjamin Franklin 

Was sind deine finanziellen Ziele?
Willst du dein traditionelles Einkommen aufbessern?
Planst du einen frühen Ruhestand?
Und strebst du letztendlich nach finanzieller Freiheit?

Auf dem Weg zum finanziellen Erfolg gibt es nur wenige Dinge, die so wichtig sind wie ein gründliches Verständnis davon, wo und wie man investiert. Lass dein Geld nicht auf der Bank liegen, nur weil dir der Aktienmarkt zu kompliziert erscheint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Algorithmic Trading with Python: Technical Analysis Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/algorithmic-trading-with-python-technical-analysis-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/algorithmic-trading-with-python-technical-analysis-strategy/</guid>
      <description>You already have knowledge in python and you want to monetize and diversify your knowledge?
You already have some trading knowledge and you want to learn about algorithmic trading?
You are simply a curious person who wants to get into this subject?

If you answer at least one of these questions, I welcome you to this course. For beginners in python, don&#39;t panic there is a python course (small but condensed) to master this python knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of Hedge Funds</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-hedge-funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-hedge-funds/</guid>
      <description>WHY HEDGE FUNDS?
Hedge funds are one of the most profitable types of alternative assets.
However, they are not easy to comprehend.
Fund structures, investment strategies, provisions and fees, and other elements.
And unfortunately, it&#39;s hard to find a course that covers the essentials of hedge funds.
So it becomes common for a student to:
Not be able to discern among the different investment strategies;
Not know if the provisions negotiated with an investor are helpful to the fund, or not at all;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of Private Equity</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-private-equity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-private-equity/</guid>
      <description>PRIVATE EQUITY, PRIVATE KNOWLEDGE
The PE industry is one of the most lucrative ones.
It&#39;s also complex to understand, if you don&#39;t have the right guide.
A lot of techniques, knowledge and hands-on tips are not usually shared.
Usually, what would find would be generic courses with theoretical materials in terms of valuations or general job descriptions, not going into the details of fund operations, the job, or other elements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to beat the Forex market quick and effective!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-beat-the-forex-market-quick-and-effective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-beat-the-forex-market-quick-and-effective/</guid>
      <description>My name is Destin Brown, a 21-year-old entrepreneur. Been trading forex for 2 years, have been through multiple programs and found they only provide you with common information and most gurus or teachers charge an arm and a leg for this sort of information. Most times it gets confusing trying to figure out which pattern is which or what the overall trend in the market is, but I am here to eliminate all of that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Option Day Trading with Chart Pattern Trading Tools</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/stock-option-day-trading-with-chart-pattern-trading-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/stock-option-day-trading-with-chart-pattern-trading-tools/</guid>
      <description>Can you make 10% in ten minutes trading stock options with Chart Pattern Trading? No one but you knows the answer to that question.
What we do promise is that you will learn the tools in this course to make make 10% in ten minutes on a regular basis. Those tools include how to use our exclusive Waves of Profits software, how to control Fear and Greed, journaling, and identifying patterns of success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Trade Forex Market Structures And Patterns</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-trade-forex-market-structures-and-patterns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-trade-forex-market-structures-and-patterns/</guid>
      <description>Discover the secrets to trading profitably and consistently for maximum profits. This course contains powerful information that can guide you on how to exploit patterns that arise now and then in the markets. Discover when and where to trade, and when and where not to trade.
Thank you for joining our course because you are about to gain more knowledge about the formation of classic forex chart patterns and structures. It is true that they are valid and do indeed work; provided that they are used properly, at the appropriate price levels, and with the correct knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOREX TRADING NOMAD | HOW TO GET FUNDED BY INVESTORS IN 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/forex-trading-nomad-how-to-get-funded-by-investors-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/forex-trading-nomad-how-to-get-funded-by-investors-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>Investors are keen to meet you. The problem is that you may not have anything to offer them yet. This course takes you by the hand and teaches you one strategy that will help you make it in the world of trading or I&#39;ll give you your money back. Then your newly gained knowledge is put to the tests. Once you have successfully passed the tests, you are introduced to the investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Passive Income With Bitcoin Lending</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-make-passive-income-with-bitcoin-lending/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 10:00:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-make-passive-income-with-bitcoin-lending/</guid>
      <description>Passive Income Course Covering Everything You Need To Passively Earn Money From Bitcoin Lending!
******************************************************************************************
Discover How to Make Passive Income Online Using A 6-Step Bitcoin Lending System:
- A step-by-step video for each of the 6-Steps in the Automated System!
- Inside look at my personal accounts!
- Unlimited earnings, with a small upfront investment!
- How to do all of this without any Fees!
- This course is about results!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Altcoin Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/altcoin-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/altcoin-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve not tried using Altcoins and invest the next generation currency, then today is the time to start!

Never before has there been an technology platform of this magnitude that will allow you to reach an audience of billions and rapidly grow your business online at next to zero cost!

Become The Ultimate Altcoins Master and join this course today to learn the same PROVEN success strategy Henry Zhang , the Crypto Currency expert and world-leading trader used to build this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capital Market Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/capital-market-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/capital-market-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Capital Market Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn fundamental knowledge about capital markets that would help you in finding value within the market to maximize your earning potential.

I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on the different aspects of the capital market as well as basic analysis on the market to analyze value of investment instruments as well as noticing important trends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Advance Options Trading Strategies (5 Courses) 11 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/diy-advance-options-trading-strategies-5-courses-11-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:35:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/diy-advance-options-trading-strategies-5-courses-11-hours/</guid>
      <description>*** Course access includes quizzes &amp;amp; homework exercises, 1-on-1 Options Trading instructor support and LIFETIME access! ***
Hear why this is one of the TOP-NOTCH Options Trading course on Udemy:
I believe it is a good value for the money. He offers a lot of information and is willing to help.
-Dwight Douglas
The Author of this course explains in great detail what is important to become a successful options trader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Trading Momentum Based Strategies1- Technical Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/stock-trading-momentum-based-strategies1-technical-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 21:16:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/stock-trading-momentum-based-strategies1-technical-analysis/</guid>
      <description>In this course we will discuss multiple momentum oscillator, which measures both the speed as well as the rise or fall of price movements of a stocks.
Relative Strength Index (or RSI), Stoch, William %R, TSI &amp;amp; MFL are one of the top Technical Analysis Indicator. In this Course these technical indicators are not only shown as merely a indicator but a Complete System for trading.
RSI, Stoch, William %R, TSI &amp;amp; MFL is used by professional to identify the trend, Selling or Buying conditions through Reversal, divergences or simple Buy and sell techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Options Trading MasterClass: Options Trading In Simple Terms</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/options-trading-masterclass-options-trading-in-simple-terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/options-trading-masterclass-options-trading-in-simple-terms/</guid>
      <description>In this Options Trading course, President of Capstone Financial &amp;amp; Author of &#34;Options Trading Strategies for Monthly Income&#34; David J. Melilli will educate you on every aspect of options trading. David will implement his unique options trading process utilizing his extensive knowledge in the area of options trading. David has spent over fifteen years in the options trading arena. This options trading course is taught in an easy to understand, user friendly manner that will excite and help build the confidence to master options trading and it has been designed to educate and enhance every individual that wants to really develop the skills required in the world of options trading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swing Trading Ninja: 12 Hour Complete Swing Trading Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/swing-trading-ninja-12-hour-complete-swing-trading-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 12:58:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/swing-trading-ninja-12-hour-complete-swing-trading-strategy/</guid>
      <description>*** Course access includes quizzes &amp;amp; homework exercises, 1-on-1 instructor support and LIFETIME access! ***
This is best strategy I ever find in my life for swing trader. This is incredible. This milloin dollar startegy. I can say here &#34;knowledge is power&#34;.
-Suhit Kalubarme
it was a great match . I am learning a lot and enjoying class. Working on paper trades as class goes on and see things that I am learning daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income: 27 Ways to Earn Passive Income Online</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/passive-income-27-ways-to-earn-passive-income-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/passive-income-27-ways-to-earn-passive-income-online/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to earn money even while you are sleeping?
Do you want to earn money automatically once you&#39;ve set up the systems?
Then this is the right course for you.
I have been earning passive income already for years and I have helped 1,000&#39;s of people worldwide to do the same through my YouTube channel, Udemy courses and blogs.
Earning passive income works in the following way (in a nutshell):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calcul stochastique pour le trading Forex</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/calcul-stochastique-pour-le-trading-forex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 17:04:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/calcul-stochastique-pour-le-trading-forex/</guid>
      <description>Aujourd&#39;hui, Médaillon, le fond le plus profitable du monde fait en moyenne plus de 60% de gain annuel. Mais comment? Ils sont spécialiser dans la finance quantitative, le trading algorithmique et la mathématisation des processus financier. Ici, dans cette formation, nous allons nous intéresser au calcul stochastique. Nous allons voir qu&#39;elles sont les méthodes de bases du calcul stochastique, voir comment l&#39;appliquer au indice boursier et au forex. 
L&#39;idée principale de cette formation est de voir les bénéfices que l&#39;on peut avoir en combinant deux disciplines très utilisées en finance quantitative: le calcul stochastique et le machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MASTERCLASS: &#39;Inversión en Fondos Mutuos&#39;</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/masterclass-inversi%C3%B3n-en-fondos-mutuos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/masterclass-inversi%C3%B3n-en-fondos-mutuos/</guid>
      <description>Si usted considera que los métodos tradicionales de ahorro que le ofrecen las entidades bancarias de su país no son lo suficientemente buenas para usted debido a su baja rentabilidad y a la creciente inflación, pero a su vez considera que aún no está preparado para dar el gran salto a las inversiones en las bolsas de valores, puesto que ha oído hablar de que es muy riesgoso y que requiere de mucha preparación, entonces esta Masterclass gratuita es adecuada para usted, mi nombre es Jean Pierre Chayña Salas (Economista de profesión) y le mostraré que es posible invertir y sacarle dinero al mercado financiero de forma indirecta jugando bajo sus propios términos y condiciones, aprovechando los beneficios de la banca tradicional y del mercado de valores a través de su banca por Internet BBVA y todo esto desde la comodidad de su casa y ¿Cómo lo haremos?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Trading Ninja: 12 Hours DIY Day Trading Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/day-trading-ninja-12-hours-diy-day-trading-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/day-trading-ninja-12-hours-diy-day-trading-strategy/</guid>
      <description>*** Course access includes quizzes &amp;amp; homework exercises, 1-on-1 instructor support and LIFETIME access! ***
Hear why this is one of the TOP-NOTCH Day Trading course on Udemy:
very practical course , I already made more than 10000$ from 100$ using this course principles . I would like to thank the author for such a good effort. I would like to recommend everyone this course who is struggling in the forex market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aprende las bases para invertir en la bolsa</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aprende-las-bases-para-invertir-en-la-bolsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aprende-las-bases-para-invertir-en-la-bolsa/</guid>
      <description>En este curso aprenderás a leer los 3 estados financieros más importantes que reportan las empresas que cotizan en la bolsa americana (empresas públicas.) Estos son el estado de ingresos, la hoja de balance y el flujo de caja. Con el conocimiento ganado podrás reconocer si ha mejorado o empeorado el desempeño de una empresa pública. De esta forma, sabrás si es conveniente invertir en la empresa analizada. Estaremos usando Yahoo Finanzas para analizar los estados financieros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Futures Trading Mastery 2021 | FREE Top 45 Trading Signals!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/futures-trading-mastery-2021-free-top-45-trading-signals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/futures-trading-mastery-2021-free-top-45-trading-signals/</guid>
      <description>My exclusive course teaches you how to start a successful futures trading business from scratch with zero experience. As one of the world’s 10 years veteran traders, I, Henry Zhang, will personally teach you the same proven strategy I used to build my trading empire from nothing.

Start a lucrative and sustainable trading business today with this complete A-Z guide designed to help everyone from beginners to existing traders looking to increase profits.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>