<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investing &amp; Trading on </title>
    <link>/tags/investing-trading/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Investing &amp; Trading on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 17:46:02 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/investing-trading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Day Trading Ninja: 12 Hours DIY Day Trading Strategy</title>
      <link>/day-trading-ninja-12-hours-diy-day-trading-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 17:46:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/day-trading-ninja-12-hours-diy-day-trading-strategy/</guid>
      <description>*** Course access includes quizzes &amp;amp; homework exercises, 1-on-1 instructor support and LIFETIME access! ***
Hear why this is one of the TOP-NOTCH Day Trading course on Udemy:
very practical course , I already made more than 10000$ from 100$ using this course principles . I would like to thank the author for such a good effort. I would like to recommend everyone this course who is struggling in the forex market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Forex- learn to trade forex by yourself</title>
      <link>/introduction-to-forex-learn-to-trade-forex-by-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/introduction-to-forex-learn-to-trade-forex-by-yourself/</guid>
      <description>The financial markets are not very easy to handle and to trade. The Forex market is the biggest of those with more than 2 trillion dollars exchanged on a daily basis. But, there is a way to make profit out of all those transaction with forex trading and this is the goal of this course. Indeed, if you :
- Are someone who is interested in forex trading but never actually started</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Options Trading MasterClass: Options Trading In Simple Terms</title>
      <link>/options-trading-masterclass-options-trading-in-simple-terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/options-trading-masterclass-options-trading-in-simple-terms/</guid>
      <description>In this Options Trading course, President of Capstone Financial &amp;amp; Author of &#34;Options Trading Strategies for Monthly Income&#34; David J. Melilli will educate you on every aspect of options trading. David will implement his unique options trading process utilizing his extensive knowledge in the area of options trading. David has spent over fifteen years in the options trading arena. This options trading course is taught in an easy to understand, user friendly manner that will excite and help build the confidence to master options trading and it has been designed to educate and enhance every individual that wants to really develop the skills required in the world of options trading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aprende las bases para invertir en la bolsa</title>
      <link>/aprende-las-bases-para-invertir-en-la-bolsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aprende-las-bases-para-invertir-en-la-bolsa/</guid>
      <description>En este curso aprenderás a leer los 3 estados financieros más importantes que reportan las empresas que cotizan en la bolsa americana (empresas públicas.) Estos son el estado de ingresos, la hoja de balance y el flujo de caja. Con el conocimiento ganado podrás reconocer si ha mejorado o empeorado el desempeño de una empresa pública. De esta forma, sabrás si es conveniente invertir en la empresa analizada. Estaremos usando Yahoo Finanzas para analizar los estados financieros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income: 27 Ways to Earn Passive Income Online</title>
      <link>/passive-income-27-ways-to-earn-passive-income-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/passive-income-27-ways-to-earn-passive-income-online/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to earn money even while you are sleeping?
Do you want to earn money automatically once you&#39;ve set up the systems?
Then this is the right course for you.
I&amp;nbsp;have been earning passive income already for years and I have helped 1,000&#39;s of people worldwide to do the same through my YouTube channel, Udemy courses and blogs.
Earning passive income works in the following way (in a nutshell):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Futures Trading Mastery 2021 | FREE Top 45 Trading Signals!</title>
      <link>/futures-trading-mastery-2021-free-top-45-trading-signals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/futures-trading-mastery-2021-free-top-45-trading-signals/</guid>
      <description>My exclusive course teaches you how to start a successful futures trading business from scratch with zero experience. As one of the world’s 10 years veteran traders, I, Henry Zhang, will personally teach you the same proven strategy I used to build my trading empire from nothing.

Start a lucrative and sustainable trading business today with this complete A-Z guide designed to help everyone from beginners to existing traders looking to increase profits.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
