<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investing &amp; Trading on </title>
    <link>/tags/investing-trading/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Investing &amp; Trading on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 09:01:52 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/investing-trading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Passive Income With Bitcoin Lending</title>
      <link>/how-to-make-passive-income-with-bitcoin-lending/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 09:01:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-make-passive-income-with-bitcoin-lending/</guid>
      <description>Passive Income Course Covering Everything You Need To Passively Earn Money From Bitcoin Lending!
******************************************************************************************
Discover How to Make Passive Income Online Using A 6-Step Bitcoin Lending System:
- A step-by-step video for each of the 6-Steps in the Automated System!
- Inside look at my personal accounts!
- Unlimited earnings, with a small upfront investment!
- How to do all of this without any Fees!
- This course is about results!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swing Trading Ninja: 12 Hour Complete Swing Trading Strategy</title>
      <link>/swing-trading-ninja-12-hour-complete-swing-trading-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 09:01:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/swing-trading-ninja-12-hour-complete-swing-trading-strategy/</guid>
      <description>*** Course access includes quizzes &amp;amp; homework exercises, 1-on-1 instructor support and LIFETIME access! ***
This is best strategy I ever find in my life for swing trader. This is incredible. This milloin dollar startegy. I can say here &#34;knowledge is power&#34;.
-Suhit Kalubarme
it was a great match . I am learning a lot and enjoying class. Working on paper trades as class goes on and see things that I am learning daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Forex- learn to trade forex by yourself</title>
      <link>/introduction-to-forex-learn-to-trade-forex-by-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/introduction-to-forex-learn-to-trade-forex-by-yourself/</guid>
      <description>The financial markets are not very easy to handle and to trade. The Forex market is the biggest of those with more than 2 trillion dollars exchanged on a daily basis. But, there is a way to make profit out of all those transaction with forex trading and this is the goal of this course. Indeed, if you :
- Are someone who is interested in forex trading but never actually started</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income: 27 Ways to Earn Passive Income Online</title>
      <link>/passive-income-27-ways-to-earn-passive-income-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/passive-income-27-ways-to-earn-passive-income-online/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to earn money even while you are sleeping?
Do you want to earn money automatically once you&#39;ve set up the systems?
Then this is the right course for you.
I have been earning passive income already for years and I have helped 1,000&#39;s of people worldwide to do the same through my YouTube channel, Udemy courses and blogs.
Earning passive income works in the following way (in a nutshell):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calcul stochastique pour le trading Forex</title>
      <link>/calcul-stochastique-pour-le-trading-forex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 17:04:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/calcul-stochastique-pour-le-trading-forex/</guid>
      <description>Aujourd&#39;hui, Médaillon, le fond le plus profitable du monde fait en moyenne plus de 60% de gain annuel. Mais comment? Ils sont spécialiser dans la finance quantitative, le trading algorithmique et la mathématisation des processus financier. Ici, dans cette formation, nous allons nous intéresser au calcul stochastique. Nous allons voir qu&#39;elles sont les méthodes de bases du calcul stochastique, voir comment l&#39;appliquer au indice boursier et au forex. 
L&#39;idée principale de cette formation est de voir les bénéfices que l&#39;on peut avoir en combinant deux disciplines très utilisées en finance quantitative: le calcul stochastique et le machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MASTERCLASS: &#39;Inversión en Fondos Mutuos&#39;</title>
      <link>/masterclass-inversi%C3%B3n-en-fondos-mutuos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/masterclass-inversi%C3%B3n-en-fondos-mutuos/</guid>
      <description>Si usted considera que los métodos tradicionales de ahorro que le ofrecen las entidades bancarias de su país no son lo suficientemente buenas para usted debido a su baja rentabilidad y a la creciente inflación, pero a su vez considera que aún no está preparado para dar el gran salto a las inversiones en las bolsas de valores, puesto que ha oído hablar de que es muy riesgoso y que requiere de mucha preparación, entonces esta Masterclass gratuita es adecuada para usted, mi nombre es Jean Pierre Chayña Salas (Economista de profesión) y le mostraré que es posible invertir y sacarle dinero al mercado financiero de forma indirecta jugando bajo sus propios términos y condiciones, aprovechando los beneficios de la banca tradicional y del mercado de valores a través de su banca por Internet BBVA y todo esto desde la comodidad de su casa y ¿Cómo lo haremos?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Altcoin Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/altcoin-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/altcoin-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve not tried using Altcoins and invest the next generation currency, then today is the time to start!

Never before has there been an technology platform of this magnitude that will allow you to reach an audience of billions and rapidly grow your business online at next to zero cost!

Become The Ultimate Altcoins Master and join this course today to learn the same PROVEN success strategy Henry Zhang , the Crypto Currency expert and world-leading trader used to build this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Trading Ninja: 12 Hours DIY Day Trading Strategy</title>
      <link>/day-trading-ninja-12-hours-diy-day-trading-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/day-trading-ninja-12-hours-diy-day-trading-strategy/</guid>
      <description>*** Course access includes quizzes &amp;amp; homework exercises, 1-on-1 instructor support and LIFETIME access! ***
Hear why this is one of the TOP-NOTCH Day Trading course on Udemy:
very practical course , I already made more than 10000$ from 100$ using this course principles . I would like to thank the author for such a good effort. I would like to recommend everyone this course who is struggling in the forex market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Options Trading MasterClass: Options Trading In Simple Terms</title>
      <link>/options-trading-masterclass-options-trading-in-simple-terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/options-trading-masterclass-options-trading-in-simple-terms/</guid>
      <description>In this Options Trading course, President of Capstone Financial &amp;amp; Author of &#34;Options Trading Strategies for Monthly Income&#34; David J. Melilli will educate you on every aspect of options trading. David will implement his unique options trading process utilizing his extensive knowledge in the area of options trading. David has spent over fifteen years in the options trading arena. This options trading course is taught in an easy to understand, user friendly manner that will excite and help build the confidence to master options trading and it has been designed to educate and enhance every individual that wants to really develop the skills required in the world of options trading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aprende las bases para invertir en la bolsa</title>
      <link>/aprende-las-bases-para-invertir-en-la-bolsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aprende-las-bases-para-invertir-en-la-bolsa/</guid>
      <description>En este curso aprenderás a leer los 3 estados financieros más importantes que reportan las empresas que cotizan en la bolsa americana (empresas públicas.) Estos son el estado de ingresos, la hoja de balance y el flujo de caja. Con el conocimiento ganado podrás reconocer si ha mejorado o empeorado el desempeño de una empresa pública. De esta forma, sabrás si es conveniente invertir en la empresa analizada. Estaremos usando Yahoo Finanzas para analizar los estados financieros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Futures Trading Mastery 2021 | FREE Top 45 Trading Signals!</title>
      <link>/futures-trading-mastery-2021-free-top-45-trading-signals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/futures-trading-mastery-2021-free-top-45-trading-signals/</guid>
      <description>My exclusive course teaches you how to start a successful futures trading business from scratch with zero experience. As one of the world’s 10 years veteran traders, I, Henry Zhang, will personally teach you the same proven strategy I used to build my trading empire from nothing.

Start a lucrative and sustainable trading business today with this complete A-Z guide designed to help everyone from beginners to existing traders looking to increase profits.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
