<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Taxes on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/taxes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Taxes on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/taxes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Partnership Income Tax (Form 1065)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/partnership-income-tax-form-1065/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/partnership-income-tax-form-1065/</guid>
      <description>This course currently consists of a comprehensive problem showing the data input process of a Partnership into tax Form 1065.
This course will put together a systematic format of entering data into a Form 1065 that will minimize errors, isolate problems as they happen, and remove the possibility of having to start the process all over again.
We will enter each M-1 adjustment individually into both the tax return and an Excel worksheet so that we fully understand how they work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Income Tax Complete Certification Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/indian-income-tax-complete-certification-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/indian-income-tax-complete-certification-course/</guid>
      <description>Do you find it difficult to understand the Income Tax laws?
Or are you struggling with filing your own income tax return?
Many a time we hear people saying that they don’t understand tax, they are not aware of when tax is to be deducted (TDS), they find it difficult to apply for their own PAN number or they find it difficult to file their return of income.
So, friends to simplify all your problems and giving you an excellent clarity of all concepts, we have made this course on “Income Tax” presented by Direct and Corporate Tax expert CA Natasha Shah.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
