<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Design on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lumion : Landscape Design &amp; Photorealistic Rendering</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lumion-landscape-design-photorealistic-rendering/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lumion-landscape-design-photorealistic-rendering/</guid>
      <description>This class is designed to teach you concepts from creating to rendering of landscape scene in Lumion.
In this class we will be producing a aesthetic landscape model on SketchUp and render it into images and video clips. I will tech you how to design model and turn it into realistic visuals through images and videos from Lumion. Landscape architecture is about creating great cities, streets, parks and public spaces – ones that inspire healthy living and wellbeing while protecting natural environments and people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence in Video Creation: Supreme Edition</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-in-video-creation-supreme-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-in-video-creation-supreme-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the most amazing 2022 course titled &#34;Artificial Intelligence in Video Creation: Supreme Edition&#34;. The new-age technologies in video creation are here.
This incredible artificial intelligence video creation course 2022 will cover the tools called Biteable and Lumen5 which are the world&#39;s simplest video makers offering hundreds of free animated, live-action, or photo scenes in lots of different styles made by top designers.
I will teach you to easily add your own text, photos, colours, and sound to customise your video and edit it all on a simple drag-and-drop timeline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence Presentation Creation (2022 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-presentation-creation-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-presentation-creation-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>Creating presentation decks can get hectic and time-consuming! Believe it or not! Just imagine, what if an Artificial Intelligence (AI) tool does it for you? Welcome to this course that teaches you AI tech tools to achieve this sole purpose.
A must-to-take course for each one of us to enrol in 2022 that is ideal for students, educators, marketers, and of course - graphic designers.
Ready to create instant powerful presentation decks in just minutes?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event Management in 3D Virtual Worlds (2022 Grand Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/event-management-in-3d-virtual-worlds-2022-grand-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/event-management-in-3d-virtual-worlds-2022-grand-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the online course focussed on Event Management in 3D Virtual Worlds (2022 Grand Edition).
&#34;Virtual and augmented reality techniques are changing the way that organizers, sponsors, and vendors engage with attendees at various events.&#34; The metaverse has emerged and the technology is expanding quite rapidly. It is predicted that at every level, the metaverse will spark a thriving new economy. It means another revenue stream for content creators and VR developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphic Design Certification &#43; Live Class</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-certification--live-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-certification--live-class/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the incredible series-based course &#34;Graphic Design Certification - Legendary Edition&#34;.
We know that design helps us understand the world better, and its patterns allow us to keep up with the times. You should always be conscious of the latest trends in graphic design, whether you are a designer, developer, or a newbie. This course is a testament to the latest trends in the field of graphic design, this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Create a Professional Presentation in PowerPoint</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-create-a-professional-presentation-in-powerpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-create-a-professional-presentation-in-powerpoint/</guid>
      <description>Dear PEOPLE from all over the WORLD!
We are Anton and Natalia, founders of NeitDesign, and we specialize in PowerPoint presentations. We started creating presentations in 2015 and now we are Top Rated Seller on Fiverr and Fiverr PRO in Presentation Design. However, we must confess - we also made MISTAKES. And, these mistakes cost us time and money. What we mean is when we began our career, we received huge number of REVISION requests from our clients who wanted to make their presentations look PERFECT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advance logo design course: Bear mascot shape design</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advance-logo-design-course-bear-mascot-shape-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advance-logo-design-course-bear-mascot-shape-design/</guid>
      <description>***** Learn mascot logo design: Professional bear mascot logo design quickly and step by step *****
Learn mascot bear logo design in adobe illustrator step and step very easy way. If you are familiar with adobe illustrator then this course is for you. I will mostly use the Pen tool to draw shapes and some other tools but you can also use Adobe Photoshop if you have basic knowledge of it but I prefer adobe illustrator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Infographics in PowerPoint</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/creative-infographics-in-powerpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/creative-infographics-in-powerpoint/</guid>
      <description>You certainly know that boring PowerPoint presentation can kill a brilliant idea?
Is there a way to make it better, way better? Sure, and I&#39;ll tell you how! A tip: use data to make your presentation more convincing. Don&#39;t use standard Microsoft PowerPoint charts and graphs to visualize the data. They are boring! Instead, do something different, unexpected! A creative infographic! In this course you&#39;ll learn:
what informational graphic is and why people use it (very quick insight);</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sıfırdan V6 Otomobil Motoru Montajı &amp; Uygulamalar | Catia-NX</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/s%C4%B1f%C4%B1rdan-v6-otomobil-motoru-montaj%C4%B1-uygulamalar-catia-nx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/s%C4%B1f%C4%B1rdan-v6-otomobil-motoru-montaj%C4%B1-uygulamalar-catia-nx/</guid>
      <description>Bu eğitimde Catia V5 programının montaj modülüne yani Assembly Design modülüne değiniyor olacağız. Ayrıca Catia V5 programı içerisinde bulunan, kinematik olarak simülasyonlar yapmamıza imkan tanıyan ve kinematik montaj olarak da bilinen DMU Kinematics modülüne de temel olarak değiniyor olacağız. Eğitim içerisinde montaj komutlarını ileri seviye örnekler üzerinden sizlere anlatmaya çalıştık. Eğitimin asıl konusunu V6 motor montajı kısmı oluşturmaktadır. Bir V6 otomobil motorunu hem Catia V5 programında hem de NX programında tüm montaj komutlarını görerek, öğrenerek ve anlayarak birlikte montajlıyacağız.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Basics Of Adobe After Effects CC 2022 for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-basics-of-adobe-after-effects-cc-2022-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-basics-of-adobe-after-effects-cc-2022-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the “Adobe After Effects 2022 - The Beginner&#39;s Basics” course.
Adobe After Effects is a digital visual effects, motion graphics, and compositing application developed by Adobe Systems and used in the post-production process of film making, video games, and television production.
Motion Graphics and Visual Effects are becoming increasingly valuable and important in any video created. Learning how to create these animations using Adobe After Effects has become essential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Basics of Adobe Photoshop CC 2022 for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-basics-of-adobe-photoshop-cc-2022-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-basics-of-adobe-photoshop-cc-2022-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Want to learn Photoshop but don’t know where to start from?
This course is well designed and prepared to make you a decent Photoshop user. All the course contents and examples are wisely chosen and each chapter is explained using the step-by-step method to better fit your needs. The initial chapters are basics and further chapters are explained in more details without making things overcomplicated. To help you follow along with the lectures, exercise files are included in each chapter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Editing with Avid Media Composer First for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-editing-with-avid-media-composer-first-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-editing-with-avid-media-composer-first-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Requirements
A licensed copy of Avid Media Composer First ( Free to download )
Description
Avid Media Composer is widely used video production software in Film and TV industry. This training class provides the critical fundamentals of video editing with Avid Media Composer for beginners.
In this course we have covered the basics of editing with Avid where you get a detailed look at the workings of the interface and learn how to do Basic Edits and apply Transitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Figma UI/UX Web Design &amp; Animation with 5 Projects (2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/figma-ui/ux-web-design-animation-with-5-projects-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:33:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/figma-ui/ux-web-design-animation-with-5-projects-2022/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED JUNE 2022
Hello, Creative Minds,
Figma is a free, online UI tool to create, collaborate, prototype, and hand off. It’s currently the industry’s leading interface design tool and companies such as Notion, Zoom, Uber are using Figma.
In this course, you will learn the process of web design in Figma, which starts at the product brief and ends with a beautiful design.
We will start everything from scratch and I will share all the techniques and shortcuts that increase your workflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Clip Studio Paint Megacourse: Beginner to Expert</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-clip-studio-paint-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-clip-studio-paint-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Learn digital art with Clip Studio Paint!
Design like a pro!
Have you ever wanted to get into digital art? In today’s world, we see it everywhere - from book covers, to movie posters, fanart and bespoke custom illustrations. Whether you’re an aspiring artist eager to create original and fan content, or an experienced artist looking to expand from traditional into digital media, the possibilities when painting digitally are endless. Even someone who’s never picked up a stylus before can learn the skills and start creating beautiful pieces of art - and we’re here to teach you how.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Design A Great Movie Poster That Works</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-design-a-great-movie-poster-that-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-design-a-great-movie-poster-that-works/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m an independent filmmaker and I know the importance of good looking poster for a film. Especially for independent films. Let me say the way it is, your movie poster is the deciding factor for the audience when deciding what to watch. As simple as that. It&#39;s beyond important. Imagine getting home from work, getting comfortable on a sofa in front of your tv, and scrolling through hundreds of tv shows and movies deciding what to watch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Design for Beginners: Build Websites in HTML &amp; CSS 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/web-design-for-beginners-build-websites-in-html-css-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/web-design-for-beginners-build-websites-in-html-css-2022/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to get started with web design, front-end development, or web development in general? If the answer is yes then you are in for a treat. In this course, you are going to learn everything you need to know about HTML and CSS which are basically the starting point of your career as a web developer. So why choose this course? why not any other course? Because I have made sure that every part of the course is informative, fun, and practical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Design a STAND-OUT social media content in Canva.</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-design-a-stand-out-social-media-content-in-canva./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:11:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-design-a-stand-out-social-media-content-in-canva./</guid>
      <description>Have you been stuck in creating your own graphics for social media, but don’t know how to begin? Have you researched graphic design tutorials online only to find that they never cover what you&#39;re really looking for? I know that sometimes designing can be frustrating! It takes a lot of a hard time to create custom graphics yourself, especially when you’re just starting out with no previous experience. I’ve been there too… Spending countless hours online searching for the right tutorial - but always coming up short.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Illustrator 2022 Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-illustrator-2022-ultimate-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-illustrator-2022-ultimate-guide/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone and welcome to Adobe Illustrator 2022 Ultimate Guide.
In this video, we&#39;re going to go over an in-depth overview of what we&#39;re going to be learning throughout this course.
So let&#39;s jump into it.
So in Section two, we&#39;re going to talk about Adobe Creative Cloud 2022 plans and pricing.
So we&#39;ll cover individuals, business students and teachers and schools, universities.
Then we&#39;ll talk about how to set up a free creative cloud account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creo Parametric Training_In Hindi</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/creo-parametric-training_in-hindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/creo-parametric-training_in-hindi/</guid>
      <description>Creo is a 3D CAD modelling software, which is useful for engineering students and Professionals, in this course you will learn how to make a realistic 3D CAD model using CREO Parametric and learn how to model engine parts. The following modules are included in this course.
1. Sketcher
2. Part modelling - Solid
3. part modelling - Surface
4. Part modelling - Sheet metal
5. Assembly design
6. Detailing and drafting</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Creative Cloud 2022 Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-creative-cloud-2022-ultimate-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-creative-cloud-2022-ultimate-guide/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Adobe Creative Cloud but don’t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Designs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Creative Cloud 2022 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Adobe Creative Cloud is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I’ll take you through everything you need to know to start working with Adobe Creative Cloud like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe After Effects 2022 Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-after-effects-2022-ultimate-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-after-effects-2022-ultimate-guide/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone and welcome to Adobe After Effects 2022 Ultimate Guide.
In this video, we&#39;re going to go over a course overview of what we&#39;re going to be learning throughout the course.
So in Section two, we&#39;re going to do a deep dive into creative cloud plans and pricing.
So we&#39;ll cover individuals, business students and teachers and schools and universities.
Then we&#39;ll learn how to create a creative cloud account for free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Animate 2022 Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-animate-2022-ultimate-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-animate-2022-ultimate-guide/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Animate Video but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Videos and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Animate 2022 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Animation is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start Animating Videos like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Creative Cloud 2022 Projects</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-creative-cloud-2022-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-creative-cloud-2022-projects/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Adobe Creative Cloud but don’t know where to start? Would you like to make amazing Designs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Creative Cloud 2022 Projects is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Adobe Creative Cloud is an in-demand skill in 2022.
The course begins with the basics.
I’ll take you through everything you need to know to start working with Adobe Creative Cloud like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Dreamweaver 2022 Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-dreamweaver-2022-ultimate-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-dreamweaver-2022-ultimate-guide/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Edit Websites but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Websites and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Dreamweaver 2022 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Web Tools are an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start Editing Websites like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe InDesign 2022 Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-indesign-2022-ultimate-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-indesign-2022-ultimate-guide/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone and welcome to Adobe InDesign 2022 Ultimate Guide.
In this video, we&#39;re going to go over a course overview of what we&#39;re going to be learning throughout the course.
So in Section two, we&#39;re going to talk about Adobe Creative Cloud plans.
So we&#39;ll cover individuals, business students and teachers and schools and universities.
Then we&#39;ll talk about how to use Adobe Creative Cloud Web to install Adobe InDesign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop 2022 Photo Editing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-2022-photo-editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-2022-photo-editing/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Design but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Photos and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Photoshop 2022 Photo Editing is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Photo Editing is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start Editing Photos like an expert with Adobe Photoshop 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro CC Video Editing Course Beginners To Pro</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-video-editing-course-beginners-to-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-video-editing-course-beginners-to-pro/</guid>
      <description>Hi There,
My name is Stephen Koel Soren and I am a graphics and web expert. If you are absolute beginner or if you never open Adobe Premiere pro cc before than this is a perfect class for you. This is a beginner level class so so together me you we will learn Adobe Premiere pro from basic to advance.
The Main Topics you will learn:
· Set your workspace. How to efficiently import and organize your media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe XD 2022 Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-xd-2022-ultimate-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-xd-2022-ultimate-guide/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone and welcome to Adobe XD 2022 Ultimate Guide.
In this video we&#39;re going over a course overview of what we&#39;re going to be learning throughout the course.
So in Section two, we&#39;re going to talk about Adobe Creative Cloud plans.
So cover individuals, business students and teachers, schools and universities.
Next, we&#39;ll talk about how to create a free creative cloud account.
And then we&#39;ll talk about Adobe Creative Cloud Web and how to install Adobe XD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Guide to Product Design: Design Thinking Approach</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-guide-to-product-design-design-thinking-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-guide-to-product-design-design-thinking-approach/</guid>
      <description>**Course Updated - June 2022**
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; COURSE REGULARLY UPDATED: NEW TIPS, MORE LESSONS &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; CERTIFIED COACH, SPEAKER AND TRAINER &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; OVER 180,000 STUDENTS IN TOTAL &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
The world finally understands the essential role of design. Products look better than ever, interfaces feel intuitive, and companies are hiring designers at an increasing rate. But, the designer’s role has been changing over the last few years. It’s no longer enough to iterate and understand your user, instead of in today’s world, designers should be able to do both – identify problems and build solutions, which will increase their worth by at least 10 times for any company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Sketching S01: Create Amazing Designs with Procreate</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/design-sketching-s01-create-amazing-designs-with-procreate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/design-sketching-s01-create-amazing-designs-with-procreate/</guid>
      <description>Christmas Sale! 3 hours of extensive course for just 19 USD!! Turn your iPad into the most powerful design tool on earth with Procreate and Apple Pencil!
Design Sketching: Create Amazing Designs with Procreate This is a learn anywhere video course, where you will be able to use all of Procreates features to ideate and sketch effectively on your iPad or iPad Pro. I’ve covered all the core knowledge and practical theory you need to know in order to utilize Procreate to a professional level to create super cool design sketches on your iPad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Audition 2022 Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-audition-2022-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-audition-2022-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Edit Audio but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Videos and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Audition 2022 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Audio Editing is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start Editing Audio like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Web Front End Learning Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-web-front-end-learning-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-web-front-end-learning-guide/</guid>
      <description>في هذه الدورة افترض الشخص الذي امامي لا يعرف اي شي عن عالم الويب
سكتون الدورة من الصفر فلا تحتاج لاي مؤهلات للدخول للدورة الدورة مركزة اكثر للمبتدئين، للاشخاص اللذين يريدون الدخول لعالم الويب
يعتبر تصميم الويب هو الجزء الابسط والامتع من الويب
هذه الدورة عبارة عن خمس دورات مجمعة في دورة واحدة
JavaScript is THE most important programming language you need to learn as a web developer - and with this course, you make sure that you will not miss a single thing you have to know as a JavaScript developer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress for Complete Beginners!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/wordpress-for-complete-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/wordpress-for-complete-beginners/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re here because you want to create your own WordPress websites, right?
You don&#39;t Need Coding Ath All no Javascript no html no css no Php
This WordPress for Beginners course is the perfect place to start. This complete WordPress course is designed for beginners like you who have never built a WordPress website (or any website for that matter).
WordPress is the perfect tool for creating a fully customized website for any purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphic Designing for People with Autism, Dyslexia etc</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-designing-for-people-with-autism-dyslexia-etc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-designing-for-people-with-autism-dyslexia-etc/</guid>
      <description>Here, this Digital Tech training course is part of a series of various other classes made Specifically for Special Needs People.
The Special Needs people are mainly those who are Autistic, Dyslexic, having Down Syndrome, Asperger’s, Cerebral Palsy and various others.
They are are known to have exceptional talents, which only need to be uncovered. However, once their hidden talents are tapped, they are capable of producing wonders.
Unfortunately, they are rarely given fair chances i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multimedia and Graphic designing Course for Special Needs</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/multimedia-and-graphic-designing-course-for-special-needs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/multimedia-and-graphic-designing-course-for-special-needs/</guid>
      <description>This Digital Tech training course is part of a series of various other classes made Specifically for Special Needs People.
The Special Needs people are mainly those who are Autistic, Dyslexic, having Down Syndrome, Asperger’s, Cerebral Palsy and various others.
The Special Needs people are known to have exceptional talents, which only need to be uncovered. However, once their hidden talents are tapped, they are capable of producing wonders.
Unfortunately, they are rarely given fair chances i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aprende Photoshop en 18 días</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprende-photoshop-en-18-d%C3%ADas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprende-photoshop-en-18-d%C3%ADas/</guid>
      <description>En este curso aprenderás a conocer desde CERO todas las herramientas de PHOTOSHOP CC 2017 - 2018, además conocerás algunos filtros, fusiones de capas y otras herramientas; además podrás realizar ejercicios prácticos donde aplicaras todas las herramientas aprendidas; podrás aprender de forma rápida y cómoda; y realizar ejercicios en el horario que mejor que convenga, ¿Qué esperas, aceptas el reto? únete al mejor curso de Photoshop y aprende a utilizar el software desde CERO en solo 18 días.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Incredible Visual Graphics with Canva (2022 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-incredible-visual-graphics-with-canva-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-incredible-visual-graphics-with-canva-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Create Incredible Visual Graphics with Canva (2022 Edition)&#34;.
So, you&#39;re looking for an online course that will train you on Canva - the superb graphic design tool, very easily?
You&#39;ve come to the right place, my passionate learner. Look no further.
Welcome, my name is Srinidhi Ranganathan. My fans fondly call me &#34;Digital Marketing Legend&#34;. Teaming up with Saranya and Stefi, we have now put this course together to help people just like you quickly master Canva.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cómo Crear una Tarjeta De Presentación con WordPress</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/c%C3%B3mo-crear-una-tarjeta-de-presentaci%C3%B3n-con-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/c%C3%B3mo-crear-una-tarjeta-de-presentaci%C3%B3n-con-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>WORDPRESS es una plataforma para construir y diseñar sitios web, sin tener experiencia en diseño web y programación, de forma rápida y sencilla.
El 38% de los sitios web de Internet han sido creados con WordPress. Es una herramienta muy fácil de aprender, en el cual puede personalizar un sitio web desde cero para cualquier propósito. Ya sea que desee crear una tarjeta digital interactiva, un blog o una tienda online para vender sus productos y servicios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Animation Film-Making with Plotagon (2022 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/3d-animation-film-making-with-plotagon-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/3d-animation-film-making-with-plotagon-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the mind-blowing course titled &#34;3D Animation Film-Making with Plotagon (2022 Edition)&#34;.
With this mind-blowing ultra-speed course on creating 3D animation movies in 2022, you can go ahead and bring your ideas to life with an award-winning 3D animation software taught called “Plotagon”. Plotagon is the only software in the market that allows you to create amazing 3D animation videos in the fastest time possible using highly-futuristic technology. With Plotagon 3D animation software, you can promote your business, engage your target audience segments, or educate your employees as it is a simple, yet powerful tool to leverage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence Photo Colorisation Tools (2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-photo-colorisation-tools-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-photo-colorisation-tools-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Artificial Intelligence Photo Colorisation Tools (2022)&#34;.
Colours are a vital part of how stories are told through photography and we know this. Now, it&#39;s high time to bring new life to old photos by automatically applying colour to them with the power of Artificial Intelligence (AI) tools.
This 2022 mind-blowing and incredible course focussed on &#34;Artificial Intelligence Photo Colorisation Tools&#34; created by Digital Marketing Legend &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34; teaches you how to leverage Deep Learning to the maximum use in order for colourizing Black and white photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create lightning-fast videos with InVideo in 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-lightning-fast-videos-with-invideo-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-lightning-fast-videos-with-invideo-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Create lightning-fast videos with InVideo in 2022&#34;.
Video creation was a tough process - until now !!! Do you want to learn to produce some incredible videos without all the hassle of using complex editing software, without straining yourself too much?
Are you looking to create wow-inspiring videos to promote your brand to the highest level?
You&#39;ve come to the right place, finally. This amazing course on Udemy will introduce you to the world’s most versatile video creator for Quick &amp;amp; Professional videos called &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-Speed 3D Game Development using GameGuru (2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultra-speed-3d-game-development-using-gameguru-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultra-speed-3d-game-development-using-gameguru-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Ultra-Speed 3D Game Development using GameGuru (2022)&#34;.
Say &#34;Hi&#34; to the most awesome course on &#34;GameGuru (Ultra-Speed 3D Game Development)&#34;, game making for everyone taught by digital marketing legend &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34; &amp;amp; Civil Engineering Mastermind &#34;Saranya Srinidhi&#34;. We will teach you this mind-blowing software that will help you to create the easiest and most enjoyable game ever in 3D. Imagine creating a fantasy world that you and your friends come together and play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence (AI) Logo Design Tools: 2022 Edition</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-ai-logo-design-tools-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-ai-logo-design-tools-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience the online course &#34;Artificial Intelligence (AI) Logo Design Tools: 2022 Edition&#34;.
When designing a logo for your new company or project, the first step is to determine which design method fits your budget, schedule, and creative needs.
A new wave of graphic design has come to the limelight with artificial intelligence gaining prominence in all fields of technology, providing an affordable alternative for bootstrapped entrepreneurs and startups. As a powerful and easy alternative to DIY logo design (which is extremely time-consuming) and hiring a designer (which is more or less expensive), an AI-powered logo creation tool is a smart way to create logos that look professional and appealing to your target audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autocad | Sıfırdan Uzmanlığa 30&#43; Saat Sektörel Eğitim Seti</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/autocad-s%C4%B1f%C4%B1rdan-uzmanl%C4%B1%C4%9Fa-30-saat-sekt%C3%B6rel-e%C4%9Fitim-seti/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/autocad-s%C4%B1f%C4%B1rdan-uzmanl%C4%B1%C4%9Fa-30-saat-sekt%C3%B6rel-e%C4%9Fitim-seti/</guid>
      <description>Autocad eğitimini kalıp tasarım mühendislerinden öğrenmeye hazır mısınız? Tüm tasarım ve imalat tecrübelerimizi sizinle paylaşacağımız Autocad eğitiminde göreceğiniz ileri seviye çizim teknikleri ile piyasada rahatlıkla fark yaratabileceksiniz! Eğitmenler olarak uzun yıllar çalıştığımız plastik enjeksiyon ve sac metal kalıp tasarımlarında edindiğimiz bilgi birikimlerimizi şimdi sizinle paylaşmaya hazırız! Bu eğitimimizde Autocad programının önemli olan tüm özelliklerine sıfırdan başlayarak, ileri seviyeye kadar değineceğiz. Eğitimimiz gelen istekler doğrultusunda her zaman güncel tutulmaya da çalışılacaktır. Aynı zamanda da tüm sorularınızı eğitimi izlerken anında sorabilirsiniz ve 24 saat içerisinde sorularınıza yanıt almış olacaksınız!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art Of Drawing Cartoon Comic Strips [NEW]</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-art-of-drawing-cartoon-comic-strips-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-art-of-drawing-cartoon-comic-strips-new/</guid>
      <description>NOW IS THE MOMENT Updated - 18/10/2021
Learn to communicate your ideas through visual Art.
More and More film companies employ Graphic artists and Cartoonist for their Animations.
Here is Your Opportunity
Do You Want To Be a Creative?
Join Thousands of students learn how to Draw &amp;amp; Create cartoon Comic Strips.
This Masterclass is the Compilation 0f 13 years of my Life&#39;s Learning &amp;amp; Pesronal experience on the Subject of Drawing Cartoons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whiteboard Video Creation with VideoScribe (2022 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/whiteboard-video-creation-with-videoscribe-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/whiteboard-video-creation-with-videoscribe-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Whiteboard Video Creation with VideoScribe (2022 Edition)&#34;.
In a typical product training session - imagine you&#39;ve made a presentation which you believe, may engage or wow the audience. However, it doesn&#39;t work out at the end of the day. It simply doesn&#39;t. The audience just walks out bleary-eyed, shell-shocked, and bored after a long line of presenters has in-fact bombarded them with PowerPoint slide presentations. This would include your 30 slider presentation on the latest and greatest products, features, functions, or benefits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curso WordPress 2022:  Cómo Crear una Página Web Desde Cero</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-wordpress-2022-c%C3%B3mo-crear-una-p%C3%A1gina-web-desde-cero/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 21:50:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-wordpress-2022-c%C3%B3mo-crear-una-p%C3%A1gina-web-desde-cero/</guid>
      <description>WORDPRESS es una plataforma para construir y diseñar un sitio web, sin tener experiencia en diseño web y programación, de forma rápida y sencilla.
El 38% de los sitios web de Internet han sido creados con WordPress. Es una herramienta muy fácil de aprender, en el cual puede personalizar un sitio web desde cero para cualquier propósito. Ya sea que desee crear un portafolio personal, un blog o un sitio web comercial para vender sus productos y servicios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Revit Guide - Model a Modern Multistory Building</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-revit-guide-model-a-modern-multistory-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-revit-guide-model-a-modern-multistory-building/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Revit Guide is your course for perfecting your BIM and Revit design and collaboration skills.
Revit is a complex program with lots of levers. To learn the most, you need to fundamentals while also learning industry workflows. In this comprehensive course, you will learn how to use Revit to plan, model and develop a project based on actual Architectural designs, so you can perfect your skill for your next team project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto en Diseño de Escenografías Teatrales</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/experto-en-dise%C3%B1o-de-escenografi%CC%81as-teatrales/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/experto-en-dise%C3%B1o-de-escenografi%CC%81as-teatrales/</guid>
      <description>Experto en Diseño de Escenografías Teatrales
Aprende de forma integral el proceso de diseño y ejecución de espacios escenográficos en teatros
Instructores: Arquitecto Álvaro García y Arquitecta Lucía Fernández Actualizado: Mayo de 2022 Estudiantes: +3.000
Descripción del Curso:
La escenografía es el arte de realizar decoraciones escénicas. El término, que tiene su origen en un vocablo griego, también permite nombrar al conjunto de los decorados que se utilizan en una representación escénica.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto en Diseño de Espacios para Mascotas</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/experto-en-dise%C3%B1o-de-espacios-para-mascotas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/experto-en-dise%C3%B1o-de-espacios-para-mascotas/</guid>
      <description>Experto en Diseño de Espacios para Mascotas
Conviértete en un Experto en el Diseño de Hogares y Espacios destinados a todo tipo de Mascotas
Instructores: Arquitecto Álvaro García y Arquitecta Lucía Fernández Actualizado: Mayo de 2022 Estudiantes: +3.000 Descripción del Curso:
La formación te permitirá convertirte en un experto en la materia, y todo ello desde una formación principalmente práctica. A través de variadas actividades y proyectos completos podrás adquirir los conocimientos suficientes para ejercer profesionalmente de forma solvente.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SketchUp Architectural Design Essentials Kit</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sketchup-architectural-design-essentials-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sketchup-architectural-design-essentials-kit/</guid>
      <description>Learn Architectural Design In SketchUp with the SketchUp Architectural Design Essentials Kit Course.
SketchUp Models are easy to start modeling on a basic idea, but getting your models into a clear Architectural language takes a bit more than adding a few lines and forms.
In this course, we will develop an existing building model into an Architecturally detailed one. We will walk through what is needed in the site, in the windows, doors, facades, roof and other elements so that the model will read as Architecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Patternmaking Kit: Learn How To Draft Trousers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/easy-patternmaking-kit-learn-how-to-draft-trousers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/easy-patternmaking-kit-learn-how-to-draft-trousers/</guid>
      <description>The Easy Patternmaking Kit - Trouser Drafting Course teaches you how to construct a beautiful pair of trousers.
In this course, you learn to draft a pattern for a pair of trousers along wit belt and zipper attachments, using fitting measurements, and quality techniques. We begin with organizing your pattern paper with accurate measurements laid out properly. You will then learn to calculate the circumference measurements, the darts, and allowances for a quality fit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patternmaking For Beginners: Draft An Offshoulder Dress</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/patternmaking-for-beginners-draft-an-offshoulder-dress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/patternmaking-for-beginners-draft-an-offshoulder-dress/</guid>
      <description>The Easy Sewing Kit - Learn To Draft An Offshoulder Dress Course teaches you how to construct a beautiful dress in the offshoulder style.
In this course, you learn to draft a pattern for an offshoulder dress and sleeve, using fitting measurements, and quality techniques. We begin with organizing your pattern paper with accurate measurements laid out properly. You will then learn to calculate the armhole, the waist darts, and allowances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOLAR COURSE for Beginners of Solar Energy-</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/solar-course-for-beginners-of-solar-energy-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:57:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/solar-course-for-beginners-of-solar-energy-/</guid>
      <description>Hello, Dear Solar Enthusiast!
I welcome you to this Solar Energy course, designed with the goal to share the learning for the beginners of Solar Energy. Let me share with you that I have tried to develop this course keeping in mind that a beginner could learn the technicality of the Solar field in a simpler and easier manner. I have tried to all the aspects of the Solar plants which include Technicals, Financial calculations, Financial modelling, Net Metering, Different types of Installations, Monitoring etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe InDesign. Aprende a maquetar de manera profesional</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-indesign.-aprende-a-maquetar-de-manera-profesional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 20:40:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-indesign.-aprende-a-maquetar-de-manera-profesional/</guid>
      <description>Adobe InDesign es un software de diseño, utilizado para la maquetación de cualquier documento, ya sean periódicos, revistas, libros o cualquier material de publicación que se nos ocurra. Es un programa fácil de comprender y dinámico. Nos permite diseñar y maquetar de una manera ágil y creativa incluyendo elementos como títulos, textos, imágenes e incluso enlaces para su visualización posterior en páginas web. También nos permite configurar nuestras propias plantillas, crear hojas de estilo para automatizar parámetros como la fuente, el tamaño, el color, etc… y otros muchos accesos directos para acelerar el proceso de diseño y hacer la vida del maquetador un poco más sencilla.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art Of Drawing The Face | Beginner&#39;s Course (NEW) 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-art-of-drawing-the-face-beginners-course-new-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 13:36:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-art-of-drawing-the-face-beginners-course-new-2022/</guid>
      <description>Learn How to Draw Anyone, Anytime!
••• VERY EASY •••
Realistic Drawing Course
Imagine Moment; that you could Draw your Friends, the Face of the one you Love, Your Family Members.
Imagine you could Draw just anyone and you made them so happy each time.
Imagine the Joy and Fulfilment.
DRAWING IS A Basic Instinct; We are all born with.
Many People think that Drawing is Hard but The Truth is that Drawing is a Skill and with the right knowledge and Practice, You can master the Art of Drawing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create an animated promo video in PowerPoint</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-create-an-animated-promo-video-in-powerpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 15:08:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-create-an-animated-promo-video-in-powerpoint/</guid>
      <description>After you complete this course, you will get to know and practice:
major tools and techniques of PowerPoint. Even if you never worked in PowerPoint before, we will explain step by step, so you will not have any complications. It will help you to create professional presentations by yourself.
PowerPoint hotkeys. To optimize working process and increase speed, we will use hotkeys. We will explain how they work and how to use them, and by the end of the course you will easily use them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cómo Crear una Tienda Online con WordPress Desde Cero 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/c%C3%B3mo-crear-una-tienda-online-con-wordpress-desde-cero-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/c%C3%B3mo-crear-una-tienda-online-con-wordpress-desde-cero-2022/</guid>
      <description>¿QUIERES CREAR UNA TIENDA ONLINE CON WORDPRESS Y VENDER TUS PRODUCTOS POR INTERNET?
Únete a nuestro curso completo para mostrarte cómo crear una tienda online profesional y totalmente personalizada en WordPress. Independientemente del propósito de tu tienda online, este curso te mostrará todo lo que necesita saber para crear una tienda online impresionante. He estado creando y usando tiendas virtuales durante más de 5 años para mis negocios en línea, lo que me convierte en el más calificado para enseñarte sobre cómo crear una tienda online con WordPress desde cero.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Proven Steps to Make a Silver Ring</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/8-proven-steps-to-make-a-silver-ring/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:57:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/8-proven-steps-to-make-a-silver-ring/</guid>
      <description>Are you curious about silver jewellery making but don&#39;t know where to start, unsure what tools you need or whether you&#39;ll enjoy jewellery making? Would you love to learn jewellery making but don&#39;t want a big expense and commitment? Are the courses you&#39;ve researched too long, unavailable right now, not near you, at inconvenient times or fully booked?
On this course you will :-
Learn how to set up your workspace at home with 5 short easy to follow videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diseño de Cabañas</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/dise%C3%B1o-de-caba%C3%B1as/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:57:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/dise%C3%B1o-de-caba%C3%B1as/</guid>
      <description>Diseño de Cabañas
Aprende de forma integral el proceso de diseño y ejecución de cabañas. Instructores: Arquitecto Álvaro García y Arquitecta Lucía Fernández Actualizado: Mayo de 2022 Estudiantes: +3.000 Descripción del Curso:
La formación te permitirá convertirte en un experto en la materia, y todo ello desde una formación principalmente práctica. A través de variadas actividades y proyectos completos podrás adquirir los conocimientos suficientes para ejercer profesionalmente de forma solvente. Además conocerás en detalle mi flujo de trabajo a la hora de afrontar un proyecto profesional.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New illustration Painting - Digital Photoshop Drawing Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/new-illustration-painting-digital-photoshop-drawing-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:57:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/new-illustration-painting-digital-photoshop-drawing-course/</guid>
      <description>In 2021, about 40,000 students have learned this &#39;Guochao&#39; illustration course in China. Just come and join them to see what you can create.
What is &#39;Guochao&#39; illustration style?
There are many kinds of Chinese style illustration, &#39;Guochao&#39; is one of them. &#39;Guochao&#39; means based on the Chinese traditional culture background, adding some modern fashion elements. It is also the illustration style mainly introduced in this course.
This course has 4 parts (total 11 lessons) with downloadable resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Architectural Shop Drawing Plans in AutoCAD 2020</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/architectural-shop-drawing-plans-in-autocad-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/architectural-shop-drawing-plans-in-autocad-2020/</guid>
      <description>Part 1: Learn the basics commands in AutoCAD to be ready to the shop drawing practice ( How to draw lines, How to draw polyline, Copy, Move, Mirror, Offset, Fillet, Trim, Rotate, How to draw X-line, How to draw circle, How to draw Hatch in AutoCAD, How to do match properties in AutoCAD, How to print a sheet in AutoCAD.
Part 2: Architectural Shop Drawing in AutoCAD 2020
Do you need more practice with AutoCAD?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop CC- Basic Photoshop training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-cc-basic-photoshop-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:10:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-cc-basic-photoshop-training/</guid>
      <description>Learning the basics of Adobe Photoshop is definitely not easy, especially if you have no prior knowledge in this field. But, this course can teach you everything you need to know to start using photoshop and making your own projects with pictures that you take yourself or pictures that you have simply found on the internet. If you:
- Are a student and need to learn how to properly use Photoshop</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Adobe Photoshop CC Course With Advance Training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/professional-adobe-photoshop-cc-course-with-advance-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:10:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/professional-adobe-photoshop-cc-course-with-advance-training/</guid>
      <description>A professional photoshop course with advance photoshop training where a student will learn about selection and masking, how to design logo, t-shirt, business card, resume, mug, bottle, calendar, cover, gif, along with that student will learn how to earn money by graphics designing work, retouching, advance use of photoshop tools etc. It’s a professional photoshop course specially for graphics designers and before enrol this course you must have knowledge about basic photoshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop CC Fundamentals and Essentials Training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-cc-fundamentals-and-essentials-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-cc-fundamentals-and-essentials-training/</guid>
      <description>Hi There, I am Stephen Koel Soren and I am a Graphics and Web Expert. If you are a beginner and looking to learn photoshop from scratch then this course will help you to learn Adobe Photoshop Professionally. For learning graphics design and photoshop retouching from beginner to advanced this course can be a lighthouse for you. You can learn from this course about Photoshop Layer, Color and Adjustment, Photoshop Color Correction, Shape and Symbol, Content-Aware &amp;amp; Cropping, Photoshop Text Style, Gradient Stroke &amp;amp; Bevel, Shadow, Blending, Selection, Photoshop Masking, Blur &amp;amp; Filters, Transform, Warp &amp;amp; Distort, Clipping Mask, Retouch, Photoshop Retouching, Effect Of Visual Style, Brush, Export, Earning Money With Graphics Design Work, Advance Tool and many more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Figma Megacourse: UI/UX Design Beginner to Expert</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-figma-megacourse-ui/ux-design-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-figma-megacourse-ui/ux-design-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>This course is constantly being revised and updated with new lessons.
Have you ever wanted to design your own app, website or blog? These days, we use them without a second thought. They have become an integral part of both the human experience and the financial market. It’s easy to come up with a new idea for a viral new app, but not as easy to make that app a reality - or so you might think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Blender Megacourse: Beginner to Expert</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-blender-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 17:17:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-blender-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Learn 3D modeling and animation in Blender 3.0!
Design like a pro!
Have you ever wanted to create 3D models? In the era of technology, at-home digital entertainment is more popular than ever and is showing no sign of slowing. Maybe you’d like to try your hand at making your own animated film, or perhaps, you want to create your own video game. Whether you’re new to working with Blender, or hoping to make a career out of it, 3D creation isn’t only for the pros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solar Specialist Certification Interview Practice Test 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/solar-specialist-certification-interview-practice-test-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 17:17:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/solar-specialist-certification-interview-practice-test-2022/</guid>
      <description>Description
FULLY UPDATED for April 2022 Want to Excel in the growing field of Solar Energy? I wish to understand all the aspects of Solar Energy, Be it Technical, Financial, Monitoring, Net Metering, Components etc. You&#39;re in the right place! With 175+ questions and the most detailed explanations, you&#39;ll be able to ace the Solar Energy field and excel in your career. Please don&#39;t take my word for it; read the student reviews below :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clone yourself in a video using ScreenFlow 9 in 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/clone-yourself-in-a-video-using-screenflow-9-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 16:26:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/clone-yourself-in-a-video-using-screenflow-9-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Clone yourself in a video using ScreenFlow 9 in 2022&#34;.
&#34;Ever wondered how to multiply yourself in the videos you create? Well, now is the right time to start learning that craft&#34;.
This mind-blowing course titled &#34;Clone Yourself in a Video using ScreenFlow 9 in 2022&#34; created by Digital Marketing Legend &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34; and Mastermind &#34;Saranya Srinidhi&#34; will teach you the simplest method to execute this trick using ScreenFlow 9 on Mac.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comic Creation for Entrepreneurs (2022 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/comic-creation-for-entrepreneurs-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 22:09:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/comic-creation-for-entrepreneurs-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience the course &#34;Comic Creation for Entrepreneurs (2022 Edition)&#34;.
Nowadays online marketing has become increasingly important to all businesses worldwide. Digital comics have become a market having a high ROI. The comic industry has come a long way and it has the potential to enter the minds of customers to help provoke decision-making. Most startup companies and SME&#39;s (Small Medium Enterprises) aren&#39;t even aware of this astonishing fact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Super-Fast Videos and Online Courses with WeVideo</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-super-fast-videos-and-online-courses-with-wevideo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 22:09:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-super-fast-videos-and-online-courses-with-wevideo/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience the course &#34;Create Super-Fast Videos and Online Courses with WeVideo&#34;.
Are you looking to learn how to create incredible videos fast and easily without installing complex software? Are you still worried about the videos you edited that are taking ages to render?
Want to create wow-inspiring videos to promote your brand to gain maximum exposure? Welcome to the next generation of cloud-based video creation with WeVideo. WeVideo caters to all the needs mentioned above and also gives you the power to do more with fewer resources, time, and effort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SketchUp and V-Ray Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sketchup-and-v-ray-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:16:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sketchup-and-v-ray-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Hello, this is your instructor Shivam. If you are here, you probably know what SketchUp and V-Ray is. SketchUp is widely used application in myriad vocations, be it Architecture or product designing. In this course, we are gonna learn SketchUp from scratch to advance level. The course follows advance methods of teaching and additionally there is example to learn steps in modeling an actual building as well as adding V-ray material, lights, scene management and much more in depth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe After Effects 2022 Projects</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-after-effects-2022-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-after-effects-2022-projects/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Edit Video but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Videos and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe After Effects 2022 Projects is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Video Editing is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start Editing Videos like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop 2022 Projects</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-2022-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-2022-projects/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Design but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Designs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Photoshop 2022 Projects is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Design is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building designs like an expert with Adobe Photoshop 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Animate 2022 Projects</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-animate-2022-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-animate-2022-projects/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Animate Video but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Videos and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Animate 2022 Projects is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Animation is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start Animating Videos like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Course in CATIA</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-course-in-catia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-course-in-catia/</guid>
      <description>CATIA V5, developed by Dassault Systemes, France, is a completely re-engineered, next-generation family of CAD/CAM/CAE software solutions for Product Lifecycle Management. CATIA V5 delivers innovative technologies for maximum productivity and creativity through its exceptionally easy-to-use and state-of-the-art user interface, from inception to the final product. CATIA V5 reduces the learning curve, as it allows the flexibility of using feature-based and parametric designs. CATIA V5 serves the design tasks by providing different workbenches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cómo Crear una Landing Page con WordPress Desde Cero 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/c%C3%B3mo-crear-una-landing-page-con-wordpress-desde-cero-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 19:20:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/c%C3%B3mo-crear-una-landing-page-con-wordpress-desde-cero-2022/</guid>
      <description>WORDPRESS es una plataforma para construir y diseñar sitios web, tales como blogs, tiendas virtuales, escuelas virtuales y landing pages (páginas de aterrizaje), sin necesidad de tener experiencia en diseño web y programación, puedes diseñar cualquier tipo de sitio web de forma fácil y simple.
El 38% de los sitios web de Internet han sido creados con WordPress. Es una herramienta muy fácil de aprender y se puede personalizar un sitio web de WordPress para cualquier propósito.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Thumbnail Blaster: Create 3D Video Thumbnails (2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-thumbnail-blaster-create-3d-video-thumbnails-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-thumbnail-blaster-create-3d-video-thumbnails-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;YouTube Thumbnail Blaster&#34; course.
So, want to create breathtaking and clickable video thumbnails for your YouTube videos, but not knowing how?
You&#39;ve come to the right place, my passionate learner. Look no further than this course.
Welcome, my name is Srinidhi Ranganathan. My fans fondly call me &#34;Digital Marketing Legend&#34;. Teaming up with Saranya, I have now put this training course &#34;YouTube Thumbnail Blaster: Create 3D Video Thumbnails&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Figma Basics Super Easy Crash Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/figma-basics-super-easy-crash-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/figma-basics-super-easy-crash-course/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Figma Basics Super Easy Crash Course. Figma is an interface design application that runs in the browser—but it’s actually much more than that. I would go so far as to say it’s probably the best application for team-based collaborative design projects. If you are new to Figma or Designing as a whole then this is the right place for you.
Figma is a collaborative web-based editing and design interface tool that offers a web API, plus- it’s free!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Substation Power Engineering Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/substation-power-engineering-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/substation-power-engineering-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Substation Power Engineering Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn industry specific knowledge about power substations that you would not have known unless you worked within the utility industry for a number of years.
I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on substations as well as key pointers to look out for in substation designs, such as site preparations and equipment specifications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course on Design Thinking and Product Development</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/course-on-design-thinking-and-product-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 21:29:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/course-on-design-thinking-and-product-development/</guid>
      <description>Crisp and straight to the point lectures!
This course will cover the following topics.
· Design thinking
- You will learn about the 5 stages of Design thinking process: Empathize, Define, Ideate, Prototype &amp;amp; Test
· Challenges faced during successful Product development
· Characteristics of Product development
· Cost &amp;amp; Duration of product development
· Case study on Electronic brakeforce distribution system
· Difference between Agile, Design thinking Design sprint</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Drawing Cartoon : Baby Viking 2.0 (NEW)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-art-of-drawing-cartoon-baby-viking-2.0-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-art-of-drawing-cartoon-baby-viking-2.0-new/</guid>
      <description>Have you been laughed at and told you&#39;re not creative?
Do you want to learn how to draw professional colored Cartoon Characters straight from your imagination to impress your &#34;Talented&#34; Friends and Family?
Give me a moment of your time and I will show you how to draw and edit your own colored Cartoon Character from your imagination.
My name is T.S Amachree and I am a Cartoonist. This Masterclass is an improved version with a never before seen Step- by - Step Guide for Drawing A Cartoon Character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducción al diseño web: HTML y CSS</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introducci%C3%B3n-al-dise%C3%B1o-web-html-y-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 16:17:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introducci%C3%B3n-al-dise%C3%B1o-web-html-y-css/</guid>
      <description>El lenguaje de marcado de hipertexto (HTML) es el lenguaje de marcado estándar para los documentos diseñados para ser vistos en un navegador web. Puede ayudarse de tecnologías como las hojas de estilo en cascada (CSS). CSS describe cómo deben mostrarse los elementos HTML en la pantalla, en el papel o en otros medios.
Juntos entenderemos cómo crear una página web utilizando HTML y CSS
HTML5, CSS3, Head, Body, Semantic Tags.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Affinity Publisher Guide - Affinity Publisher for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/affinity-publisher-guide-affinity-publisher-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 21:32:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/affinity-publisher-guide-affinity-publisher-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Affinity Publisher Guide - Affinity Publisher for Beginners!
The only course you will need to start with Affinity Publisher, one of the best publishing software in the industry.
Affinity Publisher is an easy-to-use desktop publishing software that helps you create beautiful layouts with custom graphics and images in minutes. It&#39;s the perfect choice for a graphic designer who wants to take on a more creative role, or for someone who has always wanted to create their own book, magazine, or brochure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cartoon Drawing Course : Angry Mom Driving in Traffic</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cartoon-drawing-course-angry-mom-driving-in-traffic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 21:27:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cartoon-drawing-course-angry-mom-driving-in-traffic/</guid>
      <description>This course will help you with the knoweldge on How to Draw and Color Cartoons, with these simplified and easy to follow techniques to enable you become a Professional Cartoonist.
Created by a Amazing Cartoonist ( over 10 years Experience) T.S Amachree to help you Draw and Color Amazing Cartoons Straight from Your Imagination even with your little experience in Drawing.
What You&#39;ll Learn
How to Draw &amp;amp; Color A Cartoon School Bus</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Voice to 3D Animation Course (2022 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-voice-to-3d-animation-course-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 21:27:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-voice-to-3d-animation-course-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>&#34;3D animation is a technique which allows for each object or person to have their own three-dimensional space; this can create the illusion of depth while simultaneously creating motion within that world.&#34; Good 3D animation is hard to create or execute and we all know it. What we must further be aware of is what is harder still is being committed to it in the long run as 3D animation is a vast, tiring and long process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Express your Stories with Cartoons</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-express-your-stories-with-cartoons/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 13:34:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-express-your-stories-with-cartoons/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED VERSION 21/10/2021
Are you Creative with Stories but You Don&#39;t really Know how to bring it to life visually? This Course is for you.
Hello; I&#39;m T.S Amachree and I&#39;m a Professional Cartoonist.
In this detailed Cartoon Comic Series Course; I will be sharing with you my knowledge &amp;amp; secrets in Drawing and Developing Cartoon Comic series from your Imagination.
This course will teach you easy yet powerful techniques and tricks to help you create amazing Comic Series that will impress your friends and family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Painting using FlowScape: Paint Dream Worlds in 3D (2021)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/3d-painting-using-flowscape-paint-dream-worlds-in-3d-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/3d-painting-using-flowscape-paint-dream-worlds-in-3d-2021/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the fifth course in Level 3 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Creative Arts, Design and Animation&#34;.
Fantasy Environment construction has never been this easy !! Want to Digitally 3D paint for the first time ever with no technical or animation skills? Anyone can do this. Just Click and Paint.
In this mind-blowing course on &#34;3D Painting using FlowScape: Paint Dream Worlds in 3D&#34;, created by Digital Marketing Legend &#39;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#39; and Civil Engineering MasterMind &#39;Saranya Srinidhi&#39;, you can learn to create your own fantasy world nature scenes in 3D simply by painting with your mouse or keyword keys inside the software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Lightroom Classic Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-lightroom-classic-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:30:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-lightroom-classic-basics/</guid>
      <description>SO, YOU’RE LOOKING FOR A COURSE THAT WILL TEACH YOU BASIC LIGHTROOM CLASSIC QUICKLY &amp;amp; IN A FUN MANNER?
I’ve got just the course for you!
Welcome, my name is Josh Werner with Learn Tech Plus and I’ve put this course together to help people just like you quickly master Basic Lightroom Classic...Whether you’re a beginner or experienced with existing Adobe Applications!
If your goal is to become a user of Basic Lightroom Classic, then this course is perfect for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curso de HostGator 2022: El Hosting Ideal Para WordPress</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-de-hostgator-2022-el-hosting-ideal-para-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 22:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-de-hostgator-2022-el-hosting-ideal-para-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>HOSTGATOR es un servicio de alojamiento web que proporciona alojamiento compartido, alojamiento en la nube, soluciones empresariales, alojamiento de correo electrónico y registro de dominio. Es uno de los proveedores de hosting (alojamiento web) más populares y con más demanda del internet. Es uno de los mejores hosting para sitios de WordPress y te permite publicar sitios web de manera fácil y rápida.
HostGator proporciona servicios de alojamiento web para sitios web de WordPress , Joomla , Magento , Drupal , PrestaShop y WooCommerce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>الاظهار المعماري للمسقط الافقي بالخامات المختلفة للمبتدئين</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%B8%D9%87%D8%A7%D8%B1-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D8%B9%D9%85%D8%A7%D8%B1%D9%8A-%D9%84%D9%84%D9%85%D8%B3%D9%82%D8%B7-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%81%D9%82%D9%8A-%D8%A8%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AE%D8%A7%D9%85%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D8%AE%D8%AA%D9%84%D9%81%D8%A9-%D9%84%D9%84%D9%85%D8%A8%D8%AA%D8%AF%D8%A6%D9%8A%D9%86/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 19:14:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%B8%D9%87%D8%A7%D8%B1-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D8%B9%D9%85%D8%A7%D8%B1%D9%8A-%D9%84%D9%84%D9%85%D8%B3%D9%82%D8%B7-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%81%D9%82%D9%8A-%D8%A8%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AE%D8%A7%D9%85%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D8%AE%D8%AA%D9%84%D9%81%D8%A9-%D9%84%D9%84%D9%85%D8%A8%D8%AA%D8%AF%D8%A6%D9%8A%D9%86/</guid>
      <description>أهلا بكم في الكورس التعليمي &#34;الاظهار المعماري للمسقط الافقي بالخامات المختلفة للمبتدئين&#34;. كان هدفي بهذا الكورس الاحساس بالمتعة من خلال التعامل مع الاظهار لمجموعة من المساقط الافقية الصغيرة المساحة لكي تكون مناسبة للمبتدئين لتعلم اساسيات ومبادئ الاظهار المعماري اليدوي بالخامات المختلفة مثل أقلام الرصاص / الالوان الخشب / الوان الماركر من المستوي صفر لاظهار امكانيات كل خامة من الالوان وقدرتها على التعبير بجرأة في الاظهار المعماري, وذلك بناء علي تكنيك مبسط وسهل في استعمال كل خخامة الاقلام الرصاص بمختلف درجاتها.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-Shirt Design Masterclass In Photoshop | Sell Your T-Shirt</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/t-shirt-design-masterclass-in-photoshop-sell-your-t-shirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 13:12:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/t-shirt-design-masterclass-in-photoshop-sell-your-t-shirt/</guid>
      <description>In this course you will learn How to create or design your own custom T-Shirt In Photoshop. This course is for Intermediate skill levels, so you will find this course easy to follow if you have basic photoshop knowledge. You will learn how to design a fire fighter tshirt, how to design hero soldier or I’d rather die like a man than live like a coward tagline design, how to design a wanted black and white tshirt, how design a lumberjack tshirt using only with elements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Cartoon Drawing  Course :  a Kid driving a Car</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/simple-cartoon-drawing-course-a-kid-driving-a-car/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 13:12:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/simple-cartoon-drawing-course-a-kid-driving-a-car/</guid>
      <description>Drawing a Car can be very complicated when editing the transparent windShield; in this masterclass, i will teach you a simple technique to achieve Transparent Glasses using aKid in His Toy Car. This is a Real Time Step-By Step Process of the entire Drawing and Editing using Photoshop.
Hello I&#39;m T.S Amachree, I have been a Cartoonist for more than 13 years and I have upgraded my techniques over the years; I love deeply sharing my Knoweldge and Experience with you, How I Draw and Color My Cartoon Characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catia V5 Composites Design Eğitimi! | Kompozit Tasarımı!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/catia-v5-composites-design-e%C4%9Fitimi-kompozit-tasar%C4%B1m%C4%B1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/catia-v5-composites-design-e%C4%9Fitimi-kompozit-tasar%C4%B1m%C4%B1/</guid>
      <description>CATIA, bir Fransız Havacılık Şirketi tarafından tasarlanan ileri seviye bir CAD (Computer Aided Design), yani Bilgisayar Destekli Tasarım Programıdır. İçerisinde bir çok sektöre hitap eden modüllerin bulunması, CATIA programının birinci tercih edilme sebebidir. Programın bu kadar çok modüle sahip olmasından da en çok ülkemizde Otomotiv, Havacılık ve Savunma Sanayi gibi sektörlerde kullanılmaktadır. Aynı zamanda da ülkemizde CATIA programının en çok kullanılan versiyonu da CATIA V5 versiyonudur. Bu eğitim de CATIA V5 R21 sürümü ile hazırlanmıştır.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalıp Tasarım Mühendislerinden Solidworks Eğitimi!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kal%C4%B1p-tasar%C4%B1m-m%C3%BChendislerinden-solidworks-e%C4%9Fitimi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kal%C4%B1p-tasar%C4%B1m-m%C3%BChendislerinden-solidworks-e%C4%9Fitimi/</guid>
      <description>Solidworks eğitimini Kalıp Tasarım Mühendislerinden öğrenmeye hazır mısınız? Tüm tasarım ve imalat tecrübelerimizi sizinle paylaşacağımız Solidworks eğitiminde göreceğiniz ileri seviye 3D modelleme teknikleri ile piyasada rahatlıkla fark yaratabileceksiniz! Eğitmenler olarak uzun yıllar çalıştığımız plastik enjeksiyon ve sac metal kalıp tasarımlarında edindiğimiz bilgi birikimlerimizi şimdi sizinle paylaşmaya hazırız! Bu eğitimimizde Solidworks programının önemli olan tüm modüllerine sıfırdan başlayarak, ileri seviyeye kadar değineceğiz. Eğitimimiz gelen istekler doğrultusunda her zaman güncel tutulmaya da çalışılacaktır.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NX ile EDM Tezgahları için Bakır Elektrot Tasarımı Eğitimi!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/nx-ile-edm-tezgahlar%C4%B1-i%C3%A7in-bak%C4%B1r-elektrot-tasar%C4%B1m%C4%B1-e%C4%9Fitimi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/nx-ile-edm-tezgahlar%C4%B1-i%C3%A7in-bak%C4%B1r-elektrot-tasar%C4%B1m%C4%B1-e%C4%9Fitimi/</guid>
      <description>Elektroerozyon (EDM), iş parçasına istenilen şekli vermek için elektrik boşalmasından faydalanılan üretim yöntemidir. Elektrik iletkeni malzemelere uygulananır. Metal aşındırma işlemi takım görevini yapan bir elektrot ile iş parçası arasında meydana gelen kıvılcımların yardımıyla gerçekleştirilir. Kıvılcımlar, ergime ve buharlaşma yoluyla çok küçük malzeme parçacıkları kaldırarak parça yüzeyini erozyona tabi tutar ve parça üzerinde ufak çukurlar oluşturur. EDM sırasında elektrot ile iş parçası arasındaki mesafe 0,0125 mm ile 0,05 mm arasındadır. Bu mesafe takım ve iş parçası arasında elektrik arkı oluşması için yeterlidir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NX ile Maçalar için Hidrolik Piston Tasarımı Eğitimi!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/nx-ile-ma%C3%A7alar-i%C3%A7in-hidrolik-piston-tasar%C4%B1m%C4%B1-e%C4%9Fitimi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/nx-ile-ma%C3%A7alar-i%C3%A7in-hidrolik-piston-tasar%C4%B1m%C4%B1-e%C4%9Fitimi/</guid>
      <description>Hidrolik pistonlar, üzerindeki sıvı basıncını, silindir şeklindeki piston mekanizması sayesinde hareket enerjisine dönüştürebilen, yani uygulanan basınçla mekanik enerji üretebilen sistemlerdir. Hidrolik pompalar tarafından üretilen enerji çeşitli silindirler yardımıyla doğrusal veya açısal harekete dönüşmektedir. Buradaki açığa çıkan kuvvetin büyüklüğünü belirleyen en önemli faktörler, silindirin çapı ve çeşididir.
Hidrolik silindir gövde ve piston olarak iki ana parçadan meydana gelir. Bunların yanında sızdırmazlık elemanları ve bağlantı elemanları silindir üzerinde bulunmaktadır. Çok yüksek basınçlarda kullanıldığı için gömlek et kalınlığı kaldırabileceği basınca göre hesaplanır.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming A UX Writer</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/becoming-a-ux-writer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 12:27:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/becoming-a-ux-writer/</guid>
      <description>UX writing is the verbal user communication within digital interfaces. It appears in apps, websites, and all other kinds of digital products that users interact with – and, as such, it is an integral part of the user experience. For writers and designers, however, UX writing is much more than that: Since big tech companies have become increasingly aware of the importance of UX writing, the young discipline offers promising job opportunities, exciting tasks, and a great career outlook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canva: Certificação Designer Gráfico Profissional | 2022 |</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/canva-certifica%C3%A7%C3%A3o-designer-gr%C3%A1fico-profissional-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 13:18:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/canva-certifica%C3%A7%C3%A3o-designer-gr%C3%A1fico-profissional-2022/</guid>
      <description>Olá! Seja bem vind@ ao curso mais completo de Canva 2022 aqui da plataforma! Muito prazer, eu sou o professor Rafael Galvão, sou designer gráfico a mais de 3 anos e tenho mais de 8 milhões de visualizações em todos os meus projetos! Já desenvolvi trabalhos para pequenas, médias e grandes empresas e Universidades no Brasil e no exterior! Vou compartilhar contigo no curso por meio de uma metodologia de fácil compreensão várias dicas estratégicas para o desenvolvimento dos seus projetos do absoluto zero até o mercado!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rigging a Character with Duik Bassel in After Effects</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/rigging-a-character-with-duik-bassel-in-after-effects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 06:56:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/rigging-a-character-with-duik-bassel-in-after-effects/</guid>
      <description>You may have the same question that Is it possible to rig a character and then create a walk cycle for it, in the shortest time and easiest way?
To answer this question I have to say: Yes, The Duik Basel script has provided this. With this script you can easily rig your character, just by one click and also you can create walk cycle animation for your character, just by one click.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Der ultimative Adobe Photoshop CC Wekzeuge Kurs [2021]</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/der-ultimative-adobe-photoshop-cc-wekzeuge-kurs-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:46:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/der-ultimative-adobe-photoshop-cc-wekzeuge-kurs-2021/</guid>
      <description>Info zu dem Kurs
In diesem ultimativen Adobe Photoshop CC Werkzeuge Kurs auf deutsch lernst Du nicht nur die Einstellungen aller Werkzeuge kennen, sondern ich werde Dir auch noch ein paar Anwendungsbeispiele zeigen, die man als Designer oder Fotograf für Grafiken und Fotobearbeitung ganz gut gebrauchen kann. Ganz egal ob Webdesigner, Mediendesigner, Logodesigner, Grafikdesigner, Künstler, Fotograf, Freelancer oder einfacher Hobby Photoshopper in diesem Kurs ist für jeden etwas dabei! Zusätzlich werde ich Dir neben den Werkzeugen auch noch zeigen wo Du kostenlose Pinsel und Schriftarten herunterladen kannst und ich werde Dir auch die Mischmodis, Pinseleinstellungen, den Farbwähler, auswählen + maskieren und die Kopierquellen beibringen, daher diese Punkte auch alle mit den Photoshop Werkzeugen zusammenhängen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Nothing To Pro: Business Card Design With Photoshop CC</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/from-nothing-to-pro-business-card-design-with-photoshop-cc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 09:53:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/from-nothing-to-pro-business-card-design-with-photoshop-cc/</guid>
      <description>From Nothing To Pro: Business Card Design With Photoshop CC Graphics Design Theory In this course, I&#39;m going to be doing a really practical and comprehensive dive into photoshop business card design for you going through every single aspect of the graphics design theory I used all round.
When you are done learning, there&#39;s a bonus class which takes you by the hand and show you how to make side income designing business card for brands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/wordpress-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/wordpress-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to learn how to instantly create an amazing website for your business, blog or any other endeavor? Would you like me to teach you how to setup said website in under two hours, with your only upfront costs being hosting and a domain name ? Can you follow the easy instructions I will lay down for you in order to setup your very own commerce or entertainment platform?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Dreamweaver 2021 Projects</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-dreamweaver-2021-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-dreamweaver-2021-projects/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Edit Websites but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Websites and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Dreamweaver 2021 Projects is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Web Tools are an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start Editing Websites like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop 2021 Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-2021-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-2021-basics/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Design but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Designs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Photoshop 2021 Basics is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Design is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building designs like an expert with Adobe Photoshop 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Создание бизнес презентации в PowerPoint с нуля</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D1%81%D0%BE%D0%B7%D0%B4%D0%B0%D0%BD%D0%B8%D0%B5-%D0%B1%D0%B8%D0%B7%D0%BD%D0%B5%D1%81-%D0%BF%D1%80%D0%B5%D0%B7%D0%B5%D0%BD%D1%82%D0%B0%D1%86%D0%B8%D0%B8-%D0%B2-powerpoint-%D1%81-%D0%BD%D1%83%D0%BB%D1%8F/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D1%81%D0%BE%D0%B7%D0%B4%D0%B0%D0%BD%D0%B8%D0%B5-%D0%B1%D0%B8%D0%B7%D0%BD%D0%B5%D1%81-%D0%BF%D1%80%D0%B5%D0%B7%D0%B5%D0%BD%D1%82%D0%B0%D1%86%D0%B8%D0%B8-%D0%B2-powerpoint-%D1%81-%D0%BD%D1%83%D0%BB%D1%8F/</guid>
      <description>Курс &#34;Создание бизнес презентации в PowerPoint с нуля&#34; состоит из 10 основных лекций, каждая из которых посвящена созданию 1 из 10 слайдов. Опыт показывает, что 10-12 слайдов – это оптимальный размер бизнес-презентации. Помимо лекций, к курсу прилагается папка с исходными файлами, чтобы облегчить Вам поиск необходимых для дизайна иконок и фото.
Также к курсу прилагаются 7 бонусных видео и домашние задания, разработанные к каждой теме. В них я делюсь секретами профессионального дизайнера, даю советы и вдохновляю Вас на лучшие результаты.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Realistic Interior creation/render with blender from scratch</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/realistic-interior-creation/render-with-blender-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 13:13:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/realistic-interior-creation/render-with-blender-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>The course has been created using a free software blender 2.83 software, Students can make use of either blender 2.8 or any later version(2.81, 2.82, 2.83.....)This course has been developed to meet the need of anyone who wants to learn to use the blender software to create stunning interior images. It has been designed to meet the needs of those who either haven&#39;t used Blender software at all, have an understanding of the software interface, or perhaps make use of other software programs and want to learn to use blender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop Quick Start for Absolute Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-quick-start-for-absolute-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-quick-start-for-absolute-beginners/</guid>
      <description>If you want to learn the basics of photoshop but do not have a great deal of time, this course is for you!
Adobe Photoshop used to be this really complex and even cryptic piece of software that only a few people knew how to really get in there and work. I have been using Photoshop off and on for about 20 years and not just for digital art. My name is rich Grayson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income: Beginners Design &amp; Print on demand</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/passive-income-beginners-design-print-on-demand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/passive-income-beginners-design-print-on-demand/</guid>
      <description>This is an awesome Photoshop course that teaches you how to use this program from a complete beginner to create a design and selling option for it. Even if you&#39;ve never touched Photoshop in your life. I can teach you how to design like a pro. I have also added a few tips &amp;amp; tricks that I learned over the years. This course is like no other course on the internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Las Patologías en Edificios y Construcción Arquitectónica</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/las-patolog%C3%ADas-en-edificios-y-construcci%C3%B3n-arquitect%C3%B3nica/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/las-patolog%C3%ADas-en-edificios-y-construcci%C3%B3n-arquitect%C3%B3nica/</guid>
      <description>Las Patologías en los Edificios
Introducción a la interpretación de las posibles causas de patologías en edificación. Instructores: Arquitecto Álvaro García y Arquitecto Técnico Jaime López. Contenido Actualizado: Octubre 2021 Calificación: ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐
Descripción del Curso:
Los edificios tienen una vulnerabilidad propia que resulta más o menos importante, pero inevitable. Las deficiencias inherentes a las técnicas y los materiales utilizados en su ejecución, por un lado, y el uso funcional de los mismos a lo largo de su vida útil, por otro, hace que vayan sufriendo un implacable deterioro que obliga a alguna intervención en un momento determinado de su vida, a pesar, incluso, de un adecuado mantenimiento.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VRay SketchUp. De Básico a Profesional Experto (ChaosGroup)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/vray-sketchup.-de-b%C3%A1sico-a-profesional-experto-chaosgroup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/vray-sketchup.-de-b%C3%A1sico-a-profesional-experto-chaosgroup/</guid>
      <description>VRay 2.0 para SketchUp. De Básico a Profesional Experto
Renderiza tus modelos de SketchUp y consigue imágenes hiperrealistas que muestren tus proyectos de forma más atractiva.
Instructor: Arquitecto Álvaro García. Contenido Actualizado: Octubre 2021 Calificación: ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐
···························································································································································
Nota: Si tienes una versión de VRay superior o igual a la 3.4 accede a mi curso &#34;SketchUp 2020 + VRay Next. Aprende con Proyectos 3D Reales&#34;
···························································································································································
Descripción del Curso:
En este curso te enseño a dominar V-Ray para SketchUp, una de las herramientas líderes en el renderizado por su rapidez y realismo, con un rico y completo set de funciones y características.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become Professional Social Media Visual Designer | Canva</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/become-professional-social-media-visual-designer-canva/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/become-professional-social-media-visual-designer-canva/</guid>
      <description>Canva helps you to professionally prepare many images such as social media posts, logos, posters, presentations, invitations, cards, advertisements from your phone, tablet or computer. Every design has some rules, of course, but it depends on the imagination on the basis of design ability. Canva gives you exactly this support. You don&#39;t need to have miracle design knowledge to use Canva. All you have to do is use your imagination and with the support of us, effortlessly pour all this into the design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphic Design: Side Hustle to Self-Employed</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-side-hustle-to-self-employed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-side-hustle-to-self-employed/</guid>
      <description>Are you thinking about going full-time as a freelancer in graphic design?
Even if you are just ramping up your freelance life after hours, this class will give you a bunch of tools and tips that will set you up for success!
It&#39;s a huge endeavor to get a business off the ground - especially if the business is in creative production ( like graphic design, 3D modeling, illustration, etc). Not only are you responsible for your day-to-day deliverables, but you also have to market yourself, bill clients, network, and so much more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>»PHOTOSHOP | realiza 100 DISEÑOS en un minuto «</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/photoshop-realiza-100-dise%C3%B1os-en-un-minuto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/photoshop-realiza-100-dise%C3%B1os-en-un-minuto/</guid>
      <description>Desde hace tiempo estas usando Photoshop ya sea como fotógrafo, diseñador o community manager, sin embargo, a pesar de que manejas muy bien el programa en tu área de interés, tu flujo de trabajo es sumamente lento, durando horas en procesos que te consumen todo el tiempo.
En este curso avanzado de Photoshop te desvelo todos mis secretos para que al igual que yo puedas tener un flujo de trabajo acelerado, gracias a los procesos automatizados de Photoshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphic Design - Biding For Online Work 101</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-biding-for-online-work-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 10:06:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-biding-for-online-work-101/</guid>
      <description>eBook Included in Class!
There are lots of ways to build your portfolio, meet new clients and make money with graphic design. One of those avenues is online bid-for-work websites like Upwork. These sites let you upload your portfolio, check out job listings, and offer a bid to do the work based on the client&#39;s description of the job they need to be done. Seems easy enough? Not always!
If you are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A complete Website Development tool without Programming</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/a-complete-website-development-tool-without-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/a-complete-website-development-tool-without-programming/</guid>
      <description>Free Website Designing without Programming Language :
Once you pay for your web design, you are the owner of your website. We don’t use any proprietary software to keep you locked down. You’re free to take your website with you and make any changes.
Dynamic CMS
Get a site with all dynamic options of CMS. Site will be mobile ready and fit itself into any browser.
Features
We give you Blog, Photo / Video Gallery, News, Testimonial, Contact Form with Map with easy frontend editing option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photoshop Challenge</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/photoshop-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 21:40:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/photoshop-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Adobe Photoshop es el programa más potente del mercado para la transformación, retoque y reparación de imágenes digitales, así como para la elaboración de todo tipo de creatividades.
Este curso pretende ser un curso diferente. Aprenderemos jugando! A través de 9 ejercicios, 9 retos de una dificultad creciente, este curso nos proporcionará todas las habilidades necesarias para tener un conocimiento profundo de las herramientas más importantes de Adobe Photoshop. Se trata de un curso eminentemente práctico en donde se proponen 10 ejercicios para que el alumno los realice primero por si solo antes de ver el video y ponga a prueba sus conocimientos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Adobe Photoshop CC Masterclass Basics To Advanced</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-adobe-photoshop-cc-masterclass-basics-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-adobe-photoshop-cc-masterclass-basics-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Learn Adobe Photoshop CC From Scratch &amp;amp; Ultimate Photoshop Masterclass Course For Newbie. If you are a beginner and looking to learn photoshop from scratch then this course will help you to learn Adobe Photoshop Professionally. For learning graphics design and photoshop retouching from beginner to advanced this course can be a lighthouse for you. You can learn from this course about Photoshop Layer, Color and Adjustment, Photoshop Color Correction, Shape and Symbol, Content-Aware &amp;amp; Cropping, Photoshop Text Style, Gradient Stroke &amp;amp; Bevel, Shadow, Blending, Selection, Photoshop Masking, Blur &amp;amp; Filters, Transform, Warp &amp;amp; Distort, Clipping Mask, Retouch, Photoshop Retouching, Effect Of Visual Style, Brush, Export, Earning Money With Graphics Design Work, Advance Tool and many more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphic Design - Passive Income Downloads &amp; Self Publishing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-passive-income-downloads-self-publishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 10:48:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-passive-income-downloads-self-publishing/</guid>
      <description>-- Updated 6/28/21, remixed audio on all lessons --
So what is the deal with selling downloads and print-on-demand (AKA Self Publishing)? The answers are in this class!
It doesn&#39;t matter how far along you are in your creative arts business, how old you are, how extensive your portfolio is - setting up downloads NOW creates passive future income for years to come. PLUS I show you how you can use them NOW as your own marketing tools while having the same items pull double duty as passive income streams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All In One Adobe Photoshop Essential Course For Everyone</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/all-in-one-adobe-photoshop-essential-course-for-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 13:19:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/all-in-one-adobe-photoshop-essential-course-for-everyone/</guid>
      <description>In this course you will Learn 7 Types Important Work Of Adobe Photoshop With Step-By-Step Video Tutorial for your brand or business or for your personal use!
· This course is actually for anyone because this course provides 7 Essential practical projects
· Do you want to create your own social media graphics, business card, logo or something but you have no idea that how to use Photoshop or don&#39;t know where to begin?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn User Experience Design from A-Z: Adobe XD UI/UX Design</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-user-experience-design-from-a-z-adobe-xd-ui/ux-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 13:19:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-user-experience-design-from-a-z-adobe-xd-ui/ux-design/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Learn User Experience Design from A-Z: Adobe XD UI UX Design
Where you’re going to learn how to get started with User Experience and User Interface Design (UX/UI) Design and how to land your first job as a UX Designer even if you have no prior knowledge or experience.
In this practical, hands-on course our main objective is to give you the education not just to understand the ins and outs of UX and UI Design, but also to learn exactly how the web development industry works, the different roles within a team, how color psychology and color schemes work , so you can learn first hand exactly how to design websites and mobile apps in Adobe XD and create an amazing user experience as a UX &amp;amp; UI Designer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Procreate: Getting Started With Procreate on the iPad (2021)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/procreate-getting-started-with-procreate-on-the-ipad-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/procreate-getting-started-with-procreate-on-the-ipad-2021/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to use Procreate 5X on the iPad with the Apple Pencil for digital art, illustration, drawing and painting.
The iPad (Pro, Air 3, Mini 5, iPad 7) with Procreate 5X can be turned into a mini art studio, a powerful digital drawing tool that you can take with you anywhere. Procreate is one of the best digital art apps in the world of digital art.
I believe in the Learning by Doing principle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graphic Design - Bulletproof Freelance Business</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-bulletproof-freelance-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:16:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/graphic-design-bulletproof-freelance-business/</guid>
      <description>Creating the graphics is only one part of the job!
There is so much more that goes on behind the scenes that can eat into your design time - and PROFITS - if you don’t have your business model set up to protect you and create a transparent and open designer/client relationship at the same time.
Running a small business always has a fair share of the unexpected. Things happen outside the usual ‘get hired - do the design - get paid’ operations that can slow you down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Cinema 4D: Low Poly Planet</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-cinema-4d-low-poly-planet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-cinema-4d-low-poly-planet/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to learn 3D modelling quickly &amp;amp; easily by creating trendy low poly artwork? You can do it in this course and learn the basics of Cinema 4D by creating a Low Poly Planet! This class is perfect for web designers, graphic designers, illustrators and anyone else who would like to learn a bit of 3D modelling to add to their designs. Get started with 3D modelling &amp;amp; take this course now to learn Cinema 4D in just a few hours!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Adobe Animate Megacourse: Beginner to Expert</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-adobe-animate-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-adobe-animate-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to learn how to animate? From childhood and adult favourites like Disney, to advertisements and short films, animation is all around us. Whether you’re an artist out to create original and fan content like short films and sketches, or a designer looking to expand their professional portfolio, animation isn’t just for the professionally-trained artist. Even someone with no animation background can learn the skills and start creating beautiful pieces of art - and we’re here to teach you how.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop CC Crash Course Learn Photoshop In Two Hour</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-cc-crash-course-learn-photoshop-in-two-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-cc-crash-course-learn-photoshop-in-two-hour/</guid>
      <description>Hi There, I am Stephen Koel Soren and I am a Graphics and Web Expert. This is a crash course for Adobe Photoshop and You will learn only the essential part that is really required for design in Photoshop within hour. You will learn from this course:
Color and Adjustment
Content-Aware &amp;amp; Cropping
Text Style
Shadow
Selection &amp;amp; Masking
Blur &amp;amp; Filters
Retouch
and many more.
This course is especially designed for beginner those who want to learn photoshop basic and essential part within a short time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Course of After Effects: Learn From an Expert</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-course-of-after-effects-learn-from-an-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-course-of-after-effects-learn-from-an-expert/</guid>
      <description>Hi. This is Mohammad Fazel, motion designer and i have 10 years of experience in this field. I&#39;ll be glad to share my exprience in After Effects with you. in this course, I&#39;ll explore all capabilities that After Effects has in making Motion graphics and visual Effects.
after watching this course, you&#39;ll absolutely be ready to enter the world of motion graphics and visual effects.
you don&#39;t need any prior knowledge for this course and I&#39;ll teach you from introducing you to after effects to the point that you learn everything about the software.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
