<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Other Personal Development on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/other-personal-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Other Personal Development on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/other-personal-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quit your smartphone addiction with(in) 30 days challenges</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quit-your-smartphone-addiction-within-30-days-challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quit-your-smartphone-addiction-within-30-days-challenges/</guid>
      <description>This course is by no means a course in treating nomophobia, which is the term for the fear of losing one&#39;s phone, and an abbreviation for No More Phone (NoMoPhone/Phobia). It is merely a set of activities that anyone can do in an attempt to control and reduce the use and abuse of time spent on a smartphone. The average time spent online is around 7 hours per day, and most of it is done via a smartphone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn to drive a car: real world driving &amp; exam preparation</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-to-drive-a-car-real-world-driving-exam-preparation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-to-drive-a-car-real-world-driving-exam-preparation/</guid>
      <description>Driving can be a daunting task if you lack the experience or the knowledge. Learners commonly feel unconfident when they step into the car next to their examiner for their final exam and make unnecessary mistakes because of it. This often results in insecurity, which drags on into their future driving time.Our lessons are packed with tips, tricks and how-to&#39;s to help you enjoy driving. Whether you simply want to improve your driving skills, become a more confident driver or want to pass that driving exam, this is your course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neuroplasticity: Discover How To Rewire Your Anxiety</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/neuroplasticity-discover-how-to-rewire-your-anxiety/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/neuroplasticity-discover-how-to-rewire-your-anxiety/</guid>
      <description>The human brain is capable of integrating intricate and diverse inputs from multiple sensory systems simultaneously in order to rapidly comprehend and assess the information for planning and execution of complex actions. These and other cognitive functions are performed by the vastly interconnected neural networks formed by the roughly 100 billion neurons of the brain. The precise patterns of connectivity among neurons within these networks determines their function, and through experience, these connectivity patterns change over time to enable acquisition of new skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storytelling With Imagery For Persuasion &amp; Personal Brand</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/storytelling-with-imagery-for-persuasion-personal-brand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 20:40:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/storytelling-with-imagery-for-persuasion-personal-brand/</guid>
      <description>Learn storytelling in two ways:
1) The traditional story arch and all the important story elements
2) Create creative imagery with your writing and vocal presentation that inspires emotions in your audience, becomes memorable, and leaves a lasting and impactful lesson and impression.
USE EMOTIONS FOR PERSUASION
People make decisions emotionally much more than logically. That&#39;s why great storytelling is about painting a picture in someone&#39;s mind and making them see things your way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post pandemic love. The undoing effect</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/post-pandemic-love.-the-undoing-effect/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/post-pandemic-love.-the-undoing-effect/</guid>
      <description>The current pandemic has made an impact not only on physical well-being and mortality,, but also on our mental health. Recent studies have shown increases in the prevalence of depression and anxiety as well as increases in post-traumatic stress disorder and substance abuse worldwide.
Many people all over the globe have already experienced different kind of challenges like loss of closed ones, loss of job, loss of business, financial problems, relationship problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence (AI) Tools For Job Seekers (2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-ai-tools-for-job-seekers-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-ai-tools-for-job-seekers-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience the technology covering &#34;Artificial Intelligence (AI) Tools For Job Seekers&#34;.
Do you want to teach your students how they can create a resume super-fast to beat the competition? Or, are you actually looking to learn the practical concepts of the entire process of job-seeking all by yourself? You have come to the right place.
We must understand that people cannot live without progressive technologies, because they have become an integral part of our daily lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOP G1 driver’s license Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/top-g1-drivers-license-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/top-g1-drivers-license-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>G1 Test Practice: Free ON “Drive Test” G1 Practice Test 2021
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily
Our G1 Practice Test with multiple choice questions, is intended to help you prepare for the Ontario G1 practice test and learners driver’s test that is required before you can get your Canadian driver’s license.
This free practice Written G1 driving test is a lesson that is essential for getting your Ontario driver’s license at your local licensing office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Citizenship Test Your Immigration Dream</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/canadian-citizenship-test-your-immigration-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 21:10:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/canadian-citizenship-test-your-immigration-dream/</guid>
      <description>Canadian Citizenship Test Your Immigration Dream
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily
Canadian-Citizenship Practice Test Canadian Symbols Modern Canada Canada’s Economy Justice System and History The Canadian Citizenship Test is a test, administered by the Department of Immigration, Refugees and Citizenship Canada, that is required for all applicants for Canadian citizenship who are aged between 14 and 64 and who meet the basic requirements for citizenship.
The exam is commonly written, however in a few cases it might be oral and take vicinity inside the form of an interview with a citizenship officer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australian Citizenship Test  The Dream</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/australian-citizenship-test-the-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/australian-citizenship-test-the-dream/</guid>
      <description>Welcome ! get Ready for Certificate of Australian Citizenship CAC
Get ready to say &#34;I am Australian.&#34;
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily
2021 Australian Citizenship Test
Congratulations on choosing to become an Australian citizen. It takes courage, endeavor and commitmentto live in a new country and participate fully as a citizen. We value your contribution to our peaceful anddemocratic society. Australian citizenship is an important step in your migration story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Repair - Auto Repair &amp; Tuning - Auto Technician Training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/car-repair-auto-repair-tuning-auto-technician-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/car-repair-auto-repair-tuning-auto-technician-training/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
One of the things that I find most interesting about automotive technology is how it advances and changes. It is also interesting that ideas from many years ago often return to favour. In this course I have therefore concentrated on core technologies, in other words how the technology works, rather than giving too many examples from specific vehicles. However, I have included some examples of Formula 1 technology, arguably the pinnacle of automotive engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
