<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business Analytics &amp; Intelligence on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/business-analytics-intelligence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business Analytics &amp; Intelligence on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/business-analytics-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Spotfire Interview Tech Questions Answered with Explanation</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/spotfire-interview-tech-questions-answered-with-explanation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/spotfire-interview-tech-questions-answered-with-explanation/</guid>
      <description>Get that dream Business Intelligence Job in Spotfire..!
Welcome to this course on Spotfire Technical interview Questions and Answers where you are going to excel the Spotfire Technical job interview. Take the course, learn the material and go into interview with a confidence that you are prepared!
This course will take your knowledge in Spotfire to a different level, making you 100% prepared for the Technical Round. The Questions here are the actual questions being asked in Interviews and a Detail explanation is given for each, so you just not know, but understand the whole concept, making you well prepared for any Interview.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TIBCO Spotfire Development : Beginners To Advanced Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tibco-spotfire-development-beginners-to-advanced-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tibco-spotfire-development-beginners-to-advanced-course/</guid>
      <description>This TIBCO Spotfire course will help you to become a Data Visualization Expert and will enhance your BI skills by offering you comprehensive knowledge, and the required hands-on experience on this widely used BI tool, by solving real-time industry-based projects.
Topics Covered : Adding &amp;amp; Managing Data, Using Data Canvas, Creating &amp;amp; Configuring all Chart Types, Data Limit, Data on Demand, Details on Demand, Advanced Custom Expressions, Subsets, Hierarchy, Marking, Filtering, Action Control, Document Properties, Iron Python Scripting, R Scripts, Collaboration, Visualization Mods, Spotfire Cloud and a lot more !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft SQL Server: Análisis de datos con Tableau</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-sql-server-an%C3%A1lisis-de-datos-con-tableau/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-sql-server-an%C3%A1lisis-de-datos-con-tableau/</guid>
      <description>¿Por qué estudiar SQL?
El Lenguaje SQL (Structured Query Language) es un lenguaje de computación diseñado para el fácil acceso y obtención de información de una Base de Datos.
Saber programar en SQL es la habilidad más solicitada por las empresas de todo el mundo. ¿Qué esperas? ¡Inscríbete ya!
Como la mayoría de los datos comerciales se almacenan en bases de datos relacionales, aprender SQL es esencial para cualquier persona que desee ser analista de datos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tableau: Empieza desde cero</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tableau-empieza-desde-cero/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tableau-empieza-desde-cero/</guid>
      <description>¡Vuélvete un experto en el Business Intelligence con TableauI!
Si eres un estudiante o profesionista que quiere potenciar su carrera profesional te tengo una buena noticia:
¡Encontraste el curso indicado!
¿Sientes que tu carrera profesional esta estancada?
¿Tu perfil no destaca entre el de los demás?
¿Sientes que en la escuela no aprendiste nada útil para el mundo laboral?
¿Crees que Excel es la única herramienta para analizar datos y hacer gráficas?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel Analytics: Linear Regression Analysis in MS Excel</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-analytics-linear-regression-analysis-in-ms-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-analytics-linear-regression-analysis-in-ms-excel/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re looking for a complete Linear Regression course that teaches you everything you need to create a Linear Regression model in Excel, right?
You&#39;ve found the right Linear Regression course!
After completing this course you will be able to:
· Identify the business problem which can be solved using linear regression technique of Machine Learning.
· Create a linear regression model in Excel and analyze its result.
· Confidently practice, discuss and understand Machine Learning concepts</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Course on Data Cleaning in MS Excel</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-course-on-data-cleaning-in-ms-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:33:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-course-on-data-cleaning-in-ms-excel/</guid>
      <description>Excel is one of the most in-demand skills at all levels and having complete knowledge of this tool will help you to grow and earn.
Data is the new oil. Data that is downloaded from software, and survey forms have errors in terms of formatting, duplications, numbers saved as text, numbers saved as negative, etc., There is a need to clean all these data errors to prepare the data for a meaningful and insightful interpretation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Business Analytics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-business-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 20:12:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-business-analytics/</guid>
      <description>This is a non-technical program, no coding background is required.
This course offers an introduction to big data analytics, statistics and data-driven decision making for all business professionals, including those with no prior analytics knowledge.
Analytical skills are essential in any business. There is a growing need for employees across all areas to know how to read, interpret, and present data in a way that can be understood across all functions and inform decision making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Power BI 2022: The Complete Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-power-bi-2022-the-complete-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 20:12:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-power-bi-2022-the-complete-guide/</guid>
      <description>Learn one of the most in demand business intelligence tool in the world and master the most important concepts in the Power BI Ecosystem.
Power BI is an essential tool for anyone working with Data!
This course is hands-on and you will LEARN BY DOING!
COURSE PROJECT
We will be using a really cool Formula One Dataset to create an interactive report with some amazing visualizations.
We will connect to various data sources including csv, excel, JSON and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dashboards with Excel</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/dashboards-with-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/dashboards-with-excel/</guid>
      <description>GENERAL
When controllers create reports or tools, they are not always read by management.
Too often, the reports contain superfluous material, such as clipart, or confusing graphics and numerous legends.
In this Online-Course you will learn how to create professional Business Charts with Excel step by step.
The concept named OPO - one page only.
At PUMA AG I was responsible for the worldwide Retail Controlling and developed a new Reporting-System for the stores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistics for Business Analytics using MS Excel</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/statistics-for-business-analytics-using-ms-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/statistics-for-business-analytics-using-ms-excel/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re looking for a complete course on understanding Statistics for Business Analytics, right?
You&#39;ve found the right Statistics for Business Analytics using MS Excel course! This course will teach you data-driven decision-making and the use of analytical and statistical methods in business settings.
After completing this course you will be able to:
Understand how to formulate a business problem as an analytics problem
Summarize business data into tables and charts to communicate information effectively</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Análisis de datos con Google Data Studio</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/an%C3%A1lisis-de-datos-con-google-data-studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/an%C3%A1lisis-de-datos-con-google-data-studio/</guid>
      <description>Para aquellos de ustedes que aún no lo saben, Google Data Studio es una herramienta de informes de fácil uso, personalización y difusión. Le permite transformar sus datos en informes atractivos e informativos para su audiencia. Es una gran herramienta para realizar un seguimiento de los KPI que respaldan los objetivos comerciales y generan informes periódicos. En este momento, Data Studio beta se ofrece de forma gratuita a los usuarios de la cuenta de Google y a los clientes de Google Cloud Platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Pro-Business &amp; Personal-One QuickBooks File</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-pro-business-personal-one-quickbooks-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-pro-business-personal-one-quickbooks-file/</guid>
      <description>Both business and personal financial, bookkeeping, and tax information in one QuickBooks file using class tracking. This course will demonstrate how to use the class tracking feature in QuickBooks Pro Desktop 2019, applying the feature to tracking both business and personal financial information in one QuickBooks file. Note that tracking both business and personal data in one QuickBooks file will not be the best option for many businesses but is a good option for small businesses who want one location to track and analyze financial data and generate financial reports that can be used for tax preparation, budgeting, and business planning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Decision Trees, Random Forests, AdaBoost &amp; XGBoost in Python</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/decision-trees-random-forests-adaboost-xgboost-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 20:03:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/decision-trees-random-forests-adaboost-xgboost-in-python/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re looking for a complete Decision tree course that teaches you everything you need to create a Decision tree/ Random Forest/ XGBoost model in Python, right?
You&#39;ve found the right Decision Trees and tree based advanced techniques course!
After completing this course you will be able to:
Identify the business problem which can be solved using Decision tree/ Random Forest/ XGBoost of Machine Learning.
Have a clear understanding of Advanced Decision tree based algorithms such as Random Forest, Bagging, AdaBoost and XGBoost</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data analysis &amp; Business Intelligence | Advanced MySQL</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/data-analysis-business-intelligence-advanced-mysql/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/data-analysis-business-intelligence-advanced-mysql/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: This is an ADVANCED SQL course, built on topics and skills covered in the previous course or on prior knowledge in SQL queries....Please have the minimum prerequisite skills or complete the Beginner SQL course to be able to complete the course
In this course you will develop real-world analytics and Business Intelligence skills using Advanced SQL by Analyzing an ecommerce store to get insight for the performance of the website, products and user experience</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Analyst Skill path in Hindi - हिंदी में सीखें</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/data-analyst-skill-path-in-hindi-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%96%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 21:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/data-analyst-skill-path-in-hindi-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%96%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re looking for a complete course on how to become a data analyst, right?
You&#39;ve found the right Data Analyst Masterclass with Excel, SQL &amp;amp; Python course! This course will teach you data-driven decision-making, data visualization, data analytics in SQL, and the use of predictive analytics like linear regression in business settings.
After completing this course you will be able to:
Master Excel&#39;s most popular lookup functions such as Vlookup, Hlookup, Index, and Match</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Einstieg in Excel-Dashboards</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/einstieg-in-excel-dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 20:24:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/einstieg-in-excel-dashboards/</guid>
      <description>Allgemein
In Excel bestehen unzählige Möglichkeiten, Diagramme zu erstellen. Dabei können viele Fehler gemacht werden. Die Excel-Diagramme sind dann nicht aussagekräftig bzw. finden beim Empfänger kein Gehör, weil diese zu einfach erstellt wurden.
In diesem Video-Kurs lernen Sie die Grundlagen für professionelle Dashboards im Controlling.
Inhalt
Abweichung bei 2 Werten
Monate mit roten und grünen Pfeilen
Trennstrich zwischen den Monaten
Beschriftung links im gestapelten Säulen-Diagramm
Tacho-Diagramm
Thermometer
Projektplan
Zusätzlich erhalten Sie die fertigen Excel-Dateien zur Übung und Vertiefung.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL Masterclass: SQL for Data Analytics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sql-masterclass-sql-for-data-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sql-masterclass-sql-for-data-analytics/</guid>
      <description>6 Reasons why you should choose this SQL course
Carefully designed curriculum teaching you everything in SQL that you will need for Data analysis in businesses
Comprehensive - covers basics, advanced SQL statements, PostgreSQL, mySQL, interview tips and performance tuning tips as well
Business related examples and case studies based on SQL techniques, PostgreSQL, mySQL, data analysis techniques
Ample practice exercises because, like any other data analysis tools, SQL requires practice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pentaho for ETL &amp; Data Integration Masterclass 2022 - PDI 9</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pentaho-for-etl-data-integration-masterclass-2022-pdi-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 19:15:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pentaho-for-etl-data-integration-masterclass-2022-pdi-9/</guid>
      <description>What is ETL?
The ETL (extract, transform, load) process is the most popular method of collecting data from multiple sources and loading it into a centralized data warehouse. ETL is an essential component of data warehousing and analytics.
Why Pentaho for ETL?
Pentaho has phenomenal ETL, data analysis, metadata management and reporting capabilities. Pentaho is faster than other ETL tools (including Talend). Pentaho has a user-friendly GUI which is easier and takes less time to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified Six Sigma green belt Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-six-sigma-green-belt-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-six-sigma-green-belt-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Certified Six Sigma green belt Practice Tests
Six Sigma (6σ) is a set of techniques and tools for process improvement. It was introduced by American engineer Bill Smith while working at Motorola in 1986. A six sigma process is one in which 99.99966% of all opportunities to produce some feature of a part are statistically expected to be free of defects.
Six Sigma strategies seek to improve manufacturing quality by identifying and removing the causes of defects and minimizing variability in manufacturing and business processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Power BI - Curso de Power BI Desktop</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-power-bi-curso-de-power-bi-desktop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 22:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-power-bi-curso-de-power-bi-desktop/</guid>
      <description>En este curso online de Power BI Desktop obtendrás las habilidades necesarias para visualizar tus datos y desarrollar reportes que sean de ayuda para la toma de decisiones. DESCRIPCIÓN DE CURSO
Microsoft Power BI es la solución de inteligencia de negocios #1 en el mercado global que incluye un producto o programa gratuito que es Power BI Desktop, con el cual se desarrollan reportes por completo. Ya sea si eres nuevo a esta herramienta, o la has utilizado un poco pero quieres tener más conocimientos, de cualquier forma este curso es para ti.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel: De cero a analista de datos en Power BI</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-de-cero-a-analista-de-datos-en-power-bi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 11:20:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-de-cero-a-analista-de-datos-en-power-bi/</guid>
      <description>¡Vuélvete un experto en el Business Intelligence con Microsoft Excel y Power BI!
Si eres un estudiante o profesionista que quiere potenciar su carrera profesional te tengo una buena noticia:
¡Encontraste el curso indicado!
¿Sientes que tu carrera profesional esta estancada?
¿Tu perfil no destaca entre el de los demás?
¿Sientes que en la escuela no aprendiste nada útil para el mundo laboral?
¿Crees que Excel es la única herramienta para analizar datos y hacer gráficas?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Controlling mit Excel</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/controlling-mit-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 13:12:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/controlling-mit-excel/</guid>
      <description>Allgemein
Excel ist eines der wichtigsten Werkzeuge im Controlling.
Formeln und Diagramme sind eines der Hauptinstrumente von Excel.
In diesem Kurs werden Sie alle relevanten Formeln lernen, die Sie für professionelle Analysen benötigen.
Als ausgebildeter Controller (Controller&#39;s Diplom -CA) habe ich mehrere Jahre für nationale und internationale Unternehmen gearbeitet. Für das Controller Magazin und Controlling Journal habe ich über 50 Excel-Fachartikel verfasst. Zusätzlich bin ich zertifizierter Trainer und Online-Trainer - Sie sind bei mir also was die Themen Controlling und Excel betrifft in guten Händen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google BigQuery &amp; PostgreSQL : Big Query for Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-bigquery-postgresql-big-query-for-data-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jan 2022 11:19:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-bigquery-postgresql-big-query-for-data-analysis/</guid>
      <description>6 Reasons why you should choose this PostgreSQL and BigQuery course
Carefully designed curriculum teaching you everything in SQL and Google BigQuery that you will need for Data analysis in businesses
Comprehensive - covers basic and advanced SQL statements in both PostgreSQL and Google BigQuery
Business related examples and case studies on SQL and Google BigQuery
Ample practice exercises on Google BigQuery because SQL and Google BigQuery require practice
Downloadable resources on SQL and Google BigQuery</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power BI: Empieza desde cero</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/power-bi-empieza-desde-cero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 23:49:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/power-bi-empieza-desde-cero/</guid>
      <description>¡Vuélvete un experto en el Business Intelligence con Power BI!
Si eres un estudiante o profesionista que quiere potenciar su carrera profesional te tengo una buena noticia:
¡Encontraste el curso indicado!
¿Sientes que tu carrera profesional esta estancada?
¿Tu perfil no destaca entre el de los demás?
¿Sientes que en la escuela no aprendiste nada útil para el mundo laboral?
¿Crees que Excel es la única herramienta para analizar datos y hacer gráficas?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Glue Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/amazon-glue-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/amazon-glue-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to do use Amazon Glue but don&#39;t know where to start? Would you like to rune code in response to events and automatically manage the computing resources required by code? Then Amazon Glue Ultimate Course is for you! Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Amazon Glue is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Analytics with Excel PivotTables</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/data-analytics-with-excel-pivottables/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/data-analytics-with-excel-pivottables/</guid>
      <description>About this course
This course will teach you how to do Data analytics with Excel PivotTables. With the help of this course, you will understand the concept, various scenarios, and types of Business analytics. Along with that, you will learn, how to use one of the strongest features of Microsoft Excel, which is the PivotTables. Target audience
Anyone with no knowledge to a basic knowledge of Microsoft Excel can take this course and get a thorough understanding of Excel PivotTables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revenue and Pricing Analytics with Excel &amp; Python.</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/revenue-and-pricing-analytics-with-excel-python./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/revenue-and-pricing-analytics-with-excel-python./</guid>
      <description>Course Image by @agent_illustrateur-Christine Roy from unsplash.
Python Crash section included!
in the late seventies, airline ticket prices in the united states were regulated and almost fixed, we as customers did not have the luxury to opt for economy class or business class, only one class!! Back then American airlines were the leaders in the industry. But with deregulation new disruptors as People Express entered the scene with tickets so much cheaper than American Airlines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Modern Marketing Analytics with Oribi</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-modern-marketing-analytics-with-oribi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:35:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-modern-marketing-analytics-with-oribi/</guid>
      <description>Getting lost in endless piles of data? Wondering where your visitors are coming from? Looking for a way to turn your data into action?
Well... this might be just the course for you!
Welcome to Modern Marketing Analytics with Oribi, your comprehensive guide to using marketing analytics in the data-abundant world of today. In this course, you will become familiar with what marketing analytics are, how they can be measured effectively, and the implications they can have on your business&#39;s success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cadena de suministro y análisis de datos con Excel</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cadena-de-suministro-y-an%C3%A1lisis-de-datos-con-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cadena-de-suministro-y-an%C3%A1lisis-de-datos-con-excel/</guid>
      <description>Existen muchas funciones y herramientas en Excel para analizar y trabajar con la información, algunas de las mas usadas son las siguientes:
Función BuscarV, BuscarH
Función Indice combinado con la funcion coincidir
Función Si, SiError
Funciones de Texto (Extrae, Izquierda, Derecha, Remplazar)
Función Contara, ContarSi, ContarSiConjunto
Función SumarSi, SumarSiConjunto
Funciones matematicas (sumar, restar, promedios, subtotales, redondear, redondear.mas, redondear.menosetc)
Formatos Condicionales
Tablas dinámicas
Creación de diferentes tipos gráficos
Combinación de funciones, tablas y graficas dinámicas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Intelligence using Tableau</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/business-intelligence-using-tableau/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/business-intelligence-using-tableau/</guid>
      <description>This course focuses on how business intelligence in Tableau uses business analytics tools that make it easy to combine data from multiple sources, analyze and visualize information. It helps trainees in making more informed and better decisions to guide the business. After the completion of the course trainee will be through with all the concepts of business intelligence and Tableau.
The objective of this course is to assist the folks in running a business strategically.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
