<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business Analytics &amp; Intelligence on </title>
    <link>/tags/business-analytics-intelligence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business Analytics &amp; Intelligence on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/business-analytics-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Google BigQuery &amp; PostgreSQL : Big Query for Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/google-bigquery-postgresql-big-query-for-data-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/google-bigquery-postgresql-big-query-for-data-analysis/</guid>
      <description>6 Reasons why you should choose this PostgreSQL and BigQuery course
Carefully designed curriculum teaching you everything in SQL and Google BigQuery that you will need for Data analysis in businesses
Comprehensive - covers basic and advanced SQL statements in both PostgreSQL and Google BigQuery
Business related examples and case studies on SQL and Google BigQuery
Ample practice exercises on Google BigQuery because SQL and Google BigQuery require practice
Downloadable resources on SQL and Google BigQuery</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Pro-Business &amp; Personal-One QuickBooks File</title>
      <link>/quickbooks-pro-business-personal-one-quickbooks-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quickbooks-pro-business-personal-one-quickbooks-file/</guid>
      <description>Both business and personal financial, bookkeeping, and tax information in one QuickBooks file using class tracking. 
This course will demonstrate how to use the class tracking feature in QuickBooks Pro Desktop 2019, applying the feature to tracking both business and personal financial information in one QuickBooks file. 
Note that tracking both business and personal data in one QuickBooks file will not be the best option for many businesses but is a good option for small businesses who want one location to track and analyze financial data and generate financial reports that can be used for tax preparation, budgeting, and business planning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Intelligence using Tableau</title>
      <link>/business-intelligence-using-tableau/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/business-intelligence-using-tableau/</guid>
      <description>This course focuses on how business intelligence in Tableau uses business analytics tools that make it easy to combine data from multiple sources, analyze and visualize information. It helps trainees in making more informed and better decisions to guide the business. After the completion of the course trainee will be through with all the concepts of business intelligence and Tableau.
The objective of this course is to assist the folks in running a business strategically.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
