<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business Analytics &amp; Intelligence on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/business-analytics-intelligence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business Analytics &amp; Intelligence on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/business-analytics-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data Analytics with Excel PivotTables</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/data-analytics-with-excel-pivottables/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/data-analytics-with-excel-pivottables/</guid>
      <description>About this course
This course will teach you how to do Data analytics with Excel PivotTables. With the help of this course, you will understand the concept, various scenarios, and types of Business analytics. Along with that, you will learn, how to use one of the strongest features of Microsoft Excel, which is the PivotTables. Target audience
Anyone with no knowledge to a basic knowledge of Microsoft Excel can take this course and get a thorough understanding of Excel PivotTables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google BigQuery &amp; PostgreSQL : Big Query for Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/google-bigquery-postgresql-big-query-for-data-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 13:24:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/google-bigquery-postgresql-big-query-for-data-analysis/</guid>
      <description>6 Reasons why you should choose this PostgreSQL and BigQuery course
Carefully designed curriculum teaching you everything in SQL and Google BigQuery that you will need for Data analysis in businesses
Comprehensive - covers basic and advanced SQL statements in both PostgreSQL and Google BigQuery
Business related examples and case studies on SQL and Google BigQuery
Ample practice exercises on Google BigQuery because SQL and Google BigQuery require practice
Downloadable resources on SQL and Google BigQuery</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pentaho for ETL &amp; Data Integration Masterclass 2021- PDI 9.0</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pentaho-for-etl-data-integration-masterclass-2021-pdi-9.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pentaho-for-etl-data-integration-masterclass-2021-pdi-9.0/</guid>
      <description>What is ETL?
The ETL (extract, transform, load) process is the most popular method of collecting data from multiple sources and loading it into a centralized data warehouse. ETL is an essential component of data warehousing and analytics.
Why Pentaho for ETL?
Pentaho has phenomenal ETL, data analysis, metadata management and reporting capabilities. Pentaho is faster than other ETL tools (including Talend). Pentaho has a user-friendly GUI which is easier and takes less time to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revenue and Pricing Analytics with Excel &amp; Python.</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/revenue-and-pricing-analytics-with-excel-python./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/revenue-and-pricing-analytics-with-excel-python./</guid>
      <description>Course Image by @agent_illustrateur-Christine Roy from unsplash.

Python Crash section included!
in the late seventies, airline ticket prices in the united states were regulated and almost fixed, we as customers did not have the luxury to opt for economy class or business class, only one class!! Back then American airlines were the leaders in the industry. But with deregulation new disruptors as People Express entered the scene with tickets so much cheaper than American Airlines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL Masterclass: SQL for Data Analytics</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sql-masterclass-sql-for-data-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sql-masterclass-sql-for-data-analytics/</guid>
      <description>6 Reasons why you should choose this SQL course
Carefully designed curriculum teaching you everything in SQL that you will need for Data analysis in businesses
Comprehensive - covers basics, advanced SQL statements, PostgreSQL, mySQL, interview tips and performance tuning tips as well
Business related examples and case studies based on SQL techniques, PostgreSQL, mySQL, data analysis techniques
Ample practice exercises because, like any other data analysis tools, SQL requires practice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Modern Marketing Analytics with Oribi</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-modern-marketing-analytics-with-oribi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:35:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-modern-marketing-analytics-with-oribi/</guid>
      <description>Getting lost in endless piles of data? Wondering where your visitors are coming from? Looking for a way to turn your data into action?

Well... this might be just the course for you!

Welcome to Modern Marketing Analytics with Oribi, your comprehensive guide to using marketing analytics in the data-abundant world of today. In this course, you will become familiar with what marketing analytics are, how they can be measured effectively, and the implications they can have on your business&#39;s success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotfire Interview Tech Questions Answered with Explanation</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/spotfire-interview-tech-questions-answered-with-explanation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:35:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/spotfire-interview-tech-questions-answered-with-explanation/</guid>
      <description>Get that dream Business Intelligence Job in Spotfire..!
Welcome to this course on Spotfire Technical interview Questions and Answers where you are going to excel the Spotfire Technical job interview. Take the course, learn the material and go into interview with a confidence that you are prepared!
This course will take your knowledge in Spotfire to a different level, making you 100% prepared for the Technical Round. The Questions here are the actual questions being asked in Interviews and a Detail explanation is given for each, so you just not know, but understand the whole concept, making you well prepared for any Interview.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cadena de suministro y análisis de datos con Excel</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cadena-de-suministro-y-an%C3%A1lisis-de-datos-con-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cadena-de-suministro-y-an%C3%A1lisis-de-datos-con-excel/</guid>
      <description>Existen muchas funciones y herramientas en Excel para analizar y trabajar con la información, algunas de las mas usadas son las siguientes:
Función BuscarV, BuscarH
Función Indice combinado con la funcion coincidir
Función Si, SiError
Funciones de Texto (Extrae, Izquierda, Derecha, Remplazar)
Función Contara, ContarSi, ContarSiConjunto
Función SumarSi, SumarSiConjunto
Funciones matematicas (sumar, restar, promedios, subtotales, redondear, redondear.mas, redondear.menosetc)
Formatos Condicionales
Tablas dinámicas
Creación de diferentes tipos gráficos
Combinación de funciones, tablas y graficas dinámicas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tableau: Empieza desde cero</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tableau-empieza-desde-cero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/tableau-empieza-desde-cero/</guid>
      <description>¡Vuélvete un experto en el Business Intelligence con TableauI!
Si eres un estudiante o profesionista que quiere potenciar su carrera profesional te tengo una buena noticia:
¡Encontraste el curso indicado!

¿Sientes que tu carrera profesional esta estancada?
¿Tu perfil no destaca entre el de los demás?
¿Sientes que en la escuela no aprendiste nada útil para el mundo laboral?
¿Crees que Excel es la única herramienta para analizar datos y hacer gráficas?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Pro-Business &amp; Personal-One QuickBooks File</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-pro-business-personal-one-quickbooks-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-pro-business-personal-one-quickbooks-file/</guid>
      <description>Both business and personal financial, bookkeeping, and tax information in one QuickBooks file using class tracking. 
This course will demonstrate how to use the class tracking feature in QuickBooks Pro Desktop 2019, applying the feature to tracking both business and personal financial information in one QuickBooks file. 
Note that tracking both business and personal data in one QuickBooks file will not be the best option for many businesses but is a good option for small businesses who want one location to track and analyze financial data and generate financial reports that can be used for tax preparation, budgeting, and business planning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Intelligence using Tableau</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/business-intelligence-using-tableau/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/business-intelligence-using-tableau/</guid>
      <description>This course focuses on how business intelligence in Tableau uses business analytics tools that make it easy to combine data from multiple sources, analyze and visualize information. It helps trainees in making more informed and better decisions to guide the business. After the completion of the course trainee will be through with all the concepts of business intelligence and Tableau.
The objective of this course is to assist the folks in running a business strategically.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
