<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nutrition &amp; Diet on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/nutrition-diet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nutrition &amp; Diet on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:58 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/nutrition-diet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sports Nutrition for Athletes and Fitness Enthusiasts</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sports-nutrition-for-athletes-and-fitness-enthusiasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sports-nutrition-for-athletes-and-fitness-enthusiasts/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that research by the University of South Carolina revealed that 91% of athletes and 63% of coaches have little knowledge about sports nutrition?
And indeed, most athletes and fitness enthusiasts are rushing through their daily exercise routine without even knowing the basic difference between proteins and carbs.
But conducting purposeful physical exercise without sports nutrition knowledge is like running around in a dark forest. Blindfolded.
And because those athletes and fitness enthusiasts reach far-from optimal results they are trying to compensate their knowledge BLIND SPOT by turning to crazy expensive supplements that hardly ever work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sports Nutrition for Soccer Players</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sports-nutrition-for-soccer-players/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 21:50:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sports-nutrition-for-soccer-players/</guid>
      <description>In the last Big Count, by sports governing body FIFA in 2006, it was estimated that there are 265 million people who play soccer along with more than 5 million referees. At the time of the count that equated to 4% of the world’s population!
That makes soccer the largest sport on the globe in terms of participation and there is no evidence that its popularity is on the decline. Unfortunately, the nutrition knowledge of the average football player does not reflect the popularity of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weight Loss:  A Girlfriend&#39;s Plan for Losing 5 Pounds Quick!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/weight-loss-a-girlfriends-plan-for-losing-5-pounds-quick/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:30:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/weight-loss-a-girlfriends-plan-for-losing-5-pounds-quick/</guid>
      <description>Are you a girlfriend who has a wedding, graduation or vacation coming up? or perhaps you just had a baby? or are welcoming a new grandbaby? Do you want to feel and look better in your jeans and swim suit? Do you want to be able to get on the floor and play with your child, niece or grandchild? Do you want to be active and enjoy life again? Then this course is for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy 7-DAY MEAL PLAN for Lifelong Weight LOST</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/easy-7-day-meal-plan-for-lifelong-weight-lost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 15:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/easy-7-day-meal-plan-for-lifelong-weight-lost/</guid>
      <description>Find the foods that work for YOU to finally LOSE THE WEIGHT - and KEEP IT OFF FOR LIFE - without exercise, counting calories or strict dieting!
Sounds like a bold statement - right?
Well, it should be because I&#39;ve read the books, tried the programs and diets; and, when I looked at what foods work the best for millions of others, I found a plan that will work for YOU too…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Binge-Free Healthy Lifestyle Diet</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/binge-free-healthy-lifestyle-diet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 13:38:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/binge-free-healthy-lifestyle-diet/</guid>
      <description>In This Online Binge-Free Healthy Lifestyle Diet Burning Course You Will Learn How The Pros Teach People How To Melt Away The Pounds And Boost Their Health &amp;amp; Longevity. This Course Is Not Medical Advice ... But Is Based On Scientific Research &amp;amp; Principles That Are Known To Get Results Fast! Having These Tools &amp;amp; Strategies Will Make Eating Less And Losing The Weight So Much Easier, Dramatically Increase The Results You Get &amp;amp; Help You Achieve Your Goals In Less Time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immunity Boosting Foods - Protect &amp; Boost Your Immune System</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/immunity-boosting-foods-protect-boost-your-immune-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 17:47:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/immunity-boosting-foods-protect-boost-your-immune-system/</guid>
      <description>Immunity Boosting Foods: In This Immunity Course You Will Learn Proven Strategies You Can Implement Right Away To Make Your Immune System Stronger And Body Healthier. This Immunity Training Makes Boosting Your Immune System Fast, Simple &amp;amp; Easy! Gain this HUGE Advantage In Life … One That Could Literally SAVE Your Life!
Here’s Why:Inside This Course You Will Learn The Secrets Of Boosting Your Immune System And Preventing Many Diseases. This Will Protect Your Health And Extend Your Life At The Same Time … All The While Felling Better Than Ever!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ketogenic Diet – Look &amp; Feel Amazing The Keto Diet Way!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ketogenic-diet-look-feel-amazing-the-keto-diet-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 17:47:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ketogenic-diet-look-feel-amazing-the-keto-diet-way/</guid>
      <description>Keto Diet: If you’ve been struggling to lose weight, even if you’ve been exercising regularly, this could be the ONLY solution for you.Here’s why:
No matter how frequently you exercise ... You will NOT lose weight if your body is NOT in a Fat-burning mode.
Sadly, most people start exercising with the expectation to lose weight fast.
Of course, exercising will help you to lose weight and be healthy, but it is NOT the fastest way to lose weight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegan Diet - Healthy Lifestyle (Practical Vegan Diet)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/vegan-diet-healthy-lifestyle-practical-vegan-diet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 17:47:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/vegan-diet-healthy-lifestyle-practical-vegan-diet/</guid>
      <description>In this online Vegan diet course you will learn how the pros use a vegan diet to get healthy and strong!
In 2009, only 1% of the US population was vegetarian or vegan.
In 2019 6% of Americans are vegan or vegetarian
And of all these vegans, the majority are women.
But that&#39;s not all... Because soon after that, men started following this lifestyle
At 2012, overall meat consumption decreased by 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Juicing – For Health &amp; Longevity</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/juicing-for-health-longevity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 13:37:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/juicing-for-health-longevity/</guid>
      <description>WHY JUICE?
Did you know that fruit juices are the cleansers of the human system … and vegetable juices are the builders that revitalize the body?
No one doubts that eating vegetables are good for you. But the problem with vegetables are ... They’re so boring! Nothing is more boring than chewing on a carrot for what seems like hours.
Plus, if you’re like me, then you know that vegetables like kale, ginger, and brussel sprouts are good for you, but you just can’t stand the taste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inflammation - The Hidden Source of Disease and Chronic Pain</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/inflammation-the-hidden-source-of-disease-and-chronic-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 06:56:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/inflammation-the-hidden-source-of-disease-and-chronic-pain/</guid>
      <description>It starts with well meaning doctors injecting you with toxic vaccinations, and good relatives using sweets-as-rewards. Followed by the food processors adding neurotoxins to your drink or food, and farmers growing hollow foods on depleted soils. Then grocers soaking their carrots in chlorinated water to keep them clean, and teachers sterilizing every surface with antibacterials, or soap makers adding &#34;fragrance&#34; to your detergent, and everybody else asking you to sit, take a ride, and avoid hard work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lemak dan Kesehatan</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lemak-dan-kesehatan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lemak-dan-kesehatan/</guid>
      <description>Lipida atau lemak sering kali mendapatkan konotasi yang buruk di masyarakat, membuat gemuk, menyebabkan penyakit dan sebagainya. Padahal lemak adalah zat gizi essensial yang penting bagi tubuh. Lemak terdapat pada banyak bahan makanan, meskipun terdapat variasi jumlah, jenis dan kualitasnya. Untuk mendapatkan kesehatan yang optimal kita perlu mengenal kebutuhan lemak, jenis lemak yang baik serta jumlah yang sesuai. Beberapa lemak diketahui memiliki manfaat kesehatan dan dapat melindungi dari penyakit tidak menular seperti penyakit jantung dan stroke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eating Healthy – Explode Your Physical &amp; Mental Health</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/eating-healthy-explode-your-physical-mental-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/eating-healthy-explode-your-physical-mental-health/</guid>
      <description>In this online healthy diet course you will learn discover the many benefits of simply making better diet choices. Doing this can transform your body &amp;amp; mind. Using these secrets can add many healthy years to your life, help you be more productive and prevent illnesses. Many find that existing conditions also improve or go way completely … Once they have a proper diet full of life giving nutrients.
This online course will give you hidden diet &amp;amp; nutrition secrets such as: 1) How healthy eating can be made simple &amp;amp; easy 2) How your pH level affects your health … and the foods to eat or avoid to fix this level 3) Learn about “good &amp;amp; “bad” fats 4) Discover how to cook simple healthy meals fast 5) Discover easy tricks to maintain your healthy eating &amp;amp; prevent “backsliding” 6) .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secrets To Burning Fat – How To Melt Fat Away!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-secrets-to-burning-fat-how-to-melt-fat-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-secrets-to-burning-fat-how-to-melt-fat-away/</guid>
      <description>In this online fat burning course you will learn how burn fat the way the top pros teach it. Consider this course to be your training pro guiding you to the most effective methods for fat burning &amp;amp; a healthy lifestyle. We are NOT giving medical advice … but this course contains tips, tools &amp;amp; strategies based on sound principles &amp;amp; scientific research.
This course will give you the hidden fat burning secrets of the following areas: 1) Healthy eating 2) The proper way to exercise and 3) The use of supplements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dieting - Nutrition -Weight Loss Tips for Good Healthy Life</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/dieting-nutrition-weight-loss-tips-for-good-healthy-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/dieting-nutrition-weight-loss-tips-for-good-healthy-life/</guid>
      <description>Dieting - Nutrition -Weight Loss Tips for Good Healthy LifeDieting for Weight Loss - Solid Nutrition - Fitness and a Healthy Life - Building a Diet that Works for You - Forever!
Are you tired of dieting and never seeing any long-term results?
Have you already tried the Atkins Diet, the South Beach Diet, the Paleo Diet, Milkshake Diet, the Twinkie Diet, and all the others and they didn’t work?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weight loss Certification Diploma: weight loss crash course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/weight-loss-certification-diploma-weight-loss-crash-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 10:00:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/weight-loss-certification-diploma-weight-loss-crash-course/</guid>
      <description>This course is designed for anyone who wants to lose fat, be healthy, and feel great.
My Weight Loss &amp;amp; Nutrition Course is not some random fad diet that tells you which foods you should and shouldn&#39;t eat. Instead, I will take you through each of the steps involved in setting up and following through with your diet.
Unfortunately, the internet is full of false health gurus that sell you all kinds of diet plans and supplements that are overpriced and don&#39;t work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nutrition Summary: 3 Weight Loss Methods for Becoming Slim</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/nutrition-summary-3-weight-loss-methods-for-becoming-slim/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 21:16:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/nutrition-summary-3-weight-loss-methods-for-becoming-slim/</guid>
      <description>If you ever imagined that one day you would change your life, behave different, feel different, like it isn’t you anymore – here’s your chance. I’m sure if you follow those 3 weight loss methods, you won’t feel the same anymore. You will feel better than ever and your body is going to thank you in advance.
Developing a healthy eating habit is hard, but it pays off way too much.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
