<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business Strategy on </title>
    <link>/tags/business-strategy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business Strategy on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/business-strategy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Corp Finance #10 Cost of Capital–Debt &amp; Equity Financing</title>
      <link>/corp-finance-#10-cost-of-capitaldebt-equity-financing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/corp-finance-#10-cost-of-capitaldebt-equity-financing/</guid>
      <description>This course will discusses weighted average cost of capital, debt, and equity financing from a corporate finance perspective.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Fundamentals &amp; Questions to Answer Before Launching</title>
      <link>/business-fundamentals-questions-to-answer-before-launching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/business-fundamentals-questions-to-answer-before-launching/</guid>
      <description>Business Fundamentals &amp;amp; 36 Questions to Answer Before LaunchingBusiness Fundamentals - Business Strategy - Fundamental Question You Must Ask and Answer to Succeed at Business
You can save yourself mass amounts of time and headaches by establishing your new business upon a solid foundation. This 1-hour beginners course teaches you the 36 questions that are essential for any new business leader to answer before beginning a new venture.
Your business fundamentals instructor, TJ Walker, is a serial entrepreneur who has worked closely with thousands of business leaders to help them create and build their businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/content-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/content-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Content marketing is currently one of the biggest trends in digital marketing as a whole and is an area that many website owners and brands are investing in heavily right now thanks to the impressive returns that they are seeing.
But content marketing is a complex and broad term that encompasses a number of different strategies and activities.
In order for it to be successful, you need to have a good understanding of what it is, how it works and how you can best adapt it to work for your particular brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management Consulting Essential Training</title>
      <link>/management-consulting-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/management-consulting-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>**Updated for 2021!**
Imagine you could learn the techniques taught by the world’s top consulting firms such as McKinsey and BCG without ever working at a firm! What if you could put yourself in a position to earn a six-figure salary, not to mention maximize the efficiency of any business interests you have, all from the comfort of your own home?
Management consulting involves identifying and suggesting important changes to what a company does and how they do it—developing a working strategic plan and guiding its execution with optimum effectiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management Consulting Skills Mastery</title>
      <link>/management-consulting-skills-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/management-consulting-skills-mastery/</guid>
      <description>**Updated for 2021!**
The most complete course available on management consultant. 8+hours of videos, activities, templates, case studies, articles and more.
Everything you need to know about management consulting tools and techniques from problem solving to presentation skills, from corporate strategic analysis to financial analysis.
Learn management consulting skills step-by-step. Real life consulting projects, business cases, and templates included. Learn by doing!
Management consulting involves identifying and suggesting important changes to what a company does and how they do it—developing a working strategic plan and guiding its execution with optimum effectiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing Strategies Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/pricing-strategies-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pricing-strategies-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Your price structure plays an important role in your ability to convert a prospect into a loyal customer, but assigning value to your offer goes well beyond that. Positioning your business so that it is geared towards a tight market is equally important.
Doing this will help you better tailor your offers so they meet market expectations, but it will make it easier for you to create a powerful marketing message that sets you apart from the competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systems Thinking: Enterprise Wide Change Fundamentals</title>
      <link>/systems-thinking-enterprise-wide-change-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/systems-thinking-enterprise-wide-change-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Systems Thinking: Enterprise Wide Change Fundamentals Course is a comprehensive video course where you can learn all about the fundamental knowledge about Systems Thinking that are essential in conducting changes in business.

I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on System Thinking as well as how to apply it in the business world. Learning Systems Thinking allows you to have solid understanding of how corporations work and allows you to effectively deploy enterprise wide changes in a strategic manner.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
