<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business Strategy on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/business-strategy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business Strategy on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/business-strategy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Smart Content Marketing Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/smart-content-marketing-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/smart-content-marketing-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>Even in the age of video, live streaming, and social media, content marketing is still the reigning King when it comes to building successful campaigns that will drive in traffic, and bolster sales and prospect activity. It’s also still the most effective way for both new and seasoned marketers to connect with potential leads, and to build organic traffic funnels from the major search engines.
Successful content marketing requires more effort and thought, and it requires a more complex strategy than ever before, but it’s certainly not difficult to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting 6 Businesses in 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/starting-6-businesses-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/starting-6-businesses-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>If you are a job holder and are stuck in working routine from 9 to 5 and enjoy over the weekend, than you will need to change your this mentality. This course will challenge your JOB MENTALITY and will teach you 6 businesses that you can run while doing a job. You do not need to invest more time if you know the tips and tricks taught in this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #2 Financial Ratios</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#2-financial-ratios/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#2-financial-ratios/</guid>
      <description>We will learn how to use ratio analysis to help with decision making from a corporate finance perspective. The financial statements, including the balance sheet and income statement, are the primary tools used for ratio analysis. The financial statements help us understand past performance and where the organization stands at this time. Ratio analysis helps us project future performance and where the organization may stand in the future. This course will demonstrate concepts using many practice problems, including problems using Microsoft Excel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Budgets – Managerial Accounting/Cost Accounting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-budgets-managerial-accounting/cost-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-budgets-managerial-accounting/cost-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Master budget construction, including demonstration problems, excel worksheets, practice test questions, discussion questions, and a comprehensive problem we work together using Excel in a step by step format.
The course will provide a managerial accounting overview, comparing managerial accounting and financial accounting, and providing essential managerial accounting tools we will need in the budgeting process.
We will discuss methods of budget timing and the pros and cons of each technique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Thinking Guide for Successful Professionals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/design-thinking-guide-for-successful-professionals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/design-thinking-guide-for-successful-professionals/</guid>
      <description>**Course Updated - June 2022**
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; COURSE REGULARLY UPDATED: NEW TIPS, MORE LESSONS &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; CERTIFIED COACH, SPEAKER AND TRAINER &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; OVER 180,000 STUDENTS IN TOTAL &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
Design thinking is the most understudied concept as it has actually been around for a very long time but it is never really been explored to its huge potential for the betterment of the business or organization. Organizations like Apple and Google use the concept of design thinking in their day-to-day customer interface and thus have been able to design full-proof products which only have one outcome “Success”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ESG Reporting for Businesses</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/esg-reporting-for-businesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/esg-reporting-for-businesses/</guid>
      <description>The course will extend from the fundamental of Corporate ESG and elaborate on 6 aspects related to ESG in greater depth, including
Global Landscape;
Standards &amp;amp; Frameworks;
The reasons and benefits of ESG reporting ;
Contents and Elements of good ESG Reports;
The current challenges in ESG reporting;
Trends going forward.
After completing the first section, you should be able to understand the differences and similarities between different frameworks and standards, the compatibility of frameworks, selecting the ones that are most suitable for your business based on geographical location, corporate vision and strategy, your product, the main audience of your ESG report and the aspect of ESG that is most important to your business, and finally understand how to apply the frameworks as a starting point of writing ESG report for corporations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Outreach Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/facebook-outreach-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/facebook-outreach-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>The biggest problem with Facebook in recent years is that their organic reach—the people you can reach without spending money—has declined to nearly zero.
Most people are fans of dozens, if not hundreds of pages on Facebook. If all those pages shared several articles per day, most of the posts would just get lost, anyway. There’s just too much content being posted.
So, Facebook has implemented some changes that make it so that only a small fraction of a page’s users ever see each post.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Psychology, Emotional Intelligence, Neuromarketing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/marketing-psychology-emotional-intelligence-neuromarketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/marketing-psychology-emotional-intelligence-neuromarketing/</guid>
      <description>Lean marketing psychology, get in the head of your customers, stop guessing, and create marketing materials that inspire desire to buy from you.
In this course, you&#39;ll learn:
Marketing psychology in negotiation.
Marketing psychology in converting a potential customer into a completed sale.
Common logical fallacies people fall into during the marketing and buying process.
Emotional Intelligence involved in marketing and negotiation.
Pricing psychology.
IF YOU PROMOTE AND SELL, DO IT WITH DEEP CUSTOMER UNDERSTANDING</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcasting Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/podcasting-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/podcasting-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>Podcasts are an incredible way to reach both current and new prospects, no matter what type of business you’re running, or what niche market you are positioned in.
Podcasting is also a great way to stand out, and set yourself apart from the competition. Lots of people have blogs and YouTube channels and social media profiles, but not nearly as many people have a podcast!
Podcasts are a great way to stay in touch with your audience, while also expanding it quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Postgraduate Diploma: Digitalization of Retail Banking</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/postgraduate-diploma-digitalization-of-retail-banking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/postgraduate-diploma-digitalization-of-retail-banking/</guid>
      <description>Postgraduate Diploma: Digitalization of Retail Banking: Business cases and assessment of investment profitability
Our course will be interesting for anybody who work or wish to work at areas: banking, fintech, IT, digital technologies.
We will go through introduction to topic of digitalisation and usage of digital tools at Retail Banking.
Next we will consider practical examples from business of worldwide banking group. You will see cases from Consumer Lending, Mortgage, and online and general retail banking business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corp Finance #10 Cost of Capital–Debt &amp; Equity Financing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corp-finance-#10-cost-of-capitaldebt-equity-financing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corp-finance-#10-cost-of-capitaldebt-equity-financing/</guid>
      <description>This course will discusses weighted average cost of capital, debt, and equity financing from a corporate finance perspective.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #13 Investment Banking &amp; Long-Term Debt</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#13-investment-banking-long-term-debt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#13-investment-banking-long-term-debt/</guid>
      <description>This course will discuss capital markets, investment banking, &amp;amp; long-term debt and lease financing.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.
Types of security markets include money markets and capital markets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>31 Startup Business Model: Best Course for Entrepreneurs</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/31-startup-business-model-best-course-for-entrepreneurs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/31-startup-business-model-best-course-for-entrepreneurs/</guid>
      <description>31 Types of Startup business model course is specially designed by analyzing more than 500 Startup unicorns and big tech companies worldwide.
This course is helpful for Entrepreneurs, Product Managers, Growth hackers, and Management students to build a business model framework for their business growth. We will be starting our journey with a basic definition and business model canvas and then switching gears to some advanced topics like network effect, hook and bait kind of business model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management Consulting Essential Training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/management-consulting-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/management-consulting-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>**Updated for 2022!**
Imagine you could learn the techniques taught by the world’s top consulting firms such as McKinsey and BCG without ever working at a firm! What if you could put yourself in a position to earn a six-figure salary, not to mention maximize the efficiency of any business interests you have, all from the comfort of your own home?
Management consulting involves identifying and suggesting important changes to what a company does and how they do it—developing a working strategic plan and guiding its execution with optimum effectiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MBA: Retail management, Merchandising, and E-commerce</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mba-retail-management-merchandising-and-e-commerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 20:12:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mba-retail-management-merchandising-and-e-commerce/</guid>
      <description>If you have been to a retail store do why you end up buying more than you actually need?
That&#39;s because they provide you an amazing shopping experience by using some business strategy. This course will help you understand the strategy you can follow if you are planning to start your own retail business or e-commerce brand in the future. Section 1 Introduction to Retail Management Basics
What is Retail Management</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Fundamentals &amp; Questions to Answer Before Launching</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/business-fundamentals-questions-to-answer-before-launching/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/business-fundamentals-questions-to-answer-before-launching/</guid>
      <description>Business Fundamentals &amp;amp; 36 Questions to Answer Before LaunchingBusiness Fundamentals - Business Strategy - Fundamental Question You Must Ask and Answer to Succeed at Business
You can save yourself mass amounts of time and headaches by establishing your new business upon a solid foundation. This 1-hour beginners course teaches you the 36 questions that are essential for any new business leader to answer before beginning a new venture.
Your business fundamentals instructor, TJ Walker, is a serial entrepreneur who has worked closely with thousands of business leaders to help them create and build their businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sustainability: Impact, Value (s), Innovation, and Growth</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sustainability-impact-value-s-innovation-and-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:57:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sustainability-impact-value-s-innovation-and-growth/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to use Sustainability strategies to improve your company values and supply chain resilience, differentiate from your competitors?
Do you want to embed Sustainability principles in your innovation campaigns to maximise their impact and grow your company?
If so, then this comprehensive Sustainability course is for you. This detailed Sustainability course covers all the fundamental topics you need to understand what Sustainability is about: for People; Planet, and Prosperity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management Consulting Skills Mastery</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/management-consulting-skills-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 19:27:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/management-consulting-skills-mastery/</guid>
      <description>**Updated for 2022!**
The most complete course available on management consultant. 8+hours of videos, activities, templates, case studies, articles and more.
Everything you need to know about management consulting tools and techniques from problem solving to presentation skills, from corporate strategic analysis to financial analysis.
Learn management consulting skills step-by-step. Real life consulting projects, business cases, and templates included. Learn by doing!
Management consulting involves identifying and suggesting important changes to what a company does and how they do it—developing a working strategic plan and guiding its execution with optimum effectiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best of Google SEO 2022: SEO &amp; Copywriting Made Simple &amp; Fun</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/best-of-google-seo-2022-seo-copywriting-made-simple-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:16:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/best-of-google-seo-2022-seo-copywriting-made-simple-fun/</guid>
      <description>2022’s Easy to Learn SEO &amp;amp; Copywriting Course made Fun!
This SEO course is filled with quizzes, animated videos, assignments, screen recordings, and over my shoulder explanations!!! Watch as I walk you through everything you will need to know to become a SEO, and copywriting pro in 2022! Max SEO traffic &amp;amp; sales, boost search ranking, or land your dream marketing job!!!
Learn Google SEO Fast &amp;amp; Fun!
Animations with Quizzes &amp;amp; Practical Assignments - I’ve made learning fun and organic - with animated explainers and 300+ Questions so you learn quickly and retain what you learn!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing Strategies Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pricing-strategies-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:16:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pricing-strategies-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>Your price structure plays an important role in your ability to convert a prospect into a loyal customer, but assigning value to your offer goes well beyond that. Positioning your business so that it is geared towards a tight market is equally important.
Doing this will help you better tailor your offers so they meet market expectations, but it will make it easier for you to create a powerful marketing message that sets you apart from the competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management Consulting Guide 2022: McKinsey, BCG or PwC!? :-)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/management-consulting-guide-2022-mckinsey-bcg-or-pwc-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/management-consulting-guide-2022-mckinsey-bcg-or-pwc-/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to YOUnConsulting!
1. Whom is this course for?
This course is a must-watch course for YOU if you are
An undergraduate or postgraduate student who wants to explore or firmly pursues a management consulting career as your primary career option
A young professional (i.e., with some initial work experience) who considers switching to a management consulting career
A knowledge multiplier or intermediary who serves or frequently deals with consultants for professional reasons and benefits from gaining a deeper understanding of a consultant’s life and challenges</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outsourcing Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/outsourcing-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/outsourcing-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>Outsourcing is the smart way of doing business, building an established presence in your industry quickly and developing a life-long brand that stands out and apart in your niche.
Connecting to seasoned professionals gives you the leg up, allowing you to compete, head on, with some of the biggest names in your niche.
The Outsourcing Course For EVERY Level
This course is your fast track to outsourcing success and will provide long-lasting value from your very first job description posted right through to advanced hiring and productivity campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micro MBA Course: Sales and Management Strategy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/micro-mba-course-sales-and-management-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 21:27:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/micro-mba-course-sales-and-management-strategy/</guid>
      <description>Many college students and young professionals ask if attending a top graduate business school can prepare them for a successful career.
An MBA is a common stepping stone to C-suite positions in large businesses, as well as a valuable asset for aspiring entrepreneurs. It&#39;s a certificate that many Fortune 500 leaders have, like Walmart president and CEO Doug McMillon, who obtained his MBA from the University of Tulsa in Oklahoma, and Facebook COO Sheryl Sandberg, who graduated from Harvard Business School in Massachusetts with an MBA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electrical Power Grid Modernization: Smart Grid Concepts</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/electrical-power-grid-modernization-smart-grid-concepts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:37:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/electrical-power-grid-modernization-smart-grid-concepts/</guid>
      <description>Electrical Power Grid Modernization: Smart Grid Concepts is a comprehensive video course where you can learn all about the concept of the smart grid that are essential in working in the industry.
I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on grid modernization as well as how to apply it in the utility industry.
If you are currently a professional who are interested working in the grid innovation industry, you will find this course of great help to get the fundamental knowledge you need to kick start your professional career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Plan: Learn It Fast! - Business Planning &amp; Writing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/business-plan-learn-it-fast-business-planning-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 16:23:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/business-plan-learn-it-fast-business-planning-writing/</guid>
      <description>Updated: January 2022
Business Plan - Quick Start If you are looking for a quick jumpstart into writing a comprehensive Business Plan then this course will help you achieve that goal. You can learn how to create a business plan in just one hour!
++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++ Let me explain
What makes this course different is that it summarizes all the important element that is necessary to write a great business plan and delivers it to you in a short; 1-hour training program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cat Sitting Pet Care Home Business</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cat-sitting-pet-care-home-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cat-sitting-pet-care-home-business/</guid>
      <description>Cats are so much fun to work with and within this mini-course, I will show you how you can turn a love of cats into a home-based cat sitting pet care business. I will show you how looking after cats in the pet care industry is not only much easier but looking after cats is much less hassle than walking dogs.
Spending your days cuddling fluff balls can be your dream job, with a little effort and a love of all things cats, I can guide you to run your very own cat care business, either full time or as a side hustle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Plan Success ( Including Template )</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/business-plan-success-including-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/business-plan-success-including-template/</guid>
      <description>A solid business plan will let you know where you are going and what to expect. You’re 16 to 20% more likely to create a viable business using a business plan than without one. So how do you put together a solid business plan? This course is a full step-by-step guite to writing an effective business plan that will provide everything you need to succeed in your new business venture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consulting Business Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/consulting-business-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:47:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/consulting-business-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’re looking to make some fast cash, or you’re interested in building a long-term sustainable business, consulting is one of the most lucrative opportunities available online.
The dictionary defines consultant as: “a person who provides expert advice professionally.”
As a consultant or coach, you’ll be responsible for guiding your students or clients through a learning curve until they’ve accomplished a specific goal.
This is one of those rare businesses where you don’t need a lot of clients to make a full-time income.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instant Affiliate Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/instant-affiliate-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/instant-affiliate-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>You’re probably fed on top of the instructions that inform you ways to create immediate earnings on the internet, only to be sent to absurd survey internet sites that pay out pennies hourly.
Thankfully, there really are genuine ways to generate income online that don’t consider time and effort, and often, quite hardly any upfront investment. And that’s what this unique statement is all about.
It’s centered on just one quick income opportunity and you may discover fast and easy way to make money on the internet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/content-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/content-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Content marketing is currently one of the biggest trends in digital marketing as a whole and is an area that many website owners and brands are investing in heavily right now thanks to the impressive returns that they are seeing.
But content marketing is a complex and broad term that encompasses a number of different strategies and activities.
In order for it to be successful, you need to have a good understanding of what it is, how it works and how you can best adapt it to work for your particular brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systems Thinking: Enterprise Wide Change Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/systems-thinking-enterprise-wide-change-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/systems-thinking-enterprise-wide-change-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Systems Thinking: Enterprise Wide Change Fundamentals Course is a comprehensive video course where you can learn all about the fundamental knowledge about Systems Thinking that are essential in conducting changes in business.
I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on System Thinking as well as how to apply it in the business world. Learning Systems Thinking allows you to have solid understanding of how corporations work and allows you to effectively deploy enterprise wide changes in a strategic manner.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
