<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Architectural Design on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/architectural-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Architectural Design on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/architectural-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lumion : Landscape Design &amp; Photorealistic Rendering</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lumion-landscape-design-photorealistic-rendering/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lumion-landscape-design-photorealistic-rendering/</guid>
      <description>This class is designed to teach you concepts from creating to rendering of landscape scene in Lumion.
In this class we will be producing a aesthetic landscape model on SketchUp and render it into images and video clips. I will tech you how to design model and turn it into realistic visuals through images and videos from Lumion. Landscape architecture is about creating great cities, streets, parks and public spaces – ones that inspire healthy living and wellbeing while protecting natural environments and people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto en Diseño de Escenografías Teatrales</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/experto-en-dise%C3%B1o-de-escenografi%CC%81as-teatrales/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/experto-en-dise%C3%B1o-de-escenografi%CC%81as-teatrales/</guid>
      <description>Experto en Diseño de Escenografías Teatrales
Aprende de forma integral el proceso de diseño y ejecución de espacios escenográficos en teatros
Instructores: Arquitecto Álvaro García y Arquitecta Lucía Fernández Actualizado: Mayo de 2022 Estudiantes: +3.000
Descripción del Curso:
La escenografía es el arte de realizar decoraciones escénicas. El término, que tiene su origen en un vocablo griego, también permite nombrar al conjunto de los decorados que se utilizan en una representación escénica.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SketchUp Architectural Design Essentials Kit</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sketchup-architectural-design-essentials-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sketchup-architectural-design-essentials-kit/</guid>
      <description>Learn Architectural Design In SketchUp with the SketchUp Architectural Design Essentials Kit Course.
SketchUp Models are easy to start modeling on a basic idea, but getting your models into a clear Architectural language takes a bit more than adding a few lines and forms.
In this course, we will develop an existing building model into an Architecturally detailed one. We will walk through what is needed in the site, in the windows, doors, facades, roof and other elements so that the model will read as Architecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOLAR COURSE for Beginners of Solar Energy-</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/solar-course-for-beginners-of-solar-energy-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:57:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/solar-course-for-beginners-of-solar-energy-/</guid>
      <description>Hello, Dear Solar Enthusiast!
I welcome you to this Solar Energy course, designed with the goal to share the learning for the beginners of Solar Energy. Let me share with you that I have tried to develop this course keeping in mind that a beginner could learn the technicality of the Solar field in a simpler and easier manner. I have tried to all the aspects of the Solar plants which include Technicals, Financial calculations, Financial modelling, Net Metering, Different types of Installations, Monitoring etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diseño de Cabañas</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/dise%C3%B1o-de-caba%C3%B1as/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:57:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/dise%C3%B1o-de-caba%C3%B1as/</guid>
      <description>Diseño de Cabañas
Aprende de forma integral el proceso de diseño y ejecución de cabañas. Instructores: Arquitecto Álvaro García y Arquitecta Lucía Fernández Actualizado: Mayo de 2022 Estudiantes: +3.000 Descripción del Curso:
La formación te permitirá convertirte en un experto en la materia, y todo ello desde una formación principalmente práctica. A través de variadas actividades y proyectos completos podrás adquirir los conocimientos suficientes para ejercer profesionalmente de forma solvente. Además conocerás en detalle mi flujo de trabajo a la hora de afrontar un proyecto profesional.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Architectural Shop Drawing Plans in AutoCAD 2020</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/architectural-shop-drawing-plans-in-autocad-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/architectural-shop-drawing-plans-in-autocad-2020/</guid>
      <description>Part 1: Learn the basics commands in AutoCAD to be ready to the shop drawing practice ( How to draw lines, How to draw polyline, Copy, Move, Mirror, Offset, Fillet, Trim, Rotate, How to draw X-line, How to draw circle, How to draw Hatch in AutoCAD, How to do match properties in AutoCAD, How to print a sheet in AutoCAD.
Part 2: Architectural Shop Drawing in AutoCAD 2020
Do you need more practice with AutoCAD?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SketchUp and V-Ray Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sketchup-and-v-ray-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:16:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sketchup-and-v-ray-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Hello, this is your instructor Shivam. If you are here, you probably know what SketchUp and V-Ray is. SketchUp is widely used application in myriad vocations, be it Architecture or product designing. In this course, we are gonna learn SketchUp from scratch to advance level. The course follows advance methods of teaching and additionally there is example to learn steps in modeling an actual building as well as adding V-ray material, lights, scene management and much more in depth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>الاظهار المعماري للمسقط الافقي بالخامات المختلفة للمبتدئين</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%B8%D9%87%D8%A7%D8%B1-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D8%B9%D9%85%D8%A7%D8%B1%D9%8A-%D9%84%D9%84%D9%85%D8%B3%D9%82%D8%B7-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%81%D9%82%D9%8A-%D8%A8%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AE%D8%A7%D9%85%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D8%AE%D8%AA%D9%84%D9%81%D8%A9-%D9%84%D9%84%D9%85%D8%A8%D8%AA%D8%AF%D8%A6%D9%8A%D9%86/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 19:14:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%B8%D9%87%D8%A7%D8%B1-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D8%B9%D9%85%D8%A7%D8%B1%D9%8A-%D9%84%D9%84%D9%85%D8%B3%D9%82%D8%B7-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%81%D9%82%D9%8A-%D8%A8%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AE%D8%A7%D9%85%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D8%AE%D8%AA%D9%84%D9%81%D8%A9-%D9%84%D9%84%D9%85%D8%A8%D8%AA%D8%AF%D8%A6%D9%8A%D9%86/</guid>
      <description>أهلا بكم في الكورس التعليمي &#34;الاظهار المعماري للمسقط الافقي بالخامات المختلفة للمبتدئين&#34;. كان هدفي بهذا الكورس الاحساس بالمتعة من خلال التعامل مع الاظهار لمجموعة من المساقط الافقية الصغيرة المساحة لكي تكون مناسبة للمبتدئين لتعلم اساسيات ومبادئ الاظهار المعماري اليدوي بالخامات المختلفة مثل أقلام الرصاص / الالوان الخشب / الوان الماركر من المستوي صفر لاظهار امكانيات كل خامة من الالوان وقدرتها على التعبير بجرأة في الاظهار المعماري, وذلك بناء علي تكنيك مبسط وسهل في استعمال كل خخامة الاقلام الرصاص بمختلف درجاتها.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Las Patologías en Edificios y Construcción Arquitectónica</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/las-patolog%C3%ADas-en-edificios-y-construcci%C3%B3n-arquitect%C3%B3nica/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/las-patolog%C3%ADas-en-edificios-y-construcci%C3%B3n-arquitect%C3%B3nica/</guid>
      <description>Las Patologías en los Edificios
Introducción a la interpretación de las posibles causas de patologías en edificación. Instructores: Arquitecto Álvaro García y Arquitecto Técnico Jaime López. Contenido Actualizado: Octubre 2021 Calificación: ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐
Descripción del Curso:
Los edificios tienen una vulnerabilidad propia que resulta más o menos importante, pero inevitable. Las deficiencias inherentes a las técnicas y los materiales utilizados en su ejecución, por un lado, y el uso funcional de los mismos a lo largo de su vida útil, por otro, hace que vayan sufriendo un implacable deterioro que obliga a alguna intervención en un momento determinado de su vida, a pesar, incluso, de un adecuado mantenimiento.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VRay SketchUp. De Básico a Profesional Experto (ChaosGroup)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/vray-sketchup.-de-b%C3%A1sico-a-profesional-experto-chaosgroup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/vray-sketchup.-de-b%C3%A1sico-a-profesional-experto-chaosgroup/</guid>
      <description>VRay 2.0 para SketchUp. De Básico a Profesional Experto
Renderiza tus modelos de SketchUp y consigue imágenes hiperrealistas que muestren tus proyectos de forma más atractiva.
Instructor: Arquitecto Álvaro García. Contenido Actualizado: Octubre 2021 Calificación: ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐
···························································································································································
Nota: Si tienes una versión de VRay superior o igual a la 3.4 accede a mi curso &#34;SketchUp 2020 + VRay Next. Aprende con Proyectos 3D Reales&#34;
···························································································································································
Descripción del Curso:
En este curso te enseño a dominar V-Ray para SketchUp, una de las herramientas líderes en el renderizado por su rapidez y realismo, con un rico y completo set de funciones y características.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
