<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Google on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/google/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Google on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/google/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Google Sheets: Empieza desde cero</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/google-sheets-empieza-desde-cero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/google-sheets-empieza-desde-cero/</guid>
      <description>¿Por qué aprender Google Sheets?
La forma en que usamos las hojas de cálculo está cambiando. La mayor parte de nuestro trabajo y colaboración se realiza a través de canales en línea, nuestras hojas de cálculo también se están moviendo en línea. Google Sheets es un programa de hojas de cálculo en línea que ofrece soluciones que muchas empresas necesitan en este momento.
En el pasado, el principal requisito que tenían las empresas era que los profesionales tuvieran sólidos conocimientos en Microsoft Excel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Google Slides from Scratch</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-google-slides-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-google-slides-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>Google Slide is a free web-based tool offered by Google. It is an alternative to Microsoft Powerpoint. Although, it is not so powerful as Microsoft Powerpoint and it has most of the similar features that Powerpoint has and it is completely free.

This is a complete Google Slides Course where you will learn -
Design Great looking professional presentations in Google Slides
Create a customized template or theme for work or clients</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Calendar :  Virtual Assistant</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/google-calendar-virtual-assistant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 10:00:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/google-calendar-virtual-assistant/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Google Calendar: and help you if you are a virtual assistant I&#39;ll be your calendar coach! Learn everything you need to know about Google Calendar with this complete guide!

Managing your own appointments and calendars can be daunting and stressful if you are working as a virtual assistant. ! With Google Calendar and this course, you will learn how to use all the features available to provide very powerful calendar management services</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Data Studio A-Z for Data Visualization and Dashboards</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/google-data-studio-a-z-for-data-visualization-and-dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/google-data-studio-a-z-for-data-visualization-and-dashboards/</guid>
      <description>6 Reasons why you should choose this Google Data Studio course
Carefully designed course, teaching you not only how to draw all types of charts in Google Data Studio, but also advanced Data studio specific features
Concise - you can complete this Google Data Studio course within one weekend
Business-related examples and case studies
Ample practice exercises because Data Visualization and Google Data Studio require practice
Downloadable resources for learning Google Data Studio and Data Visualization</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Workspace (G Suite) Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/google-workspace-g-suite-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 11:41:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/google-workspace-g-suite-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Google Workspace but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to manager accounts and bring your ideas to life?
Then Google Workspace 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Google Workspace is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start adding accounts like an expert with Google Workspace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Docs Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/google-docs-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/google-docs-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Google Docs but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Docs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Google Docs 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Google Docs is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building Docs like an expert with Google Docs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail Productivity Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/gmail-productivity-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/gmail-productivity-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Gmail but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Email and bring your ideas to life?
Then Gmail 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Gmail is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building Emails like an expert with Gmail.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
