<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Google on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/google/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Google on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/google/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Google Looker Masterclass: Looker &amp; LookML A-Z 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-looker-masterclass-looker-lookml-a-z-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-looker-masterclass-looker-lookml-a-z-2022/</guid>
      <description>5 Reasons why you should choose this Google Looker course
Carefully designed course, teaching you not only frontend of Looker but also the LookML part
Concise - you can complete this Google Looker course within one weekend
Business-related examples and case studies
Downloadable resources for learning Google Looker
Your queries will be responded by the Instructor himself
Start using Google Looker to its full potential to become proficient at Google Looker and LookML today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Spreadsheets: Empieza desde cero</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-spreadsheets-empieza-desde-cero/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-spreadsheets-empieza-desde-cero/</guid>
      <description>¿Por qué aprender Google Sheets?
La forma en que usamos las hojas de cálculo está cambiando. La mayor parte de nuestro trabajo y colaboración se realiza a través de canales en línea, nuestras hojas de cálculo también se están moviendo en línea. Google Sheets es un programa de hojas de cálculo en línea que ofrece soluciones que muchas empresas necesitan en este momento.
En el pasado, el principal requisito que tenían las empresas era que los profesionales tuvieran sólidos conocimientos en Microsoft Excel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Google Sheets In 1 Day With Fascinating Projects</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-google-sheets-in-1-day-with-fascinating-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-google-sheets-in-1-day-with-fascinating-projects/</guid>
      <description>Learn Google Sheets in a fascinating way by doing real-world, highly-applicable projects.
As I walk you through every important feature of Google Sheets, I&#39;ll be showing you real-world examples of situations where you can use your new Google Sheets skills. This way the course will stay interesting and move along more quickly.
Our first example will be for how to manage your SEO marketing by tracking progress in a spreadsheet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Drive Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-drive-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-drive-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Google Drive but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Docs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Google Drive 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Google Drive is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building Docs like an expert with Google Drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Forms Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-forms-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-forms-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>SO, YOU’RE LOOKING FOR A COURSE THAT WILL TEACH YOU GOOGLE FORMS QUICKLY &amp;amp; IN A FUN MANNER?
I’ve got just the course for you!
Welcome, my name is Josh Werner with Learn Tech Plus and I’ve put this course together to help people just like you quickly master Google Forms...Whether you’re a beginner or experienced with Google Forms!
If your goal is to become a master of Google Forms, then this course is perfect for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Docs Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-docs-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-docs-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Google Docs but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Docs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Google Docs 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Google Docs is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building Docs like an expert with Google Docs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Workspace (G Suite) Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-workspace-g-suite-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-workspace-g-suite-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Google Workspace but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to manager accounts and bring your ideas to life?
Then Google Workspace 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Google Workspace is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start adding accounts like an expert with Google Workspace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail Productivity Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gmail-productivity-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gmail-productivity-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Gmail but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Email and bring your ideas to life?
Then Gmail 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Gmail is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building Emails like an expert with Gmail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Data Studio Complete Beginners to Advanced Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-data-studio-complete-beginners-to-advanced-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:57:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-data-studio-complete-beginners-to-advanced-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>This Google Data Studio course will help you to become a Data Visualization Expert and will enhance your skills by offering you comprehensive knowledge, and the required hands-on experience on this widely used Cloud based BI tool, by solving real-time industry-based projects.
Top Reasons why you should learn Google Data Studio : Google data Studio is the #1 cloud based Free Business Intelligence tool used industry wide.
The demand for BI professionals is on the rise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Google Drive Course - Mastering Google Drive</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-google-drive-course-mastering-google-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-google-drive-course-mastering-google-drive/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to The Complete Google Drive Course. This course will teach you to understand how to use and become familiar with the storage and productivity component of Google Suite: Google Drive and Google Apps.
Google Drive is a safe and secure online file storage service that allows for easy collaboration and sharing. It is compatible with all types of files, ranging from PDFs to images to videos. Unlike its competitors, Google Drive offers up to 15 GB of free storage and a variety of online tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Workspace: Docs, Sheets, Slides  من الصفر للاحتراف</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-workspace-docs-sheets-slides-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B5%D9%81%D8%B1-%D9%84%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 22:09:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-workspace-docs-sheets-slides-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B5%D9%81%D8%B1-%D9%84%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81/</guid>
      <description>Google Office ابدأ تعلم جوجل اوفيس (مستندات جوجل , جوجل سلايدز , جوجل شيت) من البرامج القوية التي تستخدم كبديل قوي لبرامج ميكروسوفت اوفيس(الوورد , البوربوينت
, الاكسل) التي نحتاجها تقريبًا في كل شىء معظم الوقت
ما يميز حزمة برامج جوجل اوفيس او جوجل ورك سبيس انها مجانية تماما وايضًا اونلاين لا تحتاج لتنزيل اي شىء على جهازك غير انها مرتبطة بجوجل درايف وتقوم بحفظ كل شىء تلقائيًا في هذا الكورس سوف نتعلم اهم برامج جوجل اوفيس ; مستندات جوجل , جوجل شيت , وجوجل سلايدز Google Docs - اولًا مستندات جوجل</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Gmail Productivity Course -  More Productive Email</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-gmail-productivity-course-more-productive-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:15:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-gmail-productivity-course-more-productive-email/</guid>
      <description>Complete Gmail Productivity Course - More Productive Email: Boost Productivity - Master Gmail Tips, Tricks, and Techniques - Learn Email Strategies To Make Your Time More Effective
Secure, smart, and easy to use email: Get more done with Gmail. Now integrated with Google Chat, Google Meet, and more, all in one place. Email that&#39;s secure, private, and puts you in control. We never use your Gmail content for any ads purposes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Google Sheets Course - Google Spreadsheet Tips</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-google-sheets-course-google-spreadsheet-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:15:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-google-sheets-course-google-spreadsheet-tips/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Google Sheets Course - Google Spreadsheet Tips: Learn Google Sheets from Beginner to Advanced - Learn Pivot Tables - Graphs -Dashboards - More!
Google Sheets is a spreadsheet program included as part of the free, web-based Google Docs Editors suite offered by Google. The service also includes Google Docs, Google Slides, Google Drawings, Google Forms, Google Sites, and Google Keep. Wikipedia
We can do much cool stuff in Google Sheets, Collaborate on data, from anywhere Establish a ground truth for data in your online spreadsheet, with easy sharing and real-time editing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Slides - جوجل سلايدز من الصفر للاحتراف</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-slides-%D8%AC%D9%88%D8%AC%D9%84-%D8%B3%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%8A%D8%AF%D8%B2-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B5%D9%81%D8%B1-%D9%84%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-slides-%D8%AC%D9%88%D8%AC%D9%84-%D8%B3%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%8A%D8%AF%D8%B2-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B5%D9%81%D8%B1-%D9%84%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81/</guid>
      <description>مهارة تصميم البريزنتيشن من أهم المهارات المطلوبة
شرائح جوجل او جوجل سلايدز من افضل البرامج التي تقوم بهذه المهمة فهو من افضل بدائل البوربوينت ما يميز جوجل سلايدز انه مجاني تماما وايضًا اونلاين لا تحتاج لتنزيل اي شىء على جهازك غير انه مرتبط بجوجل درايف ويقوم بحفظ كل شىء تلقائيًا
ستتعلم فى هذا الكورس جميع اوامر جوجل سلايدز مع تطبيقات عملية وطريقة تصميم عرض تقديمي احترافى
ثم سنقوم بتجميع كل ما تعلمناه لتصميم مشروع عملى في نهاية الكورس</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail - Grundkurs für jeden Einsteiger!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gmail-grundkurs-f%C3%BCr-jeden-einsteiger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 21:29:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gmail-grundkurs-f%C3%BCr-jeden-einsteiger/</guid>
      <description>In diesem Kurs lernst Du, Gmail effektiv zu nutzen, so dass auch Du produktiver wirst und eine Ordnung in Dein Postfach bekommst.
Gmail ist mittlerweile eines der meistverwendeten E-Mail Programme der Welt und dennoch wenden die meisten nur grundsätzliche Funktionen an.
In diesem Kurs lernst Du alle wichtigen und grundlegenden Funktionen kennen, damit auch Du mit Gmail richtig durchstarten kannst, ohne dabei wichtige Zeit zu verlieren.
Wenn Du heute noch anfängst, Gmail mit samt seinen Funktionen zu nutzen, wirst Du schnell Routine bekommen und Du wirst einen super Überblick in Deinem Postfach erhalten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improve Your Business Productivity with Google Suite Apps</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/improve-your-business-productivity-with-google-suite-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:37:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/improve-your-business-productivity-with-google-suite-apps/</guid>
      <description>Greetings, Friend
Google Apps is a robust set of productivity tools. Learn how to use Google Apps and tap into its full potential at business , college or school.
Those who do not utilize cloud computing today will undoubtedly pay for it later. You have a lot of overhead to deal with as a business. There&#39;s always something to pay attention to. Every day, you only have a limited amount of time to dedicate to everything that&#39;s happening on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Calendar :  Virtual Assistant</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-calendar-virtual-assistant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-calendar-virtual-assistant/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Google Calendar: and help you if you are a virtual assistant I&#39;ll be your calendar coach! Learn everything you need to know about Google Calendar with this complete guide!
Managing your own appointments and calendars can be daunting and stressful if you are working as a virtual assistant. ! With Google Calendar and this course, you will learn how to use all the features available to provide very powerful calendar management services</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Google Slides from Scratch</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-google-slides-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-google-slides-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>Google Slide is a free web-based tool offered by Google. It is an alternative to Microsoft Powerpoint. Although, it is not so powerful as Microsoft Powerpoint and it has most of the similar features that Powerpoint has and it is completely free.
This is a complete Google Slides Course where you will learn -
Design Great looking professional presentations in Google Slides
Create a customized template or theme for work or clients</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Data Studio A-Z for Data Visualization and Dashboards</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-data-studio-a-z-for-data-visualization-and-dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-data-studio-a-z-for-data-visualization-and-dashboards/</guid>
      <description>6 Reasons why you should choose this Google Data Studio course
Carefully designed course, teaching you not only how to draw all types of charts in Google Data Studio, but also advanced Data studio specific features
Concise - you can complete this Google Data Studio course within one weekend
Business-related examples and case studies
Ample practice exercises because Data Visualization and Google Data Studio require practice
Downloadable resources for learning Google Data Studio and Data Visualization</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
