<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Google on </title>
    <link>/tags/google/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Google on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:17 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/google/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gmail Productivity Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>/gmail-productivity-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gmail-productivity-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Gmail but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Email and bring your ideas to life?
Then Gmail 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Gmail is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building Emails like an expert with Gmail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Workspace (G Suite) Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>/google-workspace-g-suite-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/google-workspace-g-suite-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Google Workspace but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to manager accounts and bring your ideas to life?
Then Google Workspace 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Google Workspace is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start adding accounts like an expert with Google Workspace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Calendar :  Virtual Assistant</title>
      <link>/google-calendar-virtual-assistant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/google-calendar-virtual-assistant/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Google Calendar: and help you if you are a virtual assistant I&#39;ll be your calendar coach! Learn everything you need to know about Google Calendar with this complete guide!

Managing your own appointments and calendars can be daunting and stressful if you are working as a virtual assistant. ! With Google Calendar and this course, you will learn how to use all the features available to provide very powerful calendar management services</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
