<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Self Esteem &amp; Confidence on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/self-esteem-confidence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Self Esteem &amp; Confidence on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/self-esteem-confidence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Success Mindset Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/success-mindset-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/success-mindset-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Most of people spent quite a bit of time thinking about what constitutes success, how they will achieve it, and how good they&#39;ll feel when they achieve their goals.
In this course you will learn 5 key steps that will help you reach your goals and accomplish what you’ve set out to do.
Learn how to nurture a mindset of success to become an unstoppable entrepreneur.

Success Mindset  Course For EVERY Level</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking: Give a Great Retirement Speech!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-give-a-great-retirement-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-give-a-great-retirement-speech/</guid>
      <description>Public Speaking: you can go out with a bang by delivering a fantastic retirement speech. Imagine giving your retirement speech and every one of your colleagues feels as though you are personally speaking to them and thanking them in a meaningful way. Wouldn&#39;t it be nice to end your career on a high note by giving a retirement speech where you hit all the right notes?  In this How to Give a Retirement Speech Public Speaking course you will learn the following:  *How to give a great retirement speech  *How to plan stories for your speech  *How to practice your speech on video  *How to use the right amount of emotion and retain composure  This public speaking course is delivered primarily through spoken lecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cultivating Gratitude with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cultivating-gratitude-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:50:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cultivating-gratitude-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>Here&#39;s what you&#39;ll discover inside of this life-changing online course with MRS JOY:

Learn that gratitude is a state of being.
Learn how to use gratitude in your relationships to develop a deeper connection.
Learn how the power of positive emotions and gratitude can change your life.
Discover how practicing mindfulness and meditation can cultivate an attitude of gratitude.
Discover what unbalanced gratitude is and how you can counteract it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solve Problems by Rising above Problems For New Perspective</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/solve-problems-by-rising-above-problems-for-new-perspective/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/solve-problems-by-rising-above-problems-for-new-perspective/</guid>
      <description>Solve Problems by Rising above Problems for New Perspective
5 Star Review
GREAT little course on how to overcome your fears, anxiety, stress, problems by using your imagination with self-hypnosis and/or EFT tapping.
Ivon Timmermans
Learn how you can easily change your perspective of old experiences that have clouded how you see the world and people in it. Because not everyone has the same life experiences that hold them back, but it is those past experiences that have created who you are today because of your perspective of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comunicazione: come gestirla in maniera efficace</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/comunicazione-come-gestirla-in-maniera-efficace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/comunicazione-come-gestirla-in-maniera-efficace/</guid>
      <description>In questo corso ti spiegherò nei minimi dettagli come poter superare le difficoltà del parlare in pubblico e rendere più incisivo il tuo modo di Comunicare.  Esporrò tecniche precise e dettagliate, ti darò consigli teorici e pratici per far sì che tu possa padroneggiare nel migliore dei modi la Voce(intesa come Contenuto e Comunicazione Para-Verbale) ed il linguaggio del corpo (Comunicazione Non Verbale) spiegandoti l&#39;importanza del tenere viva l&#39;attenzione dall&#39;esordio alla conclusione di un discorso.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Confidence Building Course - Exude Confidence Now</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-confidence-building-course-exude-confidence-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-confidence-building-course-exude-confidence-now/</guid>
      <description>Complete Confidence Building Course - Exude Confidence NowBuild Your Confidence - Increase Self-Esteem - Radiate More Confidence - Become a Truly Confident Person - Communication
Imagine going through life filled with confidence. You are confident in your abilities, your talents, your communication skills, your appearance and in having an accurate sense of how others perceive you. and other people judge you as supremely confident (though not cocky or arrogant!)
Confidence is not something you are born with.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>