<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Other IT &amp; Software on </title>
    <link>/tags/other-it-software/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Other IT &amp; Software on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:16:32 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/other-it-software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Docker - Almost Complete Guide with Hands-On for 2021</title>
      <link>/docker-almost-complete-guide-with-hands-on-for-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:16:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docker-almost-complete-guide-with-hands-on-for-2021/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to take your DevOps skills and career to the next level, take this course now!
You will go from zero to Docker hero in couple of hours.
Why choosing this course?
This course is very hands on, Himanshu has put lots effort to provide you with not only the theory but also real-life examples of developing Docker applications that you can try out on your own laptop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helm 3 - Package Manager For Kubernetes for 2021</title>
      <link>/helm-3-package-manager-for-kubernetes-for-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:16:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/helm-3-package-manager-for-kubernetes-for-2021/</guid>
      <description>What you&#39;ll learn
Working with Helm Charts and Releases
Helm Architecture and concepts
Create custom Helm Charts and Deploy applications to Kubernetes using Helm
Working with Stable and Custom Helm Charts
Create Automated Kubernetes Deployments with Helm
Helm package manager installation and configuration
Working with Chartmuseum Repository
Expert Secrets from Industry - master troubleshooting tricks that you won’t find anywhere else
Description
You will learn all the required topics as given below for HELM - The Package Manager for Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes: CKA/CKAD, Production Grade Course for 2021</title>
      <link>/kubernetes-cka/ckad-production-grade-course-for-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:16:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kubernetes-cka/ckad-production-grade-course-for-2021/</guid>
      <description>In this Course you are going to learn most of the things which everyone is looking for. This course will help you in understading production environment and i have capture most of the things in the course which you going to face in the Interview and while working in production. Like what are the options we can use to create a cluster, Like Kubeadm, KOPS, Rancher, K3s, EKS . Have almost covered from the Installation to deploying the applications and securing them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linkerd - Service mesh for Kubernetes - 2021</title>
      <link>/linkerd-service-mesh-for-kubernetes-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:16:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/linkerd-service-mesh-for-kubernetes-2021/</guid>
      <description>A different kind of service mesh
Ultra light, ultra simple, ultra powerful. Linkerd adds security, observability, and reliability to Kubernetes, without the complexity. CNCF-hosted and 100% open source.

Instant platform health metrics
Instantly track success rates, latencies, and request volumes for every meshed workload, without changes or config.
Simpler than any other mesh
Minimalist, Kubernetes-native design. No hidden magic, as little YAML and as few CRDs as possible.
Zero-config mutual TLS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETHICAL HACKING IN TAMIL</title>
      <link>/ethical-hacking-in-tamil/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ethical-hacking-in-tamil/</guid>
      <description>In This Course You Will be Taught many Hacking Demonstration Like Android Hacking,Instagram Hacking, Wifi Hacking and Cybersecurity Related Challenges like CTF etc.


Know The Some Basics

What is Ethical Hacking?

Ethical Hacking sometimes called as Penetration Testing is an act of intruding/penetrating into system or networks to find out threats, vulnerabilities in those systems which a malicious attacker may find and exploit causing loss of data, financial loss or other major damages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MS Word for Novice to Expert : 2021 Updated</title>
      <link>/ms-word-for-novice-to-expert-2021-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ms-word-for-novice-to-expert-2021-updated/</guid>
      <description>An ultimate course for novice who want to learn basic MS Word. This course will help you to have clear concept of using MS Word. After complete this course using of MS Word will be very easy and friendly to you. This course focused from beginner level to advance level and its covered up with almost every major part of MS Word for using in personal and business uses.  Ratings: 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python And Flask Framework Complete Course</title>
      <link>/python-and-flask-framework-complete-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/python-and-flask-framework-complete-course/</guid>
      <description>This course is a depth introduction to fundamental python programming concepts.
Learn Python From Beginner To Advanced Level
 I’ve created thorough, extensive, but easy to follow content which you’ll easily understand and absorb.
 The course starts with the basics, including Python fundamentals, programming, and user interaction.

The curriculum is going to be very hands-on as we walk you from start to finish becoming a professional Python developer. We will start from the very beginning by teaching you Python basics and programming fundamentals, and then going into advanced topics and different career fields in Python so you can get real-life practice and be ready for the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Beginner Guide to Streamlabs OBS (OBS)</title>
      <link>/ultimate-beginner-guide-to-streamlabs-obs-obs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ultimate-beginner-guide-to-streamlabs-obs-obs/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Ultimate Beginner Guide to Streamlabs OBS (OBS)!
Nick Nyxson here, Your Instructor for this course.
In this course, you will learn how to start using Streamlabs OBS which is live streaming software made by Streamlabs and is a modified version of Open Broadcaster Software (OBS).
In this course You Will Learn:
What is SLOBS (Streamlabs OBS);
How Streamlabs OBS is any different from OBS Studio;
Streamlabs OBS Settings Walkthrough;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI (Artificial Intelligence) for CXOs &amp; Senior Managers</title>
      <link>/ai-artificial-intelligence-for-cxos-senior-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ai-artificial-intelligence-for-cxos-senior-managers/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;This course covers concepts &amp;amp; case studies for executives and senior managers to better understand AI. This course doesn&#39;t cover programming aspects of AI&amp;gt;
Demystifying Artificial Intelligence including ML, DL, NLP, Industry 4.0, IoT &amp;amp; RPA with Caselets for CxOs and Senior Managers.
AI, AI, AI Everywhere! If you don’t do something about AI, you will be left behind or disrupted into extinction – this is a message that executives, Managers, Team Leaders and CXOs often hear, especially in the last year or so from consultants, vendors, industry experts or the IT organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Foundation</title>
      <link>/devops-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/devops-foundation/</guid>
      <description>If you are new to DevOps, this course will give you the basic information about DevOps, including key concepts and the terminologies. This course covers the DevOps Full Stack: People and Culture, Processes and Practices, Technology and Automation. People and Culture:
You will be able to summarize the cultural, structural, and technological barriers that IT faces, when attempting to deliver services at the right quality, speed, and cost, and why challenges are faced when implementing DevOps in today’s organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Processing Real-World Projects in Python</title>
      <link>/natural-language-processing-real-world-projects-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/natural-language-processing-real-world-projects-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to land a top-paying job in Data Science , AI &amp;amp; Natural Language Processing?
Or are you a seasoned AI practitioner who want to take your career to the next level?
Or are you an aspiring data scientist who wants to get Hands-on Data Science and Artificial Intelligence?

If the answer is yes to any of these questions, then this course is for you!
Data Science is one of the hottest tech fields to be in right now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Kanban: Kanban for Software Development Teams</title>
      <link>/agile-kanban-kanban-for-software-development-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/agile-kanban-kanban-for-software-development-teams/</guid>
      <description>Kanban is not a software development lifecycle methodology or an approach to project management.
It requires that some process is already in place so that Kanban can be applied to
incrementally change the underlying process.
—David Anderson, Kanban
Kanban is a popular framework used to implement agile and DevOps software development. It requires real-time communication of capacity and full transparency of work. Work items are represented visually on a kanban board, allowing team members to see the state of every piece of work at any time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon EKS Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>/amazon-eks-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/amazon-eks-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to do use Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service but don&#39;t know where to start?	Would you like to make amazing Kubernetes applications in AWS Cloud or on-premise and bring your ideas to life?	Then Amazon EKS Ultimate Course is for you!	Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.	Amazon EKS is an in-demand skill in 2021.&amp;nbsp; The course begins with the basics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Web- The complete Introduction to the hidden web</title>
      <link>/deep-web-the-complete-introduction-to-the-hidden-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/deep-web-the-complete-introduction-to-the-hidden-web/</guid>
      <description>Have you heard many times about the deep/dark web but you never knew what it is. Or you you have an Idea of what is it but you never visited this part of the web. Then this course for you. You will learn all the basics of the deep/dark and how to access this part of the web. At the end of the course, you will be able to use the TOR browser as your default browser and surf on all the parts of the Web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mathematics &amp; Statistics for Machine Learning</title>
      <link>/mathematics-statistics-for-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mathematics-statistics-for-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;This course doesn&#39;t cover programming related to AI but helps you to build a strong foundation in math &amp;amp; statistics needed for AI&amp;gt;
The trainer of this course is an AI expert and he has observed that many students and young professionals make the mistake of learning machine learning without understanding the core concepts in maths and statistics. This course will help to address that gap in a big way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Bootcamp 2021 Build 15 working Applications and Games</title>
      <link>/python-bootcamp-2021-build-15-working-applications-and-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/python-bootcamp-2021-build-15-working-applications-and-games/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of getting videos and lectures on just python basics and syntaxes or just strucked in college studies and hello world program. so I guess you have to give a try to this course this course is designed after analysing what a student need to study python. After analysing what they required and what they want in a course, how they can easily start any course but didn&#39;t able to finish it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cursillo Excel Básico</title>
      <link>/cursillo-excel-b%C3%A1sico/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cursillo-excel-b%C3%A1sico/</guid>
      <description>Curso de Bolsillo Excel que lo puedes llevar a todo lado. Tocaremos los temas más fundamentales pero a la vez indispensables cuando usamos Excel. Diseñado para todos aquellos que están empezando con esta poderosa herramienta. - Primero lo primero: En el primero video te cuento cuáles son los puntos a tratar. Luego, pasaremos al contenido principal del curso.&amp;nbsp; - Abordaremos Atajos y Truquitos para ya a empezar a sentir qué tan fácil resulta trabajar con la interfaz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring VirBELA 3D University Campus (2021 Edition)</title>
      <link>/exploring-virbela-3d-university-campus-2021-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/exploring-virbela-3d-university-campus-2021-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the eighth course in Term 3 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Did you know?&amp;nbsp;Virtual worlds are simulated environments accessed by multiple users through an online interface or software. Virtual worlds integrate two things which can be intrinsic to human nature; social connectivity and creativeness.
Human beings are a social species that require verbal exchange to thrive and we are constantly seeking opportunities for interaction, expression and validation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
