<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Other IT &amp; Software on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/other-it-software/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Other IT &amp; Software on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/other-it-software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Computer Basics 2022: Basic Computer Skills And Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/computer-basics-2022-basic-computer-skills-and-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/computer-basics-2022-basic-computer-skills-and-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Get most updated course to learn about computer basic 2022. In any type of job, whether it is technical or non technical, basic knowledge of computer is important. You&#39;ll learn the most necessary things that is essential if you have a computer.
We all start somewhere. I know you are a new computer user. This course is designed for absolute beginners. This course is short because most people can&#39;t finish long courses .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Essential Non Technical Skills of Effective Data Scientists</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/essential-non-technical-skills-of-effective-data-scientists/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/essential-non-technical-skills-of-effective-data-scientists/</guid>
      <description>Most data science training focuses only on key technologies like Python, R, ML etc. But real-world data science jobs require more than just technical acumen. As IT professionals rush to upgrade their current skill-set and become career ready in the field of data science, most of them forget the other part of skill development — Non-technical skills.
These skills won’t require as much technical training or formal certification, but they’re foundational to the rigorous application of data science to business problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programação em Linguagem C para Iniciantes</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/programa%C3%A7%C3%A3o-em-linguagem-c-para-iniciantes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/programa%C3%A7%C3%A3o-em-linguagem-c-para-iniciantes/</guid>
      <description>Este curso foi criado para ensinar programação a hackers e iniciantes. É um curso 100% prático, com exemplos em todas as lições.
Eventuais dúvidas poderão ser tiradas diretamente na plataforma Udemy.
Se você não entende nada de linguagem C e nem de programação, este é o curso que você precisa fazer.
Seja bem-vindo(a)! :)
Ratings: 4.90/5
Enrollments: 3125
Coupon Code: REALDISCOUNT5F
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash Course on Civil Engineering and AutoCAD: Part 7</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-7/</guid>
      <description>This brilliant and engaging course on &#34;AutoCAD 2020 and Artificial Intelligence Tools: Level 2&#34; taught by &#34;Srinidhi&#34; and &#34;Saranya&#34; will take a step further from the Part 1 course to help you explore and understand more functions and features in AutoCAD including measurement of drawing, creating dimensions, executing commands, offsetting objects etc. This course is a part of a series titled &#34;Crash Course on Civil Engineering and AutoCAD&#34; and is the seventh course on the list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>File &amp; Folder Management Using PowerShell</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/file-folder-management-using-powershell/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/file-folder-management-using-powershell/</guid>
      <description>If you want to learn File Management using PowerShell, then this course is for you.
File Management is part of Our day Today IT Operations, After completing this course, You will find yourself very efficient and confident in Advanced Automated File Management.
You will be able to do all the stuff with files and folders using PowerShell, What you can do using normal Graphical User Interface.
Now a days every Leading Platform using PowerShell as its Management Tool, whether it is Microsoft Products, VMware, Citrix, cloud Providers like Azure, AWS, or Google etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PowerShell Functions Master Class</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/powershell-functions-master-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/powershell-functions-master-class/</guid>
      <description>If you want to Master PowerShell Scripting and use the power of automation, then this course is for you.
In this Course, you will learn, All aspects of PowerShell functions like -
PowerShell Functions, benefits, Scope, Best Practices &amp;amp; Syntax
What exactly Advanced functions are &amp;amp; how they differ from Simple functions &amp;amp; the best benefits of using them
Creating parameters &amp;amp; defining their different attributes like if parameter is mandatory, does it accept Pipelined Input, Should it accept single value or multiple values, Is it positional or not etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Introduction</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aws-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aws-introduction/</guid>
      <description>This course is about AWS Introduction. You will learn to sign up for an AWS account, AWS free tier, EC2, IAM, S3, AWS security, and many other related concepts. The course is a good blend of theory and hands-on.
You will get a conceptual understanding of what AWS is, and its overview. Then you will understand the types of services offered by AWS and AWS&#39;s advantages.
Then the next section is about the AWS account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Microsoft Power BI in 21 Days</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-microsoft-power-bi-in-21-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-microsoft-power-bi-in-21-days/</guid>
      <description>If you want to learn Microsoft Power BI from the basics if you want to improve your analytical skills which have vast demand in the market.
Following are the topics you are going to learn from in this course.
What is Power BI?
What technology or toolset is needed to learn Power BI?
Why do we need Power BI?
Different components in the Power BI area.
What is Power BI Desktop?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Transaction Management with SpringBoot and Data JPA</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-transaction-management-with-springboot-and-data-jpa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-transaction-management-with-springboot-and-data-jpa/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you will learn about Transaction Management in general.
Why Transaction Management is important in any application.
We will start by setting up Java, Intellij, maven, postman and springboot from spring initializer.
We will first create entities with some fields then we will create the controller, repository layer along with the service.
Then we will go ahead and implement Transaction in our application.
You will learn to implement Transaction Management in your project</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metaverse: Avatars, NFTs, Artyfact Fi, GAN-Gough &amp; Open GL</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/metaverse-avatars-nfts-artyfact-fi-gan-gough-open-gl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:33:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/metaverse-avatars-nfts-artyfact-fi-gan-gough-open-gl/</guid>
      <description>Metaverse is a simulated digital environment that uses augmented reality (AR), virtual reality (VR), and blockchain, along with concepts from social media, to create spaces for rich user interaction mimicking the real world. It will allow people to showcase digital forms of art and property, and NFTs will allow them to put a price on that content with proof of ownership. This course is designed meticulously to impart to learners the very concept of the metaverse and its implementation in the virtual domain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TypeScript Basic: Type System, Interfaces, Types, Generics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/typescript-basic-type-system-interfaces-types-generics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:11:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/typescript-basic-type-system-interfaces-types-generics/</guid>
      <description>TypeScript is a programming language developed and maintained by Microsoft. It is a strict syntactical superset of JavaScript and adds optional static typing to the language. TypeScript is designed for the development of large applications and transcompiles to JavaScript. As TypeScript is a superset of JavaScript, existing JavaScript programs are also valid TypeScript programs.
TypeScript may be used to develop JavaScript applications for both client-side and server-side execution (as with Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop 2022 Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-2022-ultimate-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-2022-ultimate-guide/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone and welcome to Adobe Photoshop 2022 Ultimate Guide.
In this video, I&#39;m going to go over an in-depth overview of what we&#39;re going to be learning throughout the course.
So in Section two, we&#39;re going to talk about Adobe Creative Cloud plans and pricing.
So we&#39;ll cover individuals, business students and teachers and schools, universities.
Next will learn how to create a free creative cloud account.
Then from there, we&#39;ll work with Adobe Creative Cloud Web and learn step by step how to install Adobe Photoshop 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Containerize Springboot CRUD App with Docker &amp; DockerCompose</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/containerize-springboot-crud-app-with-docker-dockercompose/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/containerize-springboot-crud-app-with-docker-dockercompose/</guid>
      <description>Learn everything about Docker &amp;amp; run your Springboot apps &amp;amp; Database inside containers using Docker &amp;amp; Docker Compose
Following are the topics that you will learn in this course:
What is the need to run applications inside the container
What is Docker
What is Image
What is Container
What is Docker hub
What is Dockerfile
Benefits of using Docker and running applications inside a container
How to create your own Dockerfile</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Containerize SpringBoot Node Express Apps &amp; Deploy on Azure</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/containerize-springboot-node-express-apps-deploy-on-azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/containerize-springboot-node-express-apps-deploy-on-azure/</guid>
      <description>Learn everything about Docker &amp;amp; run your Springboot, NodeJS apps inside containers using Docker on Azure cloud.
Following are the topics that you will learn in this course:
What is the need to run applications inside the container
What is Docker
What is Image
What is Container
What is Docker hub
What is Dockerfile
Benefits of using Docker and running applications inside a container
How to create your own Dockerfile</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MariaDB Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mariadb-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mariadb-basics/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to do use MariaDB but don’t know where to start? Would you like to learn how to use MariaDB? Then MariaDB Basics is for you! Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course. MariaDB is a in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. We’ll Cover everything you need to know about MariaDB Basics from scratch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical HTML5 Mastery Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/practical-html5-mastery-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/practical-html5-mastery-course/</guid>
      <description>If you have been always thinking about learning web development or you have been thinking of becoming full-stack developer then this is the course that will not just teach you rather make you implement each and every concept of HTML5 like a pro.
Many of the students just shy away from frontend technologies because they think it&#39;s not their cup of tea, but this course will break that perception and will make you a developer by teaching you how to implement the concepts without the need of being remembering anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Computer Basics Guide for Beginners: 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-computer-basics-guide-for-beginners-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-computer-basics-guide-for-beginners-2022/</guid>
      <description>The Computer Defined, Data versus Information, Classification of Computers based on how data is handled (Analog Computers, Digital Computers Hybrid Computers)
Computers for Individual Users or Personal Computers (Desktop Computers,Workstations, Laptops, Notebooks, Tablets, Handheld PCs, Smartphones)
Computers for Organizations (Network Server, Mainframes, Minicomputers, Supercomputers)
Parts of Computer System (Hardware , Software, User and Data)
Information Processing Cycle (Input, Processing, Output, Storage)
Computer Hardware Categorized ( Processing Devices, Memory Devices, Input and Output Devices, Storage Devices, Bus Interconnection)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer Science MetaBootcamp: Beginner to Intermediate 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/computer-science-metabootcamp-beginner-to-intermediate-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/computer-science-metabootcamp-beginner-to-intermediate-2022/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wondered how the first couple of years of a general Computer Science university course looks like? Maybe you’d like to know if this is the discipline for you and if you are good at it? Wonder no longer, for we will show you how to get there, how to get good as you go along on your journey, and how life as a computer scientist is like! Money is precious, time even more so, so our priority is to push you ahead, and give you a head-start into university life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover Python</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/discover-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/discover-python/</guid>
      <description>There are a ton of programming resources available online but it is very difficult to find those resources that help you understand and retain programming concepts as a beginner. Most of those resources focus on learning coding syntax instead of teaching the computational thinking behind it as well. This course addresses the aforementioned problems and helps you learn programming by employing the following teaching methods:
1. We use 4MAT teaching style that goes through a whole learning process of experiencing, conceptualizing, applying and refining and is a product of years of research to ensure quality learning</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power BI - Data Analytics Essentials with Power BI</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/power-bi-data-analytics-essentials-with-power-bi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/power-bi-data-analytics-essentials-with-power-bi/</guid>
      <description>Many students who have taken this course have found it detailed and easy to understand.
​“In God we trust, all others must bring data”.
​The famous quote by W. Edwards Deming has never been more true than it does in today&#39;s world.
​Far gone are the days business decision makers take critical decisions based on haunches, intuition and gut feelings.
​These days, everyone has come to realise that better and more accurate decisions can be made when data is put into good use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Analytics,Storage,Mining &amp; Visual Big Data Technologies</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/data-analyticsstoragemining-visual-big-data-technologies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/data-analyticsstoragemining-visual-big-data-technologies/</guid>
      <description>You will learn the following interesting topics in this course
Big Data Technology Fields
Types of Big Data Technologies
Big Data Technologies in Data Storage
Big Data Technologies in Data Analytics
Big Data Technologies in Data Mining
Big Data Technologies in Data Visualization
You will learn the following interesting topics in this course.
Big Data Technology Fields
Types of Big Data Technologies
Big Data Technologies in Data Storage
Big Data Technologies in Data Analytics</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FullStack Application Spring Boot and React</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fullstack-application-spring-boot-and-react/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fullstack-application-spring-boot-and-react/</guid>
      <description>Build Full-Stack Application with Spring Boot and React. Backend Development with Spring Boot and Mysql with IDE IntelliJ. Front End Development with Reactjs, React Hooks, and Material UI. We will be using Postman for testing APIs. By the end of this course, you will be able to develop the full stack application using Spring boot and React, and Mysql. To follow this course you need to have basic knowledge of Java and Javascript.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hands-On SQL Server,ManagementStudio,SQL Queries,AzureStudio</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hands-on-sql-servermanagementstudiosql-queriesazurestudio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hands-on-sql-servermanagementstudiosql-queriesazurestudio/</guid>
      <description>1) Detailed Course with Hands-On Practical Lab Sessions on SQL Server Installation, Writing SQL Queries, Database Creation, Installation of SQL Server Management Studio &amp;amp; Azure Data Studio,
How to Connect and Use SQL Server Management Studio &amp;amp; Azure Data Studio.
2) Practical Course includes practical assignment activities for students to practice lab activities.
3) Students will learn the following topics in this detailed hands-on course.
What is SQL Server ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Income Tax – Schedule C Small Business Sole Proprietor</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/income-tax-schedule-c-small-business-sole-proprietor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/income-tax-schedule-c-small-business-sole-proprietor/</guid>
      <description>This course will focus on tax preparation for taxpayers who have self-employment incomed generally reported on a Schedule C.
We will look at each new concept from multiple angles, starting with a presentation discussing the topic and then looking at examples to better understand the concepts in action.
The example section will use tax forms to work problems and an accounting equation method using Excel so learners will understand the impact on the actual tax return and visualize the concepts using a tax formula.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Big Data Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-big-data-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-big-data-basics/</guid>
      <description>In this course, Students will Learn the following topics.
Big Data Concepts
History &amp;amp; Jobs in Big Data
Types of Big data
Characteristics of Big data
Categories of Big data
Big Data Frameworks &amp;amp; Programming Paradigms
Big Data Programming Languages
This course is for beginners interested to learn big data basics for their career growth.
In this course, Students will Learn the following topics.
Big Data Concepts
History &amp;amp; Jobs in Big Data</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer Vision with Python</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/computer-vision-with-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/computer-vision-with-python/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the ultimate online course on Python for Computer Vision!
This course is your best resource for learning how to use the Python programming language for Computer Vision.
We&#39;ll be exploring how to use Python and the OpenCV (Open Computer Vision) library to analyze images and video data.
The most popular platforms in the world are generating never before seen amounts of image and video data. Every 60 seconds users upload more than 300 hours of video to Youtube, Netflix subscribers stream over 80,000 hours of video, and Instagram users like over 2 million photos!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash Course on Civil Engineering and AutoCAD: Exam (Vol.1)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-exam-vol.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-exam-vol.1/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to all AutoCAD experts and students from the Civil Engineering field. We all know that AutoCAD is a commercial computer-aided design (CAD) and drafting software. It is developed and greatly marketed by Autodesk. AutoCAD is used in the construction industry, by top architects, engineers, graphic designers, city-planners and other working professionals. AutoCAD helps you gain complete productivity in 2D and 3D design.
Some of you might have used AutoCAD, played around with the software and mastered the commands too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash Course on Civil Engineering and AutoCAD: Part 8</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-8/</guid>
      <description>AutoCAD is one of the most important software for any engineer and it will remain so. We believe that you probably won&#39;t be able to find a better tool for all your needs than AutoCAD 2020. Let&#39;s read on, further.
This fascinating course in the series titled &#34;Crash Course on Civil Engineering and AutoCAD&#34; created by Legend &#39;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#39; and Mastermind &#39;Saranya Srinidhi&#39; will cover more functions and features in AutoCAD including measurement of drawing, executing commands like RECTANG, DIM, EXTEND, FILLET, CHAMFER, JOIN, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenCV and Java: Build a Webcam Biofeedback Game</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/opencv-and-java-build-a-webcam-biofeedback-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/opencv-and-java-build-a-webcam-biofeedback-game/</guid>
      <description>If you want to learn Java, or, if Java is your first language, or, preferred language, or, if you already know Java and have limited time to pick up other languages and want to get started quickly on building rich gui-based computer vision applications, the fun and easy way, then this course is for you. You will learn how to use Eclipse and Java to create webcam applications and image processing applications that perform innovative functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build your own powerful super-computer on cloud in 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/build-your-own-powerful-super-computer-on-cloud-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/build-your-own-powerful-super-computer-on-cloud-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Build your own powerful super-computer on cloud in 2022&#34;.
Fasten your harnesses right now, because the era of cloud computing is on the rise. Whether you are a software developer, video editor, or animation artist - you can speed up and automate all your tasks with this giant phenomenon of what we call &#34;Cloud Computing&#34;. Surely, they are ready to change the world of PC usage in our everyday lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash Course on Civil Engineering and AutoCAD: Part 6</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-6/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this mind-blowing course that teaches you &#34;AutoCAD 2020 and Artificial Intelligence Tools&#34;. This course is part of a series-based course which is titled &#34;Crash Course on Civil Engineering and AutoCAD&#34;.
This Part 6 course in the series introduces you to AutoCAD 2020 and covers AutoCAD 2020 with relevant Artificial Intelligence (AI) Tools. The course is created by Digital Marketing Legend &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34; and Civil Mastermind &#34;Saranya Srinidhi&#34;. It will help you understand the concepts of what is AutoCAD 2020, the history of AutoCAD, its usage, installation and of course - the various commands in the interface dashboard etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digishock 1.0: Experience World-Changing Technologies</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digishock-1.0-experience-world-changing-technologies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digishock-1.0-experience-world-changing-technologies/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the exhaustive course series &#34;Digishock&#34;. &#34;Digishock 1.0: Experience World-Changing Technologies&#34; is the first course in this ultimate series. Ready to know what it is all about? Let&#39;s dive right in. &#34;Digishock 1.0&#34; is the ultimate technology course in 2022 to make you a technology expert today. This is the first beginner&#39;s part course of getting involved with Machine Learning and the unique technologies associated with the field. Most of my students have been waiting for me to launch this course and now they are very happy that it is launched.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/devops-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 21:50:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/devops-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>DevOps is not only a set of processes and tools but is more rightly represented by the culture of enhanced communication and collaboration between IT operation guys and Developers. DevOps culture is guided by principles of DevOps such as Automation, infrastructure as code, practices such as continuous integration, continuous delivery, and implemented by a large set of DevOps tools. In this course, DevOps concepts are explained in easy to understand language along with hands-on examples on basic tools of DevOps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentos de Programación: Aprende a programar desde cero</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentos-de-programaci%C3%B3n-aprende-a-programar-desde-cero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentos-de-programaci%C3%B3n-aprende-a-programar-desde-cero/</guid>
      <description>Este es un curso pensado para dotar al estudiante de los conocimientos necesarios para comenzar a trabajar en el ámbito de la programación. A continuación sus principales características:
División en capítulos que forman una unidad en sí mismo, en donde se exponen los objetivos de aprendizaje en forma concreta y práctica, con un marco teórico explicado en forma clara y concisa, proponiendo enseguida ejercicios para aplicar y entender lo visto en cada capítulo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Payroll - QuickBooks Pro Desktop</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-payroll-quickbooks-pro-desktop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-payroll-quickbooks-pro-desktop/</guid>
      <description>QuickBooks Desktop Pro 2019 payroll will describe the payroll process for a small business in detail, so bookkeepers, accountants, and business owners can better understand how to set up payroll, process payroll, and troubleshoot problems related to payroll. This course will introduce the payroll set-up in the QuickBooks Desktop Pro 2019 system, walking through payroll screens for both the paid version and the free manual version of payroll within QuickBooks Desktop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACE the WordPress Interview : 50 Most Asked WordPress Q&amp;A</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ace-the-wordpress-interview-50-most-asked-wordpress-qa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:57:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ace-the-wordpress-interview-50-most-asked-wordpress-qa/</guid>
      <description>More than 35 percent of internet sites are WordPress, So huge demand for qualified WordPress developers is not surprising. So let discuss WordPress developers in demand in 2022.
After all, someone needs all the WordPress websites and integrations that so many of us use every day to build and maintain them. WordPress developers around the world are in demand and are paying high wages, making WordPress development for many aspiring technologies an attractive career journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Chat Bot in Python from Scratch.</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/facebook-chat-bot-in-python-from-scratch./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 20:03:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/facebook-chat-bot-in-python-from-scratch./</guid>
      <description>In this course you will learn how to Install Python 3.
In this course you will learn how to use python IDLE.
In this course you will learn how to choose Python IDE to learn coding.
In this course you will learn how to Install Anaconda for Python coding.
In this course you will learn how to use Online Jupyter for Python Programming.
In this course you will learn how to use Python IDLE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL Introduction: SQL Crash Course.</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sql-introduction-sql-crash-course./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 20:40:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sql-introduction-sql-crash-course./</guid>
      <description>You will learn many tips and tricks in PostgreSQL to query data through the following Topics covered in this course:
Using Real World PostgreSQL Database Airlines Database.
What is a Database
SQL database for beginners.
Installing PostgreSQL database.
Creating Tables in database using SQL.
Drop table from SQL database
SELECT Statement use with SQL database data querying WHERE Clause use with SQL database data querying Operators used with Where clause in SQL database data querying .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Illustrator 2022 Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-illustrator-2022-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-illustrator-2022-basics/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Design but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Designs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Illustrator 2022 Basics is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Design is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building designs like an expert with Adobe Illustrator 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Java Programming Certification Beginner to Advance</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-java-programming-certification-beginner-to-advance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-java-programming-certification-beginner-to-advance/</guid>
      <description>Complete Java Programming Certification Course
Goals of this course: Be completely ready to get a full time Java Developer Course at the end of the Course
Have projects to impress your Employer and land that dream job!
You will learn the most in-demand and essential components for becoming a Core Java developer in this course, which is intended to help you master them. This is especially true if you&#39;re going on a job interview or working on a Java project that requires your best effort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Analysis, Data Science &amp; Visualization: Python &amp; Pandas</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/data-analysis-data-science-visualization-python-pandas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/data-analysis-data-science-visualization-python-pandas/</guid>
      <description>Why Data Analysis?
As organizations seek to create insights and push their businesses forward with the assistance of data, the field of data analytics is expanding at a fast pace. Learn what data analytics is, why it is important, the many kinds of data analytics, and the numerous data analytics applications in this Data Analytics Complete Course. You will also learn how to use data analytics.
Why Enroll in our course?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer Basics, Computer Fundamentals Hardware &amp; Networking</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/computer-basics-computer-fundamentals-hardware-networking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/computer-basics-computer-fundamentals-hardware-networking/</guid>
      <description>LAND A JOB IN Computer Science : Computer Basics / Computer Fundamentals / Basic Computer Skills / Computer Hardware &amp;amp; Networking
Using a Computer to Its Full Potential: A Comprehensive Introduction to Computers The following are some of the skills you&#39;ll need: - Desktop support; IT support; computer fundamentals; and basic computer skills.
Understand each and every topic of computer science and become an expert in its application. Because we all have computers or are computer students, I am concentrating my efforts in this course on assisting you in understanding every vital concept you will encounter for the first time because Computer Basic is the most important concept you will encounter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developing CRUD Application using FASTAPI Python &amp; MongoDB</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/developing-crud-application-using-fastapi-python-mongodb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/developing-crud-application-using-fastapi-python-mongodb/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you will learn to develop Rest API using FAST API, Python and MongoDB.
FastAPI is a modern, fast (high-performance), web framework for building APIs with Python 3.6+ based on standard Python type hints.
We will develop REST API using HTTP methods like GET, POST, PUT and DELETE, and respond data in JSON format with proper HTTP status codes.
We will connect MongoDB with our FastAPI application and perform the required CRUD operation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frontend Development with ReactJS and Bootstrap</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/frontend-development-with-reactjs-and-bootstrap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/frontend-development-with-reactjs-and-bootstrap/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you will learn everything that is needed for you to become a Pro React JS developer in a hands-on step by step approach.
There is no prerequisite for this course.
Everything will be taught from scratch with practical examples.
You will learn to install the required software needed for the development.
You will learn how to create components in React.
You will learn to integrate Boostrap with React project, you will also learn to use React Bootstrap and use the components.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master HTML5 Bootstrap5 &amp; ReactJs From Scratch</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-html5-bootstrap5-reactjs-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-html5-bootstrap5-reactjs-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you will learn to develop any kind of website using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap 5 and ReactJs.
We will start by setting up our local development environment, first we will learn to install Visual Studio Code editor, then we will go ahead and install NodeJS runtime.
Next we will move on to creating the first react app, then we will move on to understanding how a create application work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Security Speciality practice test [NEW]</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aws-certified-security-speciality-practice-test-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aws-certified-security-speciality-practice-test-new/</guid>
      <description>These Practice exams going to give you the education and the knowledge you need before the real exam, Because this practice exam aren’t thrown together to make a quick buck
Real Exam info:
Number and titler of Exam: SCS-C01: AWS Certified Security – Specialty
Exam Price: $300
Format: Multiple Choice
Number of Questions: 65
Duration: 170 minutes
Passing score: 75%
Our Practice Exam info:
Real exam experience
Questions with a complete explanation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Azure Virtual Desktop (WVD - Advanced Training)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mastering-azure-virtual-desktop-wvd-advanced-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mastering-azure-virtual-desktop-wvd-advanced-training/</guid>
      <description>Here&#39;s what you will learn in this AZ-140 Azure Virtual Desktop (AVD) Course Introduction and Quick Start
What is Microsoft Azure Virtual Desktop (Introduction)
Highlight business needs and use case scenarios
Explore Microsoft Azure Virtual Desktop formerly (Windows Virtual Desktop) benefits
Understand Azure Virtual Desktop Pricing and Estimate the Cost using Azure Pricing Calculator
Understanding Azure Virtual Desktop Licenses requirement and covered by Microsoft 365 License Infrastructure Preparation and AVD Prerequisites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Computing &amp;  Encryption: Basics to leading trends</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quantum-computing-encryption-basics-to-leading-trends/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quantum-computing-encryption-basics-to-leading-trends/</guid>
      <description>This course would enable you to gain insight into the realm of Quantum Computing. The students would be able to learn and develop expertise in Quantum algorithms, gates, and implementation of these codes. The undergraduate students would particularly find it very imperative for realizing their final year projects and reports. Furthermore, this course is an introduction to the fundamental concepts of quantum circuits and algorithms. The course will provide tools that allow students to implement quantum circuits and algorithms using quantum computing libraries and to run them using quantum simulators as well as real hardware.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cursillo Excel Básico</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cursillo-excel-b%C3%A1sico/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cursillo-excel-b%C3%A1sico/</guid>
      <description>Curso de Bolsillo Excel que lo puedes llevar a todo lado. Tocaremos los temas más fundamentales pero a la vez indispensables cuando usamos Excel. Diseñado para todos aquellos que están empezando con esta poderosa herramienta. - Primero lo primero: En el primero video te cuento cuáles son los puntos a tratar. Luego, pasaremos al contenido principal del curso. - Abordaremos Atajos y Truquitos para ya a empezar a sentir qué tan fácil resulta trabajar con la interfaz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git with Visual Studio Code</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/git-with-visual-studio-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 17:17:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/git-with-visual-studio-code/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to get stared quickly to use Git, right inside your favorite IDE, Visual Studio Code?
Then you are at the right place!
Welcome to my Git with Visual Studio Code course, where you will learn everything you need in order to keep track of your awesome projects!
Here you will learn only what you need, no extra content, because time is precious!
Ratings: 4.33/5
Enrollments: 42264
Coupon Code: FREEMAR3</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Visual Studio Code</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mastering-visual-studio-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 17:17:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mastering-visual-studio-code/</guid>
      <description>In just 3 years, Visual Studio Code became the number 1 tool any programmer should use. Even if you need a simple code editor, or a complex IDE, with rich features like refactoring, linting or debugger, VSCode is the tool you need. Why use one tool for your HTML and CSS, one for your back-end development and another one for course control, when you can have everything you need in one single, fast and beautiful program: Visual Studio Code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical GIS in QGIS - Project-based GIS, Spatial Analysis</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/practical-gis-in-qgis-project-based-gis-spatial-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 20:10:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/practical-gis-in-qgis-project-based-gis-spatial-analysis/</guid>
      <description>GIS &amp;amp; Spatial Analysis in the latest QGIS - Master Geographic Information Systems (GIS) via GIS-based project analysis
This course provides an introduction to GIS (geographic information systems) and also introduce students to Remote Sensing in a project-oriented way. This course is based on the newest version of the open-source QGIS software available for free to get started with GIS, Remote Sensing, and geospatial data analysis. My practical geospatial analysis course will provide you with an understanding of the GIS in a very short time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQLite Made Easy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sqlite-made-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 20:10:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sqlite-made-easy/</guid>
      <description>SQL is the most used Database language in the world, it is at heart of the Internet and every database system. Learn the basic SQL language you need to succeed Almost every database system in the world uses SQL. It&#39;s in websites, operating systems, computer programs, mobile devices and many other places. If you are in IT, you are really missing out if you don&#39;t learn SQL. So, don&#39;t be left behind!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Dreamweaver 2022 Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-dreamweaver-2022-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-dreamweaver-2022-basics/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Edit Websites but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Websites and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Dreamweaver 2022 Basics is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Web Tools are an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start Editing Websites like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe InDesign 2022 Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-indesign-2022-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-indesign-2022-basics/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Design but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Designs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe InDesign 2022 Basics is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Design is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building designs like an expert with Adobe InDesign 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe XD 2022 Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-xd-2022-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-xd-2022-basics/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Design but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Designs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe XD 2022 Basics is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Design is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building designs like an expert with Adobe XD 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Real-Time Use Cases using Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/5-real-time-use-cases-using-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:15:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/5-real-time-use-cases-using-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to start your path to becoming a Data Scientist or ML Engineer?
This comprehensive course will be your guide to learning how to use the power of Python to analyze data, create beautiful visualizations, and use powerful machine learning algorithms! Data Scientist has been ranked the number one job on Glassdoor and the average salary of a data scientist is over $120,000 in the United States according to Indeed!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash Course on Civil Engineering and AutoCAD: Part 9</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 19:20:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-9/</guid>
      <description>We all know that AutoCAD is the most leading CAD program, with thousands of industries using it every day. Having tried it before, you’ll know that the software can seem very advanced if you don’t know what features and functionalities you’re actually working on. There are a plethora of tools and AutoCAD keyboard shortcuts and commands to get to learn - not to mention the actual interface. After spending countless hours in front of AutoCAD working on a client project, you will have faced many problems - only in order to arrive at a conclusion that using a set of favourite commands would have helped to complete the project super fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Computers and Technology Quiz (2022 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-computers-and-technology-quiz-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-computers-and-technology-quiz-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>Computer technologies, being a fascinating subject have sprawled and evolved in recent years. The importance of computers and technology has greatly increased since the start of the 21st century. A computer is a useful tech tool for advancing educationally in traditional and yet non-traditional ways. Learners rely on leveraging computers to research and access educative information, or to submit their project work to their teacher. Moreover, in gradual time computers have become smaller and faster and in fact, enabling all types of people to use them virtually in any kind of location.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyperledger Fabric 2.x Multihost Deployment (4 Org, 4 VM)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hyperledger-fabric-2.x-multihost-deployment-4-org-4-vm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 18:10:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hyperledger-fabric-2.x-multihost-deployment-4-org-4-vm/</guid>
      <description>Description:
Coupon Code: 60999640877B5D56013C
Setup Hyperledgr Fabric Application on multiple hosts. We are going to use the following configuration for deploying fabric applications.
1) 4 Virtual Machine, One Org on each VM.
2) 4 Orgs (3 Peer Orgs, 1 Orderer Orgs)
3) 4 Certificates Authority for creating certificates. (Each Org has One dedicated CA)
4) Separate API Server(On vm1-Org1) for Transaction Invocation.
What we cover in this course
Purely Hands-on experience of VM Creation &amp;amp; Network Setup (4 Orgs - 4 VM)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jira Advanced | Managing and administrating Jira like a pro</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/jira-advanced-managing-and-administrating-jira-like-a-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 19:15:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/jira-advanced-managing-and-administrating-jira-like-a-pro/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Jira Advanced course! If you already know how Jira works and are looking to expand your toolkit, or aspiring to become a Jira administrator, this course is for you.
Here you will learn all the ins and outs of Jira advanced settings and administration tools. Each section starts with a quick overview of basics and goes deep into the subject so that you build a holistic picture of Jira setup and administration best practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT Deployments - Business &amp; Technical Support Planning</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/it-deployments-business-technical-support-planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/it-deployments-business-technical-support-planning/</guid>
      <description>Over this course, you&#39;ll learn the different aspects that you need to consider when either deploying equipment to a new site, or integrating a pre-existing IT environment from a recently acquired company, topics included on this course are as follows:
* Site Survey
* Identifying key services
* Regulatory considerations
* Software and hardware compatibility overview
* Identifying custom software and any considerations needed
* How to minimise service downtime during a migration</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neural Networks with Tensorflow</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/neural-networks-with-tensorflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/neural-networks-with-tensorflow/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re going to learn the most popular library to build networks and machine learning algorithms. In this hands-on, practical course, you will be working your way through with Python, Tensorflow, and Jupyter notebooks.
What you will learn:
Basics of Tensorflow
Artificial Neurons
Feed Forward Neural Networks
Activations and Softmax Output
Gradient Descent
Backpropagation
Loss Function
MSE
Model Optimization
Cross-Entropy
Linear Regression
Logistic Regression
Convolutional Neural Networks (with examples)
Text and Sequence Data</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software architecture</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/software-architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/software-architecture/</guid>
      <description>The architecture describes the processes and structures of the entire project, determining the data throughput in different parts of the project, and allows you to optimize and scale the project in the future.
Good architects are often people who learn from even better architects. Perhaps this is because some conceptual requirements are inherent in almost all projects. Each conceptual requirement is formulated as a question that the architect must ask himself during the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer Graphics ( For Engineering, BCA &amp; Entrance Exams)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/computer-graphics-for-engineering-bca-entrance-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/computer-graphics-for-engineering-bca-entrance-exams/</guid>
      <description>Hi, Welcome to Computer Graphics Course for Engineering, Bachelor&#39;s of Computer Application and various Entrance examination This course is about the basics of computer graphics where we will learn not only theoretical concepts along with that we are also going to solve a lot of numerical problems and see how to implement the different computer graphics algorithms using the c language
Here in this course, I have assumed that the student may know nothing about computer graphics so I have designed this course in such a way that we are going to start from the very basics and here in this course 3D Geogebra and other smart tools are being used in order to create a meaningful content so have a look at some lectures I hope you will like this course Here in this course, I have assumed that the student may know nothing about computer graphics so I have designed this course in such a way that we are going to start from the very basics and here in this course 3D Geogebra and other smart tools are being used in order to create a meaningful content so have a look at some lectures I hope you will like this course I&#39;m very much sure that you will enjoy this course and will have a wonderful learning experience thank you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curso SiteGround 2022: El Mejor Hosting para WordPress</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-siteground-2022-el-mejor-hosting-para-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-siteground-2022-el-mejor-hosting-para-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>SITEGROUND es un servicio de alojamiento web que proporciona alojamiento compartido, alojamiento en la nube, soluciones empresariales, alojamiento de correo electrónico y registro de dominio. Actualmente proporciona alojamiento para aproximadamente 2,000,000 de dominios en todo el mundo.
SiteGround proporciona servicios de alojamiento web para sitios web de WordPress , Joomla , Magento , Drupal , PrestaShop y WooCommerce. Si estas pensando crear un sitio web, blog o tienda virtual, este es el curso ideal para ti.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Kanban: Kanban for Software Development Teams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-kanban-kanban-for-software-development-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 21:06:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-kanban-kanban-for-software-development-teams/</guid>
      <description>Kanban is not a software development lifecycle methodology or an approach to project management.
It requires that some process is already in place so that Kanban can be applied to
incrementally change the underlying process.
—David Anderson, Kanban
Kanban is a popular framework used to implement agile and DevOps software development. It requires real-time communication of capacity and full transparency of work. Work items are represented visually on a kanban board, allowing team members to see the state of every piece of work at any time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nagios XI Network Monitoring: Setup &amp; Overview for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/nagios-xi-network-monitoring-setup-overview-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 13:12:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/nagios-xi-network-monitoring-setup-overview-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Over this course, we&#39;ll be covering some of the basics surrounding Nagios XI. Some of the topics covered on this course are as follows:
* An overview of Nagios XI and the features it contains
* Setting up different types of new user account, these being admin and user
* Setting up new alerts for hosts and services on your organisation&#39;s network
* Viewing the status of configured hosts and services and acknowledging any alerts that appear on the console</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curso  De  Algoritmos</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-de-algoritmos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 12:24:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-de-algoritmos/</guid>
      <description>CURSO ALGORITMOS
Desarrolla las competencias básicas para ser un excelente programador
Después de tomar nuestro curso, estarás listo para enfrentar con facilidad cualquier lenguaje de programación.
Fácil práctico y garantizado y al alcance de todos
Queremos darles la bienvenida a una nueva experiencia de aprendizaje en la programación .
La cual haremos de una manera muy fácil y práctica . Ya que estamos convencidos que todos estamos en la capacidad de programar en cualquier lenguaje.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GDPR Compliance &amp; Data Protection/Data Privacy for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gdpr-compliance-data-protection/data-privacy-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:37:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gdpr-compliance-data-protection/data-privacy-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>**Please note that the contents of this course are intended as guidance in regards to best practice within organisations and do not constitute legal advice. For information specific to your company with regards to data protection, please contact your organisation’s data protection officer**
Over this course, you&#39;ll learn about the following aspects of GDPR and Data Protection / Data Privacy Compliance
* An overview of the General Data Protection Regulations themselves</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Manage Any Project With Amazing Trello Platform</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-manage-any-project-with-amazing-trello-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:37:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-manage-any-project-with-amazing-trello-platform/</guid>
      <description>Thаt’ѕ whаt Trello іѕ thеrе fоr. It сrеаtеѕ vіѕіbіlіtу аnd ассоuntаbіlіtу. It саn fіt іn thе wау thе wоrk аnd саn аdарt tо уоur buѕіnеѕѕ рrосеѕѕеѕ. It gаthеr аll уоur tеаm іn one place аnd hеlр thеm collaborate wіth еасh оthеr whіlе уоu’ll ѕtіll be аblе tо knоw exactly іn еvеrу dеtаіlѕ whаt’ѕ going оn іn еасh рhаѕе оf thе рrоjесt dеvеlорmеnt. It hеlрѕ уоu fосuѕ оn thе іmроrtаnt thіngѕ thаt mаttеr аnd thаt аllоw уоu tо grоw уоur business fаѕtеr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crack Information Technology: All-Time Ultimate Quiz of 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crack-information-technology-all-time-ultimate-quiz-of-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crack-information-technology-all-time-ultimate-quiz-of-2021/</guid>
      <description>Know your terabytes from the gigabytes or PetaBytes? Are you an Information Technology (IT) expert or deem to be one?
Want to test your Information Technology (IT) knowledge or skills, before attending a corporate interview in 2021? Look no further than this practice test course. New to IT? Please do your research or study before taking this test. It will definitely help you to score well.
&#34;Information technology (IT) means the ultimate use of any computers, storage, networking and other physical devices, infrastructure and processes to create, process, store, secure and exchange all forms of electronic data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring VirBELA 3D University Campus (2021 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/exploring-virbela-3d-university-campus-2021-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/exploring-virbela-3d-university-campus-2021-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the eighth course in Term 3 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Did you know? Virtual worlds are simulated environments accessed by multiple users through an online interface or software. Virtual worlds integrate two things which can be intrinsic to human nature; social connectivity and creativeness.
Human beings are a social species that require verbal exchange to thrive and we are constantly seeking opportunities for interaction, expression and validation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Online (QBO) Bookkeeping With Bank Feeds 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-qbo-bookkeeping-with-bank-feeds-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 12:27:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-qbo-bookkeeping-with-bank-feeds-2021/</guid>
      <description>This course is a project based course that will dive into bank feeds in detail using a step by step process. We will start by setting up a free 30 day trial QuickBooks Online QBO file for the practice problem. Intuit, the owner of QuickBooks Online QBO, often offers a free 30 day trial period, a great tool for practice. The course will demonstrate how to link QuickBooks Online QBO to the bank to receive bank data directly from the bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master React Redux via Real world analogy &amp; Building Project</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-react-redux-via-real-world-analogy-building-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 13:37:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-react-redux-via-real-world-analogy-building-project/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you will Learn React Redux in the most simple way through real world example and hands-on project based approach.
Following are the topics we will cover:
1.1-What is Redux
1.2-Redux real world explanation
1.3-Installing nodejs and VS code
1.4-Creating new react application
1.5-Code cleanup
1.6-Understanding React application flow and JSX
1.7-Installing the required npm packages
1.8-Redux lifecycle
1.9-Creating the required folders
2.1-Creating Actions and Action constants
2.2-Creating product reducer</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP y MYSQL: Convierte cualquier template HTML en una WebAPP</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/php-y-mysql-convierte-cualquier-template-html-en-una-webapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 19:59:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/php-y-mysql-convierte-cualquier-template-html-en-una-webapp/</guid>
      <description>Este curso se enfoca en enseñar como convertir una plantilla HTML a una aplicación con PHP, usando MySQL como base de datos. Internet se ha convertido en el mecanismo que utilizamos a diario para trabajar, estudiar, comunicarnos con otras personas, realizar compras, entre otras. Todo esto lo realizamos por medio de la web, la cual funciona por medio de documentos que se enlazan por medio de un servidor y se proyectan en un navegador web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master C&#43;&#43; Programming From Beginner To Advance - C&#43;&#43; Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-c-programming-from-beginner-to-advance-c-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 17:51:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-c-programming-from-beginner-to-advance-c-course/</guid>
      <description>Master C++ Programming From Beginner To Advance - C++ Course
C++ Programming , C++ Tutorial, C++ Lecture, C++ Course
Concepts of C++ Programming are made very simple and easy.
Course Highlights
Explained each topic with help of picture and example.
Practical Session for each Topic
3-Projects - ATM system, Student Management &amp;amp; Hacking Tool - keylogger in C++
Mind-map
Notes - ppt
100+ MCQ&#39;s
15 Assignments
Interview Preparation ( Top Frequently asked Questions )</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Reddit bots with Python: Beginner to Advanced</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-reddit-bots-with-python-beginner-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 14:54:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-reddit-bots-with-python-beginner-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Join the most comprehensive Reddit Bot Python course on Udemy and learn how to build amazing real-world use Reddit Bots!
This is the only pure Reddit Bot Course on Udemy and will guide you through various interesting and practical projects with a code-along structure course style. Along the way, you will learn how to build your own Reddit Bots and utilise them in real world situations.
After completing this course you will be able to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creación de API REST Web Service con Python y MySQL</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/creaci%C3%B3n-de-api-rest-web-service-con-python-y-mysql/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 22:42:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/creaci%C3%B3n-de-api-rest-web-service-con-python-y-mysql/</guid>
      <description>¿Qué es Python?
Python es un lenguaje de programación interpretado cuya filosofía hace hincapié en la legibilidad de su código.​ Se trata de un lenguaje de programación multiparadigma, ya que soporta parcialmente la orientación a objetos, programación imperativa y, en menor medida, programación funcional
¡En este curso aprenderás a crear webservices con Python y MySQL!
Al realizar este curso de Python aprenderás los fundamentos de Python desde el principio. No requiere ningún conocimiento previo en Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python And Flask Framework Complete Course For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/python-and-flask-framework-complete-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 18:19:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/python-and-flask-framework-complete-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Learn Python From Scratch
I’ve created thorough, extensive, but easy to follow content which you’ll easily understand and absorb.
The course starts with the basics, including Python fundamentals, programming, and user interaction.
The curriculum is going to be very hands-on as we walk you from start to finish becoming a professional Python developer. We will start from the very beginning by teaching you Python basics and programming fundamentals, and then going into advanced topics and different career fields in Python so you can get real-life practice and be ready for the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CRUD con PHP, MySQL y JS en el Modelo MVC</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crud-con-php-mysql-y-js-en-el-modelo-mvc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 21:19:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crud-con-php-mysql-y-js-en-el-modelo-mvc/</guid>
      <description>Bienvenido al curso del desarrollo de un CRUD(Create,Read,Update,Delete) en PHP POO, PDO, MySQL, JQuery Ajax, Json, Bootstrap, vas a aprender paso a paso como desarrollar un CRUD desde cero y lo podrás ver en cualquier dispositivo móvil con responsive design.Vas a aprender como desarrollar sistemas de control de contenidos utilizando el lenguaje de programación más popular y con más oportunidades de trabajo PHP, trabajaremos con la programación orientada a Objetos, PDO (PHP Data Objects) y el gestor de base de datos MySql, para el diseño y la administración de las tablas de la base de datos trabajaremos con la herramienta PhpMyadmin, utilizaremos HTML5, CSS3 para el diseño de las vistas de las páginas web del proyecto, también vamos a trabajar con el framework Bootstrap para hacer más fácil nuestro diseño web, usaremos la librería JQuery y JS, la tecnología Ajax y Json para hacer dinámico nuestras páginas del proyecto web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JAVA - Job Interview Preparation</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/java-job-interview-preparation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 13:35:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/java-job-interview-preparation/</guid>
      <description>Looking for an perfect job interview preparation? Searching in the web brings you only partial information? Congrats! You found what you are looking for!
Do you have a job interview related to JAVA? If you can answer this question with a yes, you are in the absolute perfect place.
This course provides you 2 different job interview preparation. As we have deep insides in different industries, we know exactly what matters contentwise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving software development productivity</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/improving-software-development-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 16:23:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/improving-software-development-productivity/</guid>
      <description>What will be in the course:​
Personal experience;​
How I structured the work in my team;​
What my team and I use;​
What are the alternatives to my tools;​
Which helped speed up development.​
What this course will not include:​
A huge amount of theory;​
Calculations that prove how to design;​
Imposing opinions and proving that problems need to be solved only this way and nothing else.​
As a result, this course will be useful not only for the technical leader of the development group, but also for managers of different levels, developers and testers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce Certified Platform Developer I Practice Exams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/salesforce-certified-platform-developer-i-practice-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 13:12:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/salesforce-certified-platform-developer-i-practice-exams/</guid>
      <description>In this course, I fully prepare you for what it is like to take the Salesforce Certified Platform Developer I Exam. With 2 practice exams, each of which is timed, I have carefully hand-crafted each question to put you to the test.
I have followed the official Exam Guide from Salesforce Certified Platform Developer I, along with the all Knowledge Areas and corresponding weighting for each, so you can approach the actual Salesforce Certified Platform Developer I Exam with confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT Fundamentals Information Technology Essentials IT Support</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/it-fundamentals-information-technology-essentials-it-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 14:59:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/it-fundamentals-information-technology-essentials-it-support/</guid>
      <description>IT Fundamentals Information Technology Essentials IT Support
Information Technology fundamentals IT Fundamentals CompTIA IT Fundamentals IT Fundamentals IT Support Desktop Support Computer Hardware Computer Architecture IT Fundamentals Information Technology Essentials Computer Network Computer Science its great information about Information Technology and Computer &#39;science which help you learn about Modern area of Computer and Information Technology IT Fundamentals Information Technology Essentials IT Support
IT Support IT Fundamentals Desktop Support Computer Architecture IT Support Computer Organization Computer Hardware Instruction Set Architecture</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OBS Studio - Ultimate Livestreaming Guide to OBS Studio</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/obs-studio-ultimate-livestreaming-guide-to-obs-studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 12:00:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/obs-studio-ultimate-livestreaming-guide-to-obs-studio/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to OBS Studio - Ultimate Livestreaming Guide to OBS Studio!
Nick Nyxson here, your instructor.
In this course, you will learn how to start using Open Broadcaster Software (OBS Studio) for Livestreaming on Twitch, YouTube, Mixer, and other platforms, even if you have no idea where to start.
In this course You Will Learn:
Which version of OBS Studio (Open Broadcaster Software) You need to use;
How to download OBS Studio;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>¡Curso Profesional Excel 2021– Para Empresas!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-profesional-excel-2021-para-empresas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-profesional-excel-2021-para-empresas/</guid>
      <description>El curso te proporciona los cimientos que todo Profesional Excel debe poseer. Obtendrás un vasto conocimiento lleno de recursos y estarás capacitado para hacer frente a cualquier tarea en Excel de una manera eficaz y productiva.
Al terminar el curso, habrás dominado Excel y nada te será desconocido para empezar a trabajar como todo un Profesional.
El curso Incluye:
⭐ Más de 8 Horas de Contenido Exclusivo
⭐ Tareas Prácticas Al Final de Cada Capitulo (Desafíos)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>مهارات معالجة الكلمات باستخدام مايكروسوفت وورد 2016</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D9%85%D9%87%D8%A7%D8%B1%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D9%85%D8%B9%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AC%D8%A9-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%83%D9%84%D9%85%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D8%A8%D8%A7%D8%B3%D8%AA%D8%AE%D8%AF%D8%A7%D9%85-%D9%85%D8%A7%D9%8A%D9%83%D8%B1%D9%88%D8%B3%D9%88%D9%81%D8%AA-%D9%88%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%AF-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D9%85%D9%87%D8%A7%D8%B1%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D9%85%D8%B9%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AC%D8%A9-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%83%D9%84%D9%85%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D8%A8%D8%A7%D8%B3%D8%AA%D8%AE%D8%AF%D8%A7%D9%85-%D9%85%D8%A7%D9%8A%D9%83%D8%B1%D9%88%D8%B3%D9%88%D9%81%D8%AA-%D9%88%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%AF-2016/</guid>
      <description>يهدف هذا البرنامج إلى إكساب المشاركين المهارات الأساسية في استخدام برنامج معالجة الكلمات &#34;مايكروسوفت وورد&#34;، في إنشاء المستندات وتنسيق النصوص وإخراج المستندات بشكل جذاب ومنظم، من خلال التعرف على عمليات التحرير في المستند (تحديد، نسخ، قص، لصق) وكذلك عمليات التنسيق في المستند (تنسيق الخط، تنسيق الفقرة، تنسيق التعداد) والالوان والحدود للخطوط والنصوص المستخدمة في المستند، كذلك تصميم الجداول وتنسيقها، وإدراج الرسوم والصور والأشكال الذكية والهياكل التنظيمية إلى غير ذلك من أدوات الرسم والأشكال الأخرى، فضلاً عن مراجعة المستند والترجمة ومعرفة عدد الكلمات والفقرات في المستند وأدوات المراجعة الأخرى، وبنهاية التدريب سيتمكن المشاركون من:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon EKS Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/amazon-eks-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/amazon-eks-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to do use Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service but don&#39;t know where to start?	Would you like to make amazing Kubernetes applications in AWS Cloud or on-premise and bring your ideas to life?	Then Amazon EKS Ultimate Course is for you!	Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.	Amazon EKS is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Redshift Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/amazon-redshift-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/amazon-redshift-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to do use Amazon Redshift but don&#39;t know where to start?	Would you like to access data lakes and bring your data to life?	Then Amazon Redshift Ultimate Course is for you!	Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Amazon Redshift is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. We&#39;ll Cover everything you need to know about Amazon Redshift from scratch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Key DAX functions in POWER BI</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/understanding-key-dax-functions-in-power-bi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/understanding-key-dax-functions-in-power-bi/</guid>
      <description>Course covers different functions that are used in day to day reporting development and is helpful to understand the core concepts of these DAX functions. The videos are precise to topic and no additional information is covered other than the topic itself. ** This is not recommended for you , if you are already good at DAX and understand the core DAX functionality , as this course is designed for who wanted to explore the KEY DAX functions and just getting to learn DAX.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tout connaître sur PowerPoint</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tout-conna%C3%AEtre-sur-powerpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tout-conna%C3%AEtre-sur-powerpoint/</guid>
      <description>Avec 4 projets d&#39;applications, plus de 47 vidéos, 10 questionnaires ce cours est incontestablement le plus complet pour tout apprendre sur PowerPoint ! Vous apprendrez toutes les fonctionnalités de PowerPoint, des techniques pour être plus productif et surtout les bases du design de présentations pour captiver votre auditoire !
Le ton pédagogique est de mise, chaque notion est étudiée trois fois sous différentes formes (vidéos théoriques, projet simple et projet complexe), des adresses de contact sont disponibles pour les moindres questions sans oublier les questionnaires qui vous permettront de valider vos compétences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lua&#39;s Core Syntax (Programming Language)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/luas-core-syntax-programming-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/luas-core-syntax-programming-language/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you&#39;ll learn about Lua&#39;s Core Syntax.
In each lecture, I&#39;ll discuss a few lines of code explaining a concept. Over in the lecture resources, you&#39;ll be linked to the code, which you can fork, run, &amp;amp; alter to complete some easy exercises.
I&#39;m using an online IDE called replit. This means that you can start coding right away and learn easily, even on your tablet or smartphone. Don’t waste time setting up your environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Beginner Guide to Streamlabs OBS (OBS)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-beginner-guide-to-streamlabs-obs-obs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-beginner-guide-to-streamlabs-obs-obs/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Ultimate Beginner Guide to Streamlabs OBS (OBS)!
Nick Nyxson here, Your Instructor for this course.
In this course, you will learn how to start using Streamlabs OBS which is live streaming software made by Streamlabs and is a modified version of Open Broadcaster Software (OBS).
In this course You Will Learn:
What is SLOBS (Streamlabs OBS);
How Streamlabs OBS is any different from OBS Studio;
Streamlabs OBS Settings Walkthrough;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science Real World Projects in Python</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/data-science-real-world-projects-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/data-science-real-world-projects-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to land a top-paying job in Data Science?
Or are you a seasoned AI practitioner who want to take your career to the next level?
Or are you an aspiring data scientist who wants to get Hands-on Data Science and Artificial Intelligence?
If the answer is yes to any of these questions, then this course is for you!
Data Science is one of the hottest tech fields to be in right now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qt 6 Core Advanced with C&#43;&#43;</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/qt-6-core-advanced-with-c-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/qt-6-core-advanced-with-c-/</guid>
      <description>This is not a beginners course! This is an advanced Qt 6 course using C++ to create high performance applications on Windows, Mac and Linux. This course also includes advanced topics such as threading, networking, libraries, plugins, databases, unit testing, and application deployment.
This is a followup to the Udemy Qt 5 Core for beginners and intermediate courses and picks up where they both left off. It is highly recommended to take those courses before attempting this one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qt 6 Core Beginners with C&#43;&#43;</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/qt-6-core-beginners-with-c-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/qt-6-core-beginners-with-c-/</guid>
      <description>Learn cross platform programming with Qt and C++, write once, build anywhere – Qt runs on virtually anything. You probably have applications built with Qt running on your computer, smart phone, television, and other electronics.
No experience necessary, this is a beginners course that will teach you the foundations of both Qt 6 and C++. This course is meant as a direct replacement for an introduction to C++ class. This course starts off with simple topics such as &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Web- The complete Introduction to the hidden web</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/deep-web-the-complete-introduction-to-the-hidden-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/deep-web-the-complete-introduction-to-the-hidden-web/</guid>
      <description>Have you heard many times about the deep/dark web but you never knew what it is. Or you you have an Idea of what is it but you never visited this part of the web. Then this course for you. You will learn all the basics of the deep/dark and how to access this part of the web. At the end of the course, you will be able to use the TOR browser as your default browser and surf on all the parts of the Web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build and Deploy Dialogflow Chatbot Waitress Lilis</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/build-and-deploy-dialogflow-chatbot-waitress-lilis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/build-and-deploy-dialogflow-chatbot-waitress-lilis/</guid>
      <description>This course provides a step-by-step guild to create a chatbot waitress Lilis who works at a coffee shop using Dialogflow.
You will learn how to design the architecture of a chatbot
the 7 Minimum-Viable-Product Features of a chatbot waiter
modify Default Welcome and Fallback Intents for chatbot&#39;s purpose
code fulfillment and webhook with javascript to handle intents for taking customer orders
code fulfillment webhook for product availability check
code follow-up intents to handle user responses: yes, no, or change</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Programming Full Course for Beginners 2021 ( Hindi )</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/python-programming-full-course-for-beginners-2021-hindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/python-programming-full-course-for-beginners-2021-hindi/</guid>
      <description>Full Course OF Python With HD Practical Video. Self Placed Videos.
Python3 We will Learn In This Course.
VS Code IDE We will Use For Python Coding.
Udemy Verified Course Completion Certificate.
Lifetime Access of all the Course Content.
All the Videos Explanation in Hindi .
Guaranteed Instructor Support.
This Course Fully Beginners Course
After Complete This Course You Will Become Master In Python
Q&amp;amp;A Forum where you can post your doubts for any given particular lecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Architecture: 8 Crucial Software Architecture KPIs!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/software-architecture-8-crucial-software-architecture-kpis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/software-architecture-8-crucial-software-architecture-kpis/</guid>
      <description>Are your systems build for change? Are you measuring technical debt?Are you suffering from low developer productivity?Did you know that secure software follows software quality? If you can not answer these questions, this course is made for you! Within one hour you will understand the most important software quality concepts essential for software architects. This knowledge is essential for software quality assurance.
Can you explain this without showing code?Yes. The software quality concepts are technology independent and are explained by making use of analogies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin blockchain - Under the hood for beginners.</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bitcoin-blockchain-under-the-hood-for-beginners./</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bitcoin-blockchain-under-the-hood-for-beginners./</guid>
      <description>In this course you will learn how bitcoin blockchain works internally and technical concepts which people generally don&#39;t know.
Topics you will learn are :
Bitcoin Introduction
Addresses - Private key and public address
How to generate addresses.
Who are miners?
Proof of work
What makes blockchain so secure.
Ways to buy and sell bitcoin.
Merits and demerits of using online exchanges
Other Applications of blockchain.
Analysis of latest block of bitcoin blockchain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Python 3 Programming for the Absolute Beginner</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/starting-python-3-programming-for-the-absolute-beginner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/starting-python-3-programming-for-the-absolute-beginner/</guid>
      <description>Python is the fastest programming language out there!It is popular among developers, hobbyists, data scientists and is the language of choice of the big tech companies.
For beginners that want to learn Python in a structured way, it can be confusing to find a great resource that teaches you Python step-by-step from the ground up covering fundamentals to give you a strong foundation to grow from.
Searching for good material online often takes hours and hours and this course is meant to make it easy for you, save time and get you proficient in Python as quickly as possible in a hands-on way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python For Absolute Beginners : Learn Python From Scratch</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/python-for-absolute-beginners-learn-python-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:47:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/python-for-absolute-beginners-learn-python-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>There is no doubt that Python is the most popular programming language at the moment. Python is used in Machine Learning, Data Science, Web Development and almost all the areas of Software Development. If you want to learn Python and don&#39;t know how to start, then this course is for you. This course is designed for complete beginners.
Ratings: 4.14/5
Enrollments: 25206
Coupon Code: 45B5C0549D3571620CD9
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker - Almost Complete Guide with Hands-On for 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/docker-almost-complete-guide-with-hands-on-for-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/docker-almost-complete-guide-with-hands-on-for-2021/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to take your DevOps skills and career to the next level, take this course now!
You will go from zero to Docker hero in couple of hours.
Why choosing this course?
This course is very hands on, Himanshu has put lots effort to provide you with not only the theory but also real-life examples of developing Docker applications that you can try out on your own laptop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helm 3 - Package Manager For Kubernetes for 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/helm-3-package-manager-for-kubernetes-for-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/helm-3-package-manager-for-kubernetes-for-2021/</guid>
      <description>What you&#39;ll learn
Working with Helm Charts and Releases
Helm Architecture and concepts
Create custom Helm Charts and Deploy applications to Kubernetes using Helm
Working with Stable and Custom Helm Charts
Create Automated Kubernetes Deployments with Helm
Helm package manager installation and configuration
Working with Chartmuseum Repository
Expert Secrets from Industry - master troubleshooting tricks that you won’t find anywhere else
Description
You will learn all the required topics as given below for HELM - The Package Manager for Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes: CKA/CKAD, Production Grade Course for 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kubernetes-cka/ckad-production-grade-course-for-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kubernetes-cka/ckad-production-grade-course-for-2021/</guid>
      <description>In this Course you are going to learn most of the things which everyone is looking for. This course will help you in understading production environment and i have capture most of the things in the course which you going to face in the Interview and while working in production. Like what are the options we can use to create a cluster, Like Kubeadm, KOPS, Rancher, K3s, EKS . Have almost covered from the Installation to deploying the applications and securing them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angular Material Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/angular-material-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/angular-material-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to do use Angular Material but don&#39;t know where to start? Would you like to learn components and bring Angular Material Code to Life? Then Angular Material Ultimate Course is for you! Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course. Angular Material is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. We&#39;ll Cover everything you need to know about Angular Material from scratch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Processing Real-World Projects in Python</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/natural-language-processing-real-world-projects-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/natural-language-processing-real-world-projects-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to land a top-paying job in Data Science , AI &amp;amp; Natural Language Processing?
Or are you a seasoned AI practitioner who want to take your career to the next level?
Or are you an aspiring data scientist who wants to get Hands-on Data Science and Artificial Intelligence?
If the answer is yes to any of these questions, then this course is for you!
Data Science is one of the hottest tech fields to be in right now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>أسرع دورة لتعلم مايكروسوفت ورد من البداية (Word 2019)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%A3%D8%B3%D8%B1%D8%B9-%D8%AF%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%A9-%D9%84%D8%AA%D8%B9%D9%84%D9%85-%D9%85%D8%A7%D9%8A%D9%83%D8%B1%D9%88%D8%B3%D9%88%D9%81%D8%AA-%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%AF-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A8%D8%AF%D8%A7%D9%8A%D8%A9-word-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%A3%D8%B3%D8%B1%D8%B9-%D8%AF%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%A9-%D9%84%D8%AA%D8%B9%D9%84%D9%85-%D9%85%D8%A7%D9%8A%D9%83%D8%B1%D9%88%D8%B3%D9%88%D9%81%D8%AA-%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%AF-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A8%D8%AF%D8%A7%D9%8A%D8%A9-word-2019/</guid>
      <description>تعلم مايكروسوفت ورد من البداية حتي الاحتراف (Word 2019)
هو كورس مناسب للجميع من المستوي المبتدئ وحتي المستوي المتوسط ، حيث أن الشرح يبدأ معك خطوة بخطوة من الصفر ويضعك علي بداية طريق الإحتراف. الكورس مخصص لكل شخص يحب أن يتعلم أو يرغب بتطوير مهاراته في برنامج مايكروسوفت ورد. ويهدف إلي مساعدة جميع المتعاملين مع تكنولوجيا المعلومات نحو سهولة استخدام و بداية احتراف برنامج مايكروسوفت ورد.
في هذه الدورة سوف تتعلم أساسيات مايكروسوفت ورد ثم ستتعرف على الأدوات الرئيسية التي يجب استخدامها لإنشاء ملفات ورد ، ثم ستتعرف علي أبسط طرق تنسيق المستندات الخاصة بك ، ثم ستتعرف علي طرق إضافة الصور والجداول وغيرها من العناصر ، ثم ضبط حجم الصفحة و أبعادها ، و أخيرا الإعدادات المختلفة لطباعة المستنات.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>تعلم برمجة تطبيقات الموبايل للمبتدئين</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%AA%D8%B9%D9%84%D9%85-%D8%A8%D8%B1%D9%85%D8%AC%D8%A9-%D8%AA%D8%B7%D8%A8%D9%8A%D9%82%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D9%88%D8%A8%D8%A7%D9%8A%D9%84-%D9%84%D9%84%D9%85%D8%A8%D8%AA%D8%AF%D8%A6%D9%8A%D9%86/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%AA%D8%B9%D9%84%D9%85-%D8%A8%D8%B1%D9%85%D8%AC%D8%A9-%D8%AA%D8%B7%D8%A8%D9%8A%D9%82%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D9%88%D8%A8%D8%A7%D9%8A%D9%84-%D9%84%D9%84%D9%85%D8%A8%D8%AA%D8%AF%D8%A6%D9%8A%D9%86/</guid>
      <description>تطبقات الموبايل هي نوع من أنواع البرمجيات التي يتم تشغيلها على الموبايل أو التابلت أو الساعات الرقمية و التي تعد من أحدث أنواع البرمجياتو هناك نوعان من أنواع أنظمة التشغيل الخاصة بالموبايل (الاندرويد و الاي أو اس).
في هذه الدورة التدريبية سوف نتعلم كيفية تطوير برامج للموبايل بطريقة سهلة و مبسرة و لا تحتاج إلى أي خبرة سابقة بالبرمجة سوف نستخدم برنامج MIT App Inventor في تطوير برامج الموبايل و الذي تم تصميمه من جامعة MIT و شركة Google العالمية.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Bootcamp 2021 Build 15 working Applications and Games</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/python-bootcamp-2021-build-15-working-applications-and-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/python-bootcamp-2021-build-15-working-applications-and-games/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of getting videos and lectures on just python basics and syntaxes or just strucked in college studies and hello world program. so I guess you have to give a try to this course this course is designed after analysing what a student need to study python. After analysing what they required and what they want in a course, how they can easily start any course but didn&#39;t able to finish it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create own Artificial Neural Network in Python</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-own-artificial-neural-network-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-own-artificial-neural-network-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Artificial neural networks (ANNs), also known as neural networks (NNs), are computer systems that are modelled after the biological neural networks that make up animal brains.
In this course ,we will learn to create our own neural networks with python.
Details are:
Introduction to artificial neural network
Python basics
Let&#39;s understand algorithm
Implement ANN in python
Wrapping up
Introduction to artificial neural network: Artificial neural networks simulates the functioning of human brain .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linkerd - Service mesh for Kubernetes - 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/linkerd-service-mesh-for-kubernetes-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/linkerd-service-mesh-for-kubernetes-2021/</guid>
      <description>A different kind of service mesh
Ultra light, ultra simple, ultra powerful. Linkerd adds security, observability, and reliability to Kubernetes, without the complexity. CNCF-hosted and 100% open source.
Instant platform health metrics
Instantly track success rates, latencies, and request volumes for every meshed workload, without changes or config.
Simpler than any other mesh
Minimalist, Kubernetes-native design. No hidden magic, as little YAML and as few CRDs as possible.
Zero-config mutual TLS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETHICAL HACKING IN TAMIL</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ethical-hacking-in-tamil/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ethical-hacking-in-tamil/</guid>
      <description>In This Course You Will be Taught many Hacking Demonstration Like Android Hacking,Instagram Hacking, Wifi Hacking and Cybersecurity Related Challenges like CTF etc.
Know The Some Basics
What is Ethical Hacking?
Ethical Hacking sometimes called as Penetration Testing is an act of intruding/penetrating into system or networks to find out threats, vulnerabilities in those systems which a malicious attacker may find and exploit causing loss of data, financial loss or other major damages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MS Word for Novice to Expert : 2021 Updated</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ms-word-for-novice-to-expert-2021-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ms-word-for-novice-to-expert-2021-updated/</guid>
      <description>An ultimate course for novice who want to learn basic MS Word. This course will help you to have clear concept of using MS Word. After complete this course using of MS Word will be very easy and friendly to you. This course focused from beginner level to advance level and its covered up with almost every major part of MS Word for using in personal and business uses. Ratings: 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python And Flask Framework Complete Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/python-and-flask-framework-complete-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/python-and-flask-framework-complete-course/</guid>
      <description>This course is a depth introduction to fundamental python programming concepts.
Learn Python From Beginner To Advanced Level
I’ve created thorough, extensive, but easy to follow content which you’ll easily understand and absorb.
The course starts with the basics, including Python fundamentals, programming, and user interaction.
The curriculum is going to be very hands-on as we walk you from start to finish becoming a professional Python developer. We will start from the very beginning by teaching you Python basics and programming fundamentals, and then going into advanced topics and different career fields in Python so you can get real-life practice and be ready for the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI (Artificial Intelligence) for CXOs &amp; Senior Managers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ai-artificial-intelligence-for-cxos-senior-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ai-artificial-intelligence-for-cxos-senior-managers/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;This course covers concepts &amp;amp; case studies for executives and senior managers to better understand AI. This course doesn&#39;t cover programming aspects of AI&amp;gt;
Demystifying Artificial Intelligence including ML, DL, NLP, Industry 4.0, IoT &amp;amp; RPA with Caselets for CxOs and Senior Managers.
AI, AI, AI Everywhere! If you don’t do something about AI, you will be left behind or disrupted into extinction – this is a message that executives, Managers, Team Leaders and CXOs often hear, especially in the last year or so from consultants, vendors, industry experts or the IT organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Foundation</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/devops-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/devops-foundation/</guid>
      <description>If you are new to DevOps, this course will give you the basic information about DevOps, including key concepts and the terminologies. This course covers the DevOps Full Stack: People and Culture, Processes and Practices, Technology and Automation. People and Culture:
You will be able to summarize the cultural, structural, and technological barriers that IT faces, when attempting to deliver services at the right quality, speed, and cost, and why challenges are faced when implementing DevOps in today’s organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mathematics &amp; Statistics for Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mathematics-statistics-for-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mathematics-statistics-for-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;This course doesn&#39;t cover programming related to AI but helps you to build a strong foundation in math &amp;amp; statistics needed for AI&amp;gt;
The trainer of this course is an AI expert and he has observed that many students and young professionals make the mistake of learning machine learning without understanding the core concepts in maths and statistics. This course will help to address that gap in a big way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
