<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Video &amp; Mobile Marketing on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/video-mobile-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Video &amp; Mobile Marketing on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/video-mobile-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Video Production, Video Marketing, &amp; YouTube Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-video-production-video-marketing-youtube-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-video-production-video-marketing-youtube-course/</guid>
      <description>Become a filmmaker, upgrade your lifestyle, travel the world, and tap into the fastest growing, most profitable media income stream around with this POWERFUL Step-By-Step Guide to Video Production and Video Marketing... Just one well-made video could turnaround your business, bringing you a slew of new customers, boosting your sales, social media followers and sign ups, and helping you hit those all-important first page spots on Google and YouTube...
Dear Students,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn 10 Ways to Make MORE Money on YouTube!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-10-ways-to-make-more-money-on-youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 13:24:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-10-ways-to-make-more-money-on-youtube/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to make money on YouTube even while you are sleeping?
The work that you do today can make you money for months and years to come!
In this YouTube Audience Growth course, you&#39;ll learn at least 5 Ways to Make Money on YouTube.
You&#39;ll learn how to attract 1,000,000&#39;s of Views and Grow Your YouTube Channel Into a MONEY-MAKING MACHINE
I published some videos back in 2017 and they are still generating me money EVERY.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Branded TV Channel Creation (Neon Edition 2021)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/online-branded-tv-channel-creation-neon-edition-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/online-branded-tv-channel-creation-neon-edition-2021/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the seventh course in Term 3 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
You&#39;ll totally love this course.
Know that this course focussing on &#34;Online Branded TV Channel Creation (Neon 2021 Edition)&#34; created by Digital Marketing Legend &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34; can redefine inbound marketing and Online TV Channel Creation - altogether. Do you know about the growth of internet television in 2021? It&#39;s unexplained and the answer is &#39;tremendous&#39;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viral YouTube Marketing - Crash Course (2021 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/viral-youtube-marketing-crash-course-2021-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/viral-youtube-marketing-crash-course-2021-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the fifth course in Term 1 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Did you know? 
Millions of videos are uploaded to YouTube on a daily basis. YouTube seems the greatest place to grow your own brand, drive traffic to your website, and earn money from ads (leveraging AdSense) that are generated through advertisers who bid on Google and your product and service promotions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Thumbnail Masterclass / Ultimate to Guide Thumbnails</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/youtube-thumbnail-masterclass-/-ultimate-to-guide-thumbnails/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/youtube-thumbnail-masterclass-/-ultimate-to-guide-thumbnails/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s not a secret to anyone anymore. YouTube Thumbnails matter. A lot. It&#39;s the first thing people see when browsing YouTube and it&#39;s what will make them click on your video to watch it or not. It can mean the difference between a million views and no views. YouTube thumbnails are often the most influential factor in determining whether or not viewers will watch your video. This is because it&#39;s the first thing they see when browsing YouTube and is what will make them click on it to watch or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Youtube Business Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/youtube-business-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:47:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/youtube-business-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Youtube is the most popular video-streaming service boasting massive online traffic and constant streaming services.
And it’s the second most-visited website on the Internet with nearly 2 billion monthly users logging on to watch videos every day.
Youtube channel can maximize exposure and help your brand become recognized within your market.
It’s a great way to connect with your audience and keep them engaged for longer periods of time, while encouraging repeat traffic and views.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified YouTube Marketing Professional | CPD Accredited</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/certified-youtube-marketing-professional-cpd-accredited/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/certified-youtube-marketing-professional-cpd-accredited/</guid>
      <description>Two YouTube Marketing Certificates for the Price of One! Finish your Udemy course and Contact us to get your Continuing Professional Development (CPD) Certificate! Check out &#34;This is How You Earn Your CPD Accrdeited Certificate!&#34; Lecture for more information!

Doing business with YouTube has become the best technique for success, hungry marketers, to make the most from their marketing efforts, and if not given adequate importance to, it can prove fatal for your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Gain More Customers With Video Marketing</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-gain-more-customers-with-video-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-gain-more-customers-with-video-marketing/</guid>
      <description>In recent years, we can see the emergence of many websites on the Internet and even more intense competition between these sites. Everyone is trying to make their website better and more attractive than the competitor&#39;s, but still, everyone uses the same methods and tools to promote their business.
But many people forget about another very effective method, like video marketing, in which video is the main tool for promoting a business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Marketing 2021: Strategies and Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/youtube-marketing-2021-strategies-and-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/youtube-marketing-2021-strategies-and-growth/</guid>
      <description>When you take this course, we will start you from an idea that you want to do YouTube video marketing and we will end with you crafting a professional YouTube channel as well as a strategy for how you will use it.&amp;nbsp;
Boomy and Lara are both internet marketing professionals committed to helping guide you with videos demonstrating the best and the worst in YouTube. We wanted this to be a course that you could watch while you work on your own channel, so it may take longer then the hour of video content.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>