<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Video &amp; Mobile Marketing on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/video-mobile-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Video &amp; Mobile Marketing on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/video-mobile-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Online Branded TV Channel Creation (Neon Edition 2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/online-branded-tv-channel-creation-neon-edition-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/online-branded-tv-channel-creation-neon-edition-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this mind-blowing course. You&#39;ll totally love this course and the concepts taught here.
Know that this course focussing on &#34;Online Branded TV Channel Creation (Neon 2022 Edition)&#34; created by Digital Marketing Legend &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34; can redefine inbound marketing and Online TV Channel Creation - altogether. Do you know about the growth of internet television in 2022? It&#39;s unexplained and the answer is &#39;tremendous&#39;.
Historically, television has been a broadcast medium where everyone picks from a very small number of channels - until Now !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viral YouTube Marketing - Crash Course &#43; Live Class</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/viral-youtube-marketing-crash-course--live-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/viral-youtube-marketing-crash-course--live-class/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Viral YouTube Marketing - Crash Course (2022 Grand Edition)&#34;.
Did you know? Millions of videos are uploaded to YouTube on a daily basis. YouTube seems the greatest place to grow your own brand, drive traffic to your website, and earn money from ads (leveraging AdSense) that are generated through advertisers who bid on Google and your product and service promotions. And this superb course is the perfect one for you to kickstart your own YouTube Channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Production - Inexpensive Talking Head Video - Business</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-production-inexpensive-talking-head-video-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-production-inexpensive-talking-head-video-business/</guid>
      <description>Video Production can be time-consuming, difficult, technical and expensive, but it doesn&#39;t have to be. This video production course is about how to do simple, easy talking head videos for a wide range of business communication needs. There is a video explosion going on in the online world. Are you missing out? Are you unsure where to start? This course will lead you through the simplest and easiest ways to start communicating with your customers, clients, prospects and colleagues in the most effective manner: talking head video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Production, YouTube Marketing, &amp; Video Marketing Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-production-youtube-marketing-video-marketing-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-production-youtube-marketing-video-marketing-guide/</guid>
      <description>Become a filmmaker, upgrade your lifestyle, travel the world, and tap into the fastest growing, most profitable media income stream around with this Powerful Step-by-Step Guide to Video Production and YouTube Marketing... Just one well-made video could turnaround your business, bringing you a slew of new customers, boosting your sales, social media followers and sign ups, and helping you hit those all-important first page spots on Google and YouTube...
The Complete Video Production &amp;amp; YouTube Marketing Course was updated with: Animated videos</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn 10 Ways to Make MORE Money on YouTube!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-10-ways-to-make-more-money-on-youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-10-ways-to-make-more-money-on-youtube/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to make money on YouTube even while you are sleeping?
The work that you do today can make you money for months and years to come!
In this YouTube Audience Growth course, you&#39;ll learn at least 5 Ways to Make Money on YouTube.
You&#39;ll learn how to attract 1,000,000&#39;s of Views and Grow Your YouTube Channel Into a MONEY-MAKING MACHINE
I published some videos back in 2017 and they are still generating me money EVERY.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Facebook Event Ad, Youtube Channel &amp; Google Ad 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/run-facebook-event-ad-youtube-channel-google-ad-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 20:12:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/run-facebook-event-ad-youtube-channel-google-ad-2022/</guid>
      <description>This course is designed to teach you from scratch every single thing I have done or currently doing related to my own youtube channels and how I to setup your facebook page, First google ad and facebook events ad.
1) Setup Youtube channel 2) Create Facebook Page
3) Create facebook events ad
4) Run google search Ad
This is a beginner&#39;s course so please check course content before you enroll!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tubebuddy Masterclass - Guide to YouTube Keyword Tool</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tubebuddy-masterclass-guide-to-youtube-keyword-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tubebuddy-masterclass-guide-to-youtube-keyword-tool/</guid>
      <description>Finally, a YouTube Channel Management Tool That Makes Creating &amp;amp; Growing A YouTube Channel Fun &amp;amp; Easy!
With a good YouTube channel management tool, you can have a complete overview of your channel&#39;s analytics. You can easily see which videos are performing best, which ones need improvement and what your audience is most interested in. And it is completely free!
Tubebuddy is a revolutionary new YouTube creation tool that was designed to make it easier for creators on the platform to grow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence Powered Audiobook Creation Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-powered-audiobook-creation-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-powered-audiobook-creation-course/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Artificial Intelligence Powered Audiobook Creation Course&#34;
If you know Siri, Cortana from Microsoft, Denise from Nextos, Alexa from Amazon or those handy voice GPS directions on smartphones, then congrats! You’re already acquainted with TTS. This course will just help you bridge the gap through an ocean of knowledge with the power of Artificial intelligence based TTS tools.
Text to speech, abbreviated as TTS, is a synthesis of speech that transforms text into voice output.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Thumbnail Masterclass - Quadruple Your Video Views</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-thumbnail-masterclass-quadruple-your-video-views/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:57:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-thumbnail-masterclass-quadruple-your-video-views/</guid>
      <description>Only 1% of YouTube thumbnails succeed.
They:
Attract attention
Grab views
Convince people to subscribe
Make the channel money
Turn YouTubers into superstars
You can achieve all this with your own thumbnails and join the elite 1%.
But how?
By learning:
The importance of thumbnails
How to create a thumbnail that “Sells-the-click”
The theory behind attractive thumbnail design
How to use Cavna (free) quickly and efficiently to create impactful thumbnails</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Como crear y configurar tu canal de Youtube desde cero 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/como-crear-y-configurar-tu-canal-de-youtube-desde-cero-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 21:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/como-crear-y-configurar-tu-canal-de-youtube-desde-cero-2022/</guid>
      <description>Como crear y configurar tu canal de Youtube desde cero
Crea y configura tu canal de Youtube desde cero, sube videos de la manera correcta y aprende a utilizar las herramientas
Este curso esta diseñado para aprender desde cero cada aspecto que he trabajado o me encuentro trabajando en mi propio canal, utilizando las herramientas disponibles así también como otras externas a Youtube, como Facebook
Este es un curso para principiantes así que revisa el contenido del curso antes de inscribirte !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VidIQ Masterclass - Full Guide to YouTube Keyword Tool</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/vidiq-masterclass-full-guide-to-youtube-keyword-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 17:17:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/vidiq-masterclass-full-guide-to-youtube-keyword-tool/</guid>
      <description>Finally, a YouTube Channel Management Tool That Makes Creating &amp;amp; Growing A YouTube Channel Fun &amp;amp; Easy!
With the right YouTube channel management tool, you can get a complete overview of your channel and all its analytics and data. You can easily spot which videos work best and which ones need more work. And it&#39;s completely free!
VidIQ is a revolutionary YouTube tool that was designed to make it easier for creators on the platform like yourself to grow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Create a Marketing Video for Your Business or Product</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-create-a-marketing-video-for-your-business-or-product/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:16:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-create-a-marketing-video-for-your-business-or-product/</guid>
      <description>Video marketing is a simple but powerful SKILL you can use to leverage your business, products and services. Efficient marketing videos are simple and can be done by virtually anyone with the right guidance. We understand the impact that video marketing has over the selling process. That&#39;s why we created this course, to help people like you get the skills you need to produce your very own marketing videos. Every product can be explained through VIDEO, and it&#39;s scientifically proven that they have a much higher influence over regular marketing methods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTubeフィットネスチャンネルの作り方｜ヨガ、筋トレ、ダンス系で日本と海外の動画比較</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube%E3%83%95%E3%82%A3%E3%83%83%E3%83%88%E3%83%8D%E3%82%B9%E3%83%81%E3%83%A3%E3%83%B3%E3%83%8D%E3%83%AB%E3%81%AE%E4%BD%9C%E3%82%8A%E6%96%B9%E3%83%A8%E3%82%AC%E7%AD%8B%E3%83%88%E3%83%AC%E3%83%80%E3%83%B3%E3%82%B9%E7%B3%BB%E3%81%A7%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%AC%E3%81%A8%E6%B5%B7%E5%A4%96%E3%81%AE%E5%8B%95%E7%94%BB%E6%AF%94%E8%BC%83/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:16:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube%E3%83%95%E3%82%A3%E3%83%83%E3%83%88%E3%83%8D%E3%82%B9%E3%83%81%E3%83%A3%E3%83%B3%E3%83%8D%E3%83%AB%E3%81%AE%E4%BD%9C%E3%82%8A%E6%96%B9%E3%83%A8%E3%82%AC%E7%AD%8B%E3%83%88%E3%83%AC%E3%83%80%E3%83%B3%E3%82%B9%E7%B3%BB%E3%81%A7%E6%97%A5%E6%9C%AC%E3%81%A8%E6%B5%B7%E5%A4%96%E3%81%AE%E5%8B%95%E7%94%BB%E6%AF%94%E8%BC%83/</guid>
      <description>はじめまして、ビビアンです。
本講座に興味を持っていただいてありがとうございます。
講座を見ているあなたは、以下のような未来を実現したいかもしれません：
・YouTubeでレッスン動画を出している
・他人のスケジュールに合わせないで自分のレッスンを提供している
・趣味にお金をかけるのではなく、趣味で副収入を得ている
こんな未来が手に入ったら、どんな気持ちになりそうでしょうか?
コロナ以来、フィットネスレッスンのオンライン化が進んでいます。
中にはストアカのような第三者のプラットフォームでレッスンを提供している個人のインストラクターもいれば、
独自で開発したシステムでレッスンを販売している会社もあります。
プレースリリースの会社、PRTimesの調査によると、
コロナでオンラインヨガを始めた人が約6割もあるのです！
対面教室の閉鎖と、安全性の懸念による利用者数が減ってきている中、
運動不足を解消するためにオンラインのレッスンをはじめた人は少なくありません。
視聴者からのニーズが高まっている今では、
簡単にスタートできるYouTubeは特に注目されています。
YouTubeでファンを集めることができたら、
大好きなことで新しいライフスタイルを手にし、もっと大きな可能性を手にすることができます。
この講座では、
フィットネスインストラクターや、フィットネスビジネスをしている方に、
日本と海外のフィットネス人気YouTuberの動画を分析
登録者数が少ないチャンネルでも上位表示されるコツ
海外のファンを集め、視聴率を上げる方法
等々、
フィットネスをテーマにしたチャンネルの作り方を公開しています。
講座の中では特にニーズの高い人気ジャンル：
ヨガ系
筋トレ系
ダンス系
この3つを中心に詳しく分析しています。
すでにフィットネスを教えている方、もしくはこれからはじめたい方には、実用的な情報を盛り込んでいます。
講座の内容が気になれば、
ぜひレッスンのプレビューをみてみてください。
それでは、講座のなかでお会いしましょう。
Ratings: 0.00/5
Enrollments: 212
Coupon Code: 7129EA927CB9B161BB3A
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Thumbnail Masterclass / Ultimate Guide to Thumbnails</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-thumbnail-masterclass-/-ultimate-guide-to-thumbnails/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 17:16:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-thumbnail-masterclass-/-ultimate-guide-to-thumbnails/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s not a secret to anyone anymore. YouTube Thumbnails matter. A lot. It&#39;s the first thing people see when browsing YouTube and it&#39;s what will make them click on your video to watch it or not. It can mean the difference between a million views and no views. YouTube thumbnails are often the most influential factor in determining whether or not viewers will watch your video. This is because it&#39;s the first thing they see when browsing YouTube and is what will make them click on it to watch or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Oasis: The Ultimate Live-Streaming Course (2021)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-oasis-the-ultimate-live-streaming-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:30:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-oasis-the-ultimate-live-streaming-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the first course in Term 3 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Ready to learn some amazing live-streaming tools that can take your brand to great heights of success on social media?
The Internet as we know it is a large place. The benefits of live streaming on social media for your brand is very high. Typically, the word&#39; live-streaming means broadcasting live streams: one-to-many links that go out to many users at once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Video Marketing Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/live-video-marketing-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 12:27:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/live-video-marketing-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>Live video is quickly becoming one of the most powerful methods of reaching people. Chances are, live video had a part in all the product’s hype.
In this course , you’re going to learn some of the best ways to use live video to promote your own products and generate the kind of interest companies like Apple do!
The Live Video Marketing Course For EVERY Level
This course is your fast track to Live Video Marketing success and will provide long-lasting value from your very first live sessionright through to advanced sales and marketing campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Youtube Business Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-business-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 19:17:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-business-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>YouTube is the most popular video-streaming service boasting massive online traffic and constant streaming services.
And it’s the second most-visited website on the Internet with nearly 2 billion monthly users logging on to watch videos every day.
YouTube channel can maximize exposure and help your brand become recognized within your market.
It’s a great way to connect with your audience and keep them engaged for longer periods of time, while encouraging repeat traffic and views.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified YouTube Marketing Professional | CPD Accredited</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-youtube-marketing-professional-cpd-accredited/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 15:38:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-youtube-marketing-professional-cpd-accredited/</guid>
      <description>Two YouTube Marketing Certificates for the Price of One! Finish your Udemy course and Contact us to get your Continuing Professional Development (CPD) Certificate! Check out &#34;This is How You Earn Your CPD Accrdeited Certificate!&#34; Lecture for more information about your Certified YouTube Marketing Professional Certificate!
Doing YouTube Marketing has become the best technique for success, hungry marketers, to make the most from their marketing efforts, and if not given adequate importance to, it can prove fatal for your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Optimierung - Mehr Klicks, Shares und Abonnenten</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-optimierung-mehr-klicks-shares-und-abonnenten/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 21:12:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-optimierung-mehr-klicks-shares-und-abonnenten/</guid>
      <description>YouTube Optimierung - Mehr Klicks, Shares und AbonnentenDieser Youtube Kurs hilft dir dabei, mehr aus deinen Videos herauszuholen.
In diesem Kurs zeige ich dir, wie du deine Videos so optimierst, dass du mehr Zuschauer erreichst damit sich am Ende der Aufwand für deine Videos auch wirklich gelohnt hat.
*** In diesem kompakten, aber extrem wertvollen Kurs wirst du folgendes lernen:
Wie du deine Videos noch vor dem Upload auf Erfolg trimmen kannst</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PODCAST MASTERY: How to Make, Market, and Monetize Podcasts</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/podcast-mastery-how-to-make-market-and-monetize-podcasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 15:46:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/podcast-mastery-how-to-make-market-and-monetize-podcasts/</guid>
      <description>Ricky Shetty and Scott Paton recently celebrated their 500th podcast episode in 18 months: Digital Nomad Mastery Podcast. It gets 1000&#39;s of downloads a month and growing daily. Scott has been teaching podcasting since 2005.
In this fast-paced course, Ricky and Scott share how they were able to create such a successful podcast and leverage it into the vehicle that funds their dream lives of traveling the world.
You&#39;ll discover:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Gain More Customers With Video Marketing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-gain-more-customers-with-video-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-gain-more-customers-with-video-marketing/</guid>
      <description>In recent years, we can see the emergence of many websites on the Internet and even more intense competition between these sites. Everyone is trying to make their website better and more attractive than the competitor&#39;s, but still, everyone uses the same methods and tools to promote their business.
But many people forget about another very effective method, like video marketing, in which video is the main tool for promoting a business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Marketing 2021: Strategies and Growth</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-marketing-2021-strategies-and-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-marketing-2021-strategies-and-growth/</guid>
      <description>When you take this course, we will start you from an idea that you want to do YouTube video marketing and we will end with you crafting a professional YouTube channel as well as a strategy for how you will use it.&amp;nbsp;
Boomy and Lara are both internet marketing professionals committed to helping guide you with videos demonstrating the best and the worst in YouTube. We wanted this to be a course that you could watch while you work on your own channel, so it may take longer then the hour of video content.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
