<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Teaching &amp; Academics on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/teaching-academics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Teaching &amp; Academics on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/teaching-academics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Engineering Drawing / Graphics : Hands-on training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/engineering-drawing-/-graphics-hands-on-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/engineering-drawing-/-graphics-hands-on-training/</guid>
      <description>Students will be able to draw after instructors steps. As instructor has drawn with actual instruments of drawing learner will not get any difficulty to draw. Instructor will give learner step by step approach to draw various topics from engineering drawing/graphics. This course is for first year all branches engineering students, first year all branches polytechnic/diploma students and for 12th science students. Ratings: 4.39/5
Enrollments: 29605
Coupon Code: LEARNING3
Current Price: FREE</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>master layer farm management the business of millionaires</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-layer-farm-management-the-business-of-millionaires/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-layer-farm-management-the-business-of-millionaires/</guid>
      <description>introduction history of industry POULTRY-KEEPING is interesting because it gives pleasure as well as profit to persons of both sexes, all ages all walks in life m all sections of the country It is useful alike on the farm and in the City back-yard In the cold in the sunny, in the hill and mountain country, or on the plain It may be conducted as an exclusive business or as a side line It affords pleasure and profit for rich and poor It is the universal agricultural industry he best way to start a poultry enterprise is to begin modestly and let the business build its increases It is believed that poultry production started in Asia over 3000 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where should you start your Arabic language learning?</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/where-should-you-start-your-arabic-language-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/where-should-you-start-your-arabic-language-learning/</guid>
      <description>Arabic is widely taught in schools and universities and is used to varying degrees in workplaces, government and the media. Arabic, in its standard form, is the official language of 26 states, as well as the liturgical language of the religion of Islam, since the Quran and Hadith were written in Arabic.
In this course, you will learn how to read Arabic. by taking lessons gradually and easily, after finishing this course you will start practice reading by yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aerospace Masterclass: Transonic Aerodynamics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aerospace-masterclass-transonic-aerodynamics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aerospace-masterclass-transonic-aerodynamics/</guid>
      <description>This transonic aerodynamics course focuses on the study of the flow of air about an aircraft, but many of the concepts explored are relevant to a wide variety of applications from regular cars to Formula 1 bolides. Students completing this aerodynamics course will gain advanced understanding of concepts and techniques used to aerodynamically analyze and design transonic aircraft.
All transport aircrafts today are flying in with transonic speeds, so here you will learn everything you need to know for designing commercial aircraft such as Boeing or Airbus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethics of Research-A Basic Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ethics-of-research-a-basic-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ethics-of-research-a-basic-course/</guid>
      <description>Research ethics is vital when conducting research with people. Non ethical research may put research subjects at risk and even jeopardies the validity of the findings. As we undertake more and more research using increasingly diverse methods like the internet, it is important to get it right the first time.
On this course, you will learn the principles of ethical research, and how to manage human subject research in sensitive and appropriate ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intelligence Quotient [ IQ ] Tests and Answers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/intelligence-quotient-iq-tests-and-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/intelligence-quotient-iq-tests-and-answers/</guid>
      <description>Intelligence Quotient [ IQ ] Tests and Answers Challenging Questions to assess your brain and intelligence An intelligence quotient (IQ) is a total score derived from a set of standardized tests or subtests designed to assess human intelligence. The abbreviation &#34;IQ&#34; was coined by the psychologist William Stern for the German term Intelligenzquotient, his term for a scoring method for intelligence tests at University of Breslau he advocated in a 1912 book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops und Seminare professionell vorbereiten und leiten</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/workshops-und-seminare-professionell-vorbereiten-und-leiten/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/workshops-und-seminare-professionell-vorbereiten-und-leiten/</guid>
      <description>Dieser Kurs hilft dir bei der Vorbereitung, Leitung und Durchführung eines professionellen Workshops.
Freue dich auf glückliche und zufriedene Teilnehmer, ebenso wie gut zahlende Kunden! Es ist kein Geheimnis, dass Workshops eine großartige Möglichkeit sind, Menschen zusammenzubringen, um Wissen und Erfahrung auszutauschen. Aber was ist, wenn du nicht weisst, wie du sie organisieren sollst? Oder was, wenn du befürchtest, dass dir die Zeit ausgeht oder du nicht in der Lage bist, alle Teilnehmer bei der Stange zu halten?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bachelor Exam</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bachelor-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bachelor-exam/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to this online course about how to prepare and present your license exam. This course is an intensive one and is aimed at developing those skills that are useful and necessary for achieving successful presentations and talking in public with ease and impact.
In the next couple of hours, we will go through the right steps so that you perform in your oral presentations, whether they are online or face to face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Georgian Course: Learn Georgian for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-georgian-course-learn-georgian-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-georgian-course-learn-georgian-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our ultimate ultimate Georgian beginner course that will teach you Georgian faster than you thought possible! If you’ve ever dreamed of travelling to Georgia and holding your own in real-life situations, being independent and able to communicate with the locals, this is the course for you!
During our course you will learn:
Lots and lots of vocabulary
How to read and write in Georgian
Useful everyday phrases
Basic sentence structures</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>speak arbic like natives</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/speak-arbic-like-natives/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/speak-arbic-like-natives/</guid>
      <description>Arabic is an old language . It is believed to have originated in the Arabian Peninsula. rabic, which first emerged in the northwest of the Arabian Peninsula, is a member of the Semitic family of languages which also includes Hebrew and Aramaic. Whilst very early manifestations of Arabic date back as far as the 8th century BCE, the language has been defined and refined over a considerable period of time.Arabic is at least 1,500 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TESOL and TPRS Course (For Language Teachers)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tesol-and-tprs-course-for-language-teachers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tesol-and-tprs-course-for-language-teachers/</guid>
      <description>Although uneducated parents can teach a languge to their children, how can educated teachers not teach a foreign language? In this course, you will learn how to teach a languge with a contemporary method but ancient.
In ancient times, people used to travel by horses or camels but then they invented cars and began to go everywhere with them. Today, we use planes. There is no doubt that cars are faster than horses, but planes are the fastest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Write Dreamy, Heartfelt, Soulful Poetry - Creative Writing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/write-dreamy-heartfelt-soulful-poetry-creative-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/write-dreamy-heartfelt-soulful-poetry-creative-writing/</guid>
      <description>Learn to write dreamy and imaginative poetry that inspires readers and takes them to new worlds.
Create beauty with your writing and give the gift of inspiration to others.
What you will learn
We&#39;ll start with poetry basics like similes, rhyming, metaphors, and building imagery. We will also explore the brain science of what makes people feel certain feelings. We&#39;ll combine the science with philosophy to help you understand what goes on in the mind of a reader or listener.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Repair | Automotive Electrician and Mechanic Training |</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/car-repair-automotive-electrician-and-mechanic-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/car-repair-automotive-electrician-and-mechanic-training/</guid>
      <description>The Role of Electricity in the automobile in the past, electrical systems was basically stand-alone. For example, the ignition system was only responsible for supplying the voltage needed to fire the spark plugs. Ignition timing was controlled by vacuum and mechanical advance systems. Today there are very few electrical systems that are still independent. Today, most manufacturers network their electrical systems together through computers. This means that information gathered by one system can be used by another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English grammar tenses made easy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-grammar-tenses-made-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-grammar-tenses-made-easy/</guid>
      <description>This course will indeed be beneficial for those students who want to learn the simple, continuous and perfect forms of present, past and future tenses. The course will cover a plethora of examples in order to demonstrate the structure of the different tenses in English grammar. This course will be especially useful for students who are new to English language and are passionate about learning grammatical rules insofar as tenses are concerned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation - Part 1 &#43; Live Class</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-part-1--live-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-part-1--live-class/</guid>
      <description>Do you remember the &#34;Jetsons show&#34;? The Jetsons fascinated me and everyone else around me. Thoughts of moving sidewalks, self-driving vehicles and robot housekeepers - fuelled my daydreams to the core. Let&#39;s now talk about the present time and the tech that is evolving.
Nowadays, I can command a robotic tool, device or tech to tell me the next day’s weather, read an e-book to me, play my preferred podcasts and even vacuum my flooring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carbon Offsets and Climate Change Mitigation</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/carbon-offsets-and-climate-change-mitigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/carbon-offsets-and-climate-change-mitigation/</guid>
      <description>Carbon offsets have been a popular climate change mitigation option for individuals and companies alike, but they have also been very contentious. This course provides you with an in-depth understanding of what kind of commodity carbon offsets are, how they have evolved, the biggest challenges offsets have encountered when it comes to delivering climate change mitigation, and where offset markets might be headed next. It answers several key questions: What defines a carbon offset?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General bacteriology a concise course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/general-bacteriology-a-concise-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/general-bacteriology-a-concise-course/</guid>
      <description>Bacteriology basics principles in half hour in in easy way it is suitable for professional need to refresh their knowledge and for beginners i and for student in secondary school and medical student science students agriculture students
In this course we introduce basics in interesting methods slides quizzes assignments we give a brief about history of microbiology he beginnings of bacteriology paralleled the development of the microscope. The first person to see microorganisms was probably the Dutch naturalist van Leeuwenhoek, who in 1683 described some animalcules, as they were then called, in water, saliva, and other substances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>general mycology a brief review</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/general-mycology-a-brief-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/general-mycology-a-brief-review/</guid>
      <description>Topics In this course you find
introduction
history of science development
Morphology of fungi
Growth of fungi
Metabolism of fungi Genetics f fungi
Diseases caused by fungi Allergies Mycosis Mycotoxin
Laboratory diagnosis of fungi
Antifungal Drugs used in treatment fungal diseases
HISTORY OF THE SCIENCE GIVE AN IDEA OF ITS DEVELOPEMENT STAGES
The term &#34;mycology&#34; is derived from Greek word &#34;mykes&#34; meaning mushroom. Therefore mycology is the study of fungi The ability of fungi to invade plant and animal tissue was observed in early 19th century but the first documented animal infection by any fungus was made by Augastino Bassi , who in 1835 studied the muscardine disease of silkworm proved that the infection was caused by a fungus Beauveria bassiana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>practical bacteriology from scratch</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/practical-bacteriology-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/practical-bacteriology-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>practical bacteriology from scratch your safety first take care when working with pathogenic microorganisms wear coat when you are in lab and remove after finish keep the lab disk for equipment only wear gloves when dealing with microorganisms clean clean table before and after test mask eye protect keep your hand away from mouth and eye and nose use mechanical pipetting report the spill and disinfect the area well wash hands after any procedure deal well with fire smooth small one with towel large one use expenditure follow the instructions included in lab safety manual be professional in handling microscope there are many types with many uses bright field microscope dark field microscope phase contrast microscope fluorescent microscope electro microscope it is essential tool practice using the microscope with low power medium power high power and take care when use oil immersion lens sterilization the most important topic in microbiology without keeping your environment sterile it is impossible to obtain Apure culture sterilization methods heat sterilization sterilization by radiation sterilization by disinfectant chemicals use of antimicrobial bacterial culture is a method for isolate bacteria the culture may be natural in origin or synthetic or both culture may be ordinary enriched blood agar is enriched media They contain substances Blood ,Serum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electrical  Engineering Interview Practice Questions</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/electrical-engineering-interview-practice-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:33:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/electrical-engineering-interview-practice-questions/</guid>
      <description>Electrical engineering is a basic branch and one of oldest engineering branch. It includes generation , transmission and distribution of electricity. Many students of electrical branch aspire to get placed in core electrical companies. For this you must be well prepared with basics of electrical engineering. Students get confused about what to prepare and what not to. I have come up with a course of practice test for such aspiring students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For Ukraine</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/for-ukraine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/for-ukraine/</guid>
      <description>All the revenue received by me (the Instructor!) from sales of this course will go to help those in Ukraine/fleeing from Ukraine. Not &#39;profit&#39; but REVENUE. The Videographer/Videoeditor has waived all fees too. This course is about the war in Ukraine. It is divided into five main sections:
Relevance - each lecture explains how this course is RELEVANT to you if you study....(range of subjects)
Truth - we look at how &#39;truth&#39; has suffered in this war</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Radio Access Network (RAN) Technologies - 5G and 6G</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-radio-access-network-ran-technologies-5g-and-6g/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:11:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-radio-access-network-ran-technologies-5g-and-6g/</guid>
      <description>Advanced 5G and Beyond Potential Technologies – From Beginner to Expert
The course cover topics such as mMTC, URLLC, IoT, OFDM Numerologies, 5G/6G waveforms, NOMA, OTFS, In-band Full-duplex, LiFi, mmWave, massive MIMO, etc.
If you want to prepare yourself to work in Telecom companies, such as NOKIA, HUAWEI, SAMSUNG, APPLE, GOOGLE, FACEBOOK, MICROSOFT, ERICSSON, QUALCOMM, INTEL, ZTE, etc., or want to find new interesting research topics related to 5G, 6G, ad beyond wireless generations, then this course is just for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orthogonal Frequency Division Multiplexing (OFDM)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/orthogonal-frequency-division-multiplexing-ofdm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:11:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/orthogonal-frequency-division-multiplexing-ofdm/</guid>
      <description>Due to its numerous advantages, orthogonal frequency division multiplexing (OFDM) has been the most dominantly used transmission waveform in the vast majority of the currently available standards, such as WiFi, WiMax, DVB, LTE, and NB-IoT. Moreover, it should not be a surprise that the OFDM waveform (with its new parametrized waveforms to meet the diverse requirements of different emerging applications and services) has successfully maintained its dominance in 5G systems. It has been adopted due to its desirable properties and features, including higher spectral efficiency, robustness to multipath with simple equalization in the frequency domain, easy integration with MIMO systems, and multi-user diversity where time and frequency resources are flexibly scheduled among users based on their requirements and channel conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test your Knowledge in Wireless Communications</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/test-your-knowledge-in-wireless-communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:11:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/test-your-knowledge-in-wireless-communications/</guid>
      <description>Test your Knowledge Level in Wireless Communications Field
You will get two Practice Tests that enable you to examine your Knowledge in the Wireless Communications Field
=============== Note that the exam is prepared based on the material presented in the course titled &#34;Wireless Communications: From Basics to Advanced&#34;, which can be accessed from our main page on Udemy.
===============
Wireless Communication Principles – Basics to Advanced.
If you want to prepare yourself to work in companies like NOKIA, HUAWEI, SAMSUNG, APPLE, GOOGLE, FACEBOOK, MICROSOFT, ERICSSON, QUALCOMM, INTEL, ZTE, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internal Combustion Engine Emissions &amp; Control</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/internal-combustion-engine-emissions-control/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/internal-combustion-engine-emissions-control/</guid>
      <description>Cars, trucks, buses, and off-road vehicles are all considered mobile sources of air pollution. Carbon monoxide, nitrogen oxides, and hydrocarbons are released when fuel burns in an internal combustion engine. They may also be released when vehicle tailpipes emit air and fuel residuals. Gasoline vapors also escape into the atmosphere during refueling and when fuel vaporizes from engines and fuel systems caused by vehicle operation or hot weather.
The pollutants in engine emissions from vehicles and lawn equipment cause damage to lung tissue and can lead to and aggravate respiratory diseases, such as asthma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Chinese, Basic Mandarin Chinese, HSK 1 Preparation</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-chinese-basic-mandarin-chinese-hsk-1-preparation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-chinese-basic-mandarin-chinese-hsk-1-preparation/</guid>
      <description>This HSK course is designed according to HSK standard course book with detailed explanation and assignments for Chinese beginners. This course will help you learn Chinese like kids, learn Chinese words stroke by stroke. We divided each unit to several lessons, each HSK lesson is less than 8 mins, which will help you learn Chinese in a less pressure way. You will be able to learn Chinese easily and pass the HSK1 exam without any difficulties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Guide to TOEFL iBT | Mastering the Skills</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-guide-to-toefl-ibt-mastering-the-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-guide-to-toefl-ibt-mastering-the-skills/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my Complete Guide to TOEFL iBT | Mastering the Skills course!
This course is aimed to help you develop all the skills you need to earn a high score in the TOEFL test.
This course is comprised of 6 units.
Introduction
Grammar &amp;amp; Vocabulary for TOEFL
Reading Section
Listening Section
Speaking Section
Writing Section. This course is designed to reflect the changes to the TOEFL test format. Therefore, as well as learning proper ways to tackle each question, you will learn the correct format for the test so that there are no surprises on the test day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Easy Way to Speak English For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-easy-way-to-speak-english-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-easy-way-to-speak-english-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to speak English more clearly and more confidently with this amazing English course. This course is for beginners who want to speak English or anyone who suffers a lot when speaking English and want to find an easy way to speak English with confidence,
You will improve your speaking skills, listening skills and pronunciation in English.
Includes videos, Pdf files and free resources to online speaking and pronunciation activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate Practice Exams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-practice-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-practice-exams/</guid>
      <description>AWS Certified Solutions Architect
Exam Topics and Subtopics
The Amazon AWS Certified Solutions Architect – Associate certification exam covers four topic areas. These are design resilient architectures; design high-performing architectures; design secure architectures and applications; designing cost-optimized architectures. When preparing for the test, it is critical to take note of the associated percentage for each of these domains. This indicates the volume of questions that may be administered during the delivery of the exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Italian for Beginners: Speak Italian like a Pro</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-italian-for-beginners-speak-italian-like-a-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-italian-for-beginners-speak-italian-like-a-pro/</guid>
      <description>**The ultimate Italian beginner course that will teach you Italian faster than you thought possible**
Suppose you&#39;ve ever wanted to travel to Italy and be able to hold your own in real-life circumstances, be independent, and converse with the people. In that case, our complete Italian beginners&#39; course is the right place to start!
This comprehensive Italian course will teach you all you need to know to become a natural Italian speaker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Método Completo de Escritura de Novela Psicológica</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/m%C3%A9todo-completo-de-escritura-de-novela-psicol%C3%B3gica/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/m%C3%A9todo-completo-de-escritura-de-novela-psicol%C3%B3gica/</guid>
      <description>Hola querido/a escritor/a:
Si estás leyendo estas líneas significa que John ha muerto y ha escapado a Francia con nuestros ahorros!!!
Obviamente, si estás leyendo esto es porque estás buscando aprender a escribir una novela, o ya tienes una idea y te falta un poquito de ayuda para ponerla a andar. Siempre es necesario un signo que nos indique el camino. En este caso, este curso te indicará el camino correcto.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English placement test - Unofficial</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-placement-test-unofficial/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-placement-test-unofficial/</guid>
      <description>Who wants to know his / her level... you have to answer these tests and be okay with them.
You have to revise your language before tests.
these tests only to know your level.
test your English with your own...
practice test, just to know your level to improve it.
focus on your language and your grammer...
it&#39;s at all your English placement test...
You can also share the test results with us and get advice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generative Adversarial Networks in Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/generative-adversarial-networks-in-artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/generative-adversarial-networks-in-artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>AI is an enabler in transforming diverse realms by exploiting deep learning architectures.
The course aims to expose students to cutting-edge algorithms, techniques, and codes related to AI and particularly the Generative Adversarial Networks used for data creation in deep learning routines. This course encompasses multidimensional implementations of the themes listed below; 1. Deep Learning: A subset of Hybrid Artificial Intelligence
2. Big Data is Fueling Applied AI.
3. How to model a problem in AI using datasets in Python (Keras &amp;amp; TensorFlow Libraries).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group Dynamics: Psychology of Group Behavior</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/group-dynamics-psychology-of-group-behavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/group-dynamics-psychology-of-group-behavior/</guid>
      <description>Everyone can gain an advantage in their social world by understanding the ways in which social interaction is structured and the ways that groups influence our behavior and our sense of identity. You&#39;ll learn the psychology of group dynamics! In this course we cover five core topics relating to group psychology Inclusion and Identity - Learn how we internalize group values and goals and how our social groups become part of the way we identify ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2022 - Part 3</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2022-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2022-part-3/</guid>
      <description>Ready to create ebooks in minutes in 2022?
Welcome to this superb course that will walk you through the future of content creation and eBook generation. Taking a leap from RoboAuthor Part 2, this Part 3 course taught by Digital Marketing Legend Srinidhi Ranganathan will continue your adventure in content writing to unlock opportunities for ultra-fast eBook writing and creation with the power of Artificial Intelligence. We must know that artificial intelligence will create amazing content today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Book of Jonah: Insightful Overview &amp; Life Applications</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-book-of-jonah-insightful-overview-life-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-book-of-jonah-insightful-overview-life-applications/</guid>
      <description>Contrary to popular misrepresentation, this minor prophetic book is not about the great or big fish. It is the great big God.
The God who shows, love, mercy and compassion even in the of events that cry for justice. It is about God and His immanent activities on the earth.
In this we see Jonah fleeing his mission (chapters 1–2)
We see him purporting to give up on his and take to flight (1:1–3)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improve English by Listening Movies – 1b</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/improve-english-by-listening-movies-1b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/improve-english-by-listening-movies-1b/</guid>
      <description>Are you feeling so much difficulty to understand people in real life? Can’t understand exactly what that guy is telling you on the phone? Not able to understand the speech when you are watching the video on the web? You can easily understand a piece of text by reading, but you are not able to understand people by listening, have you been suffering from this problem since you started to learn English?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improve English by Movies</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/improve-english-by-movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/improve-english-by-movies/</guid>
      <description>Let’s go back to our childhood and think about primary school for a moment.
I am talking about the time when we were six or seven years old.
The question here is,
What was the first thing they taught us at primary school? First thing they taught us was Writing and Reading, right?
Why it wasn’t Listening and Speaking? Of course, listening and speaking were the core abilities that we were accepted to a primary school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Would in English</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/use-would-in-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/use-would-in-english/</guid>
      <description>One of the difficulties of English learners is to understand &#39;would&#39; clearly.
Understanding &#39;would&#39; is a challenge and be able to use it in a sentence is another challenge, isn’t it?
No matter how many times I attempted to understand &#39;would&#39; either by looking up the dictionaries or the grammar books, none of them made any difference and I ended up not to understand it. Curious thing is that I came across would quite often and it was literally driving me crazy because I was not able to discover the hidden secret behind it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improve English by Listening Movies – 1c</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/improve-english-by-listening-movies-1c/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/improve-english-by-listening-movies-1c/</guid>
      <description>Are you feeling so much difficulty to understand people in real life?
Can’t understand exactly what that guy is telling you on the phone?
Not able to understand the speech when you are watching the video on the web?
You can easily understand a piece of text by reading, but you are not able to understand people by listening, have you been suffering from this problem since you started to learn English?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids English Vocabulary Set One - Nouns</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kids-english-vocabulary-set-one-nouns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kids-english-vocabulary-set-one-nouns/</guid>
      <description>What will children learn?
Kids will learn new words in English language from different parts of speech that they can use later in their speaking
Are there any course requirement? There are absolutely no requirements of the course except your device to enjoy watching our videos.
Who are the targeted audience?
The targeted audience are children aged 4-12 (with the permisson and supervision of their parents; please read the crucial note)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 150 Most Important Irregular Verbs in English. Volume 1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-150-most-important-irregular-verbs-in-english.-volume-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 21:50:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-150-most-important-irregular-verbs-in-english.-volume-1/</guid>
      <description>Support available in: English Spanish French
I can&#39;t wait to share with you this exciting English course based on Irregular Verbs. Do you feel unsure about the right conjugation when you try use irregular verbs in every day conversation?
Are you frustrated of having to memorize unending word lists? Then this course is for you. It is not a secret that Irregular Verbs are hard to learn. So when Enlglish learners try to use the verbs in a professional situation it is very embarrassing not to use the right conjugation, and your chances to give a good impression to your potential employer are gone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American English Pronunciation for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/american-english-pronunciation-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:57:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/american-english-pronunciation-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling with your English pronunciation? Do you have a strong accent when speaking English?
Do native speakers always ask you to repeat yourself?
Do you want to begin speaking with an American accent confidently?
Do you what tips and help with speaking with an American accent? I welcome you to this - “American English Pronunciation Training - course where I will patiently guide you through the basic techniques you need to pronounce English sounds correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Video Lessons with Online Video Maker InVideo</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/creating-video-lessons-with-online-video-maker-invideo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:57:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/creating-video-lessons-with-online-video-maker-invideo/</guid>
      <description>In this course you will learn how to create a dynamic and attention-grabbing video lectures fast and easy with InVideo. Together we shall go through all steps of creating process, starting from InVideo features, designing a lecture by scenes, adding and editing a voiceover.
You can use your article/post/thesis and get a custom video lecture in the end of this course. Or you can use the attached materials to this course: my company’s article on 4 Principles of Design in PowerPoint, a text for a voiceover and a script for each scene, graphic materials regarding the topic, and mp3 files for a voiceover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STAAD Pro V8 Structural design of R.C building from A to Z</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/staad-pro-v8-structural-design-of-r.c-building-from-a-to-z/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:57:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/staad-pro-v8-structural-design-of-r.c-building-from-a-to-z/</guid>
      <description>This course teaches you all the things required for the structural analysis and design of a R.C building. This course, as the title says, doesn&#39;t require you to have any prior experience in this software or any other structural design software. It will teach all the aspects of the software from very basic and will take you to the higher levels of the software as the course progresses. The course has been very systematically arranged so that you can best understand the software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question On PLC -&gt; beginning to Advanced Level</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-plc-beginning-to-advanced-level/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 20:40:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-plc-beginning-to-advanced-level/</guid>
      <description>Dear Students,
Are you preparing for Job Exam and Interview in programmable logic controller (PLC)?
Don’t be stressed, Take our PLC Based Practice Test and prepare yourself for the Interview. Here we Discuss the Practical Questions on the PLC.
Here we are going to build your confidence by Providing Practice Test on PLC based questions. There will be a series of practice Tests where you can test your Knowledge in the field of PLC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Egyptian Arabic through Cartoons</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-egyptian-arabic-through-cartoons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 20:40:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-egyptian-arabic-through-cartoons/</guid>
      <description>This is actually a new idea in teaching a foreign language , Hello everyone. I&#39;m Mr,Bakoor. I have been teaching Arabic for several years. so I have enough experience in teaching Arabic, in this course I come up with a new idea a new strategy to Egyptian Arabic this idea is you will get fun while learning Egyptian dialect. this idea will make memorization easier to, you will find it enjoyable and easy to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water Supply System A-Z - Mechanical Engineering</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/water-supply-system-a-z-mechanical-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 20:40:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/water-supply-system-a-z-mechanical-engineering/</guid>
      <description>Hi! Welcome to our course. If you are starting to study the MECHANICAL ENGINEERING industry, you are on the right course!. This Course covers Full Water Supply System. it will build your knowledge slowly until you reach the point that you can understand Plumbing Fixtures, Pumping systems. And a full description of Pipes, Fittings, and Valves, and How to Design your system!
In this course you&#39;ll Study : Plumbing Standard &amp;amp; Codes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book of Romans: By Apostle Paul &amp; 16 Life Changing Lessons!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/book-of-romans-by-apostle-paul-16-life-changing-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 15:08:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/book-of-romans-by-apostle-paul-16-life-changing-lessons/</guid>
      <description>----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Apart from the Book of Revelations, The Epistle to the Romans has made some of the most significant contributions into our Christian walk today. Beginning with Chapter #1, Paul uses the local knowledge of &#34;Power&#34; as the instrument to illustrate the &#34;The Gospel as the Power to save&#34; He makes it known that everyone needs the unmerited favour of God - Grace. No one is excluded. The Gentiles for their worship of the created things and the Jews for their inability to fulfill the law they have used to judge others!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Coding Interview :Data structures &#43; Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-coding-interview-data-structures--algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-coding-interview-data-structures--algorithms/</guid>
      <description>Our Students Speak :
⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️
The teacher has fantastic ability to transfer understanding of a concept not just pass along his knowledge of the concept.-Liam Bailes
⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️
This course is excellent and a great method to learn about Data Structures and Algorithms. It&#39;s fantastic for learning how to solve problems and construct reasoning.-Parth
⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️
Best course. Since Data structure is one of the basic subject for programming, this course provides an complete overview of all components of Data Structures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Udemy Course Creation - Udemy Instructor Guide (Unofficial)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/udemy-course-creation-udemy-instructor-guide-unofficial/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/udemy-course-creation-udemy-instructor-guide-unofficial/</guid>
      <description>Have you dreamt of being a Udemy instructor? Have you thought about how to create your first course? It doesn&#39;t have to be difficult. This is an in-depth course that will take you through every stage needed to create a great Udemy course. From planning, to production, and finally publishing your video course, this comprehensive guide will have you creating your own Udemy courses within weeks.
This comprehensive guide will walk you through the process of creating your own Udemy course from start to finish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops - systemisch konzipieren und gestalten</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/workshops-systemisch-konzipieren-und-gestalten/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/workshops-systemisch-konzipieren-und-gestalten/</guid>
      <description>Würden Sie gerne Ihre Fähigkeiten als (zukünftige) Führungskraft hinsichtlich Vorträge und Workshops verbessern? Dieser Kurs ist mit dem systemischen Ansatz am neuesten Stand und gibt Ihnen das notwendige Hintergrundwissen, damit Sie mit Ihren eigenen Projekten gleich durchstarten können.
Zielgruppe sind (zukünftige) Führungskräfte, Projektleiter/innen, Personen mit Leitungsfunktionen oder einfach alle Menschen mit Verantwortung im Job.
Ich habe sowohl wissenschaftliche Inhalte als auch meine eigene Erfahrungen als Trainer, Coach und Führungskraft in diesen Lektionen eingebaut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Grammar Practice Tests Level B1 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-grammar-practice-tests-level-b1-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:57:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-grammar-practice-tests-level-b1-2021/</guid>
      <description>The course contains six practice tests. A practice test contains 25 questions.
Target audience are students before an English Level B1 exam; alternatively, English language learning students who want to test English Level B1 knowledge.
The purpose of the practice test is to support students before an English Level B1 exam.
#englishgrammar #englishb1 #englishexam #englishlevelb1 What is the B1 English level Test?
CEFR or CEFRL (Common European Framework of Reference) is an international language ability standard by the Council of Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English vocabulary: Learn more than 200 words for beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-vocabulary-learn-more-than-200-words-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:30:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-vocabulary-learn-more-than-200-words-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>The course discusses the most important vocabulary used in the English language and not vocabulary only but uses this vocabulary in a situational sentence. English vocabulary is the basis of sentence structure if you get more words, you can express yourself much better. Vocabulary is n&#39;t mere words, it is the expressions of your feelings and communicates with others around you. Ratings: 3.18/5
Enrollments: 55553
Coupon Code: C4EEB045E9D888B621B0
Current Price: FREE</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Tenses Structures : Upgrade your Understanding</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-tenses-structures-upgrade-your-understanding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 20:40:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-tenses-structures-upgrade-your-understanding/</guid>
      <description>In this course, I will explain in detail all the English tenses that cause problems for the English learners. Present, past, and future tenses will be discussed also passive structures for every tense. What makes this course different? I will explain the course in both languages English and Arabic. That&#39;s because I found many students asked me to explain in Arabic. So I will give more explanations in both languages for more benefit for students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autodesk Revit &amp; Robot Structural Analysis &#43; Sheets &#43; BOQ</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/autodesk-revit-robot-structural-analysis--sheets--boq/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/autodesk-revit-robot-structural-analysis--sheets--boq/</guid>
      <description>This course not just a tutorial on software Revit and Robot but it is a complete understanding about structural design analysis, how civil engineer must begin with the project, how he/she must think, how we can determine the dimension of the element before modeling them check it in the software. In this course we will design a 15 stories of a residential buildings, within the work we will define and design all types of slabs such as (waffle slab, one way ribbed slab, two way ribbed slab, flat slab and solid slab), all types of foundations such as (isolated,combined,strip and mat), earthquake loads, columns and beams and shear walls + Advanced lectures in Revit + Advanced lectures in Robot + design a swimming pool in Robot</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Civil Engineering Structural Shop Drawing in AutoCAD</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/civil-engineering-structural-shop-drawing-in-autocad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/civil-engineering-structural-shop-drawing-in-autocad/</guid>
      <description>Part 1: Introduction for beginner civil engineers in manual calculation of structural elements Manual calculation of : 1- Slab thickness ( How we can determine manually the thickness of all types of slabs: waffles slabs type 1 and type 2, Ribbed slabs, Solid Slabs , and Flat Slabs + Show the properties advantages and disadvantages of these slabs) 2- Beams thickness interior and exterior beams in all types of slabs and how we can choose the optimized design of Slab- beams system</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Polish Course: Learn Polish for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-polish-course-learn-polish-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-polish-course-learn-polish-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to learn Polish? As the second most-spoken Slavic language with over 55 million native speakers, there are many benefits to learning this familiar, yet exotic language.
In this course, we’re going to take you through the first steps of your Polish journey, from absolute beginner to an intermediate level. Our lessons will cover everything, from teaching you how to read and write the Polish alphabet, to conjugating verbs and declining nouns, to forming sentences and describing yourself, the world around you and actions that take place within it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Creation On Udemy Passive Income Monthly~Unofficial</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/course-creation-on-udemy-passive-income-monthly~unofficial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/course-creation-on-udemy-passive-income-monthly~unofficial/</guid>
      <description>Would you like your own e-learning course business where you make money while you sleep? I have launched over 30 Udemy Courses with 750K Students and more than 3800+ Reviews, I will teach you exactly how I build my passive income empire from scratch on Udemy since 2018. If you are good at anything and can teach it to other people then this is for you. Get ready to build a passive income stream through Udemy and follow my secret strategy to success!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Csi ETABS in the Structural analysis of 15 stories&#43; basement</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/csi-etabs-in-the-structural-analysis-of-15-stories-basement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/csi-etabs-in-the-structural-analysis-of-15-stories-basement/</guid>
      <description>This course not just a tutorial on software ETABS but it is a complete understanding about structural design analysis, how civil engineer must begin with the project, how he/she must think, how we can determine the dimension of the element before modeling them check it in the software. In this course we will design a 15 stories of a residential buildings, within the work we will define and design all types of slabs such as (waffle slab, one way ribbed slab, two way ribbed slab, flat slab and solid slab), earthquake with static and dynamic case, wind loads, columns and beams and shear walls</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI Sap2000 3D building design &#43; all type of (Stairs&#43;Tanks)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/csi-sap2000-3d-building-design--all-type-of-stairs-tanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/csi-sap2000-3d-building-design--all-type-of-stairs-tanks/</guid>
      <description>This course not just a tutorial on software Sap2000 but it is a complete understanding about structural design analysis, how civil engineer must begin with the project, how he/she must think, how we can determine the dimension of the element before modeling them check it in the software. In this course we will design a 15 stories of a residential buildings, within the work we will define and design all types of slabs such as (waffle slab, one way ribbed slab, two way ribbed slab, flat slab and solid slab), earthquake with static and dynamic case, wind loads, columns and beams and shear walls + Advanced lectures in ETABS + Advanced lecture in Sap2000 (design all types of Stairs + water tanks + 2D work) + Structural design of a Dome</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETABS v19 &amp; SAFE v16 in Villa Structural Design in UAE&#43;CAD</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/etabs-v19-safe-v16-in-villa-structural-design-in-uae-cad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/etabs-v19-safe-v16-in-villa-structural-design-in-uae-cad/</guid>
      <description>This course not just a tutorial on software ETABS and SAFE but it is a complete understanding about structural design analysis, how civil engineer must begin with the project, how he/she must think, how we can determine the dimension of the element before modeling them check it in the software. In this course we will design a 4 stories Villa in UAE, within the work we will show you how to select the best type of slab type for this Villa, also how to select the best type of foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robot Structural Analysis (Steel Structure)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/robot-structural-analysis-steel-structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/robot-structural-analysis-steel-structure/</guid>
      <description>This course not just a tutorial on software Robot but it is a complete understanding about structural design analysis, how civil engineer must begin with the project, how he/she must think, how we can determine the dimension of the element before modeling them check it in the software. In this course we will a &#34;Hangar&#34; steel structure with all steel structural element Rafters; Columns; Truss; Top Chord; Bottom Chord; Internal elements; Rail Sides; Beams; Wind Columns; Wind Beams; Bracing; Beam connection; Column connection; Purlins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robot structural design 15 stories residential buildings</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/robot-structural-design-15-stories-residential-buildings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/robot-structural-design-15-stories-residential-buildings/</guid>
      <description>This course not just a tutorial on Robot software but it is a complete understanding about structural design analysis, how civil engineer must begin with the project, how he/she must think, how we can determine the dimension of the element before modeling them check it in the software. In this course we will design a 15 stories of a residential buildings, within the work we will define and design all types of slabs such as (waffle slab, one way ribbed slab, two way ribbed slab, flat slab and solid slab), foundations, earthquake loads, columns and beams and shear walls + design a swimming pool in Robot</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tekla structures Shop drawings Steel Structure</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tekla-structures-shop-drawings-steel-structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tekla-structures-shop-drawings-steel-structure/</guid>
      <description>Tekla structures is a building information modeling software able to model structures that incorporate different kinds of building materials, including steel, concrete, timber, and glass.
Tekla structures the most advanced structural BIM software, lets you create, combine, manage and share multi-material 3D models packed with valuable construction information. With Tekla structures you can create accurate information-rich 3D models that have all the structural data you need to build and maintain any type of structure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced ETABS V2019 52 stories Tower different seismic sys</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-etabs-v2019-52-stories-tower-different-seismic-sys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-etabs-v2019-52-stories-tower-different-seismic-sys/</guid>
      <description>With the last version of ETABS (2019)
First of all we will show the newest features in ETABS v19
Part 1,2,3: learn structural design of R.C Tower 52 stories from A to Z included all structural element (columns, beams, slabs, foundations, shear walls, earthquake and wind design, check deflection) using different earthquake systems (Shear wall system, moment frame system, and dual system)
Part 4 :we will use in this course viscous damper and show the benefit of using them and how we can model them into ETABS Also we will learn in this course what is outrigger and how we can define and modeling it into ETABS V19 and we will show the benefits of using outrigger in high rise building</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autodesk Structural Robot R.C.C Villa Design in UAE</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/autodesk-structural-robot-r.c.c-villa-design-in-uae/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/autodesk-structural-robot-r.c.c-villa-design-in-uae/</guid>
      <description>This course not just a tutorial on Robot software but it is a complete understanding about structural design analysis, how civil engineer must begin with the project, how he/she must think, how we can determine the dimension of the element before modeling them check it in the software. In this course we will design a 4 stories Villa in UAE, within the work we will show you how to select the best type of slab type for this Villa, also how to select the best type of foundation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSI ETABSV19 steel structure analysis and design</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/csi-etabsv19-steel-structure-analysis-and-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/csi-etabsv19-steel-structure-analysis-and-design/</guid>
      <description>This course not just a tutorial on software ETABS but it is a complete understanding about structural design analysis, how civil engineer must begin with the project, how he/she must think, how we can determine the dimension of the element before modeling them check it in the software. In this course we will a &#34;Hangar&#34; steel structure with all steel structural element Rafters; Columns; Truss; Top Chord; Bottom Chord; Internal elements; Rail Sides; Beams; Wind Columns; Wind Beams; Bracing; Beam connection; Column connection; Purlins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Csi Safe &#43; AllPile foundation, slabs, beams and deflection</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/csi-safe--allpile-foundation-slabs-beams-and-deflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/csi-safe--allpile-foundation-slabs-beams-and-deflection/</guid>
      <description>This course not just a tutorial on software ETABS and SAFE but it is a complete understanding about structural design analysis, how civil engineer must begin with the project, how he/she must think, how we can determine the dimension of the element before modeling them check it in the software. Design all types of foundation shallow ( isolated, combined, strip and mat) + deep piles foundations + all types of slabs ( Waffles type 1 and 2 + Ribbed + Flat + Solid ) + design beams + Check deflection</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revit structural drawing of 15 stories residential building</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/revit-structural-drawing-of-15-stories-residential-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/revit-structural-drawing-of-15-stories-residential-building/</guid>
      <description>Structural drawing of 15 stories residential buildings in Revit. In this course student will begin from zero to expert in structural drawing of all elements (columns, beams, slabs, shear walls, stairs and foundations) + draw reinforcement of all structural elements + create structural sheets + create BOQ tables. Student through this course will show and the commands needed with structural drawing of a project.
Ratings: 4.28/5
Enrollments: 7191
Coupon Code: E15E14B723DAB7E3FB78</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tekla Structures shop drawing R.C.C Building</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tekla-structures-shop-drawing-r.c.c-building/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tekla-structures-shop-drawing-r.c.c-building/</guid>
      <description>Tekla structures is a building information modeling software able to model structures that incorporate different kinds of building materials, including steel, concrete, timber, and glass.
Tekla structures the most advanced structural BIM software, lets you create, combine, manage and share multi-material 3D models packed with valuable construction information. With Tekla structures you can create accurate information-rich 3D models that have all the structural data you need to build and maintain any type of structure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Thessalonians - Summary &amp; Life Lessons For Todays Living</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2-thessalonians-summary-life-lessons-for-todays-living/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 19:27:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2-thessalonians-summary-life-lessons-for-todays-living/</guid>
      <description>Paul wrote this letter shortly after the return of Timothy&#39;s account of how the newly found Church was emerging. He was able to deduct that certain issues identified in the first letter were still prevalent. In some cases, the scenarios have gotten worse.
One strong opposition identified was a letter supposed to have been written by Paul in which was claimed that the 2nd Coming had already taken place! Such a rumor ignited the confusion and fear responsible for idleness within this body of Christ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IEEE 1584-2018 | Guide for Performing Arc Flash Calculations</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ieee-1584-2018-guide-for-performing-arc-flash-calculations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:10:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ieee-1584-2018-guide-for-performing-arc-flash-calculations/</guid>
      <description>Welcome, Everyone!
This is Abdur from AllumiaX Engineering headquartered in Seattle, Washington. We do power systems engineering for industrial commercial customers. And in this technical course, we&#39;re going to talk about the IEEE-1584 2018 published standard. It is the guide for performing arc flash hazard calculations. And I want to walk you through some of the things that we&#39;re going to cover in this technical course. So, let&#39;s get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified Manager of Quality/Organizational Excellence Exams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-manager-of-quality/organizational-excellence-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 17:02:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-manager-of-quality/organizational-excellence-exams/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to crush the Certified Manager of Quality/Organizational Excellence CMQ-OE Exam and get certified?
Today is a competitive world and the smartest, best, and most qualified get paid a lot of money to work in amazing fields. But you don’t need a college degree, certification is an amazing path that opens up new opportunities and shows employers that you are the cream of the crop. We know that ASQ certification will add some flair to that resume and help you get amazing new roles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified Quality Engineer CQE Practice Exams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-quality-engineer-cqe-practice-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 17:02:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-quality-engineer-cqe-practice-exams/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to crush the Certified Quality Engineer and get certified?
Today is a competitive world and the smartest, best, and most qualified get paid a lot of money to work in amazing fields. But you don’t need a college degree, certification is an amazing path that opens up new opportunities and shows employers that you are the cream of the crop. We know that ASQ certification will add some flair to that resume and help you get amazing new roles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified Quality Improvement Associate CQIA Practice Exams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-quality-improvement-associate-cqia-practice-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 17:02:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-quality-improvement-associate-cqia-practice-exams/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to crush the Certified Quality Improvement Associate and get certified?
Today is a competitive world and the smartest, best, and most qualified get paid a lot of money to work in amazing fields. But you don’t need a college degree, certification is an amazing path that opens up new opportunities and shows employers that you are the cream of the crop. We know that ASQ certification will add some flair to that resume and help you get amazing new roles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMP® Practice Test Exam 2022 - PMBOK6</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pmp-practice-test-exam-2022-pmbok6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 17:02:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pmp-practice-test-exam-2022-pmbok6/</guid>
      <description>Get Ready To Prepare Like You’ve Never Prepared Before
As we often say at AFAQ Formations , work smarter not harder. You are about to see a study guide that took hours of hard collection work, expert preparation, and constant feedback. That’s why we know this exam prep will help you get that high-score on your journey to certification. Our study guides are the real thing.
What Should You Know Before Studying The PMP?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Your First Udemy Course For Beginners - Unofficial</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/creating-your-first-udemy-course-for-beginners-unofficial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/creating-your-first-udemy-course-for-beginners-unofficial/</guid>
      <description>I know its difficult time for many especially those whose jobs has been affected with a lack of economic activities during the recent lockdown. When I go grocer shopping, I see many people just having a look of uncertainty and have worried about their financial well being. Even my personal friends has been asking around for new jobs or new opportunities out there fearing they may lose their current jobs. While many companies are facing a difficult time, other industries has been booming especially ones dealing with products or services with a strong presence online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spatial Analysis using Arcgis</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/spatial-analysis-using-arcgis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/spatial-analysis-using-arcgis/</guid>
      <description>تحليل المجالي اهم الخطوات في نظم المعلومات الجغرافية
هل تجد كتب وأدلة نظم المعلومات الجغرافية والبيانات المكانية غامضة للغاية ومكلفة وغير عملية وتبحث عن دورة تأخذك بيدك وتعلمك كل المفاهيم وتبدأ في مشروع حقيقي؟
أو ربما تريد توفير الوقت ومعرفة كيفية أتمتة بعض مهام نظم المعلومات الجغرافية الأكثر شيوعًا؟ أنا متحمس جدًا لأنك وجدت دورة تحليل البيانات المكانية الخاصة بي. توفر الدورة التدريبية الخاصة بي أساسًا لتنفيذ مهام تحليل البيانات المكانية العملية الواقعية في أطر البرامج المجانية والشائعة.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Writing a scientific research article</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/writing-a-scientific-research-article/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/writing-a-scientific-research-article/</guid>
      <description>This course is here to help people who are relatively new to writing scientific research articles with the writing process. I tried to make the course that I wish I had when I was writing my own first research article. It is meant to help you become more effective at writing, and to get you started writing immediately, while taking this course. In section one, you will
Learn about the different types of scientific article</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desafío Súper Profesionales 3.0 Exponencial</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/desaf%C3%ADo-s%C3%BAper-profesionales-3.0-exponencial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/desaf%C3%ADo-s%C3%BAper-profesionales-3.0-exponencial/</guid>
      <description>La inteligencia humana va más allá de los aspectos cognitivos e intelectuales. Existen muchos estudios que demuestran que las carencias en las habilidades de Inteligencia Emocional afectan a los seres humanos dentro y fuera del contexto social.
Las personas emocionalmente inteligentes no sólo son más hábiles para percibir, comprender y manejar sus propias emociones, sino también son más capaces de extrapolar sus habilidades de percepción, comprensión y manejo a las emociones de los demás.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LSSYB: Lean Six Sigma Yellow Belt Practice Exam</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lssyb-lean-six-sigma-yellow-belt-practice-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lssyb-lean-six-sigma-yellow-belt-practice-exam/</guid>
      <description>Get Ready To Prepare Like You’ve Never Prepared Before
As we often say at AFAQ Formations, work smarter not harder. You are about to see a study guide that took hours of hard collection work, expert preparation, and constant feedback. That’s why we know this exam prep will help you get that high-score on your journey to certification.
Your Journey To Pass The LSSYB
Perhaps this is your first step toward the certification, or perhaps you are coming back for another round.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LSSBB: Lean Six Sigma Black Belt Practice Exam</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lssbb-lean-six-sigma-black-belt-practice-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lssbb-lean-six-sigma-black-belt-practice-exam/</guid>
      <description>Get Ready To Prepare Like You’ve Never Prepared Before
As we often say at AFAQ Formations, work smarter not harder. You are about to see a study guide that took hours of hard collection work, expert preparation, and constant feedback. That’s why we know this exam prep will help you get that high-score on your journey to certification.
Your Journey To Pass The LSSBB
Perhaps this is your first step toward the certification, or perhaps you are coming back for another round.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LSSGB: Lean Six Sigma Green Belt Practice Exam</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lssgb-lean-six-sigma-green-belt-practice-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lssgb-lean-six-sigma-green-belt-practice-exam/</guid>
      <description>Get Ready To Prepare Like You’ve Never Prepared Before
As we often say at AFAQ Formations, work smarter not harder. You are about to see a study guide that took hours of hard collection work, expert preparation, and constant feedback. That’s why we know this exam prep will help you get that high-score on your journey to certification.
Your Journey To Pass The LSSGB
Perhaps this is your first step toward the certification, or perhaps you are coming back for another round.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LSSMBB: Lean Six Sigma Master Black Belt Practice Exam</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lssmbb-lean-six-sigma-master-black-belt-practice-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lssmbb-lean-six-sigma-master-black-belt-practice-exam/</guid>
      <description>Get Ready To Prepare Like You’ve Never Prepared Before
As we often say at AFAQ Formations, work smarter not harder. You are about to see a study guide that took hours of hard collection work, expert preparation, and constant feedback. That’s why we know this exam prep will help you get that high-score on your journey to certification.
Your Journey To Pass The LSSMBB
Perhaps this is your first step toward the certification, or perhaps you are coming back for another round.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LSSWB: Lean Six Sigma White Belt Practice Exam</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lsswb-lean-six-sigma-white-belt-practice-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lsswb-lean-six-sigma-white-belt-practice-exam/</guid>
      <description>Get Ready To Prepare Like You’ve Never Prepared Before
As we often say at AFAQ Formations, work smarter not harder. You are about to see a study guide that took hours of hard collection work, expert preparation, and constant feedback. That’s why we know this exam prep will help you get that high-score on your journey to certification.
Your Journey To Pass The LSSWB
Perhaps this is your first step toward the certification, or perhaps you are coming back for another round.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The English Conversation Course | Master the key expressions</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-english-conversation-course-master-the-key-expressions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-english-conversation-course-master-the-key-expressions/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our English Conversation Course!
By taking this course, you will develop the most important English skill - the ability to converse in English.
In this course, you will learn how to converse in English in topics that are relevant for for beginner learners, so we deal with the most common topics, such as talking about names and age, and the language structure is appropriate for beginner learners. The main aim of this course is to develop your speaking skill, so in every video lesson, there are various speaking practices meaning that you will need to speak out loud and participate in every lesson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Google Classroom Course: Teaching Google Classroom</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-google-classroom-course-teaching-google-classroom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 16:38:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-google-classroom-course-teaching-google-classroom/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Google Classroom Course: Teaching Google Classroom: Become a Master At Teaching Google Classroom - Teaching Online with Google Classroom - Google Certified Educator
Recent Updates:
How do I record my screen recording video?
Added 3 videos guide for new Google Classroom update 1. Environment 2. Invite by URL 3. Return Once All with 1 click Added Lecture on How You Can Do Math in Google Classroom Using Docs and Math Type How to Keep Your Devices Secure Complete Guide of Making and Keeping Passwords that You Haven&#39;t Heard Of!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become a Successful Online Teacher - Teach Online Students</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/become-a-successful-online-teacher-teach-online-students/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 17:17:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/become-a-successful-online-teacher-teach-online-students/</guid>
      <description>Online course creation has never been easier, faster, or simpler. But creating a bestseller on Udemy that reaches a wide audience, has an impact, and makes your significant money is difficult. This course is designed for people who are really serious about their online instructor careers. If you are beyond the stage of being impressed with yourself just for having an online course and want more, then this course is for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn basic Italian in 2 hours</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-basic-italian-in-2-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 17:17:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-basic-italian-in-2-hours/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever found yourself wanting to learn Italian, but never actually doing so?
Start now! It is easy and fast!
You’ve heard it’s a difficult language? Don’t believe everything that they tell you.
Italian is an easy and funny language.
What about learning basic Italian in only two hours?This is a practical, fast and easy course. With it, you will immediately be able to have a basic conversation in the Italian language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aprenda rapidamente o Inglês Britânico e divirta-se. Curso#6</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprenda-rapidamente-o-ingl%C3%AAs-brit%C3%A2nico-e-divirta-se.-curso#6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 20:24:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprenda-rapidamente-o-ingl%C3%AAs-brit%C3%A2nico-e-divirta-se.-curso#6/</guid>
      <description>Please be aware. This course is for &#34;COMPLETE&#34; beginners
British English lessons easy to understand and follow. Course 1 of 50
This is the course you are looking for. A completely new approach to learning English. This is a basic English course lasting 30 to 40 minutes in each class, easy to follow and understand. We use real examples in short films in a clear conversational methodology. Prof. Steve Bradeley is British and has 30 years of teaching experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultrasonic Testing Level 1 Training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultrasonic-testing-level-1-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 20:24:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultrasonic-testing-level-1-training/</guid>
      <description>This course teaches you how to perform ultrasonic inspection from beginning to end.
The course provides you with Level 1 training in the fundamentals of Ultrasonic Testing methods. It will introduce you to the basic concepts and principles and includes hands-on training using Ultrasonic Testing equipment settings and functions.The Ultrasonic theories presented will provide the knowledge of Ultrasonic Testing required and enable you to work with individuals qualified and certified to gain needed experience for qualification as Level 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invade Your Classroom with Digital Robot Teachers in 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/invade-your-classroom-with-digital-robot-teachers-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 22:09:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/invade-your-classroom-with-digital-robot-teachers-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience the online course &#34;Invade Your Classroom with Digital Robot Teachers in 2022&#34;.
Get ready to provide professional training using computer avatars that directly interact and engage with users. The impact of avatars on education is simply incredible. Avatar-guided programs allow teachers like you to train in a virtual classroom.
What&#39;s having an avatar all about?
An avatar is a figure or character that can be created and customized using cloud-based tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teacher Training - How to Teach Online - Remote Teaching 1Hr</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/teacher-training-how-to-teach-online-remote-teaching-1hr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 20:10:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/teacher-training-how-to-teach-online-remote-teaching-1hr/</guid>
      <description>(Please note this is a beginner course designed to be completed in less than one hour for classroom teachers who are looking to become more comfortable and confident teaching online.)
Online Teacher Training
The Coronavirus has changed the world. Teachers who have spent a lifetime teaching students in the classroom must now learn (quickly!) how to teach students online and in virtual classrooms.
This course is designed for busy, stressed teachers who are battling numerous crises at the moment and don&#39;t have time for a 1-3 day course on online teacher training.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prokon Civil Engineering Structural Design R.C.C Element</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/prokon-civil-engineering-structural-design-r.c.c-element/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:16:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/prokon-civil-engineering-structural-design-r.c.c-element/</guid>
      <description>This course teaches you all the things required for the structural analysis and design of a r.c.c structural elements This course, as the title says, doesn&#39;t require you to have any prior experience in this software or any other structural design software. It will teach all the aspects of the software from very basic and will take you to the higher levels of the software as the course progresses. The course has been very systematically arranged so that you can best understand the software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STAAD Pro V8 Industrial Steel Warehouse Design from A to Z</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/staad-pro-v8-industrial-steel-warehouse-design-from-a-to-z/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:16:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/staad-pro-v8-industrial-steel-warehouse-design-from-a-to-z/</guid>
      <description>This course teaches you all the things required for the structural analysis and design of a steel warehouse building. This course, as the title says, doesn&#39;t require you to have any prior experience in this software or any other structural design software. It will teach all the aspects of the software from very basic and will take you to the higher levels of the software as the course progresses. The course has been very systematically arranged so that you can best understand the software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Grammar tenses &amp; structures</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-grammar-tenses-structures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-grammar-tenses-structures/</guid>
      <description>It is a well-crafted course. It teaches you how to build English grammar sentences which are perfect in both structures and tenses. It takes you to step by step to be able to differentiate among subject, verb, and object. It enables you to transform any English sentence from active to passive and vice versa. We provide you with daily quizzes that come with model answers.
Ratings: 4.41/5
Enrollments: 198164
Coupon Code: APRIL2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importance of Power Quality in Power System</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/importance-of-power-quality-in-power-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/importance-of-power-quality-in-power-system/</guid>
      <description>We&#39;re going to talk about the importance of power quality in the power systems, we&#39;re going to talk about the causes of power quality, uncertain events from the utility end, generation, transmission, and distribution as well as from the consumer and the manufacturer end, the common power quality issues and parameters such as on the transient side, the voltage variation side, the unbalanced voltages, the flickers, the distorted waveforms, the thing called total harmonic distortion and what that means as well as power factor and varying frequency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insight to Post Pandemic: Importance of Lean Six Sigma</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/insight-to-post-pandemic-importance-of-lean-six-sigma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/insight-to-post-pandemic-importance-of-lean-six-sigma/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this ultimate course on &#34;Insight to Post Pandemic: Importance of Lean Six Sigma&#34; that contains vaulable lessons taught by &#34;Casey Ang&#34; and &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34;.
Since its introduction as a corporate strategy by Jack Welch at General Electric in 1995, Six Sigma has come a long way. Since then, it has been widely adopted in a variety of industries.
The Greek letter sigma is used by statisticians to represent the variation in a process and we all know that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2022 - Part 5</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2022-part-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2022-part-5/</guid>
      <description>Ready to see how Artificial Intelligence (AI) will take over the fiction-writing world by storm?
Welcome to experience &#34;RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2022 - Part 5&#34;.
Computer-generated fiction might seem like a tipping point for artificial intelligence (AI), but it could help us to understand the incredible world we live in and how technology has changed from time to time. The real issue of machine intelligence and literature is always compared with the potential of what human intelligence could do and machines cannot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auto Mechanic Masterclass - Car Repair Training | CAMM&#43; 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/auto-mechanic-masterclass-car-repair-training-camm-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 18:10:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/auto-mechanic-masterclass-car-repair-training-camm-2022/</guid>
      <description>*Get the Official Certificate after Completing the Course
Learn car repair and be Car Mechanic. You will learn topics of car mechanics. Auto Mechanic Masterclass - CAMM+ 2022
The heart of every car is its engine. It produces the power that turns the wheels and electricity for lights and other systems.
Most automobiles are powered by an internal combustion engine. Fuel, usually gasoline or petrol, is burned with air to create gases that expand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book of Nehemiah - How To Develop The Leader In You!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/book-of-nehemiah-how-to-develop-the-leader-in-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 18:10:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/book-of-nehemiah-how-to-develop-the-leader-in-you/</guid>
      <description>----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
It is almost impossible to discuss &#34;Leadership&#34; from a Christian perspective without delving into the Book of Nehemiah. In my view this is the only Bible Book that details the highest concentration of Leadership Traits.
In today&#39;s world the subject focus of this books reminds us of God&#39;s intention when he made man; created communities and established societies. In a nutshell the success of the entire world rests on God and those who open themselves to His form of Leadership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on RPA (Robotic Process Automation)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-rpa-robotic-process-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 18:10:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-rpa-robotic-process-automation/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in Robotic Process Automation? Don’t be stressed, take our Robotic Process Automation based quiz and prepare yourself for your Interview.
With this Robotic Process Automation based Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Robotic Process Automation based questions. In Robotic Process Automation based Multiple Choice Questions Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Basic Knowledge in Robotic Process Automation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Robotics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-robotics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 19:15:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-robotics/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in Robotics? Don’t be stressed, take our Robotics based quiz and prepare yourself for your Interview.
With this Robotics based Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Robotics based questions. In Robotics based Multiple Choice Questions Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Basic Knowledge in Robotics. Use it for training and keep yourself updated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book of Ezra - How To Enjoy The Prophetic Word Spoken On You</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/book-of-ezra-how-to-enjoy-the-prophetic-word-spoken-on-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/book-of-ezra-how-to-enjoy-the-prophetic-word-spoken-on-you/</guid>
      <description>----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
The Book of Ezra Old Testament is tightly linked to at least 8 other Books of the Bible. It is almost impossible to fully grasp how the Children of Israel experienced their restoration without reading and understanding Ezra. Bible scholars tell us that it is probable Ezra the Priest wrote the Books of 1 and 2 Chronicles, Ezra as well as Nehemiah. This Book chronicles the returns and rebuilding of Jerusalem as well as providing the New Testament Believer with tried and tested principles that we can apply to our lives today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Mathematics Math Class 8 Practical Tests and Answers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/school-mathematics-math-class-8-practical-tests-and-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/school-mathematics-math-class-8-practical-tests-and-answers/</guid>
      <description>School Mathematics Math Class 8 Practical Tests and Answers
Mathematics Math Class 8 Practical Tests and Answers %99 PASS
Mathematics (from Greek: μάθημα, máthēma, &#39;knowledge, study, learning&#39;) is an area of knowledge, which includes the study of such topics as numbers (arithmetic and number theory), formulas and related structures (algebra), shapes and spaces in which they are contained (geometry), and quantities and their changes (calculus and analysis). There is no general consensus about its exact scope or epistemological status.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Physics Class 11 Practical Tests and Answers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/school-physics-class-11-practical-tests-and-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/school-physics-class-11-practical-tests-and-answers/</guid>
      <description>School Physics Class 11 Practical Tests and Answers
Physics Lovers Save your Time and Effort ….. Physics Class 11 Practical Tests and Answers [99%PASS]
Special thanks to Ibn-ElHaytham, Isaac Newton, Albert Einstein, and other Giants who provides us &#34;Physics&#34;
Physics is the natural science that studies matter, its fundamental constituents, its motion and behavior through space and time, and the related entities of energy and force. Physics is one of the most fundamental scientific disciplines, and its main goal is to understand how the universe behaves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Physics Class 12 Practical Tests and Answers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/school-physics-class-12-practical-tests-and-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/school-physics-class-12-practical-tests-and-answers/</guid>
      <description>School Physics Class 12 Practical Tests and Answers
Physics Lovers Save your Time and Effort ….. Physics Class 12 Practical Tests and Answers [Part 2 of 2] Special thanks to Ibn-ElHaytham, Isaac Newton, Albert Einstein, and other Giants who provides us &#34;Physics&#34;
Physics is the natural science that studies matter, its fundamental constituents, its motion and behavior through space and time, and the related entities of energy and force. Physics is one of the most fundamental scientific disciplines, and its main goal is to understand how the universe behaves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2022 Armed Services Vocational Aptitude Battery ASVAB tests</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2022-armed-services-vocational-aptitude-battery-asvab-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2022-armed-services-vocational-aptitude-battery-asvab-tests/</guid>
      <description>Armed Services Vocational Aptitude Battery ASVAB tests
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily
Welcome to Our ASVAB Practice Test!Our tests are designed to help you with your ASVAB test prep and review.Each of our free ASVAB practice tests includes challenging practice questions along with detailed explanations. Whether you are preparing for a career in the Army, Navy, Air Force, or the Marines you will need to pass the ASVAB test. If you study for this test it will make a big difference in your final score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2022 Miller Analogies Test (MAT) TOP Practical Questions</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2022-miller-analogies-test-mat-top-practical-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2022-miller-analogies-test-mat-top-practical-questions/</guid>
      <description>Hello !
Most Common Miller Analogies Test (MAT) professional Questions with your hand
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily
The Miller Analogies Test (MAT) is a standardized test used both for graduate school admissions in the United States and entrance to high I.Q. societies. Created and still published by Harcourt Assessment (now a division of Pearson Education), the MAT consists of 120 questions in 60 minutes (formerly 100 questions in 50 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Petroleum Institute API PRACTICE QUESTIONS</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/american-petroleum-institute-api-practice-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/american-petroleum-institute-api-practice-questions/</guid>
      <description>The American Petroleum Institute (API) is the largest U.S. trade association for the oil and natural gas industry. It claims to represent nearly 600 corporations involved in production, refinement, distribution, and many other aspects of the petroleum industry.
The association describes its mission as to promote safety across the industry globally and influence public policy in support of a strong, viable U.S. oil and natural gas industry. API&#39;s chief functions on behalf of the industry include advocacy, negotiation and lobbying with governmental, legal, and regulatory agencies; research into economic, toxicological, and environmental effects; establishment and certification of industry standards; and education outreach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aprenda rapidamente o Inglês Britânico e divirta-se. Curso#2</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprenda-rapidamente-o-ingl%C3%AAs-brit%C3%A2nico-e-divirta-se.-curso#2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprenda-rapidamente-o-ingl%C3%AAs-brit%C3%A2nico-e-divirta-se.-curso#2/</guid>
      <description>Suas primeiras aulas de Inglês Britânico fáceis de entender e seguir. Curso 1 de 50
Este é o curso que você procura. Uma abordagem completamente nova para aprender Inglês. Este é um curso básico de Inglês com duração de 30 à 40 minutos em cada aula, fáceis de seguir e entender. Usamos exemplos reais em curtas-metragens em uma metodologia de conversação clara. O Prof. Steve Bradeley é Britânico e tem mais de 30 anos de experiência docente.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aprenda rapidamente o Inglês Britânico e divirta-se. Curso#4</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprenda-rapidamente-o-ingl%C3%AAs-brit%C3%A2nico-e-divirta-se.-curso#4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprenda-rapidamente-o-ingl%C3%AAs-brit%C3%A2nico-e-divirta-se.-curso#4/</guid>
      <description>COURSE DESCRIPTION
Suas primeiras aulas de inglês britânico fáceis de entender e seguir.
Este é o curso que você procura. Uma abordagem completamente nova para aprender inglês. Este é um curso básico dos primeiros 30 a 40 minutos de aulas de inglês fáceis de entender. Usamos exemplos reais em curtas-metragens e uma metodologia de conversação clara. O professor é britânico e tem 30 anos de experiência docente. Ele é assistido pela mais moderna tecnologia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinical Research in Pharmaceutical Industry Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/clinical-research-in-pharmaceutical-industry-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/clinical-research-in-pharmaceutical-industry-course/</guid>
      <description>A career in clinical research promises productive jobs in the country and abroad. At present, India is the most preferred hub for clinical trials among all the Asian countries.
If you are looking for a Career in clinical research in India, then keep reading the description below:
What is Clinical Research :
The health sector is an important sector in the economy. It not only provides health care facilities but also generates great academic and career choices for aspirants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete IPQC Tests for Pharmaceutical Tablet Dosage Form</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-ipqc-tests-for-pharmaceutical-tablet-dosage-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-ipqc-tests-for-pharmaceutical-tablet-dosage-form/</guid>
      <description>The development of a drug product is a lengthy process involving drug discovery, laboratory testing, animal studies, clinical trials and regulatory registration. To further enhance the effectiveness and safety of the drug product after approval, many regulatory agencies such as the United States Food and Drug Administration (FDA) also require that the drug product be tested for its identity, strength, quality, purity and stability before it can be released for use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eCTD &amp; CTD Preparation &amp; Submission Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ectd-ctd-preparation-submission-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ectd-ctd-preparation-submission-course/</guid>
      <description>The eCTD specification has been developed to facilitate the Global electronic Submission, Review and Lifecycle management of medicinal product dossiers for regulatory applications. *Complete the course as per your free time as life time access is available.
If you are paying more than 5k INR or $70 for private institute/academy then you are in loss. Please compare the course description and amount you are paying for such course.
It broadens the scope of the CTD to include information on variations, renewals and amendments, so that it is no longer a static document but is updatable throughout the life of the product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pharmaceutical Clinical Bioequivalence Study (BA/BE)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pharmaceutical-clinical-bioequivalence-study-ba/be/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pharmaceutical-clinical-bioequivalence-study-ba/be/</guid>
      <description>Bioequivalence studies are very important for the development of a pharmaceutical preparation in the pharmaceutical industry. Their rationale is the monitoring of pharmacokinetic and pharmacodynamic parameters after the administration of tested drugs.
Note: If you are paying more than 5k INR or $15 for private institute/academy then you are in loss. Please compare the course description and amount you are paying for such course.
Bioavailability &amp;amp; Bioequivalence
Bioavailability (BA) is defined as the rate and extent to which the unchanged active substance is absorbed and becomes available in the systemic circulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Mathematics Math Class 10 Practical Tests and Answers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/school-mathematics-math-class-10-practical-tests-and-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/school-mathematics-math-class-10-practical-tests-and-answers/</guid>
      <description>School Mathematics Math Class 10 Practical Tests and Answers
Save your Time and Effort ..... Mathematics Math Class 10 Practical Tests and Answers %99 PASS
Mathematics (from Greek: μάθημα, máthēma, &#39;knowledge, study, learning&#39;) is an area of knowledge, which includes the study of such topics as numbers (arithmetic and number theory), formulas and related structures (algebra), shapes and spaces in which they are contained (geometry), and quantities and their changes (calculus and analysis).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Mathematics Math Class 11 Practical Tests and Answers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/school-mathematics-math-class-11-practical-tests-and-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/school-mathematics-math-class-11-practical-tests-and-answers/</guid>
      <description>School Mathematics Math Class 11 Practical Tests and Answers
Save your Time and Effort ..... Mathematics Math Class 10 Practical Tests and Answers [%99 PASS]
Mathematics (from Greek: μάθημα, máthēma, &#39;knowledge, study, learning&#39;) is an area of knowledge, which includes the study of such topics as numbers (arithmetic and number theory), formulas and related structures (algebra), shapes and spaces in which they are contained (geometry), and quantities and their changes (calculus and analysis).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Mathematics Math Class 9 Practical Tests and Answers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/school-mathematics-math-class-9-practical-tests-and-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/school-mathematics-math-class-9-practical-tests-and-answers/</guid>
      <description>School Mathematics Math Class 9 Practical Tests and Answers
Mathematics Math Class 9 Practical Tests and Answers %99 PASS
Mathematics (from Greek: μάθημα, máthēma, &#39;knowledge, study, learning&#39;) is an area of knowledge, which includes the study of such topics as numbers (arithmetic and number theory), formulas and related structures (algebra), shapes and spaces in which they are contained (geometry), and quantities and their changes (calculus and analysis). There is no general consensus about its exact scope or epistemological status.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arabic Language Course For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/arabic-language-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/arabic-language-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>New Updates
We added new Lessons to &#34; Arabic Language Course For Beginners &#34;
Here is what we added:
Greetings
Subject Pronouns
How to make a Sentence in Arabic
Arabic Numbers
Week Days
The Universe
Family Members
Body Parts
Introduce Yourself
At the Airport
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
السلام عليكم
In this Course, we will learn Arabic Alphabet from Alef to Yaa
Firstly, we will take general view for all letters,
then, we will learn each letter in details :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climatology - Meteorology of Climate</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/climatology-meteorology-of-climate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/climatology-meteorology-of-climate/</guid>
      <description>Climatology and Meteorology is a field of study on climate, to study the climate, we know how we can predict the weather and forecasting, If we can grasp the laws of climate we can benefit the economy and society. The resident that do laundry every day is inseparable from climate condition, as well the same as farmer, the construction worker, the seafarer, the fisherman, the miner, the traveler, the journalist, also the aviation flight that pilot the plane are closely relate to the climate condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Grammar with Movies</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-grammar-with-movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-grammar-with-movies/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to The English Grammar With Movies!
This course offers 530 intermediate to advanced level English grammar questions within 6 Practice Tests, all prepared by a certified instructor. It is highly recommended to watch the following movies before starting the course: Tropic Thunder, Interstellar, The Matrix, Inception, Pulp Fiction, Django Unchained, The Wolf of Wall Street.
Grammar topics you will practice in this course: Tenses, Articles, Irregular Verbs, Gerunds, Infinitives, Quantifiers, Prepositions, and Linking Words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HVAC Chillers system inside District cooling plant</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hvac-chillers-system-inside-district-cooling-plant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hvac-chillers-system-inside-district-cooling-plant/</guid>
      <description>Hi! Welcome to our course. If you are starting to study in the HVAC industry, or wished to gain more knowledge in an area that seems complicated and confusing to most people, you are on the right course!. This Course covers the Chilled water system in the district cooling plant and inside the building through heat exchangers, Air handling units, and FCU&#39;s, it will build your knowledge slowly until you reach the point that you can evaluating, selecting, and sizing chillers for a typical chiller plant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acting course - tools of acting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/acting-course-tools-of-acting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 16:17:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/acting-course-tools-of-acting/</guid>
      <description>In this acting course, Ram Choudhary teach about acting (camera &amp;amp; theater), diction, navras, characterisation, body language, dialogue delivery &amp;amp; importance of backstories ( how to bring real-life experiences into every role and how to build your own characters). As a trained actor from theater ,he uses advanced acting techniques to portray complex characters. he introduces students to various methods and techniques which he use to teach and enhance their acting skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ajedrez Esencial. Aprende a jugar Ajedrez desde CERO</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ajedrez-esencial.-aprende-a-jugar-ajedrez-desde-cero/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 16:17:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ajedrez-esencial.-aprende-a-jugar-ajedrez-desde-cero/</guid>
      <description>Actualmente, el ajedrez ha tomado gran protagonismo, luego de la gran serie de Netflix &#34;Gambito de dama&#34;, muchos han buscado cómo aprender a jugar y adentrarse en el deporte.
En este curso, te enseñaré a comenzar en el ajedrez sin ningún conocimiento previo, aprenderás desde las bases y comprenderás la manera de jugar al ajedrez.
Aprenderás a mover las piezas, temas estrategicos, temas tácticos, temas de finales... Con este conocimiento podrás jugar al Ajedrez con tus amigos, familiares o incluso en alguna plataforma de Ajedrez Online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of Industry 4.0</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentals-of-industry-4.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 11:27:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentals-of-industry-4.0/</guid>
      <description>Hi Friends,
In this course we will start learning about Industry 4.0 which is actually the foundation of the digital transformation of the Industry. This course is beneficial for you in Starting Level. In this Course you learn all about the Industry 4.0 that How Industry 4.0 grow from Industry 1.0.
The Content of the Course are:
What is Industry 4.0?
Industry 4.0: The Fourth Industrial Revolution
Component of Industry 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn ETABS &amp; SAFE in the Structural Design of 15 Stories RC</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-etabs-safe-in-the-structural-design-of-15-stories-rc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 13:12:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-etabs-safe-in-the-structural-design-of-15-stories-rc/</guid>
      <description>This course not just a tutorial on software ETABS and SAFE but it is a complete understanding about structural design analysis, how civil engineer must begin with the project, how he/she must think, how we can determine the dimension of the element before modeling them check it in the software. In this course we will design a 15 stories of a residential buildings, within the work we will define and design all types of slabs such as (waffle slab, one way ribbed slab, two way ribbed slab, flat slab and solid slab), all types of foundations such as (isolated,combined,strip and mat), earthquake with static and dynamic case, wind loads, columns and beams and shear walls + Advanced lectures in ETABS + Advanced lecture in SAFE and AllPile (design piles deep foundation of a tower of 25 stories) + design a swimming pool in ETABS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Melody of English</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-melody-of-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 13:12:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-melody-of-english/</guid>
      <description>Intonation signals to your audience that you are connecting thought units or ending them. Sometimes we end them with finality, uncertainty, questions, or excitement, for example. Intonation helps listeners follow you with ease. Intonation also gives language a melody and keeps it from sounding boring. This course will teach you proper breathing that works in sync with your intonation. You will also learn how to divide vowels so that the vowels can carry the intonation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Spanish Now: All-in-One Knowledge Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-spanish-now-all-in-one-knowledge-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 21:27:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-spanish-now-all-in-one-knowledge-course/</guid>
      <description>Learn Spanish Now: All-in-One Knowledge Course is a condensed Latin American Spanish (small difference from Spain Spanish) course built to teach students of all levels (from beginners to experienced) in a self-paced and approachable manner that avoids the awkwardness or time constraints of a classroom. This course delves deeper than just teaching you how to say a simple greeting or basic nouns, it actually aims to get you engaged and involved in speaking and writing in the language as soon as your first day through interactive video lessons and lectures, and resources only available to students in this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selling Your Knowledge: Learn How to Make Money Online</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/selling-your-knowledge-learn-how-to-make-money-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 21:27:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/selling-your-knowledge-learn-how-to-make-money-online/</guid>
      <description>One of the greatest ways to earn an income fast and consistently is by using what you already know and teaching it to someone else! As Bill Nye once said: &#34;Everyone you will ever meet knows something you don&#39;t.&#34; This is true and is why you don&#39;t have to worry about what you don&#39;t know because I guarantee that you most likely have a skill or know something that you know you can teach to someone else (trust me).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vector Crash Course 2022: Learn Vector in 5 Hours</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/vector-crash-course-2022-learn-vector-in-5-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 21:27:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/vector-crash-course-2022-learn-vector-in-5-hours/</guid>
      <description>How to become an expert on Vector ? It seems vector as one of the easy lesson but reality is different for some students. For those students who feels Vector as a difficult lesson, this course helps you to understand easily. It is the 50+ videos lessons and each video teaches you very important concepts in Vector. There will be some quizzes and workbooks including in the upcoming days.
Become an expert on Vector: The content is organized into the following sections:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arabic Language Course: Learn to Read Arabic, Write &amp; Listen</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/arabic-language-course-learn-to-read-arabic-write-listen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:37:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/arabic-language-course-learn-to-read-arabic-write-listen/</guid>
      <description>New Update: We added Arabic Audiobook + MP3 Files + Translation in English.
New Update: We added new Section to Learn Writing in Arabic.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
السلام عليكم
In this Course, you will learn to Read, Write &amp;amp; Listen to Arabic through Short Stories &amp;amp; Audiobooks.
This Course is divided into 9 Sections:
In the First Section: you will learn How to Write &amp;amp; Pronounce Arabic Alphabet, and we will take some words for each letter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aprenda os Tempos Verbais do Inglês A GRAMÁTICA CORRETA</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprenda-os-tempos-verbais-do-ingl%C3%AAs-a-gram%C3%A1tica-correta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 18:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprenda-os-tempos-verbais-do-ingl%C3%AAs-a-gram%C3%A1tica-correta/</guid>
      <description>Este curso rápido de 90 minutos com 14 vídeos, é projetado para você que quer tornar-se um falante fluente de Inglês em níveis Iniciante, Intermediário e Avançado e se concentrará na introdução ou aprimoramento da Gramática Inglesa. O conteúdo foi preparado e é apresentado pelo Prof. Steve W. Bradeley. Nascido no Reino Unido, é experiente no ensino de Inglês por mais de 30 anos e que além de lecionar em escolas em Londres, possui publicações voltadas no ramo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bible: 2 Timothy - 7 Lessons We Can Learn For Today!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bible-2-timothy-7-lessons-we-can-learn-for-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 18:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bible-2-timothy-7-lessons-we-can-learn-for-today/</guid>
      <description>The Book of 2 Timothy illustrates profound truths about:
God&#39;s desire for man The end of man
End times prophesy
Paul&#39;s future
Ministry succession
Hope
Loyalty
Weakness
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Whether one of your favorite scriptures is about God giving us the spirit of power, of love and of self discipline or I have fought the good fight, I have finished the race and I have kept the faith; the book of 2 Timothy includes the above and also abounds with much more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bible: Titus - 7 Lessons We Can Learn For Today!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bible-titus-7-lessons-we-can-learn-for-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 15:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bible-titus-7-lessons-we-can-learn-for-today/</guid>
      <description>Review From Other Books Book of 2 Peter
&#34;I had read Book 2 Peter after your teaching. Thank you. I wish that I could read the rest of the books in Bible thoroughly in future&#34;. - Cynthia Josephine
Book of Philippians! The instructor has a notable passion for sharing the Book of Philippians! (All the Books of the Bible) That passion drew me to seriously consider his engaging presentation. The instructor challenged me to see myself through the eyes of my Lord and Savior - not the eyes of the world!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leer Nederlands in het Nederlands 2: voor beginners (NT2-A1)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/leer-nederlands-in-het-nederlands-2-voor-beginners-nt2-a1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 15:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/leer-nederlands-in-het-nederlands-2-voor-beginners-nt2-a1/</guid>
      <description>Klaar om online Nederlands te leren? Hou je van Nederlands?
Ken je al ongeveer 100-150 woorden?
Hou je van een uitdaging?
Leer je liever online talen?
Goed zo! Je gaat met mij de Nederlandse taal leren... 100% in het Nederlands!
Een cursus voor beginners, maar niet voor absolute beginners
De cursus start niet vanaf 0, kijk naar mijn eerste cursus &#39;Nederlands in het Nederlands 1&#39; op Udemy. Je moet ongeveer 100-150 woorden begrijpen, maar veel woorden gaan we herhalen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aromaterapia Veterinaria - Aceites Esenciales en el Perro</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aromaterapia-veterinaria-aceites-esenciales-en-el-perro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aromaterapia-veterinaria-aceites-esenciales-en-el-perro/</guid>
      <description>¡Bienvenidos a este curso de Aromaterapia Veterinaria Canina!
El uso de aceites esenciales en medicina veterinaria esta en pleno auge. Muchas preguntas surgen acerca de la posibilidad de su empleo en el perro: cómo, cuánto, cuándo y cuáles aceites se pueden elegir. Este curso pretende contestar a esas preguntas, proponiendo un uso racional y medido de los aceites esenciales en el perro.
Dedicado a veterinarios, estudiantes de veterinaria, criadores y dueños responsables de mascotas, este curso permite resolver los casos más comunes con la ayuda de la aromaterapia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curso de Fitoterapia Canina : Plantas Medicinales para Perro</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-de-fitoterapia-canina-plantas-medicinales-para-perro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-de-fitoterapia-canina-plantas-medicinales-para-perro/</guid>
      <description>¡Bienvenidos a este curso de Fitoterapia Veterinaria Canina!
El uso de plantas medicinales en medicina veterinaria esta en pleno auge. Muchas preguntas surgen acerca de la posibilidad de su empleo en el perro: cómo, cuánto, cuándo y cuáles plantas se pueden eligir. Este curso pretende contestar a esas preguntas, proponiendo un uso racional y medido de las plantas en el perro.
Dedicado a veterinarios, estudiantes de veterinaria, criadores y dueños responsables de mascotas, este curso permite resolver los casos más comunes con la ayuda de la fitoterapia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2021 - Part 4</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-4/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this marvelous course that will walk you through powerful content writing tools that will aid you in your career as a content creator. Taking a leap from RoboAuthor Part 3, this Part 4 course taught by Digital Marketing Legend Srinidhi Ranganathan and Saranya Srinidhi will continue your adventure in content writing to unlock opportunities for more ultra-fast writing and creation with the ultimate power of Artificial Intelligence (AI). Until now, people believed that machines are unable to mimic the dynamic thought process or what we call imagination - that humans leverage to write.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of Electrical and Electronics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentals-of-electrical-and-electronics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:30:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentals-of-electrical-and-electronics/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in Electronics and Electrical Industry? Don’t be stressed, take our Electrical Engineering Course and prepare yourself for your Interview. In this Course You Understand the basic Concept of Electrical Engineering.
WHAT IS FOR YOU?
Knowledge of Electrical and Electronics is extremely valuable nowadays! In this Course you understand the Basic Concept of Electrical and Electronics Component. Here You Understand the Basic Concept of Current, Voltage, Energy and Power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2021 - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:30:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this superb course that will walk you through the future of content creation. Taking a leap from RoboAuthor Part 1, this Part 2 course taught by Digital Marketing Legend Srinidhi Ranganathan and MasterMind Saranya Srinidhi will continue your adventure in content writing to open a new door of opportunities that is incredibly futuristic. It is undoubtedly one of the most challenging tasks to create content for your digital marketing campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Corinthians: 13 Life Changing Lessons</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2-corinthians-13-life-changing-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 21:08:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2-corinthians-13-life-changing-lessons/</guid>
      <description>&#34;A few days before completing this course I visited my auto mechanic for a minor repair. Shortly after parking, a reckless lorry driver smashed into it.! I was completely upset because he tried to cover up the incident by not reporting himself. We had to trail through 4 hours of videotape to identify the culprit.
Whilst mauling over the situation I directed my thoughts to Romans 8 and considered that this will work together for my good somehow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Filipino Course: Learn Filipino for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-filipino-course-learn-filipino-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 17:47:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-filipino-course-learn-filipino-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>The ultimate Filipino beginner course that will teach you Filipino faster than you thought possible! Perhaps you’ve dreamed of travelling to the Philippines and holding your own in real-life situations, being independent and able to communicate with the locals. Perhaps you want to experience the rich culture and sample the delicious local cuisine or do business with local companies. Whatever your reason, this Filipino course for beginners is right for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fisioterapia Veterinaria : Masajes en pequeños animales</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fisioterapia-veterinaria-masajes-en-peque%C3%B1os-animales/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 13:37:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fisioterapia-veterinaria-masajes-en-peque%C3%B1os-animales/</guid>
      <description>Bienvenido al mundo apasionante de la terapia con las manos !
Un sistema sencillo empleado desde los inicios, resultando muchas veces en una acción instintiva, cuando nos golpeamos y nuestras madres nos frotaba la zona con la mano para calmar el dolor.
En medicina veterinaria tuvo su comienzo en los caballos en los emperadores de Roma, a los cuales se les aplicaba distintas formas de masajes. Todo esto determinado por factores económicos y sociales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arabic language conversational beginner course | byna yadek</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/arabic-language-conversational-beginner-course-byna-yadek/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 22:20:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/arabic-language-conversational-beginner-course-byna-yadek/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I&#39;m Mr.Bakoor. I have been teaching Arabic language for a while. I got students form All over the world. My respect for all of them. My students liked the way I teach because It&#39;s easy, it goes step by step, they easily understand and also show improvement, I feel so happy when I my student telling me that they are really improving in Arabic langauge, I hope to make Arabic teaching easier for everyone who think Learning Arabic is hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Churches &amp; NGO/Charity Can Generate More Income Streams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-churches-ngo/charity-can-generate-more-income-streams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 22:20:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-churches-ngo/charity-can-generate-more-income-streams/</guid>
      <description>If you answer to any of the above two questions is yes - then join this course. In this no-fluff actionable course I will reveal to you how you, your organization can start generating additional streams of income for your Charity, NGO, Church, or Social Enterprise.
I will give you ideas and suggestions that will reveal the untapped opportunities that you can use to start generating income for your organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sell Online Courses: The Course Description Writing Formula</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sell-online-courses-the-course-description-writing-formula/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 22:20:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sell-online-courses-the-course-description-writing-formula/</guid>
      <description>If your course description is not written in the right way, you get less students.
Write a course description that really sells by using a proven formula.
Also, writing a course description can take a long time. But when you have a step-by-step process, it becomes far easier and faster. I wrote this course description in less than 15 minutes.
My name is Ian Stables. At the time of writing this, I have more than 51,000 students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Chinese Vocabulary According HSK By Flash Card V2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/test-chinese-vocabulary-according-hsk-by-flash-card-v2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 22:20:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/test-chinese-vocabulary-according-hsk-by-flash-card-v2021/</guid>
      <description>Our &#34;Test Your HSK Chinese Level in 10 Minutes&#34; is very useful for school teacher and students. New video will be added every month till December.
Our &#34;Test Your Vocabulary Level in 10 Minutes&#34; is very useful for school teacher and students. New video will be added every month till December.
We create a set of teaching contents to Assess Your Progress According HSK 1-6 Vocabulary List and CEFRL A1-C2: 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basics of CRISPR/Cas9 Technology</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basics-of-crispr/cas9-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 17:15:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basics-of-crispr/cas9-technology/</guid>
      <description>CRISPR/Cas9 is a gene-editing tool that can manipulate gene expression in plants, humans, and animals. CRISPR, or Clustered Regularly Interspaced Short Palindromic Repeats, are short sections of bacterial DNA containing repetitive base sequences. CRISPR plays a crucial role in the immune response of bacteria against foreign DNA. When a bacterium detects viral DNA, it produces two strands of short RNA called guide RNA, which then go on to form a complex with an endonuclease enzyme called Cas9 (CRISPR-associated protein 9).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vowels for Advanced Chinese learners of American English</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/vowels-for-advanced-chinese-learners-of-american-english/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 17:15:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/vowels-for-advanced-chinese-learners-of-american-english/</guid>
      <description>Meaning can be altered when listeners don&#39;t understand your vowels. Changing one vowel slightly can completely change the meaning of a word. Not spending enough time on one vowel can also change the meaning! Learn how to correct the American English vowel pronunciation errors that native Chinese speakers frequently make. The instructor uses a vowel chart to demonstrate the similarities and differences between all the vowels. Then she describes and shows exactly how to produce each vowel and puts the vowels in example sentences that use advanced vocabulary from professional settings, such as high tech and business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>英検3級二次試験対策 ｜リスニングとスピーキングの強化トレーニング</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%E8%8B%B1%E6%A4%9C3%E7%B4%9A%E4%BA%8C%E6%AC%A1%E8%A9%A6%E9%A8%93%E5%AF%BE%E7%AD%96-%E3%83%AA%E3%82%B9%E3%83%8B%E3%83%B3%E3%82%B0%E3%81%A8%E3%82%B9%E3%83%94%E3%83%BC%E3%82%AD%E3%83%B3%E3%82%B0%E3%81%AE%E5%BC%B7%E5%8C%96%E3%83%88%E3%83%AC%E3%83%BC%E3%83%8B%E3%83%B3%E3%82%B0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 17:15:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%E8%8B%B1%E6%A4%9C3%E7%B4%9A%E4%BA%8C%E6%AC%A1%E8%A9%A6%E9%A8%93%E5%AF%BE%E7%AD%96-%E3%83%AA%E3%82%B9%E3%83%8B%E3%83%B3%E3%82%B0%E3%81%A8%E3%82%B9%E3%83%94%E3%83%BC%E3%82%AD%E3%83%B3%E3%82%B0%E3%81%AE%E5%BC%B7%E5%8C%96%E3%83%88%E3%83%AC%E3%83%BC%E3%83%8B%E3%83%B3%E3%82%B0/</guid>
      <description>はじめまして、講師のビビアンです。
本講座に興味を持っていただいてありがとうございます。
この案内を見ているあなたは以下の事で悩んでいるかもしれません。
「英検3級の二次試験をこれから取りたいけど、英語には自信はない」
「英語の面接に緊張してしまうから、どうしよう」
「今度こそ英検3級に合格して来年は2級を！」
もしこのようなことで悩んでいればこの講座はあなたに向いています。
英検3級の二次試験7日トレーニングでは
面接に落ちがちの理由を知って合格するための工夫ができる
試験の模擬試験を何度も繰り返すことで緊張がなくなる
ネイティブによる発音でリスニング力がグッーと上がる
しかも、講座が終わった後でも練習し続けて一遍に不安を消してしまいます。
第二次試験は5分間しかないですが、緊張や練習不足で落ちたりする人も少なくありません。
読み書きは上手ですが、スピーキングはちょっと。
そのためにできるだけ試験のフォーマットでスピーキングとリスニングが鍛えてもらえるように、7日間集中トレーニングの英検問題集を作りました！
私は中学生をメインに、英検のトレーニングをしてきました。
本当は知っているのに、緊張で間違えてしまうのはもったいない。
この講座では、模擬試験を繰り返して行い、解説を聞くことで、
質問を聴く能力が上がる、
パッセージを読むスピーキング力が上がる、
また英語っぽい英語を話すコツを身に着ける…
試験官に良い印象をつけてもらえる面接のテクニックを紹介していきます。
更に！
ボーナスとしてEnglish Onlyのオンラインテストをたくさん用意しています。
海外移住者が一日も早く英語の県境に慣れるために練習している本格的な英語を無料でアクセスしてこれから挑戦していく英検2級や1級のために実力を蓄えましょう。
この講座を受講すると、
英検3級2次試験の全体像を知り、緊張しないで面接に合格するコツを手に入れて、リアルの英語力を鍛えていけます。
そして、英検3級に合格してから使っていける練習資料を手にすることができます！
どんな感じの講座かなあと気になったら、
レッスンのプレビューを見てくださいね。
それでは、講座の中でお会いしましょう。
Ratings: 0.00/5
Enrollments: 297
Coupon Code: 0A87B29E9324A87E6DE6
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conceptos y aplicación del sistema HACCP</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/conceptos-y-aplicaci%C3%B3n-del-sistema-haccp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 21:46:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/conceptos-y-aplicaci%C3%B3n-del-sistema-haccp/</guid>
      <description>Un sistema HACCP identifica y mejora el control de peligros significativos para la inocuidad de los alimentos. El objetivo del sistema HACCP es vigilar los puntos críticos de control (PCC). Al especificar los límites críticos para las medidas de control en los PCC y las medidas correctivas cuando no se cumplen los límites, y al producir registros que se revisan antes de la liberación del producto, el HACCP proporciona un control coherente y verificable que va más allá de lo que logran los PPR o Programas Pre requisitos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aptitude Test Prep : The Most Tricky Questions and More</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aptitude-test-prep-the-most-tricky-questions-and-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 17:12:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aptitude-test-prep-the-most-tricky-questions-and-more/</guid>
      <description>An Aptitude test is a structured assessment that aims to evaluate candidates&#39; abilities to complete certain tasks and assignments without prior experience or knowledge. The world&#39;s largest organizations use pre-employment/placement tests as a part of the Applicants Tracking System (ATS) managed by third parties. Aptitude tests could be a part of the total score of the candidate (ATS may contain information as resume, personal information, previous experience, and aptitude tests results).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American English Vowels for Indian IT Professionals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/american-english-vowels-for-indian-it-professionals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 17:51:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/american-english-vowels-for-indian-it-professionals/</guid>
      <description>In this American English pronunciation course, specifically designed to meet the needs of speakers from India, learn to accurately produce the American vowels which Indian speakers of English often confuse. These tricky vowels include learning to distinguish between &#34;peek&#34; and &#34;pick&#34; and between &#34;look&#34; and &#34;Luke.&#34; Also learn to distinguish between &#34;bone and &#34;born&#34; and many other troublesome pairs. Computer professionals can learn to reduce or minimize their accents in an IT vocabulary context.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corso base di  Scrittura Creativa Vol. 1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-base-di-scrittura-creativa-vol.-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 18:19:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-base-di-scrittura-creativa-vol.-1/</guid>
      <description>Questo corso è per i veri appassionati di scrittura, per chi prova l&#39;irrefrenabile desiderio di passare da accanito lettore a scrittore cambiando l&#39;ottica e la veduta. Al contempo è destinato anche a coloro che non ambiscono ancora ad alcuna pubblicazione di opere personali ma hanno semplicemente una smoderata passione per la scrittura e aspirano a scoprirne di più per una pura passione personale.
Se tu che mi stai leggendo hai sempre nutrito il desiderio di scrivere un libro (a prescindere dal genere che esso rappresenti), ma ti sei sentito bloccato alla prima pagina, rimasta a lungo &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gospel of Mark: Experience God&#39;s Life Changing Word Today!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gospel-of-mark-experience-gods-life-changing-word-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 18:19:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gospel-of-mark-experience-gods-life-changing-word-today/</guid>
      <description>Recent Review from a previous course:
&#34;I enjoyed this concise course on the Second Book of Timothy. The instructor does an excellent job of choosing what lessons to discuss and on making the lessons apply to your life.&#34; - Bob Klug &#34;I have heard our instructor before and he is excellent.&#34; - Florence Taber-Brown
----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Said to be the first of the written Gospels; this 16 Chapter book pens a compelling pacy account of the actions, sayings and experiences of our Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colossians - 4 Life Lessons - For Effective Transformation!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/colossians-4-life-lessons-for-effective-transformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 13:19:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/colossians-4-life-lessons-for-effective-transformation/</guid>
      <description>In this set of videos, I have given some verse by verse exposition however the focus is on how the lessons from the Bible can be applied to your daily life. It is surely a deeper dive into the book and you will get a sense of what the Holy Spirit requires you to do with what you have learned or received or heard or seen.
I believe the lessons are very informative and simplistic, for anyone whether with advanced Bible knowledge or a new Believer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Galatians - 6 Life Lessons - For Effective Transformation!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/galatians-6-life-lessons-for-effective-transformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 13:19:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/galatians-6-life-lessons-for-effective-transformation/</guid>
      <description>This Pauline letter was written to address the verbal plague that was spreading through the Church. It advocated that what Jesus did on the cross was not good enough without circumcision. Hence Paul&#39;s responses were stern and yet with an unusual depth of Old Testament revelations. As an example, Paul used the story of Ishmael mocking Isaac in the book of Genesis (21v9) to explain the manner the Jewish believers were persecuting the gentile believers at that time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gospel of Luke: For Growth In Your Relationship With God!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gospel-of-luke-for-growth-in-your-relationship-with-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 13:19:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gospel-of-luke-for-growth-in-your-relationship-with-god/</guid>
      <description>Recent Review from a previous course:
&#34;Yes, it was a great course and is very helpful for Christians&#34; - Isha Singhal &#34;I enjoyed this concise course on the Second Book of Timothy. The instructor does an excellent job of choosing what lessons to discuss and on making the lessons apply to your life.&#34; - Bob Klug &#34;It helped me to summarize Mark and use the information in teaching&#34;.- Florence Taber-Brown</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impara una nuova lingua: Tutti i segreti dei poliglotti</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/impara-una-nuova-lingua-tutti-i-segreti-dei-poliglotti/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 10:34:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/impara-una-nuova-lingua-tutti-i-segreti-dei-poliglotti/</guid>
      <description>In questo corso voglio racchiudere tutte le cose che ho imparato in oltre 10 anni di studio delle lingue straniere, sia all&#39;università che da autodidatta, applicando gli insegnamenti di chi ne sapeva più di me, non solo grandi professori ed accademici, anche e soprattutto i più famosi poliglotti, grazie a questi insegnamenti ho imparato o migliorato 5 lingue straniere (spagnolo, inglese, tedesco, cinese mandarino e portoghese) e ne sto imparando di altre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carbon Neutrality Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/carbon-neutrality-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 17:13:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/carbon-neutrality-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Carbon Neutrality Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn important knowledge about carbon neutrality and how you can contribute to a better.
I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge from carbon neutral basic to best practices in contributing to a carbon neutral future.
I will teach you the basic concepts of the different greenhouse gasses as well as the different energy options that we have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Create Amazing Visuals For Your eLearning Content</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-create-amazing-visuals-for-your-elearning-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 16:23:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-create-amazing-visuals-for-your-elearning-content/</guid>
      <description>Visuals have a critical role in a successful digital learning experience. The goal of any eLearning content is to make an impact on the users and facilitate learning, which eventually will upgrade the learner in specific real-life situations. The overall goal of any learning is always to reach a desired development in the learner´s behavior, actions.
The 90 % of corporate eLearning courses are super boring and that´s mostly because of the poor visuals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kapsamlı İngilizce Kursu</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kapsaml%C4%B1-ingilizce-kursu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 12:48:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kapsaml%C4%B1-ingilizce-kursu/</guid>
      <description>Bilindiği üzere, İngilizce başta olmak üzere yabancı dil öğrenme ile ilgili her geçen gün birçok teknik ve çalışma geliştirilmektedir. İngilizce, dünyanın dili olarak, iş ve eğitim konusunda bilinmesi elzem bir dildir. Bu kurs, yabancı dil öğrenme tekniklerinin birçok araştırma neticesinde elde edilen verilerine dayanılarak oluşturulmuş ve çalışmalar, derslere, anlayabileceğiniz bir sıra ile dizayn edilmiştir.
Bu kurs, size İngilizceyi artık mevcut olan tüm tekniklerden farklı bir şekilde öğretecek.
Bu kursta alacağınız bilgileri aslında tam da ihtiyacınız olan ve anlayabileceğiniz bir sırada öğreneceksiniz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basics of the Arabic Language</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basics-of-the-arabic-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 13:12:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basics-of-the-arabic-language/</guid>
      <description>Update | Date: November 20th, 2021. If you have any questions/comments please, do not hesitate to contact me. Good Luck!
______________________________________________________________
The Arabic language is not easy to learn but, it depends on the way of learning.
In this course, you will learn a lot through a nice way of teaching and nice lecture slides design to help you start speaking Arabic with more confidence.
This course includes: Background: Culture and History</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce Certified Administrator(201) Practice Tests 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/salesforce-certified-administrator201-practice-tests-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 13:12:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/salesforce-certified-administrator201-practice-tests-2022/</guid>
      <description>In this course, I fully prepare you for what it is like to take the Salesforce Certified Administrator Exam. With 6 practice exams, each of which is timed, I have carefully hand-crafted each question to put you to the test.
I have followed the official Exam Guide from Salesforce Certified Administrator, along with the all Knowledge Areas and corresponding weighting for each, so you can approach the actual Salesforce Certified Administrator Exam with confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Virology</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-virology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 14:59:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-virology/</guid>
      <description>You will learn about basics of Virology, history of virology, shape and structure, classification of virus, types of viruses, how are viruses beneficial, virus isolation, cultivation methods, DNA virus, RNA virus, reverse transcribing virus.
There is a glossary section in section 4 which will help you out further.
Being my third course, I have tried to make it simple.
Ratings: 4.44/5
Enrollments: 160
Coupon Code: 1B34121831F412F695ED
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Paper Writing via Advanced Research Methods</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/professional-paper-writing-via-advanced-research-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 14:59:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/professional-paper-writing-via-advanced-research-methods/</guid>
      <description>This course will provide a prospect for participants to establish or progress their considerate of optimization algorithms through critical examination of research process, approaches and publishing dimensions.
The course introduces elements of the research process within quantitative, qualitative, and mixed methods domains. Participants will use these underpinnings to begin to critically understand design thinking, large scale optimization, graph mining and hashing algorithms. They would be able to develop understanding to formulate a research question and answer it by framing an effective research methodology based on market algorithms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PgMP® : Program Management Professional Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pgmp-program-management-professional-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pgmp-program-management-professional-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>What Exactly Is Certification?
Certification is an amazing pathway to getting a high paying career in some of the best jobs in the world without spending thousands of dollars attending a four-year college.
Get Ready To Prepare Like You’ve Never Prepared Before
As we often say at AFAQ Formations, work smarter not harder. You are about to see a study guide that took hours of hard collection work, expert preparation, and constant feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publish Simple Videos For a Living - Skillshare Earnings</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/publish-simple-videos-for-a-living-skillshare-earnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/publish-simple-videos-for-a-living-skillshare-earnings/</guid>
      <description>**Our 80,000+ satisfied students and our countless 5-star reviews are no accident.** We practice what we preach ! At QualiWave, we want to share only the best content that helped us expanding in the past and still growing exponentially in the future! Let us help you to make 2020 YOUR best year ever!
PLEASE WATCH THE PROMO VIDEO FOR PROOF OF INCOME Hey,
If you&#39;ve been following me for a while then you know I run multiple six figure businesses, all of them having one thing in common: video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAPM® : Certified Associate in Project Management Exams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/capm-certified-associate-in-project-management-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/capm-certified-associate-in-project-management-exams/</guid>
      <description>What Exactly Is Certification?
Certification is an amazing pathway to getting a high paying career in some of the best jobs in the world without spending thousands of dollars attending a four-year college.
Get Ready To Prepare Like You’ve Never Prepared Before
As we often say at AFAQ Formations, work smarter not harder. You are about to see a study guide that took hours of hard collection work, expert preparation, and constant feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esercizi Fisica: corso universitario/superiori</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/esercizi-fisica-corso-universitario/superiori/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 12:00:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/esercizi-fisica-corso-universitario/superiori/</guid>
      <description>DESCRIZIONE CORSO:
Nella mia esperienza universitaria ho visto tantissimi studenti in difficoltà nel superare l&#39;esame di Fisica eppure se ci pensi più o meno abbiamo già affrontato vivendo, i vari argomenti affrontati nello studio di questa materia. Infatti il corso oltre a prepararti al fine di superare l&#39;esame ti permetterà di vedere con occhi diversi la realtà.
Il corso è una raccolta di Esercizi. Gli esercizi proposti ti metteranno alla prova sulle conoscenze acquisite nella teorica iniziando con problemi semplici per prendere confidenza con le formule fino ad arrivare a svolgere esercizi di esame.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Udemy bootcamp: How to create a STUNNING course Unofficial</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/udemy-bootcamp-how-to-create-a-stunning-course-unofficial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 20:41:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/udemy-bootcamp-how-to-create-a-stunning-course-unofficial/</guid>
      <description>Let&#39;s start with the basics, right now you are a person that surely has something to offer, a certain knowledge that you have and that you think you will be able to teach. By creating this course my main objective was to help you by giving you all the tips thats I used to create online content on different plateforms. So if you are someone that is ready to start with udemy and creat your own content this course is for you !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ICBB IASSC Certified Lean Six Sigma Black Belt Practice Exam</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/icbb-iassc-certified-lean-six-sigma-black-belt-practice-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 20:28:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/icbb-iassc-certified-lean-six-sigma-black-belt-practice-exam/</guid>
      <description>Get Ready To Prepare Like You’ve Never Prepared Before
As we often say at AFAQ Formations, work smarter not harder. You are about to see a study guide that took hours of hard collection work, expert preparation, and constant feedback. That’s why we know this exam prep will help you get that high-score on your journey to certification.
Your Journey To Pass The ICBB
Perhaps this is your first step toward the certification, or perhaps you are coming back for another round.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-deep-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 21:51:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-deep-learning/</guid>
      <description>Preparing for Interview in Deep Learning? Don’t be stressed, take our Deep Learning based quiz questions and prepare your self for the interview. With this Deep Learning Quiz Questions, we are going to you build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Deep Learning based questions. Here you will get Deep Learning based Multiple Choice Questions and Answers for your next job or exam. In Deep Learning Multiple Choice Questions based practice tests, there will be a series of practice tests wherein you can test your Basic Deep Learning concepts on every Topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 21:51:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>Preparing for Machine learning Interview? Don’t be stressed, take our Machine learning based quiz questions and prepare your self for the interview. With this Machine learning Quiz Questions, we are going to you build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Machine learning questions. Here you will get Machine learning General Multiple Choice Questions and Answers for your next job or exam. In Machine learning Multiple Choice Questions based practice tests, there will be a series of practice tests wherein you can test your Basic Machine learning concepts on every Topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bible: A Survey Of Systematic Theology - Part One</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-bible-a-survey-of-systematic-theology-part-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 21:51:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-bible-a-survey-of-systematic-theology-part-one/</guid>
      <description>This is a Bible Institute level course in systematic theology. We cover the major doctrines of the Bible. This course presents classic theology from a literal and normal approach to the Bible. Key Bible passages are taught to show the relationship of important teachings to one another. There are fifty-two chapters in the book. The book is presented throughout several courses. This is the first course in the series. Content covered in this first course includes the Bible, inspiration, revelation and the Trinity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Security - Specialty- Practice Exams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aws-certified-security-specialty-practice-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 14:13:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aws-certified-security-specialty-practice-exams/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the AWS Certified Security - Specialty practice tests;
The AWS Certified Security Specialty is a certification which offers learning on advanced cloud security and securing applications in AWS. This AWS Security Certification has significant advantage over other certifications therefore, possessing it will make you eligible for reputed job roles. This AWS Certified Security Specialty practice test offers required knowledge to pass the AWS Certified Security Specialty certification exam along with the hands-on experience on advanced cloud security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRINCE2 Foundation Practice Certification Exams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/prince2-foundation-practice-certification-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 14:13:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/prince2-foundation-practice-certification-exams/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the PRINCE2 Foundation practice tests;
PRINCE2 Foundation is the first and basic level of PRINCE2 certification that confirms the overall understanding , familiarity with the PRINCE2 vocabulary and capability to work as a member of a project management team and it is therefore a good idea that all Project Stakeholders should have the opportunity to follow a PRINCE2 Foundation training.
The PRINCE2 Foundation examination is aiming to measure whether a candidate would be able to act as an informed member of a project management team using the PRINCE2 methodology within a project environment supporting PRINCE2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate- Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 00:29:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate practice tests;
The AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate exam validates technical expertise in designing and deploying scalable, highly available, and fault-tolerant systems on AWS. Take this mid-level course to learn how to prepare for the exam by exploring the exam subject areas and how they map to architecture on AWS and specific areas of study.
This new practice test is designed to help you to assess your preparedness for the AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book of 1 Thessalonians Bible Study &amp; 5 Insightful Lessons</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/book-of-1-thessalonians-bible-study-5-insightful-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 13:01:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/book-of-1-thessalonians-bible-study-5-insightful-lessons/</guid>
      <description>Why did Paul write the letter to the Thessalonians?
To ensure they remained in faith because he was unable to visit them, therefore, he had to send Timothy. He also wrote the letter to the Thessalonians to encourage them in faith so that they will not be unsettled by Paul’s trials (1 Thessalonians 2v17-3v3). He also wrote the letter to silence those who felt he took advantage of the people of Thessalonica.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arabic Writing Course For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/arabic-writing-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 14:59:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/arabic-writing-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>السلام عليكم
In this course, we will learn Writing in Arabic.
This course is divided into 3 stages:
In the first stage,
We will learn how to write each letter at any position of any word.
Then,
We will learn how to write a sentence with Diacritics.
And Finally,
We will learn how to write a paragraph with Diacritics.
By finishing this course, you will be able to write anything in Arabic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRINCE2® Foundation Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/prince2-foundation-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 14:59:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/prince2-foundation-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Get Ready To Prepare Like You’ve Never Prepared Before
As we often say at AFAQ Formations , work smarter not harder. You are about to see a study guide that took hours of hard collection work, expert preparation, and constant feedback. That’s why we know this exam prep will help you get that high-score on your journey to certification.
Your Journey To Pass The PRINCE2® Foundation
Perhaps this is your first step toward the certification, or perhaps you are coming back for another round.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginner English: Practical Foundational English Training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/beginner-english-practical-foundational-english-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 12:41:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/beginner-english-practical-foundational-english-training/</guid>
      <description>This course is a beginner level English course (A1-A2). The student understands basic phrases and instructions. He/she can interact in a very simple way and uses incomplete sentences, without real grammatical content. He/she may be able to participate in a dialogue giving personal information but in a limited way using minimal vocabulary. This course is designed to improve your English at its foundation. You will have a basic understanding of English and be able to speak it immediately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get into Top Colleges and Universities</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/get-into-top-colleges-and-universities/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 12:41:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/get-into-top-colleges-and-universities/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you&#39;ll learn to write a Personal Statement that &#34;WOWs&#34; Admissions Officers and maximizes your chance of admission. The Personal Statement is required for admission to most undergraduate, graduate, law, and MBA programs. You&#39;ll learn a proven method of writing your Personal Statement, including:
What Admissions Officers are looking for
What pitfalls to avoid
What traits and qualities Admissions Officers want to see in applicants
What types of experiences and accomplishments to write about</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRINCE2® Re-Registration Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/prince2-re-registration-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 12:41:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/prince2-re-registration-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Get Ready To Prepare Like You’ve Never Prepared Before
As we often say at AFAQ Formations, work smarter not harder. You are about to see a study guide that took hours of hard collection work, expert preparation, and constant feedback. That’s why we know this exam prep will help you get that high-score on your journey to certification.
Your Journey To Pass The PRINCE2® Re-Registration
Perhaps this is your first step toward the certification, or perhaps you are coming back for another round.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Record Your Screen Like A Pro: Create Sellable HD Videos!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/record-your-screen-like-a-pro-create-sellable-hd-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 12:41:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/record-your-screen-like-a-pro-create-sellable-hd-videos/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to know how to create high-quality video content? Would you like to finally start getting involved with Udemy, Youtube, or any other video-sharing network? Can you follow the easy instructions I will lay down for you to master the art of screencast production in no time at all? That&#39;s what I thought! Let me help you! In this course, I will teach you which free software to use, and how you can use them to shorten your learning curve and start creating video content right away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABC de ventas</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/abc-de-ventas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 23:02:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/abc-de-ventas/</guid>
      <description>El clásico proceso de venta se ha visto afectado por la introducción de internet en nuestras vidas como soporte para la toma de decisiones en la compra, es más, a día de hoy podemos hablar de un cambio radical no en cada una de las fases del proceso sino en cómo se realizan esas fases.
Para simplificar el esquema del proceso de venta, las fases fundamentales dentro de las cuales habría que diferenciar otras.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sıfırdan Konuşturan İngilizce Kursu (20&#43; Saat)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/s%C4%B1f%C4%B1rdan-konu%C5%9Fturan-ingilizce-kursu-20-saat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:36:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/s%C4%B1f%C4%B1rdan-konu%C5%9Fturan-ingilizce-kursu-20-saat/</guid>
      <description>• Bir dil en iyi doğal haliyle öğrenilir, yani çocukların öğrendiği gibi, kelimeleri sık sık duyarak.
• Hem Türkçe hem Kürtçe konuşan arkadaşınızın neden İngilizce öğrenemediğini hiç düşündünüz mü?
• İngilizce zor diye mi?
• En zor dil hangisi?
• Size göre Çince mi?
• Peki 2 milyar insan Çinceyi nasıl konuşuyor?
• Peki okuma yazma bilmeyen anne babanın bile çocuğuna konuşma dilini öğretirken, üniversitede öğretmenlik okumuş birinin neden dil öğretemediğini?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Word Placement and Grammar Test - Quiz Bank A051</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-word-placement-and-grammar-test-quiz-bank-a051/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:36:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-word-placement-and-grammar-test-quiz-bank-a051/</guid>
      <description>This test bank is prepared in five different categories. It has been prepared in such a way that everyone from all walks of life can benefit and test their knowledge, not just for English Language sentences&#39; structure knowledge interests or students. With this test, you will have the opportunity to improve yourself. At the same time, you will have the opportunity to get to know yourself and your environment better by going deeper into English Language These tests have a unique content and you can use what you do not know as a criterion to improve yourself at the end of the test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Word Placement and Grammar Test - Quiz Bank A054</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-word-placement-and-grammar-test-quiz-bank-a054/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:36:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-word-placement-and-grammar-test-quiz-bank-a054/</guid>
      <description>This test bank is prepared in five different categories. It has been prepared in such a way that everyone from all walks of life can benefit and test their knowledge, not just for English Language sentences&#39; structure knowledge interests or students. With this test, you will have the opportunity to improve yourself. At the same time, you will have the opportunity to get to know yourself and your environment better by going deeper into English Language These tests have a unique content and you can use what you do not know as a criterion to improve yourself at the end of the test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Word Placement and Grammar Test - Quiz Bank A056</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-word-placement-and-grammar-test-quiz-bank-a056/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:36:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-word-placement-and-grammar-test-quiz-bank-a056/</guid>
      <description>This test bank is prepared in five different categories. It has been prepared in such a way that everyone from all walks of life can benefit and test their knowledge, not just for English Language sentences&#39; structure knowledge interests or students. With this test, you will have the opportunity to improve yourself. At the same time, you will have the opportunity to get to know yourself and your environment better by going deeper into English Language These tests have a unique content and you can use what you do not know as a criterion to improve yourself at the end of the test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Word Placement and Grammar Test - Quiz Bank A058</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-word-placement-and-grammar-test-quiz-bank-a058/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:36:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-word-placement-and-grammar-test-quiz-bank-a058/</guid>
      <description>This test bank is prepared in five different categories. It has been prepared in such a way that everyone from all walks of life can benefit and test their knowledge, not just for English Language sentences&#39; structure knowledge interests or students. With this test, you will have the opportunity to improve yourself. At the same time, you will have the opportunity to get to know yourself and your environment better by going deeper into English Language These tests have a unique content and you can use what you do not know as a criterion to improve yourself at the end of the test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Word Placement and Grammar Test - Quiz Bank A072</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-word-placement-and-grammar-test-quiz-bank-a072/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:36:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-word-placement-and-grammar-test-quiz-bank-a072/</guid>
      <description>This test bank is prepared in five different categories. It has been prepared in such a way that everyone from all walks of life can benefit and test their knowledge, not just for English Language sentences&#39; structure knowledge interests or students. With this test, you will have the opportunity to improve yourself. At the same time, you will have the opportunity to get to know yourself and your environment better by going deeper into English Language These tests have a unique content and you can use what you do not know as a criterion to improve yourself at the end of the test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Course Creation: Teach an Online Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/online-course-creation-teach-an-online-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:36:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/online-course-creation-teach-an-online-course/</guid>
      <description>Online Course Creation can be simple once you have mastered the art of speaking in front of a camera. Imagine yourself delivering an entire course filled with great lectures. You can be the star of your own classroom--online. You can be a confident and engaging instructor of your own course. In this Online course creation Course you will earn the following: *How to speak and lecture with confidence throughout your online course creation process</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Word Placement and Grammar Test - Quiz Bank A052</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-word-placement-and-grammar-test-quiz-bank-a052/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-word-placement-and-grammar-test-quiz-bank-a052/</guid>
      <description>This test bank is prepared in five different categories. It has been prepared in such a way that everyone from all walks of life can benefit and test their knowledge, not just for English Language sentences&#39; structure knowledge interests or students. With this test, you will have the opportunity to improve yourself. At the same time, you will have the opportunity to get to know yourself and your environment better by going deeper into English Language These tests have a unique content and you can use what you do not know as a criterion to improve yourself at the end of the test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Word Placement and Grammar Test - Quiz Bank A053</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-word-placement-and-grammar-test-quiz-bank-a053/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-word-placement-and-grammar-test-quiz-bank-a053/</guid>
      <description>This test bank is prepared in five different categories. It has been prepared in such a way that everyone from all walks of life can benefit and test their knowledge, not just for English Language sentences&#39; structure knowledge interests or students. With this test, you will have the opportunity to improve yourself. At the same time, you will have the opportunity to get to know yourself and your environment better by going deeper into English Language These tests have a unique content and you can use what you do not know as a criterion to improve yourself at the end of the test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Word Placement and Grammar Test - Quiz Bank A073</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-word-placement-and-grammar-test-quiz-bank-a073/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-word-placement-and-grammar-test-quiz-bank-a073/</guid>
      <description>This test bank is prepared in five different categories. It has been prepared in such a way that everyone from all walks of life can benefit and test their knowledge, not just for English Language sentences&#39; structure knowledge interests or students. With this test, you will have the opportunity to improve yourself. At the same time, you will have the opportunity to get to know yourself and your environment better by going deeper into English Language These tests have a unique content and you can use what you do not know as a criterion to improve yourself at the end of the test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yds-Yökdil ve Ydt için Gramer Öğren</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/yds-y%C3%B6kdil-ve-ydt-i%C3%A7in-gramer-%C3%B6%C4%9Fren/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 21:12:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/yds-y%C3%B6kdil-ve-ydt-i%C3%A7in-gramer-%C3%B6%C4%9Fren/</guid>
      <description>Bu kurs, katılımcıları ülkemizde yapılan lisans üstü eğitimler için gerekli YDS, YÖKDİL sınavlarına hazırlanan ara sınıf ve üniversite mezunu öğrencileri ile 12. sınıftan mezun liselerin dil bölümü öğrencilerinin katıldığı YDT (YKS-DİL) sınavlarında başarılı olmalarını sağlamak amacıyla hazırlanmış pratik gramer bilgisi konularını içermektedir. Günlük hayatta da bu sınavlara öğrenciler hazırlayan ve onlara danışmanlık eden İngilizce Öğretmeni Serkan Coşkun tarafından özenle hazırlanan eğitimlerde temel amaç öğrencilerimize İngilizce&#39;yi sevdirmek ve onların kafasını karıştırmadan dil bilgisi konularını açık-seçik kavratmaktır.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bible: Philippians - 7 Lessons We Can Learn For Today!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bible-philippians-7-lessons-we-can-learn-for-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 17:04:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bible-philippians-7-lessons-we-can-learn-for-today/</guid>
      <description>Review - Book of Philippians 5 Star Rating
Student: Matt Hayes
The instructor has a notable passion for sharing the Book of Philippians! (All the Books of the Bible) That passion drew me to seriously consider his engaging presentation. The instructor challenged me to see myself through the eyes of my Lord and Savior - not the eyes of the world! I learned many valuable teachings about the Book of Philippians by taking this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tenses Wizard | Learn Tenses in an easy and unique way</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tenses-wizard-learn-tenses-in-an-easy-and-unique-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 17:04:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tenses-wizard-learn-tenses-in-an-easy-and-unique-way/</guid>
      <description>TENSES WIZARD is a Unique concept which aims at helping learners understanding the MOST IMPERATIVE GRAMMATICAL CONCEPT- The Tenses.
The course is designed and organized in beautiful format of One pagers which are extremely Result oriented and helps a learner understand each and every Tense properly along with the videos which explained in details .
Not only this much, learner will also get hands on 50+ practice worksheets along with the example sentences which comes as a part of Tenses Wizard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test de Citoyenneté du Canada : 210 questions</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/test-de-citoyennet%C3%A9-du-canada-210-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 17:04:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/test-de-citoyennet%C3%A9-du-canada-210-questions/</guid>
      <description>Ce cours comporte tout ce qu&#39;il faut pour réussir l&#39;examen de citoyenneté canadienne
Chaque exercice simule l&#39;examen de la citoyenneté. Vous devrez répondre à des questions sur les droits et les responsabilités des Canadiens et sur les aspects suivants du Canada :
son histoire
sa géographie
son économie
son gouvernement
ses lois
ses symboles
Les questions de ces tests sont fondées sur le guide d’étude officiel pour l’examen de citoyenneté : Découvrir le Canada – Les droits et responsabilités liés à la citoyenneté.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce Certified Administrator ADM-201 Practical Test</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/salesforce-certified-administrator-adm-201-practical-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 15:38:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/salesforce-certified-administrator-adm-201-practical-test/</guid>
      <description>Salesforce Certified Administrator ADM-201- Practice Exams
Set yourself apart with the first and only official professional certification program for Salesforce Certified Administrator ADM-201.
ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator is for the engineers and developper to validate their Salesforce Certified Administrator Practice tests are designed by experts to simulate the real exam scenario. The questions are based on the exam syllabus outlined by official documentation.
The questions that appear in each practice test are unique and not repeated in other practice tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Speaking in Hindi- English Communication skills 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-speaking-in-hindi-english-communication-skills-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 09:53:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-speaking-in-hindi-english-communication-skills-2021/</guid>
      <description>Interactive learning English speaking course on Udemy is the package of - English Speaking + Communication Skills + Storytelling.
It is Masterclass for Beginners to Advanced level, Learn English Grammar, Vocabulary &amp;amp; Storytelling &amp;amp; Interview preparation &amp;amp; presentation Skills in one course.
This course is in the Hindi language. (यह कोर्स हिंदी भाषा में है | )
A comprehensive course that focused on English speaking skills. It is specifically designed to help you build all the necessary skills for real-life day-to-day English conversations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Scrum Training, Scrum Master Certification</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-scrum-training-scrum-master-certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/agile-scrum-training-scrum-master-certification/</guid>
      <description>Agile Scrum Training, Scrum Master Certification Prep, Tests
Set yourself apart with the first and only official professional certification program for Agile Scrum Training, Scrum Master Certification Prep, Tests.
ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator is for the engineers and developper to validate their Agile Scrum Training, Scrum Master Certification Prep, Tests
Practice tests are designed by experts to simulate the real exam scenario. The questions are based on the exam syllabus outlined by official documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified  VMware VCP-DTM</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-vmware-vcp-dtm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-vmware-vcp-dtm/</guid>
      <description>We have created these practice exams with over 130 questions to help you prepare for the VCP-DTM exam and help you pass on your first attempt.
More information about the certifications :
VMware Desktop and Mobility certifications are designed to gauge your level of skill designing, installing, and managing a VMware Horizon with View environment deployed on a VMware vSphere implementation. The VCP-DTM 2021 certification validates a candidate’s skills in performing in-depth configuration and management of VMware Horizon environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oracle Database 11g - SQL/PL</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/oracle-database-11g-sql/pl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/oracle-database-11g-sql/pl/</guid>
      <description>Oracle Database 11g - SQL/PL - Practice Exams
Set yourself apart with the first and only official professional certification program for Oracle Database 11g - SQL/PL.
ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator is for the engineers and developper to validate their Oracle Database 11g - SQL/PL
Practice tests are designed by experts to simulate the real exam scenario. The questions are based on the exam syllabus outlined by official documentation.
The questions that appear in each practice test are unique and not repeated in other practice tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oracle Database 11g: Program with PL/SQL 4 Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/oracle-database-11g-program-with-pl/sql-4-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/oracle-database-11g-program-with-pl/sql-4-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>This practice test is designed to help you evaluate if you are ready to successfully complete the Oracle Database 11g: Program with PL/SQL | 1Z0-144 Certification exam.
Scenario based exam questions for Oracle Database 11g: Program with PL/SQL | 1Z0-144 Certification,
Online practice exam to be completed in Specified Time Duration.
Oracle Database 11g: Program with PL/SQL 1Z0-144 Exam is related to Oracle Database 11g and Credits towards Oracle Advanced PL/SQL Developer Certified Professional and Oracle PL/SQL Developer Certified Associate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMI-PBA certification for Business Analyst</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pmi-pba-certification-for-business-analyst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pmi-pba-certification-for-business-analyst/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to take the Microsoft PMI-PBA certification for Business Analyst Analyzing and Visualizing Data with Microsoft Power BI exam?
properly balanced based on the exam domains just like you will get in the official exam. . In addition, after taking the exam you can review your answers compared against the correct answers including comprehensive explanations of each question, links to documentation and articles, the correct and incorrect answer options</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/servicenow-certified-system-administrator/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/servicenow-certified-system-administrator/</guid>
      <description>Docker Certified Associate - Practice Exams
Set yourself apart with the first and only official professional certification program for ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator.
ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator is for the engineers and developper to validate their ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator
Practice tests are designed by experts to simulate the real exam scenario. The questions are based on the exam syllabus outlined by official documentation. The questions that appear in each practice test are unique and not repeated in other practice tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Arabic Grammar</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basic-arabic-grammar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basic-arabic-grammar/</guid>
      <description>In order to read, write, speak and understand Arabic, it is important to learn the grammar. Arabic grammar can be tough and intimidating, but it doesn’t have to be. Grammar here means the important words that give structure to a sentence, in addition to the structures themselves. In linguistics, we call such words &#34;function words&#34;. When you know these words, you’ll be able to recognize them and use them easily to understand and build simple sentences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best International Maths Olympiad/ Olympiad Mathematics-2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/best-international-maths-olympiad/-olympiad-mathematics-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/best-international-maths-olympiad/-olympiad-mathematics-2021/</guid>
      <description>Hi,
Are you or your children or your friends struggling with Math? Do you want to become a human calculator? If yes, then what are you waiting for? Enroll yourself in this course and have fun with Math. This course contains the world&#39;s fastest Vedic math techniques. It contains many solved examples, and exercises which will be help you . This course contains examples that are explained in every detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New SAT Math Practice Test Explain</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/new-sat-math-practice-test-explain/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/new-sat-math-practice-test-explain/</guid>
      <description>Course Summary In this new SAT math explain course, you’ll learn and practice the methods in doing the new SAT math by solving the math with me. You’ll learn how to do it fast, accurate and without wasting time to write redundant steps to solve the same problems.
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Why Take This Course? You’ll learn the new questions of the NEW SAT maths. Most importantly, you’ll start thinking with direction by observing how I tackle the problem step by step</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Arabic Reading</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basic-arabic-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basic-arabic-reading/</guid>
      <description>Learning Arabic is challenging in many ways. This course focuses on building the skill to read any Arabic word, by both learning the alphabet, including learning the name, sound, and shapes of each letter. In addition, the diacritics that guide the pronunciation of words are also explained. Finally, major prefixes and suffixes are also introduced. After you complete this course, you will be able to recognize the letters of any word and sound it out, which is the first step to read Arabic script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Linux (Part-1)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-linux-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-linux-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Dear Students,
Are you preparing for Job Exam and Interview in Linux?
Don’t be stressed, take our Linux Based quiz and prepare yourself for the Interview.
With this Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and tricks to solve Linux based questions. Here you will get Linux based MCQ for your next Job or Exam. In this Linux Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Knowledge in the field of Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archaische Astronomie 1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/archaische-astronomie-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/archaische-astronomie-1/</guid>
      <description>Kennst du dich am Nachthimmel aus?
In diesem einführenden Kurs zur Archaischen Astronomie beschäftigen wir uns mit den sichtbaren Planeten und deren zyklischen Wiederkehr am Sternenhimmel.
Du weißt sicher über den Mondzyklus Bescheid. Unser Zeitbegriff &#34;Monat&#34; stammt vom synodischen Mondzyklus. Es gibt aber noch weitere 5 sichtbare Planeten, deren Zyklus du mit freiem Auge beobachten kannst: Merkur, Venus, Mars, Jupiter und Saturn. Deren Bewegung lässt sich über den Lauf eines oder mehrere Jahre ohne Hilfsmittel und mit freiem Auge beobachten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Cryptography</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-cryptography/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-cryptography/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in Cryptography? Don’t be stressed, take our Cryptography based quiz and prepare yourself for your Interview. With this Cryptography based Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Cryptography based questions. In these Cryptography based Multiple Choice Questions Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Basic Knowledge in Cryptography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner: 6 Full Practice Exams 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-6-full-practice-exams-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-6-full-practice-exams-2021/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to pass the AWS Cloud Practitioner exam? Find out by testing yourself with this new offering on Udemy. Each of the 6 practice tests in this set provide an entire exam’s worth of questions, enabling you to confirm your mastery of the topics and providing you with the confidence you’ll need to take the exam.
The tests in this set are timed, so you’ll know when you’re taking more time than the official test allows, and at the end of the test you’ll receive a personal breakdown of the questions you answered correctly and incorrectly (DETAILED EXPLANATIONS) to improve your knowledge and make you more prepared to pass the actual exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Cyber Security</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-cyber-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-cyber-security/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in Cyber Security? Don’t be stressed, take our Cyber Security based quiz and prepare yourself for your Interview.
With this Cyber Security based Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Cyber Security based questions. In Cyber Security based Multiple Choice Questions Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Basic Knowledge in Cyber Security .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Engineering Arc Flash Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/power-engineering-arc-flash-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/power-engineering-arc-flash-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Power Engineering Arc Flash Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn how to do an arc flash analysis and developing an Arc Flash Safety Program for your business.
I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on Arc Flash as well as the hazards associated with it and how to do Arc Flash Mitigation.
If you are engineer, electrical worker or safety profession, you will find this course of great help to get the fundamental knowledge you need to kick start your professional career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arabic language through Drama | learn and entertain</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/arabic-language-through-drama-learn-and-entertain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/arabic-language-through-drama-learn-and-entertain/</guid>
      <description>In this course you will learn Arabic by Fun, watching Arabic series. The method will I apply in my videos are new and creative. So I have made new methods to teach you Arabic, hopefully this method will help a lot students to learn Arabic easily.
And at the end if you got any questions, don&#39;t hesitate ask me directly. I will be happy to answer all of your questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Portuguese Course: Portuguese for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-portuguese-course-portuguese-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-portuguese-course-portuguese-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our ultimate Portuguese beginner course that will teach you Portuguese faster than you thought possible! If you’ve ever dreamed of travelling to Portugal and holding your own in real-life situations, being independent and able to communicate with the locals, our beginner series is the perfect place for you to continue your Portuguese journey! There’s always more to learn, and we’ve prepared yet another course to enrich your vocabulary, advance your grammar and help you express more and more complex thoughts, all in Portuguese!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corso Completo di Scrittura Comica - Parte Seconda</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-completo-di-scrittura-comica-parte-seconda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-completo-di-scrittura-comica-parte-seconda/</guid>
      <description>In questo corso, rivolto sia ai professionisti che ai semplici appassionati, ti insegnerò come poter diventare un ottimo autore comico nei più rinomati campi dello spettacolo. Ti spiegherò, passo dopo passo, le differenti fasi dello scrivere comico partendo dall&#39;idea iniziale e dallo sviluppo di un tema fino ad approdare alla fase dell’organizzazione del materiale e la costruzione dei personaggi. Quando si ha a che fare con la scrittura comica è necessario tener sempre a mente e in piena considerazione fattori come il pubblico, lo stile e il linguaggio in perenne trasformazione, i meccanismi chiave che muovono la grande macchina della comicità.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master the English Irregular Verbs Once and For All</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-the-english-irregular-verbs-once-and-for-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-the-english-irregular-verbs-once-and-for-all/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&#39;m Carlos. I&#39;m a Trilingual Udemy Instructor, and I can&#39;t wait to help you improve your fluency, and other skills in speaking English.
I have created this shorter version for you to get a taste of another of my courses. This will help you see the quality of the course and our teaching style. Expect more information in the near future. When I designed this course, I put myself where you are now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art Legends in Art History</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/art-legends-in-art-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/art-legends-in-art-history/</guid>
      <description>We are using an ancient and proven technique in teaching you about art history. We are using storytelling. During ancient times, wise people spread the tales of the past to anyone who would listen. The art of storytelling is lost in the education space of today. We have made it our mission to teach our students about the masters of the art world, the art movements, and art history by telling stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to read Arabic for beginners | Basics &amp; principles</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-read-arabic-for-beginners-basics-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-read-arabic-for-beginners-basics-principles/</guid>
      <description>Arabic is widely taught in schools and universities and is used to varying degrees in workplaces, government and the media. Arabic, in its standard form, is the official language of 26 states, as well as the liturgical language of the religion of Islam, since the Quran and Hadith were written in Arabic.
In this course, you will learn how to read Arabic. by taking lessons gradually and easily, after finishing this course you will start practice reading by yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Course Creation - Create &amp; Sell Online Courses</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/online-course-creation-create-sell-online-courses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/online-course-creation-create-sell-online-courses/</guid>
      <description>Whatever your profession or experience may be, if you’ve ever wanted to turn your knowledge, skills or talents into a profitable online course, then you’re in the right place!
This professional masterclass training program provides absolutely everything you&#39;ll need to successfully build your own online business creating and selling online courses.
From deciding what you should be teaching, to marketing to the right audience, to buying the right equipment and knowing what to charge, I&#39;ll walk you through everything you need to know in order to create and launch a successful online course that customers will happily pay for!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick tricks in quantitative aptitude- CCAT, Wonderlic</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quick-tricks-in-quantitative-aptitude-ccat-wonderlic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quick-tricks-in-quantitative-aptitude-ccat-wonderlic/</guid>
      <description>Quantitative aptitude is a necessary requirement to enter into any higher level education and entry level jobs in any sector. About this course:
This course on Quantitative aptitude simplifies the concept in the form of quick tricks. Here, Quick trick is a formula, or a rule which helps you to solve the question in less time. This course is meticulously designed to meet your test preparation needs. Basics of numbers, ratios, averages and percentages are discussed in this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Criminology : Fundamentals of Criminal Psychology and Law</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/criminology-fundamentals-of-criminal-psychology-and-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 11:41:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/criminology-fundamentals-of-criminal-psychology-and-law/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
What is criminology?
Criminology is a branch of sociology, which traditionally examines human behavior, interaction, and organization. However, it also ties in research and concepts from other areas of study, such as philosophy, anthropology, biology, and psychology. Criminologists examine a broad range of topics related to crime. They are dedicated to studying not only the causes of crime but the social roots and impact as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Machine Learning Specialty --&gt; Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aws-certified-machine-learning-specialty--practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aws-certified-machine-learning-specialty--practice-test/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Interview in Machine Learning? Don’t be stressed, Take our Machine Learning Based Mock Test and prepare yourself for the Interview. Here you will get Machine Learning based Multiple Choice Question for your Next Interview.
What you will get in These Mock Test ? It contains sample questions which are likely to be asked in the Interview and Exam.
These Machine Learning based MCQ questions help you with self-study and self-assessment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Manipulation Works in Research</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-manipulation-works-in-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-manipulation-works-in-research/</guid>
      <description>DON&#39;T MANIPULATE RESEARCH - RESEARCH MANIPULATION
Manipulation is dangerous, regardless of where it occurs in life.
In this course, we are going to explore specifically how it occurs in scientific research.
Both researchers and other stakeholders can use a myriad methods to twist facts, change emotions in people, reduce the perceived effort of supporting someone, and other means.
This is the only course you will find that focuses on manipulation specifically for research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English grammar tenses &amp; structures, the ultimate course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-grammar-tenses-structures-the-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 11:17:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-grammar-tenses-structures-the-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>The course provides you with a variety of grammar rules that enable you to read, write and form perfect English sentences. The course forms a great combination of grammar rules with examples. It takes you step by step from understanding the rule into applying examples that enhance your English language skills. We add weekly quizzes with model answers.
Ratings: 4.39/5
Enrollments: 174726
Coupon Code: SEPTEMBER26
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adli Bilişim/Dijital Kursu</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adli-bili%C5%9Fim/dijital-kursu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:47:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adli-bili%C5%9Fim/dijital-kursu/</guid>
      <description>Günümüzün dijital dünyasında önemli bir konu olan siber dünya ile ilgili hukuki ve kanuni, ama öncesindeki süreçte de önemli bir yer teşkil ederek üzerinde bilimsel ve pratik çalışmalar yapılmaya ihtiyaç duyulan adli Dijital Bilişim, bu kursta detaylarıyla incelenerek, kursu takip edenler için hem pratikte, günlük yaşamda, hem de mesleki anlamda önemli yeterlilik bilgileri ve tecrübeleri vermektedir.
Bu kurs, Adli Bilişim ile ilgili temel ve genel bilgileri içermektedir. Dersler, akıcı ve anlaşılır bir şekilde olup, her düzeyden başlayabileceğiniz şekilde tasarlanmıştır.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drug Design and Molecular Docking by using computation Tools</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/drug-design-and-molecular-docking-by-using-computation-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/drug-design-and-molecular-docking-by-using-computation-tools/</guid>
      <description>In the filed molecular orientation modeling, Molecular Docking the perfect binding of two molecules, like prediction of ligand binding on the active size of the protein. On the basic knowledge of computer you learn ligand based Computer Aided Drug design (CADD) approach involves the analysis of ligands known to interact with a target of interest. One such course is particularly designed to maintain knowledge at the beginner level of computer Drug Discovery applications for science students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn DNA Primer Design for Polymerase Chain Reaction</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-dna-primer-design-for-polymerase-chain-reaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-dna-primer-design-for-polymerase-chain-reaction/</guid>
      <description>In this Bioinformatics course you will be find out how to DNA Primer Design for polymerase chain reaction. Primer BLAST performs only a specificity check when a target template and both primers are provided. Design primers for single- or multi-insert cloning or for your site-directed mutagenesis experiment (insertion, deletion, replacement) with our primer design tool. Primer3 is a computer program that suggests PCR primers for a variety of applications, for example to create STSs (sequence tagged sites) for radiation hybrid mapping, or to amplify sequences for single nucleotide polymor- phism discovery</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Electrical Engineering</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-electrical-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 21:16:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-electrical-engineering/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in Electrical Engineering? Don’t be stressed, take our Electrical Engineering based quiz and prepare yourself for your Interview. With this Electrical Engineering based Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Electrical Engineering based questions. In Electrical Engineering based Multiple Choice Questions Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Basic Knowledge in Electrical Engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Foundations of Biology: An Introduction</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-foundations-of-biology-an-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-foundations-of-biology-an-introduction/</guid>
      <description>This course will teach you the foundations and basics of biology and go further in-depth on various interesting concepts.
Topics Covered In Course
Characteristics of Life
Properties of Water
Atoms and Elements
Bonds
Cells
Lipid Bilayers and Osmosis
Macromolecules
Content Overview
Suitable for all levels, this is an in-depth learning course with lectures and quizzes. You do not need any prior experience to understand the material in this course. This course will walk you through your adventure into Biology and the Characteristics of Life by providing engaging video&#39;s on various topics and quizzes to test your knowledge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOEFL reading practice tests Questions and Answers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/toefl-reading-practice-tests-questions-and-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/toefl-reading-practice-tests-questions-and-answers/</guid>
      <description>TOEFL reading practice tests Questions and Answers
2022 reading tests for TOEFL Test of English as a Foreign Language
Test of English as a Foreign Language TOEFL is a standardized test to measure the English language ability of non-native speakers wishing to enroll in English-speaking universities. The test is accepted by more than 11,000 universities and other institutions in over 150 countries. TOEFL is one of the two major English-language tests in the world, the other being the IELTS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplilearn Arduino</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/simplilearn-arduino/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/simplilearn-arduino/</guid>
      <description>Arduino is an open-source computer hardware/software platform for building digital devices and interactive objects that can sense and control the physical world around them. In this class you will learn how the Arduino platform works in terms of the physical board and libraries and the IDE (integrated development environment).
Upon completing this course, you will be able to: 1. Outline the composition of the Arduino development board 2. Describe what it means to program the board&#39;s firmware 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on D.C. Machines</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-d.c.-machines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 22:18:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-d.c.-machines/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in D.C. Machines based Company? Don’t be stressed, take our D.C. Machines based quiz and prepare yourself for your Interview.
With this D.C. Machines based Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve D.C. Machines based questions. In D.C. Machines based Multiple Choice Questions Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Basic Knowledge in D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deutsch - Klare Kommunikation  A2-C1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/deutsch-klare-kommunikation-a2-c1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/deutsch-klare-kommunikation-a2-c1/</guid>
      <description>Wie kann ich klar kommunizieren, das was mir wichtig ist?
Wie können Konflikte so angesprochen werden, dass mein Gegenüber bereit ist zu kooperieren?
Lernen Sie zu formulieren was Sie möchten, anstatt nur zu sagen was sie stört.
Kann ich mich so ausdrücken, dass das was ich bin, unzweideutig mitgeteilt wird?
Neben dem Erwerb von psychosozialen Kompetenzen für den Beruf und Alltag werden im Kurshilfreiche Kommunikationsstrukturen, sowie ein differenziertes psychologisches Vokabular erlernt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Language Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-language-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-language-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>Preparing for Competitive Exams like IELTS or TOEFL and looking for more practice questions on English Grammar?
You have come to the right practice assessment course! Test your knowledge with this practice test created by experts who have years of experience in the field. Suitable for beginners who want to improve their understanding of written English or to improve their knowledge with explanations and timed tests.
Most questions and multiple choice and fill in the blank type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking for College Students: Become a Great Speaker</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-for-college-students-become-a-great-speaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 12:19:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-for-college-students-become-a-great-speaker/</guid>
      <description>Imagine speaking to a classroom or even an auditorium full of students knowing that everyone understands you, remembers your key messages and feels you are a confident speaker. Wouldn&#39;t it be great to know that you can speak to any sized audience and that you will always come across your very best? In this Public Speaking for College Students course you will learn the following: *How to speak with confidence inside and outside the classroom *How to avoid the common speaking blunders made by most other college students *How to rehearse important presentations on video *How to make fellow students and adults remember your messages This course is delivered primarily through spoken lecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Transformer</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 07:41:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-transformer/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in Transformer based Company? Don’t be stressed, take our Transformer based quiz and prepare yourself for your Interview.
With this Transformer based Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Transformer based questions. In Transformer based Multiple Choice Questions Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Basic Knowledge in Transformer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be an expert in English Grammar</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/be-an-expert-in-english-grammar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:52:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/be-an-expert-in-english-grammar/</guid>
      <description>The course has 14 sections. They display the different grammar rules in a funny way that depends on the animated cartoons. These 14 sections have 96 lectures. These 96 lectures have 2 hours of video content. This course takes you from level 1 to be a professional in the English grammar. Ratings: 4.30/5
Enrollments: 72280
Coupon Code: SEPTEMBER16
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10X Amazon Ebay Dropshipping Fba Wholesale 2021 Para Kazanma</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/10x-amazon-ebay-dropshipping-fba-wholesale-2021-para-kazanma/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/10x-amazon-ebay-dropshipping-fba-wholesale-2021-para-kazanma/</guid>
      <description>2021 yılında hala ticarete başlamadıysan bu kurs tam sana göre. Ben Akın Yılmaz, takım arkadaşlarımla beraber sizlerin ticaretinizi geliştirmenizi ve internet üzerinden gelir elde edebilmeniz için sizlere Udemy üzerinden Ücretisiz eğitimler hazırlıyoruz. Temel ticaret mantığını anlamak ve kendinizi e-ticaret alanında geliştirmek için lütfen bu kursa ve Akın Yılmaz kanalına göz atın. Buralarda sahip olmasını isteyeceğiniz çok kıymetli bilgiler var. Ve siz bu bilgileri edinmelisiniz. Artık kendi paranızı kazanma vaktiniz geldi. Tek yapmanız gereken aksiyon alıp artık başlamak ve ticaretinizi geliştirmek.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AP Physics 1 - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ap-physics-1-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ap-physics-1-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Master AP Physics 1 and get the score you want in this clear, concise, and in-depth course! This course will teach you everything, from kinematics to energy to momentum, and consists of lectures and practice problems for each unit. This is the first part of the entire AP Physics 1 course, covering the first portion of the curriculum units. Each unit has specific videos with hand-picked problems to supplement the lectures, making the overall learning process easy, efficient, and effective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Pronunciation Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-pronunciation-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-pronunciation-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Hi! My name is Professor G and I&#39;m an English teacher with more than 10 years of teaching experience. I previously studied French and Spanish at university, and I&#39;ve taught English in a number of countries around the world, including Brazil (Campinas), France (Paris) and Spain (Malaga). I understand the problems that language learners experience, especially when it comes to speaking the language. When I first moved to France, I had studied French for 5 years, but had very little speaking practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zero To Hero! Intro To Algebra: Variables, Fractions &amp; More</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/zero-to-hero-intro-to-algebra-variables-fractions-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/zero-to-hero-intro-to-algebra-variables-fractions-more/</guid>
      <description>In this course you will get professional maths tutoring to help you be successful at Algebra. We cover the basics of algebra such as variables, fractions, operations, cubes, roots and squares. You will get practical, step by step explanations, practice examples and demonstration lessons. A solid introduction to algebra is so important for the rest of your maths journey so join us in this course as we help you achieve your goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrivere un Dialogo - Scrittura Creativa Vol. 3</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/scrivere-un-dialogo-scrittura-creativa-vol.-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 18:00:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/scrivere-un-dialogo-scrittura-creativa-vol.-3/</guid>
      <description>Ciao! In questo corso ti spiegherò come poter approcciare, nel migliore dei modi, alla composizione di un’ ottima sequenza dialogica e all’importanza che essa assume all’interno di un racconto, un romanzo o qualsivoglia opera di carattere narrativo. Considera che tra i motivi del “Blocco della pagina bianca&#34; di molti scrittori alle prime armi vi è proprio il senso di inadeguatezza o incapacità nell’affrontare la scrittura dei dialoghi e ti renderai conto che ovviare eliminando gli stessi dialoghi non rappresenta affatto una soluzione effettiva.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Il Personaggio - Scrittura Creativa Vol. 5</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/il-personaggio-scrittura-creativa-vol.-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 09:03:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/il-personaggio-scrittura-creativa-vol.-5/</guid>
      <description>Come nasce l&#39;idea per un personaggio narrativo?
A chi o a cosa ispirarsi?
Dall&#39;idea di un determinato personaggio come si giunge poi al suo inserimento in un preciso contesto narrativo?
Come rivestire uno o più personaggi di credibilità??
Queste sono solo alcune delle domande che affiorano nella mente di uno scrittore quando decide di cimentarsi nella scrittura di un &#39;opera narrativa, a prescindere dal genere che deciderà di seguire o adottare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AutoCAD Course l كورس الاوتوكاد</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/autocad-course-l-%D9%83%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%B3-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%88%D8%AA%D9%88%D9%83%D8%A7%D8%AF/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/autocad-course-l-%D9%83%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%B3-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%88%D8%AA%D9%88%D9%83%D8%A7%D8%AF/</guid>
      <description>كورس الاوتوكاد كورس هنتعلم فيه مع بعض اهم الاسس اللي لازم تكون عارفها عن الاوتوكاد
هنتعلم مع بعض اوامر الرسم المختلفة وكذالك اوامر التعديل المختلفة
زي Filet , Extend , Scale , Alignment , Divide , match , hatch ,text , offset , move , rotate , mirror , Block and Explode سنتعرف على الاوامر الهامة داخل برنامج الاوتوكاد الذى لا غنى عنه فى اى تصميم او رسومات بانواعها والذى ايضاً فى حاجه له مع برامج اخرى لتوصيل الفكرة وتنفيذها بسهولة .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kamu Yönetimi Kapsamlı Kursu</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kamu-y%C3%B6netimi-kapsaml%C4%B1-kursu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kamu-y%C3%B6netimi-kapsaml%C4%B1-kursu/</guid>
      <description>Kamu Yönetimi dersleri, diğer bilim dalları ve derslerden farklı özellikler göstermektedir. Örneğin ülkelerin yapısı ve hiyerarşisine göre değişkenlik göstermesi sebebiyle uygulanış açıklama ve yorumları, evrensel bir dille genel bir yapı göstermediği için diğer dillerden bir uyarlama yapılamayıp, özgün çalışmalar gerektirir.
Bu kurs, bu sebeple daha önce yapılmış çalışmaların ışığında ve öğrencilerin sık karşılaştıkları veya karşılaşmak durumunda olacakları sorulara ve cevaplara çok fazla yer vererek, gerekli anlaşılır açıklamaların yapıldığı derslerden oluşmaktadır.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English language basics for beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-language-basics-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 12:13:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/english-language-basics-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>We make it easy for you to learn how to speak and write English fluently as a beginner learner. These English lessons will show you how to say and use almost anything in daily English conversation. Get started now with our speaking, vocabulary and grammar exercises that come with model answers. In this course, you will learn important topics and lessons in English, such as, Alphabet, numbers, saying hello, signs and symbols, telling the time, asking and answering questions about name, age, weather, classroom things, classroom instructions, days of the week, months of the year, seasons of the year, basic colors, simple shapes and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrivere per Bambini e Ragazzi - Scrittura Creativa Vol. 2</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/scrivere-per-bambini-e-ragazzi-scrittura-creativa-vol.-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 12:13:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/scrivere-per-bambini-e-ragazzi-scrittura-creativa-vol.-2/</guid>
      <description>In questo corso di scrittura creativa per bambini e per ragazzi parlerò delle tecniche che vi sono dietro lo scrivere in base a due fattori: la fascia di età e il genere. In questo corso in particolar modo i nostri lettori vengono suddivisi in quattro fasce di età:
1. al di sotto dei 5 anni
2. dai 5 ai 7 anni
3. dagli 8 agli 11
4. dai 12 ai 14</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arabic: Learn Arabic Language| Online Arabic Language Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/arabic-learn-arabic-language-online-arabic-language-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 20:51:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/arabic-learn-arabic-language-online-arabic-language-course/</guid>
      <description>Marhaba (Hello and welcome)!
My name is Nezha, and welcome to Arabic 4 U! ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
After taking this online Arabic language course, you will start to:
Speak Arabic with Arabic speakers from around the world
Understand Formal Arabic called Modern Standard Arabic MSA or Fusha
Arabic speakers learn Modern Standard Arabic in school. It is used in Arabic books, Arabic news, Arabic documentaries, Arabic road signs, and Arabic formal speeches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IEC 61850 Communication Protocol Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/iec-61850-communication-protocol-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/iec-61850-communication-protocol-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>IEC61850 Communication Protocol Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn industry specific knowledge about the IEC61850 protocol standard such as that found in the utility industry.
I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge from cable component basic to calculating for simple cable installation designs.
I will teach you the basic concepts of IEC61850 standard as well as the overall IEC61850 Data Model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Digital Marketing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-digital-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 13:08:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamental-question-on-digital-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Dear Students,
Are you Preparing for Interview in Digital Marketing? Don’t be stressed, Take our Digital Marketing quiz and prepare yourself for the Interview.
With this Digital Marketing Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and tricks to solve Digital Marketing based questions. Here you will get Digital Marketing based MCQ for your next Job or Exam.
In Digital Marketing Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Knowledge in the field of Digital Marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corso completo di Teatro per bambini 4-6 anni</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-completo-di-teatro-per-bambini-4-6-anni/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:16:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-completo-di-teatro-per-bambini-4-6-anni/</guid>
      <description>In questo corso spiegherò come poter gestire un gruppo di bambini dai 4 ai 6 anni facendo loro praticare, in modo ludico ma nello stesso tempo costruttivo e creativo, attività teatrali volte alla conoscenza di elementi fondamentali per la suddetta fascia d&#39;età. Gli scopi di un laboratorio teatrale destinato ai più piccini sono svariati tra cui: 1. Favorire la socializzazione; 2. Superare eventuali timidezze; 3. Coordinare l&#39;attività motoria; 4. Acquisire la conoscenza delle figure geometriche nello spazio; 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angiosperm :  Flowering Plant</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/angiosperm-flowering-plant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/angiosperm-flowering-plant/</guid>
      <description>The flowering plants, also known as Angiospermae, meaning hidden seeds in Greek, are the most diverse group of land plants with 64 orders, 416 families, approximately 13,000 known genera and 300,000 known species. Like gymnosperms, angiosperms, which are also known by Magnoliophyta, are seed-producing plants.
The angiosperms dominate Earth’s surface and vegetation in more environments, particularly terrestrial habitats, than any other group of plants. As a result, angiosperms are the most important ultimate source of food for birds and mammals, including humans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build your own first Voice Assistant in Python</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-build-your-own-first-voice-assistant-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-build-your-own-first-voice-assistant-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to this class
In this project you will learn how to build your first virtual assistant VA in python in less then 90 minutes.
This is a great small project to get started (even if you have little or no prior knowledge in python) and learning opportunity.
Learning through your own little projects is the best and most enjoying way to improve your skills.
In the world of today we all already use Virtual Assistants like Alexa, Siri, Google and others more and more in our daily lifes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning &amp; Data Science A-Z: Hands-on Python 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/machine-learning-data-science-a-z-hands-on-python-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/machine-learning-data-science-a-z-hands-on-python-2021/</guid>
      <description>Are you interested in data science and machine learning, but you don&#39;t have any background, and you find the concepts confusing?
Are you interested in programming in Python, but you always afraid of coding?
I think this course is for you!
Even if you are familiar with machine learning, this course can help you to review all the techniques and understand the concept behind each term.
This course is completely categorized, and we don&#39;t start from the middle!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introductory Biology: Complete course of Biology</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introductory-biology-complete-course-of-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introductory-biology-complete-course-of-biology/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt; This course is designed to meet the requirement of the students to understand the Complete Introduction of Biology.
&amp;gt;This course presents many of the topics Found in O and A level biology.
&amp;gt;The topics are presented through PowerPoints presentation.Each body system is presented separately and there are quizzes at the end of each section.
&amp;gt;In this Course , Students will learn the introduction of Biology.
&amp;gt;Understand the Division and Branches of Biology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nanotechnology Fundamentals - Most comperehensive NANOTECH</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/nanotechnology-fundamentals-most-comperehensive-nanotech/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 11:42:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/nanotechnology-fundamentals-most-comperehensive-nanotech/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
Nanotechnology is a field of research and innovation concerned with building &#39;things&#39; - generally, materials and devices - on the scale of atoms and molecules. A nanometre is one-billionth of a metre: ten times the diameter of a hydrogen atom. The diameter of a human hair is, on average, 80,000 nanometres. At such scales, the ordinary rules of physics and chemistry no longer apply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Path Loss 5</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-path-loss-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:28:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-path-loss-5/</guid>
      <description>You want to learn about network planning, especially the Access Network which is most fragile and ever changing part of the fixed and wireless network.
I have been working in the transmission field since last twenty years and I found that there is no basic training of the most commonly used access planning software and the new comers in Transmission planning learn this tool through hit and trial. That is why they are never able to fully utilize their potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corso completo di Teatro: esercizi pratici (Per Formatori)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-completo-di-teatro-esercizi-pratici-per-formatori/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:15:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-completo-di-teatro-esercizi-pratici-per-formatori/</guid>
      <description>Essere un Formatore Teatrale non è semplice, ci si ritrova ogni volta in contesti differenti, con persone di età diverse e che giungono con motivazioni più disparate. Per tali motivi ho cercato di non tralasciare alcun aspetto sul come impostare un Laboratorio Teatrale: dall&#39;organizzazione delle lezioni, alla tempistica, e poi tutti gli esercizi più importanti per fare un laboratorio teatrale, ognuno spiegato nei minimi particolari.
A dispetto di tanto impegno per fare un laboratorio di teatro, alla fine si hanno grandi soddisfazioni: si assiste lezione dopo lezione alla crescita degli aspiranti attori, li si vede affrontare i vari ostacoli e superarli, ed io stessa dopo ogni laboratorio mi sento arricchita, è qualcosa che solo chi ha sentito il profumo di un palco può capire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Allama Iqbal Poetry Explanation Course in Urdu</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-allama-iqbal-poetry-explanation-course-in-urdu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 20:19:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-allama-iqbal-poetry-explanation-course-in-urdu/</guid>
      <description>Allama Muhammad Iqbal is one of the most outstanding poet-philosophers of the Indian sub-continent belonging to the modern period. His intellectual genius has reigned supreme in the arena of Islamic philosophy during the twentieth century and is likely to direct and influence the Islamic Intellectual tradition in the twenty first century as well. His sublime poetry and philosophy inspired millions of Muslims to wake up to the reality of the times and forge a destiny for themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Academic Writing course: Research &#43; Essay Writing!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-academic-writing-course-research--essay-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 20:19:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-academic-writing-course-research--essay-writing/</guid>
      <description>This course is specially developed for students who need the essential knowledge to prepare them for writing and defending their thesis/dissertation in an efficient and effective manner. I have created 17 lectures that cover all facets of thesis writing in one and a half hour!
SummaryI will start with the end in mind; how is your thesis evaluated? Based on this central question I explain my formula of success and take you by the hand from topic selection all the way up to successful thesis defence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High School Organic Chemistry 1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/high-school-organic-chemistry-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/high-school-organic-chemistry-1/</guid>
      <description>Chemistry is fun when you learn from the best tutors. At Go2uni, we present you “High School Organic Chemistry 1”. We start from the basics and take a deep dive with clear examples and exercises to ensure every concept is understood.
Go2uni presents seasoned tutors with years of experience to offer you &#34;High School Organic Chemistry 1&#34;, the organic chemistry course you need to ace your exams.
This course will demystify Chemistry with tonnes of examples, work through exercises and take-home exercises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware Certified Professional - VCP-DTM Practice Exams 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/vmware-certified-professional-vcp-dtm-practice-exams-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/vmware-certified-professional-vcp-dtm-practice-exams-2021/</guid>
      <description>We have created these practice exams with over 130 questions to help you prepare for the VCP-DTM exam and help you pass on your first attempt.
More information about the certifications :
VMware Desktop and Mobility certifications are designed to gauge your level of skill designing, installing, and managing a VMware Horizon with View environment deployed on a VMware vSphere implementation. The VCP-DTM 2021 certification validates a candidate’s skills in performing in-depth configuration and management of VMware Horizon environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improvvisazione Teatrale e Comica: dalla teoria alla pratica</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/improvvisazione-teatrale-e-comica-dalla-teoria-alla-pratica/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/improvvisazione-teatrale-e-comica-dalla-teoria-alla-pratica/</guid>
      <description>Cos&#39;è un&#39; improvvisazione? E se si chiama IMPROVVISAZIONE perché studiarla in un corso?
Perché sono state scritte tonnellate di libri a tal riguardo?
L&#39;improvvisazione è una vera e propria Arte e come tale necessita di studio, tecnica ed esperienza. Non si può improvvisare senza possedere le conoscenze adatte.
Esistono due differenti forme di improvvisazione, quella &#34;muta&#34; nella quale l&#39;unico strumento comunicativo è rappresentato dal corpo e quella &#34;parlata&#34; durante la quale voce(storytelling) e corpo agiscono all&#39;unisono, quest&#39;ultima è l&#39;improvvisazione di cui ti parlerò in questo corso.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redação: Enem, vestibular, concurso.Teoria &#43; tira-dúvidas</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/reda%C3%A7%C3%A3o-enem-vestibular-concurso.teoria--tira-d%C3%BAvidas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/reda%C3%A7%C3%A3o-enem-vestibular-concurso.teoria--tira-d%C3%BAvidas/</guid>
      <description>Se você já tem professor para avaliar suas redações, e não&amp;nbsp; precisa de exercícios de reforço, aqui você tem as quase 8&amp;nbsp;horas de aulas em vídeo do curso completo (disponível na plataforma Udemy) + tira-dúvidas ilimitado comigo!
Você vai descobrir como escrever dissertações de provas mais rápido, sem decorar regras ou fórmulas.
Se você trava ou fica em &#34;branco&#34;, veja o que te espera:
tipos de dissertação
como começar a redação sem travar</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combined Heat and Power (CHP) Cogeneration Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/combined-heat-and-power-chp-cogeneration-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/combined-heat-and-power-chp-cogeneration-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Combined Heat and Power (CHP) Cogeneration Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn all about the concept of CHP and cogeneration that are essential in working in the industry.
I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on cogeneration as well as how to apply it in the utility industry.
If you are currently a professional who are interested working with Cogeneration plants, you will find this course of great help to get the fundamental knowledge you need to kick start your professional career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete French Course: Learn French for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-french-course-learn-french-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-french-course-learn-french-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to learn French? Dubbed the “language of love”, French is used by over 235 million speakers daily in over 54 countries. But why should you pick French out of all the languages you could be learning?
To start, France isn’t just one of the most beautiful countries in central Europe, but a global powerhouse with significant presence in the automobile, aircraft and chemical manufacturing, the electronic, machinery, metallurgy industries, as well as tourism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete General Chemistry 20&#43; hours of lectures &amp; examples</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-general-chemistry-20-hours-of-lectures-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-general-chemistry-20-hours-of-lectures-examples/</guid>
      <description>Description:
General Chemistry is a basic course for a broad range of students from different fields of science and engineering. This course is designed to help you get a firm grasp over the most important topics in chemistry that you need to know in order to do great in your exams and classes. By the end of the course you’ll learn the principals and important concepts regarding matter, atoms, solutions, phases, chemical reactions, equilibrium, kinetics, acids and bases and so much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Tamil Course: Learn Tamil for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-tamil-course-learn-tamil-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-tamil-course-learn-tamil-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to learn Tamil? As one of the oldest classical languages in the world, Tamil is spoken by over 70 million people. But why should you pick Tamil out of all the languages you could be learning?
To start, Tamil is the official language of Tamil Nadu, India’s fourth largest state, which has seen significant economic growth and foreign investment over the last decade. The state is a leading figure in several industries, such as automobile and auto-components, engineering, pharmaceuticals and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash Course on Civil Engineering and AutoCAD: Part 3</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-3/</guid>
      <description>This incredible series-based crash course takes an amazing turn here in Part 3 as&amp;nbsp;&#34;New-age Environmental Engineering &amp;amp; Artificial Intelligence&#34; concepts are taught by Digital Marketing Legend &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34;&amp;nbsp;and Narmadha.M.
Environmental Engineering is a professional engineering discipline that takes advantage of specific scientific topics such as chemistry, biology, geography, geology, hydraulics, hydrology, microbiology, and mathematics to create solutions that will preserve and also improve the health of living organisms and increase environmental quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Differential Equations | Complete Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/differential-equations-complete-differential-equations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/differential-equations-complete-differential-equations/</guid>
      <description>Learn Differential Equation:
This course includes video lectures and text explanations of everything from differential equations and its applications, and it includes 7 quizzes (with video solutions!) and&amp;nbsp; for practice worksheet with extra practice problems, to help you test your understanding along the way. &#34;Differential Equations&#34; is arranged into the following sections:
Understanding of differential equations.
Order and degree of differential equations.
Formation of differential equation.
Variable separation method.
Substitution method of solution of differential equation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Biomedical Engineering - Nanodevices RAHBME282</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/intro-to-biomedical-engineering-nanodevices-rahbme282/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/intro-to-biomedical-engineering-nanodevices-rahbme282/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Nanodevices course, brought to you by Rahsoft. In this course we will be going over the basics and fundamentals of nanodevices and nanosensors, as well as in-depth examples and practice problems to give you a better understanding of the field. The course is taught by Dennis Fer, a Biomedical Engineering Instructor at Rahsoft, and the course advisor is Ahsan Ghoncheh, the Co-Founder and Technical Advisor at Rahsoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Heat Transfer Engineering - RAHHT1 Rahsoft</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-heat-transfer-engineering-rahht1-rahsoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-heat-transfer-engineering-rahht1-rahsoft/</guid>
      <description>Heat Transfer is one of the principle courses for all the university students who study in one of the branches of chemical engineering, mechanical engineering or materials engineering. This course which is placed at the beginning semesters of bachelor programs, is offered in two separate courses as heat transfer 1 &amp;amp; 2 each credited as 3 units. Having a full grasp over the concepts of heat transfer and fully understand the mechanisms of heat transfer in different situations is a must for any students studying the fields mentioned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japanese for French speakers : katakana</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/japanese-for-french-speakers-katakana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/japanese-for-french-speakers-katakana/</guid>
      <description>C&#39;est un cours complet pour apprendre tous les katakana, l&#39;alphabet de base japonais qui est utilisé pour écrire certaines catégories de mots tels que les mots étrangers ou les onomatopées. Grâce à des photos, des illustrations animées, une bande-son et des sous-titres en français, vous apprendrez facilement à lire le tableau entier des 46 katakana, à les prononcer parfaitement et à les écrire dans le bon ordre. Vous ne serez pas ennuyés, car à la fin de chaque section vous pourrez vérifier vos progrès avec des quiz amusants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matemáticas desde aritmética a cálculo con Python</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/matem%C3%A1ticas-desde-aritm%C3%A9tica-a-c%C3%A1lculo-con-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/matem%C3%A1ticas-desde-aritm%C3%A9tica-a-c%C3%A1lculo-con-python/</guid>
      <description>En este curso te enseñaré a usar Python como una herramienta para resolver problemas de matemáticas desde la aritmética hasta el cálculo diferencial e integral. Además de que te enseñaré a usar este lenguaje de manera muy básica. Siempre he dicho que lo mejor de un curso es ir al grano, por lo que te ayudaré a hacer ejercicios matemáticos directamente con las herramientas de Google Colaborative que nos permitirán programar en Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul: A Biography: Small Group Edition</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/paul-a-biography-small-group-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/paul-a-biography-small-group-edition/</guid>
      <description>N. T. Wright&#39;s definitive biography of Paul reveals the apostle&#39;s lasting role in Christian history as an inventor of new paradigms for how we understand Jesus and what he accomplished. Wright celebrates Paul’s stature as one of the most effective and influential intellectuals in human history, while shedding fresh light on his writings, thoughts, and ideas. Consider these remarkable facts: Paul&#39;s writing occupy less than 90 pages in a modern translation yet they have, page per page, generated more sermons, books, monographs, and journal articles than any other writings from the ancient world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quadratic Equations &amp; Quadratic Expression</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quadratic-equations-quadratic-expression/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quadratic-equations-quadratic-expression/</guid>
      <description>Learn Quadratic Equations and Functions:
This 7 lessons course includes video lectures and text explanations of everything from quadratic equations and functions, and it includes 7 quizzes (with video solutions!) and&amp;nbsp; for practice worksheet with extra practice problems, to help you test your understanding along the way. &#34;Quadratic equations and expression&#34; is arranged into the following sections:
Basic concept of quadratic Equation
Solving a quadratic equation by different method
How many ways are there to solve a quadratic equation</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
