<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Teaching &amp; Academics on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/teaching-academics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Teaching &amp; Academics on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 01:44:24 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/teaching-academics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Arabic Language Course: Learn to Read Arabic, Write &amp; Listen</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-language-course-learn-to-read-arabic-write-listen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 01:44:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-language-course-learn-to-read-arabic-write-listen/</guid>
      <description>New Update: We added Arabic Audiobook + MP3 Files + Translation in English.
New Update: We added new Section to Learn Writing in Arabic.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 السلام عليكم

In this Course, you will learn to Read, Write &amp;amp; Listen to Arabic through Short Stories &amp;amp; Audiobooks.

This Course is divided into 9 Sections:
In the First Section: you will learn How to Write &amp;amp; Pronounce Arabic Alphabet, and we will take some words for each letter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce Certified Administrator ADM-201 Practical Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/salesforce-certified-administrator-adm-201-practical-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 01:44:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/salesforce-certified-administrator-adm-201-practical-test/</guid>
      <description>Salesforce Certified Administrator ADM-201- Practice Exams

Set yourself apart with the first and only official professional certification program for Salesforce Certified Administrator ADM-201.
ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator is for the engineers and developper to validate their Salesforce Certified Administrator 

Practice tests are designed by experts to simulate the real exam scenario. The questions are based on the exam syllabus outlined by official documentation.
The questions that appear in each practice test are unique and not repeated in other practice tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test de Citoyenneté du Canada : 210 questions</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/test-de-citoyennet%C3%A9-du-canada-210-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 01:44:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/test-de-citoyennet%C3%A9-du-canada-210-questions/</guid>
      <description>Ce cours comporte tout ce qu&#39;il faut pour réussir l&#39;examen de citoyenneté canadienne
Chaque exercice simule l&#39;examen de la citoyenneté. Vous devrez répondre à des questions sur les droits et les responsabilités des Canadiens et sur les aspects suivants du Canada :
son histoire
sa géographie
son économie
son gouvernement
ses lois
ses symboles
Les questions de ces tests sont fondées sur le guide d’étude officiel pour l’examen de citoyenneté : Découvrir le Canada – Les droits et responsabilités liés à la citoyenneté.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2 Corinthians: 13 Life Changing Lessons</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/2-corinthians-13-life-changing-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/2-corinthians-13-life-changing-lessons/</guid>
      <description>&#34;A few days before completing this course I visited my auto mechanic for a minor repair. Shortly after parking, a reckless lorry driver smashed into it.! I was completely upset because he tried to cover up the incident by not reporting himself. We had to trail through 4 hours of videotape to identify the culprit.
Whilst mauling over the situation I directed my thoughts to Romans 8 and considered that this will work together for my good somehow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Scrum Training, Scrum Master Certification</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/agile-scrum-training-scrum-master-certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/agile-scrum-training-scrum-master-certification/</guid>
      <description>Agile Scrum Training, Scrum Master Certification Prep, Tests

Set yourself apart with the first and only official professional certification program for Agile Scrum Training, Scrum Master Certification Prep, Tests.
ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator is for the engineers and developper to validate their Agile Scrum Training, Scrum Master Certification Prep, Tests

Practice tests are designed by experts to simulate the real exam scenario. The questions are based on the exam syllabus outlined by official documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified  VMware VCP-DTM</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/certified-vmware-vcp-dtm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/certified-vmware-vcp-dtm/</guid>
      <description>We have created these practice exams with over 130 questions to help you prepare for the VCP-DTM exam and help you pass on your first attempt.
More information about the certifications :
VMware Desktop and Mobility certifications are designed to gauge your level of skill designing, installing, and managing a VMware Horizon with View environment deployed on a VMware vSphere implementation. The VCP-DTM 2021 certification validates a candidate’s skills in performing in-depth configuration and management of VMware Horizon environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oracle Database 11g - SQL/PL</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/oracle-database-11g-sql/pl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/oracle-database-11g-sql/pl/</guid>
      <description>Oracle Database 11g - SQL/PL - Practice Exams

Set yourself apart with the first and only official professional certification program for Oracle Database 11g - SQL/PL.
ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator is for the engineers and developper to validate their Oracle Database 11g - SQL/PL

Practice tests are designed by experts to simulate the real exam scenario. The questions are based on the exam syllabus outlined by official documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oracle Database 11g: Program with PL/SQL 4 Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/oracle-database-11g-program-with-pl/sql-4-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/oracle-database-11g-program-with-pl/sql-4-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>This practice test is designed to help you evaluate if you are ready to successfully complete the Oracle Database 11g: Program with PL/SQL | 1Z0-144 Certification exam.

Scenario based exam questions for Oracle Database 11g: Program with PL/SQL | 1Z0-144 Certification,

Online practice exam to be completed in Specified Time Duration.

Oracle Database 11g: Program with PL/SQL 1Z0-144 Exam is related to Oracle Database 11g and Credits towards Oracle Advanced PL/SQL Developer Certified Professional and Oracle PL/SQL Developer Certified Associate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMI-PBA certification for Business Analyst</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pmi-pba-certification-for-business-analyst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pmi-pba-certification-for-business-analyst/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to take the Microsoft PMI-PBA certification for Business Analyst Analyzing and Visualizing Data with Microsoft Power BI exam?

properly balanced based on the exam domains just like you will get in the official exam. . In addition, after taking the exam you can review your answers compared against the correct answers including comprehensive explanations of each question, links to documentation and articles, the correct and incorrect answer options</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/servicenow-certified-system-administrator/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/servicenow-certified-system-administrator/</guid>
      <description>Docker Certified Associate - Practice Exams

Set yourself apart with the first and only official professional certification program for ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator.
ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator is for the engineers and developper to validate their ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator

Practice tests are designed by experts to simulate the real exam scenario. The questions are based on the exam syllabus outlined by official documentation. The questions that appear in each practice test are unique and not repeated in other practice tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Arabic Grammar</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/basic-arabic-grammar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/basic-arabic-grammar/</guid>
      <description>In order to read, write, speak and understand Arabic, it is important to learn the grammar. Arabic grammar can be tough and intimidating, but it doesn’t have to be. Grammar here means the important words that give structure to a sentence, in addition to the structures themselves. In linguistics, we call such words &#34;function words&#34;. When you know these words, you’ll be able to recognize them and use them easily to understand and build simple sentences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best International Maths Olympiad/ Olympiad Mathematics-2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/best-international-maths-olympiad/-olympiad-mathematics-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/best-international-maths-olympiad/-olympiad-mathematics-2021/</guid>
      <description>Hi,
Are you or your children or your friends struggling with Math? Do you want to become a human calculator? If yes, then what are you waiting for? Enroll yourself in this course and have fun with Math. This course contains the world&#39;s fastest Vedic math techniques. It contains many solved examples, and exercises which will be help you . This course contains examples that are explained in every detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Udemy bootcamp: How to create a STUNNING course Unofficial</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/udemy-bootcamp-how-to-create-a-stunning-course-unofficial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/udemy-bootcamp-how-to-create-a-stunning-course-unofficial/</guid>
      <description>Let&#39;s start with the basics, right now you are a person that surely has something to offer, a certain knowledge that you have and that you think you will be able to teach. By creating this course my main objective was to help you by giving you all the tips thats I used to create online content on different plateforms. So if you are someone that is ready to start with udemy and creat your own content this course is for you !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New SAT Math Practice Test Explain</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/new-sat-math-practice-test-explain/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/new-sat-math-practice-test-explain/</guid>
      <description>Course Summary 
 In this new SAT math explain course, you’ll learn and practice the methods in doing the new SAT math by solving the math with me. You’ll learn how to do it fast, accurate and without wasting time to write redundant steps to solve the same problems.
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Why Take This Course? 
 You’ll learn the new questions of the NEW SAT maths. Most importantly, you’ll start thinking with direction by observing how I tackle the problem step by step</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineering Drawing / Graphics : Hands-on training</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/engineering-drawing-/-graphics-hands-on-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/engineering-drawing-/-graphics-hands-on-training/</guid>
      <description>Students will be able to draw after instructors steps. As instructor has drawn with actual instruments of drawing learner will not get any difficulty to draw. Instructor will give learner step by step approach to draw various topics from engineering drawing/graphics. This course is for first year all branches engineering students, first year all branches polytechnic/diploma students and for 12th science students.  Ratings: 4.94/5
Enrollments: 11524
Coupon Code: TRAINING</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Arabic Reading</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/basic-arabic-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/basic-arabic-reading/</guid>
      <description>Learning Arabic is challenging in many ways. This course focuses on building the skill to read any Arabic word, by both learning the alphabet, including learning the name, sound, and shapes of each letter. In addition, the diacritics that guide the pronunciation of words are also explained. Finally, major prefixes and suffixes are also introduced. After you complete this course, you will be able to recognize the letters of any word and sound it out, which is the first step to read Arabic script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Linux (Part-1)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-linux-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-linux-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Dear Students,
Are you preparing for Job Exam and Interview in Linux?
Don’t be stressed, take our Linux Based quiz and prepare yourself for the Interview.
With this Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and tricks to solve Linux based questions. Here you will get Linux based MCQ for your next Job or Exam. In this Linux Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Knowledge in the field of Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archaische Astronomie 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/archaische-astronomie-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/archaische-astronomie-1/</guid>
      <description>Kennst du dich am Nachthimmel aus?

In diesem einführenden Kurs zur Archaischen Astronomie beschäftigen wir uns mit den sichtbaren Planeten und deren zyklischen Wiederkehr am Sternenhimmel.
Du weißt sicher über den Mondzyklus Bescheid. Unser Zeitbegriff &#34;Monat&#34; stammt vom synodischen Mondzyklus. Es gibt aber noch weitere 5 sichtbare Planeten, deren Zyklus du mit freiem Auge beobachten kannst: Merkur, Venus, Mars, Jupiter und Saturn. Deren Bewegung lässt sich über den Lauf eines oder mehrere Jahre ohne Hilfsmittel und mit freiem Auge beobachten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Polish Course: Learn Polish for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-polish-course-learn-polish-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-polish-course-learn-polish-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to learn Polish? As the second most-spoken Slavic language with over 55 million native speakers, there are many benefits to learning this familiar, yet exotic language.
In this course, we’re going to take you through the first steps of your Polish journey, from absolute beginner to an intermediate level. Our lessons will cover everything, from teaching you how to read and write the Polish alphabet, to conjugating verbs and declining nouns, to forming sentences and describing yourself, the world around you and actions that take place within it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Cryptography</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-cryptography/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-cryptography/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in Cryptography? Don’t be stressed, take our Cryptography based quiz and prepare yourself for your Interview. 
With this Cryptography based Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Cryptography based questions. In these Cryptography based Multiple Choice Questions Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Basic Knowledge in Cryptography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner: 6 Full Practice Exams 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-6-full-practice-exams-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-6-full-practice-exams-2021/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to pass the AWS Cloud Practitioner exam? Find out by testing yourself with this new offering on Udemy. Each of the 6 practice tests in this set provide an entire exam’s worth of questions, enabling you to confirm your mastery of the topics and providing you with the confidence you’ll need to take the exam.
The tests in this set are timed, so you’ll know when you’re taking more time than the official test allows, and at the end of the test you’ll receive a personal breakdown of the questions you answered correctly and incorrectly (DETAILED EXPLANATIONS) to improve your knowledge and make you more prepared to pass the actual exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Cyber Security</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-cyber-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-cyber-security/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in Cyber Security? Don’t be stressed, take our Cyber Security based quiz and prepare yourself for your Interview.
With this Cyber Security based Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Cyber Security based questions. In Cyber Security based Multiple Choice Questions Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Basic Knowledge in Cyber Security .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Engineering Arc Flash Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/power-engineering-arc-flash-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/power-engineering-arc-flash-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Power Engineering Arc Flash Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn how to do an arc flash analysis and developing an Arc Flash Safety Program for your business.

I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on Arc Flash as well as the hazards associated with it and how to do Arc Flash Mitigation.

If you are engineer, electrical worker or safety profession, you will find this course of great help to get the fundamental knowledge you need to kick start your professional career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arabic language through Drama | learn and entertain</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-language-through-drama-learn-and-entertain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-language-through-drama-learn-and-entertain/</guid>
      <description>In this course you will learn Arabic by Fun, watching Arabic series. The method will I apply in my videos are new and creative. So I have made new methods to teach you Arabic, hopefully this method will help a lot students to learn Arabic easily.
And at the end if you got any questions, don&#39;t hesitate ask me directly. I will be happy to answer all of your questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Portuguese Course: Portuguese for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-portuguese-course-portuguese-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-portuguese-course-portuguese-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our ultimate Portuguese beginner course that will teach you Portuguese faster than you thought possible! If you’ve ever dreamed of travelling to Portugal and holding your own in real-life situations, being independent and able to communicate with the locals, our beginner series is the perfect place for you to continue your Portuguese journey! There’s always more to learn, and we’ve prepared yet another course to enrich your vocabulary, advance your grammar and help you express more and more complex thoughts, all in Portuguese!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corso Completo di Scrittura Comica - Parte Seconda</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/corso-completo-di-scrittura-comica-parte-seconda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/corso-completo-di-scrittura-comica-parte-seconda/</guid>
      <description>In questo corso, rivolto sia ai professionisti che ai semplici appassionati, ti insegnerò come poter diventare un ottimo autore comico nei più rinomati campi dello spettacolo. Ti spiegherò, passo dopo passo, le differenti fasi dello scrivere comico partendo dall&#39;idea iniziale e dallo sviluppo di un tema fino ad approdare alla fase dell’organizzazione del materiale e la costruzione dei personaggi. Quando si ha a che fare con la scrittura comica è necessario tener sempre a mente e in piena considerazione fattori come il pubblico, lo stile e il linguaggio in perenne trasformazione, i meccanismi chiave che muovono la grande macchina della comicità.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master the English Irregular Verbs Once and For All</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/master-the-english-irregular-verbs-once-and-for-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/master-the-english-irregular-verbs-once-and-for-all/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&#39;m Carlos. I&#39;m a Trilingual Udemy Instructor, and I can&#39;t wait to help you improve your fluency, and other skills in speaking English.
I have created this shorter version for you to get a taste of another of my courses. This will help you see the quality of the course and our teaching style. Expect more information in the near future. 
When I designed this course, I put myself where you are now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sıfırdan Konuşturan İngilizce Kursu (20&#43; Saat)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/s%C4%B1f%C4%B1rdan-konu%C5%9Fturan-ingilizce-kursu-20-saat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/s%C4%B1f%C4%B1rdan-konu%C5%9Fturan-ingilizce-kursu-20-saat/</guid>
      <description>• Bir dil en iyi doğal haliyle öğrenilir, yani çocukların öğrendiği gibi, kelimeleri sık sık duyarak.

• Hem Türkçe hem Kürtçe konuşan arkadaşınızın neden İngilizce öğrenemediğini hiç düşündünüz mü?

• İngilizce zor diye mi?

• En zor dil hangisi?

• Size göre Çince mi?

• Peki 2 milyar insan Çinceyi nasıl konuşuyor?

• Peki okuma yazma bilmeyen anne babanın bile çocuğuna konuşma dilini öğretirken, üniversitede öğretmenlik okumuş birinin neden dil öğretemediğini?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art Legends in Art History</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/art-legends-in-art-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/art-legends-in-art-history/</guid>
      <description>We are using an ancient and proven technique in teaching you about art history. We are using storytelling. During ancient times, wise people spread the tales of the past to anyone who would listen. The art of storytelling is lost in the education space of today. We have made it our mission to teach our students about the masters of the art world, the art movements, and art history by telling stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to read Arabic for beginners | Basics &amp; principles</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-read-arabic-for-beginners-basics-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-read-arabic-for-beginners-basics-principles/</guid>
      <description>Arabic is widely taught in schools and universities and is used to varying degrees in workplaces, government and the media. Arabic, in its standard form, is the official language of 26 states, as well as the liturgical language of the religion of Islam, since the Quran and Hadith were written in Arabic.
In this course, you will learn how to read Arabic. by taking lessons gradually and easily, after finishing this course you will start practice reading by yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Course Creation - Create &amp; Sell Online Courses</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/online-course-creation-create-sell-online-courses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/online-course-creation-create-sell-online-courses/</guid>
      <description>Whatever your profession or experience may be, if you’ve ever wanted to turn your knowledge, skills or talents into a profitable online course, then you’re in the right place!

This professional masterclass training program provides absolutely everything you&#39;ll need to successfully build your own online business creating and selling online courses.

From deciding what you should be teaching, to marketing to the right audience, to buying the right equipment and knowing what to charge, I&#39;ll walk you through everything you need to know in order to create and launch a successful online course that customers will happily pay for!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick tricks in quantitative aptitude- CCAT, Wonderlic</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quick-tricks-in-quantitative-aptitude-ccat-wonderlic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quick-tricks-in-quantitative-aptitude-ccat-wonderlic/</guid>
      <description>Quantitative aptitude is a necessary requirement to enter into any higher level education and entry level jobs in any sector. About this course:
This course on Quantitative aptitude simplifies the concept in the form of quick tricks. Here, Quick trick is a formula, or a rule which helps you to solve the question in less time. This course is meticulously designed to meet your test preparation needs. Basics of numbers, ratios, averages and percentages are discussed in this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2021 - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Do you remember the &#34;Jetsons show&#34;? 
The Jetsons fascinated me and everyone else around me. Thoughts of moving sidewalks, self-driving vehicles and robot housekeepers - fuelled my daydreams to the core. Let&#39;s now talk about the present time and the tech that is evolving.
Nowadays, I can command a robotic tool, device or tech to tell me the next day’s weather, read a e-book to me, play my preferred podcasts and even vacuum my flooring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Ethical Hacking</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-ethical-hacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 09:38:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-ethical-hacking/</guid>
      <description>Dear Students,
Are you Preparing for Interview in Ethical Hacking? Don’t be stressed, take our Ethical Hacking quiz and prepare yourself for the Interview.
With this Ethical Hacking Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Ethical Hacking based questions. Here you will get Ethical Hacking based MCQ for your next Job or exam. In Ethical Hacking Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Knowledge in the field of Ethical Hacking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Criminology : Fundamentals of Criminal Psychology and Law</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/criminology-fundamentals-of-criminal-psychology-and-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 11:41:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/criminology-fundamentals-of-criminal-psychology-and-law/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
What is criminology?
Criminology is a branch of sociology, which traditionally examines human behavior, interaction, and organization. However, it also ties in research and concepts from other areas of study, such as philosophy, anthropology, biology, and psychology. Criminologists examine a broad range of topics related to crime. They are dedicated to studying not only the causes of crime but the social roots and impact as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Petroleum Institute API PRACTICE QUESTIONS</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/american-petroleum-institute-api-practice-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/american-petroleum-institute-api-practice-questions/</guid>
      <description>The American Petroleum Institute (API) is the largest U.S. trade association for the oil and natural gas industry. It claims to represent nearly 600 corporations involved in production, refinement, distribution, and many other aspects of the petroleum industry.
The association describes its mission as to promote safety across the industry globally and influence public policy in support of a strong, viable U.S. oil and natural gas industry. API&#39;s chief functions on behalf of the industry include advocacy, negotiation and lobbying with governmental, legal, and regulatory agencies; research into economic, toxicological, and environmental effects; establishment and certification of industry standards; and education outreach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Machine Learning Specialty --&gt; Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-machine-learning-specialty-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-machine-learning-specialty-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Interview in Machine Learning? 
Don’t be stressed, Take our Machine Learning Based Mock Test and prepare yourself for the Interview. Here you will get Machine Learning based Multiple Choice Question for your Next Interview.
What you will get in These Mock Test ? 
It contains sample questions which are likely to be asked in the Interview and Exam.
These Machine Learning based MCQ questions help you with self-study and self-assessment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Manipulation Works in Research</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-manipulation-works-in-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-manipulation-works-in-research/</guid>
      <description>DON&#39;T MANIPULATE RESEARCH - RESEARCH MANIPULATION
Manipulation is dangerous, regardless of where it occurs in life.
In this course, we are going to explore specifically how it occurs in scientific research.
Both researchers and other stakeholders can use a myriad methods to twist facts, change emotions in people, reduce the perceived effort of supporting someone, and other means.
This is the only course you will find that focuses on manipulation specifically for research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>Preparing for Machine learning Interview? Don’t be stressed, take our Machine learning based quiz questions and prepare your self for the interview. With this Machine learning Quiz Questions, we are going to you build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Machine learning questions. Here you will get Machine learning General Multiple Choice Questions and Answers for your next job or exam. In Machine learning Multiple Choice Questions based practice tests, there will be a series of practice tests wherein you can test your Basic Machine learning concepts on every Topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English grammar tenses &amp; structures, the ultimate course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/english-grammar-tenses-structures-the-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 11:17:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/english-grammar-tenses-structures-the-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>The course provides you with a variety of grammar rules that enable you to read, write and form perfect English sentences. The course forms a great combination of grammar rules with examples. It takes you step by step from understanding the rule into applying examples that enhance your English language skills. We add weekly quizzes with model answers.
 Ratings: 4.39/5
Enrollments: 174726
Coupon Code: SEPTEMBER26
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultrasonic Testing Level 1 Training</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ultrasonic-testing-level-1-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:50:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ultrasonic-testing-level-1-training/</guid>
      <description>This course teaches you how to perform ultrasonic inspection from beginning to end.
The course provides you with Level 1 training in the fundamentals of Ultrasonic Testing methods. It will introduce you to the basic concepts and principles and includes hands-on training using Ultrasonic Testing equipment settings and functions.The Ultrasonic theories presented will provide the knowledge of Ultrasonic Testing required and enable you to work with individuals qualified and certified to gain needed experience for qualification as Level 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adli Bilişim/Dijital Kursu</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/adli-bili%C5%9Fim/dijital-kursu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:47:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/adli-bili%C5%9Fim/dijital-kursu/</guid>
      <description>Günümüzün dijital dünyasında önemli bir konu olan siber dünya ile ilgili hukuki ve kanuni, ama öncesindeki süreçte de önemli bir yer teşkil ederek üzerinde bilimsel ve pratik çalışmalar yapılmaya ihtiyaç duyulan adli Dijital Bilişim, bu kursta detaylarıyla incelenerek, kursu takip edenler için hem pratikte, günlük yaşamda, hem de mesleki anlamda önemli yeterlilik bilgileri ve tecrübeleri vermektedir.
Bu kurs, Adli Bilişim ile ilgili temel ve genel bilgileri içermektedir. Dersler, akıcı ve anlaşılır bir şekilde olup, her düzeyden başlayabileceğiniz şekilde tasarlanmıştır.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drug Design and Molecular Docking by using computation Tools</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/drug-design-and-molecular-docking-by-using-computation-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/drug-design-and-molecular-docking-by-using-computation-tools/</guid>
      <description>In the filed molecular orientation modeling, Molecular Docking the perfect binding of two molecules, like prediction of ligand binding on the active size of the protein. On the basic knowledge of computer you learn ligand based Computer Aided Drug design (CADD) approach involves the analysis of ligands known to interact with a target of interest. One such course is particularly designed to maintain knowledge at the beginner level of computer Drug Discovery applications for science students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn DNA Primer Design for Polymerase Chain Reaction</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-dna-primer-design-for-polymerase-chain-reaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-dna-primer-design-for-polymerase-chain-reaction/</guid>
      <description>In this Bioinformatics course you will be find out how to DNA Primer Design for polymerase chain reaction. Primer BLAST performs only a specificity check when a target template and both primers are provided. Design primers for single- or multi-insert cloning or for your site-directed mutagenesis experiment (insertion, deletion, replacement) with our primer design tool. Primer3 is a computer program that suggests PCR primers for a variety of applications, for example to create STSs (sequence tagged sites) for radiation hybrid mapping, or to amplify sequences for single nucleotide polymor- phism discovery</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Electrical Engineering</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-electrical-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 21:16:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-electrical-engineering/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in Electrical Engineering? Don’t be stressed, take our Electrical Engineering based quiz and prepare yourself for your Interview. 
With this Electrical Engineering based Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Electrical Engineering based questions. In Electrical Engineering based Multiple Choice Questions Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Basic Knowledge in Electrical Engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Armed Services Vocational Aptitude Battery ASVAB tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-armed-services-vocational-aptitude-battery-asvab-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-armed-services-vocational-aptitude-battery-asvab-tests/</guid>
      <description>Armed Services Vocational Aptitude Battery ASVAB tests
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily

Welcome to Our ASVAB Practice Test!Our tests are designed to help you with your ASVAB test prep and review.Each of our free ASVAB practice tests includes challenging practice questions along with detailed explanations. Whether you are preparing for a career in the Army, Navy, Air Force, or the Marines you will need to pass the ASVAB test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Foundations of Biology: An Introduction</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-foundations-of-biology-an-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-foundations-of-biology-an-introduction/</guid>
      <description>This course will teach you the foundations and basics of biology and go further in-depth on various interesting concepts.
Topics Covered In Course
Characteristics of Life
Properties of Water
Atoms and Elements
Bonds
Cells
Lipid Bilayers and Osmosis
Macromolecules
Content Overview
Suitable for all levels, this is an in-depth learning course with lectures and quizzes. You do not need any prior experience to understand the material in this course. This course will walk you through your adventure into Biology and the Characteristics of Life by providing engaging video&#39;s on various topics and quizzes to test your knowledge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOEFL reading practice tests Questions and Answers</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/toefl-reading-practice-tests-questions-and-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/toefl-reading-practice-tests-questions-and-answers/</guid>
      <description>TOEFL reading practice tests Questions and Answers
2022 reading tests for TOEFL Test of English as a Foreign Language

Test of English as a Foreign Language TOEFL is a standardized test to measure the English language ability of non-native speakers wishing to enroll in English-speaking universities. The test is accepted by more than 11,000 universities and other institutions in over 150 countries. TOEFL is one of the two major English-language tests in the world, the other being the IELTS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplilearn Arduino</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/simplilearn-arduino/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/simplilearn-arduino/</guid>
      <description>Arduino is an open-source computer hardware/software platform for building digital devices and interactive objects that can sense and control the physical world around them. In this class you will learn how the Arduino platform works in terms of the physical board and libraries and the IDE (integrated development environment).
Upon completing this course, you will be able to: 1. Outline the composition of the Arduino development board 2. Describe what it means to program the board&#39;s firmware 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on D.C. Machines</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-d.c.-machines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 22:18:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-d.c.-machines/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in D.C. Machines based Company? Don’t be stressed, take our D.C. Machines based quiz and prepare yourself for your Interview.
With this D.C. Machines based Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve D.C. Machines based questions. In D.C. Machines based Multiple Choice Questions Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Basic Knowledge in D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deutsch - Klare Kommunikation  A2-C1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/deutsch-klare-kommunikation-a2-c1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/deutsch-klare-kommunikation-a2-c1/</guid>
      <description>Wie kann ich klar kommunizieren, das was mir wichtig ist?
Wie können Konflikte so angesprochen werden, dass mein Gegenüber bereit ist zu kooperieren?
Lernen Sie zu formulieren was Sie möchten, anstatt nur zu sagen was sie stört.
Kann ich mich so ausdrücken, dass das was ich bin, unzweideutig mitgeteilt wird?
Neben dem Erwerb von psychosozialen Kompetenzen für den Beruf und Alltag werden im Kurshilfreiche Kommunikationsstrukturen, sowie ein differenziertes psychologisches Vokabular erlernt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Language Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/english-language-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/english-language-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>Preparing for Competitive Exams like IELTS or TOEFL and looking for more practice questions on English Grammar?
You have come to the right practice assessment course! 
Test your knowledge with this practice test created by experts who have years of experience in the field. Suitable for beginners who want to improve their understanding of written English or to improve their knowledge with explanations and timed tests.

Most questions and multiple choice and fill in the blank type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Egyptian Arabic through Cartoon movie</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-egyptian-arabic-through-cartoon-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-egyptian-arabic-through-cartoon-movie/</guid>
      <description>This is actually a new idea in teaching a foreign language , Hello everyone. I&#39;m Mr,Bakoor. I have been teaching Arabic for several years. so I have enough experience in teaching Arabic, in this course I come up with a new idea a new strategy to Egyptian Arabic this idea is you will get fun while learning Egyptian dialect. this idea will make memorization easier to, you will find it enjoyable and easy to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking for College Students: Become a Great Speaker</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-for-college-students-become-a-great-speaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 12:19:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-for-college-students-become-a-great-speaker/</guid>
      <description>Imagine speaking to a classroom or even an auditorium full of students knowing that everyone understands you, remembers your key messages and feels you are a confident speaker. Wouldn&#39;t it be great to know that you can speak to any sized audience and that you will always come across your very best?  In this Public Speaking for College Students course you will learn the following:  *How to speak with confidence inside and outside the classroom  *How to avoid the common speaking blunders made by most other college students  *How to rehearse important presentations on video  *How to make fellow students and adults remember your messages  This course is delivered primarily through spoken lecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Transformer</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 07:41:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-transformer/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in Transformer based Company? Don’t be stressed, take our Transformer based quiz and prepare yourself for your Interview.
With this Transformer based Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Transformer based questions. In Transformer based Multiple Choice Questions Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Basic Knowledge in Transformer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be an expert in English Grammar</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/be-an-expert-in-english-grammar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:52:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/be-an-expert-in-english-grammar/</guid>
      <description>The course has 14 sections. They display the different grammar rules in a funny way that depends on the animated cartoons. These 14 sections have 96 lectures. These 96 lectures have 2 hours of video content. This course takes you from level 1 to be a professional in the English grammar.  Ratings: 4.30/5
Enrollments: 72280
Coupon Code: SEPTEMBER16
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TESOL and TPRS Course (For Language Teachers)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tesol-and-tprs-course-for-language-teachers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:52:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/tesol-and-tprs-course-for-language-teachers/</guid>
      <description>Although uneducated parents can teach a languge to their children, how can educated teachers not teach a foreign language? In this course, you will learn how to teach a languge with a contemporary method but ancient.

In ancient times, people used to travel by horses or camels but then they invented cars and began to go everywhere with them. Today, we use planes. There is no doubt that cars are faster than horses, but planes are the fastest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2021 - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this superb course that will walk you through the future of content creation. Taking a leap from RoboAuthor Part 1, this Part 2 course taught by Digital Marketing Legend Srinidhi Ranganathan and MasterMind Saranya Srinidhi will continue your adventure in content writing to open a new door of opportunities that is incredibly futuristic. 
It is undoubtedly one of the most challenging tasks to create content for your digital marketing campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2021 - Part 3</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-3/</guid>
      <description>Ready to create ebooks in minutes?
Welcome to this superb course that will walk you through the future of content creation and eBook generation. Taking a leap from RoboAuthor Part 2, this Part 3 course taught by Digital Marketing Legend Srinidhi Ranganathan will continue your adventure in content writing to unlock opportunities for ultra-fast eBook writing and creation with the power of Artificial Intelligence. 
We must know that artificial intelligence will create amazing content today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10X Amazon Ebay Dropshipping Fba Wholesale 2021 Para Kazanma</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/10x-amazon-ebay-dropshipping-fba-wholesale-2021-para-kazanma/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/10x-amazon-ebay-dropshipping-fba-wholesale-2021-para-kazanma/</guid>
      <description>2021 yılında hala ticarete başlamadıysan bu kurs tam sana göre. Ben Akın Yılmaz, takım arkadaşlarımla beraber sizlerin ticaretinizi geliştirmenizi ve internet üzerinden gelir elde edebilmeniz için sizlere Udemy üzerinden Ücretisiz eğitimler hazırlıyoruz. Temel ticaret mantığını anlamak ve kendinizi e-ticaret alanında geliştirmek için lütfen bu kursa ve Akın Yılmaz kanalına göz atın. Buralarda sahip olmasını isteyeceğiniz çok kıymetli bilgiler var. Ve siz bu bilgileri edinmelisiniz. Artık kendi paranızı kazanma vaktiniz geldi. Tek yapmanız gereken aksiyon alıp artık başlamak ve ticaretinizi geliştirmek.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AP Physics 1 - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ap-physics-1-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ap-physics-1-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Master AP Physics 1 and get the score you want in this clear, concise, and in-depth course! This course will teach you everything, from kinematics to energy to momentum, and consists of lectures and practice problems for each unit. This is the first part of the entire AP Physics 1 course, covering the first portion of the curriculum units. Each unit has specific videos with hand-picked problems to supplement the lectures, making the overall learning process easy, efficient, and effective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Pronunciation Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/english-pronunciation-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/english-pronunciation-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Hi! My name is Professor G and I&#39;m an English teacher with more than 10 years of teaching experience. I previously studied French and Spanish at university, and I&#39;ve taught English in a number of countries around the world, including Brazil (Campinas), France (Paris) and Spain (Malaga). I understand the problems that language learners experience, especially when it comes to speaking the language. When I first moved to France, I had studied French for 5 years, but had very little speaking practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zero To Hero! Intro To Algebra: Variables, Fractions &amp; More</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/zero-to-hero-intro-to-algebra-variables-fractions-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/zero-to-hero-intro-to-algebra-variables-fractions-more/</guid>
      <description>In this course you will get professional maths tutoring to help you be successful at Algebra. We cover the basics of algebra such as variables, fractions, operations, cubes, roots and squares. You will get practical, step by step explanations, practice examples and demonstration lessons. A solid introduction to algebra is so important for the rest of your maths journey so join us in this course as we help you achieve your goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrivere un Dialogo - Scrittura Creativa Vol. 3</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/scrivere-un-dialogo-scrittura-creativa-vol.-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 18:00:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/scrivere-un-dialogo-scrittura-creativa-vol.-3/</guid>
      <description>Ciao! 
 In questo corso ti spiegherò come poter approcciare, nel migliore dei modi, alla composizione di un’ ottima sequenza dialogica e all’importanza che essa assume all’interno di un racconto, un romanzo o qualsivoglia opera di carattere narrativo. Considera che tra i motivi del “Blocco della pagina bianca&#34; di molti scrittori alle prime armi vi è proprio il senso di inadeguatezza o incapacità nell’affrontare la scrittura dei dialoghi e ti renderai conto che ovviare eliminando gli stessi dialoghi non rappresenta affatto una soluzione effettiva.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Il Personaggio - Scrittura Creativa Vol. 5</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/il-personaggio-scrittura-creativa-vol.-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 09:03:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/il-personaggio-scrittura-creativa-vol.-5/</guid>
      <description>Come nasce l&#39;idea per un personaggio narrativo?
A chi o a cosa ispirarsi?
Dall&#39;idea di un determinato personaggio come si giunge poi al suo inserimento in un preciso contesto narrativo?
Come rivestire uno o più personaggi di credibilità??
Queste sono solo alcune delle domande che affiorano nella mente di uno scrittore quando decide di cimentarsi nella scrittura di un &#39;opera narrativa, a prescindere dal genere che deciderà di seguire o adottare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AutoCAD Course l كورس الاوتوكاد</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/autocad-course-l-%D9%83%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%B3-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%88%D8%AA%D9%88%D9%83%D8%A7%D8%AF/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/autocad-course-l-%D9%83%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%B3-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%88%D8%AA%D9%88%D9%83%D8%A7%D8%AF/</guid>
      <description>كورس الاوتوكاد كورس هنتعلم فيه مع بعض اهم الاسس اللي لازم تكون عارفها عن الاوتوكاد
 هنتعلم مع بعض اوامر الرسم المختلفة وكذالك اوامر التعديل المختلفة
زي Filet , Extend , Scale , Alignment , Divide , match , hatch ,text , offset , move , rotate , mirror , Block and Explode 
سنتعرف على الاوامر الهامة داخل برنامج الاوتوكاد الذى لا غنى عنه فى اى تصميم او رسومات بانواعها والذى ايضاً فى حاجه له مع برامج اخرى لتوصيل الفكرة وتنفيذها بسهولة .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kamu Yönetimi Kapsamlı Kursu</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/kamu-y%C3%B6netimi-kapsaml%C4%B1-kursu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/kamu-y%C3%B6netimi-kapsaml%C4%B1-kursu/</guid>
      <description>Kamu Yönetimi dersleri, diğer bilim dalları ve derslerden farklı özellikler göstermektedir. Örneğin ülkelerin yapısı ve hiyerarşisine göre değişkenlik göstermesi sebebiyle uygulanış açıklama ve yorumları, evrensel bir dille genel bir yapı göstermediği için diğer dillerden bir uyarlama yapılamayıp, özgün çalışmalar gerektirir.
Bu kurs, bu sebeple daha önce yapılmış çalışmaların ışığında ve öğrencilerin sık karşılaştıkları veya karşılaşmak durumunda olacakları sorulara ve cevaplara çok fazla yer vererek, gerekli anlaşılır açıklamaların yapıldığı derslerden oluşmaktadır.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English language basics for beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/english-language-basics-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 12:13:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/english-language-basics-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>We make it easy for you to learn how to speak and write English fluently as a beginner learner. These English lessons will show you how to say and use almost anything in daily English conversation. Get started now with our speaking, vocabulary and grammar exercises that come with model answers. In this course, you will learn important topics and lessons in English, such as, Alphabet, numbers, saying hello, signs and symbols, telling the time, asking and answering questions about name, age, weather, classroom things, classroom instructions, days of the week, months of the year, seasons of the year, basic colors, simple shapes and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrivere per Bambini e Ragazzi - Scrittura Creativa Vol. 2</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/scrivere-per-bambini-e-ragazzi-scrittura-creativa-vol.-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 12:13:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/scrivere-per-bambini-e-ragazzi-scrittura-creativa-vol.-2/</guid>
      <description>In questo corso di scrittura creativa per bambini e per ragazzi parlerò delle tecniche che vi sono dietro lo scrivere in base a due fattori: la fascia di età e il genere. 

In questo corso in particolar modo i nostri lettori vengono suddivisi in quattro fasce di età:
1. al di sotto dei 5 anni
2. dai 5 ai 7 anni
3. dagli 8 agli 11
4. dai 12 ai 14</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arabic: Learn Arabic Language| Online Arabic Language Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-learn-arabic-language-online-arabic-language-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 20:51:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-learn-arabic-language-online-arabic-language-course/</guid>
      <description>Marhaba (Hello and welcome)!
My name is Nezha, and welcome to Arabic 4 U!   ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
After taking this online Arabic language course, you will start to:
 Speak Arabic with Arabic speakers from around the world

 Understand Formal Arabic called Modern Standard Arabic MSA or Fusha
 Arabic speakers learn Modern Standard Arabic in school. It is used in Arabic books, Arabic news, Arabic documentaries, Arabic road signs, and Arabic formal speeches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IEC 61850 Communication Protocol Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/iec-61850-communication-protocol-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/iec-61850-communication-protocol-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>IEC61850 Communication Protocol Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn industry specific knowledge about the IEC61850 protocol standard such as that found in the utility industry.

I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge from cable component basic to calculating for simple cable installation designs.
I will teach you the basic concepts of IEC61850 standard as well as the overall IEC61850 Data Model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Digital Marketing</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-digital-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 13:08:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-digital-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Dear Students,
Are you Preparing for Interview in Digital Marketing? Don’t be stressed, Take our Digital Marketing quiz and prepare yourself for the Interview.
With this Digital Marketing Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and tricks to solve Digital Marketing based questions. Here you will get Digital Marketing based MCQ for your next Job or Exam.
In Digital Marketing Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Knowledge in the field of Digital Marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corso completo di Teatro per bambini 4-6 anni</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/corso-completo-di-teatro-per-bambini-4-6-anni/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:16:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/corso-completo-di-teatro-per-bambini-4-6-anni/</guid>
      <description>In questo corso spiegherò come poter gestire un gruppo di bambini dai 4 ai 6 anni facendo loro praticare, in modo ludico ma nello stesso tempo costruttivo e creativo, attività teatrali volte alla conoscenza di elementi fondamentali per la suddetta fascia d&#39;età. 
Gli scopi di un laboratorio teatrale destinato ai più piccini sono svariati tra cui: 
1. Favorire la socializzazione; 2. Superare eventuali timidezze; 3. Coordinare l&#39;attività motoria; 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insight to Post Pandemic: Importance of Lean Six Sigma</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/insight-to-post-pandemic-importance-of-lean-six-sigma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:16:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/insight-to-post-pandemic-importance-of-lean-six-sigma/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this ultimate course on &#34;Insight to Post Pandemic: Importance of Lean Six Sigma&#34; that contains vaulable lessons taught by &#34;Casey Ang&#34; and &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34;.
Since its introduction as a corporate strategy by Jack Welch at General Electric in 1995, Six Sigma has come a long way. Since then, it has been widely adopted in a variety of industries.
The Greek letter sigma is used by statisticians to represent the variation in a process and we all know that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angiosperm :  Flowering Plant</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/angiosperm-flowering-plant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/angiosperm-flowering-plant/</guid>
      <description>The flowering plants, also known as Angiospermae, meaning hidden seeds in Greek, are the most diverse group of land plants with 64 orders, 416 families, approximately 13,000 known genera and 300,000 known species. Like gymnosperms, angiosperms, which are also known by Magnoliophyta, are seed-producing plants.
The angiosperms dominate Earth’s surface and vegetation in more environments, particularly terrestrial habitats, than any other group of plants. As a result, angiosperms are the most important ultimate source of food for birds and mammals, including humans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build your own first Voice Assistant in Python</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-build-your-own-first-voice-assistant-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-build-your-own-first-voice-assistant-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to this class
In this project you will learn how to build your first virtual assistant VA in python in less then 90 minutes.
This is a great small project to get started (even if you have little or no prior knowledge in python) and learning opportunity.
Learning through your own little projects is the best and most enjoying way to improve your skills.
In the world of today we all already use Virtual Assistants like Alexa, Siri, Google and others more and more in our daily lifes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning &amp; Data Science A-Z: Hands-on Python 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/machine-learning-data-science-a-z-hands-on-python-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/machine-learning-data-science-a-z-hands-on-python-2021/</guid>
      <description>Are you interested in data science and machine learning, but you don&#39;t have any background, and you find the concepts confusing?
Are you interested in programming in Python, but you always afraid of coding?
I think this course is for you!
Even if you are familiar with machine learning, this course can help you to review all the techniques and understand the concept behind each term.
This course is completely categorized, and we don&#39;t start from the middle!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introductory Biology: Complete course of Biology</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introductory-biology-complete-course-of-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introductory-biology-complete-course-of-biology/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt; This course is designed to meet the requirement of the students to understand the Complete Introduction of Biology.

&amp;gt;This course presents many of the topics Found in O and A level biology.

&amp;gt;The topics are presented through PowerPoints presentation.Each body system is presented separately and there are quizzes at the end of each section.

&amp;gt;In this Course , Students will learn the introduction of Biology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nanotechnology Fundamentals - Most comperehensive NANOTECH</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/nanotechnology-fundamentals-most-comperehensive-nanotech/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 11:42:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/nanotechnology-fundamentals-most-comperehensive-nanotech/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
Nanotechnology is a field of research and innovation concerned with building &#39;things&#39; - generally, materials and devices - on the scale of atoms and molecules. A nanometre is one-billionth of a metre: ten times the diameter of a hydrogen atom. The diameter of a human hair is, on average, 80,000 nanometres. At such scales, the ordinary rules of physics and chemistry no longer apply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Path Loss 5</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-path-loss-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:28:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-path-loss-5/</guid>
      <description>You want to learn about network planning, especially the Access Network which is most fragile and ever changing part of the fixed and wireless network.

I have been working in the transmission field since last twenty years and I found that there is no basic training of the most commonly used access planning software and the new comers in Transmission planning learn this tool through hit and trial. That is why they are never able to fully utilize their potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corso completo di Teatro: esercizi pratici (Per Formatori)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/corso-completo-di-teatro-esercizi-pratici-per-formatori/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:15:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/corso-completo-di-teatro-esercizi-pratici-per-formatori/</guid>
      <description>Essere un Formatore Teatrale non è semplice, ci si ritrova ogni volta in contesti differenti, con persone di età diverse e che giungono con motivazioni più disparate. Per tali motivi ho cercato di non tralasciare alcun aspetto sul come impostare un Laboratorio Teatrale: dall&#39;organizzazione delle lezioni, alla tempistica, e poi tutti gli esercizi più importanti per fare un laboratorio teatrale, ognuno spiegato nei minimi particolari.
 A dispetto di tanto impegno per fare un laboratorio di teatro, alla fine si hanno grandi soddisfazioni: si assiste lezione dopo lezione alla crescita degli aspiranti attori, li si vede affrontare i vari ostacoli e superarli, ed io stessa dopo ogni laboratorio mi sento arricchita, è qualcosa che solo chi ha sentito il profumo di un palco può capire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Allama Iqbal Poetry Explanation Course in Urdu</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-ultimate-allama-iqbal-poetry-explanation-course-in-urdu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 20:19:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-ultimate-allama-iqbal-poetry-explanation-course-in-urdu/</guid>
      <description>Allama Muhammad Iqbal is one of the most outstanding poet-philosophers of the Indian sub-continent belonging to the modern period. His intellectual genius has reigned supreme in the arena of Islamic philosophy during the twentieth century and is likely to direct and influence the Islamic Intellectual tradition in the twenty first century as well. His sublime poetry and philosophy inspired millions of Muslims to wake up to the reality of the times and forge a destiny for themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Academic Writing course: Research &#43; Essay Writing!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ultimate-academic-writing-course-research-essay-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 20:19:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ultimate-academic-writing-course-research-essay-writing/</guid>
      <description>This course is specially developed for students who need the essential knowledge to prepare them for writing and defending their thesis/dissertation in an efficient and effective manner. I have created 17 lectures that cover all facets of thesis writing in one and a half hour!
SummaryI will start with the end in mind; how is your thesis evaluated? Based on this central question I explain my formula of success and take you by the hand from topic selection all the way up to successful thesis defence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High School Organic Chemistry 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/high-school-organic-chemistry-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/high-school-organic-chemistry-1/</guid>
      <description>Chemistry is fun when you learn from the best tutors. At Go2uni, we present you “High School Organic Chemistry 1”. We start from the basics and take a deep dive with clear examples and exercises to ensure every concept is understood.
Go2uni presents seasoned tutors with years of experience to offer you &#34;High School Organic Chemistry 1&#34;, the organic chemistry course you need to ace your exams.
This course will demystify Chemistry with tonnes of examples, work through exercises and take-home exercises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Miller Analogies Test (MAT) TOP Practical Questions</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-miller-analogies-test-mat-top-practical-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-miller-analogies-test-mat-top-practical-questions/</guid>
      <description>Hello !
Most Common Miller Analogies Test (MAT) professional Questions with your hand
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily
The Miller Analogies Test (MAT) is a standardized test used both for graduate school admissions in the United States and entrance to high I.Q. societies. Created and still published by Harcourt Assessment (now a division of Pearson Education), the MAT consists of 120 questions in 60 minutes (formerly 100 questions in 50 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware Certified Professional - VCP-DTM Practice Exams 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/vmware-certified-professional-vcp-dtm-practice-exams-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/vmware-certified-professional-vcp-dtm-practice-exams-2021/</guid>
      <description>We have created these practice exams with over 130 questions to help you prepare for the VCP-DTM exam and help you pass on your first attempt.
More information about the certifications :
VMware Desktop and Mobility certifications are designed to gauge your level of skill designing, installing, and managing a VMware Horizon with View environment deployed on a VMware vSphere implementation. The VCP-DTM 2021 certification validates a candidate’s skills in performing in-depth configuration and management of VMware Horizon environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Computer Basics Guide for Beginners: 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-computer-basics-guide-for-beginners-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-computer-basics-guide-for-beginners-2021/</guid>
      <description>The Computer Defined, Data versus Information, Classification of Computers based on how data is handled (Analog Computers, Digital Computers Hybrid Computers)
Computers for Individual Users or Personal Computers (Desktop Computers,Workstations, Laptops, Notebooks, Tablets, Handheld PCs, Smartphones)
Computers for Organizations (Network Server, Mainframes, Minicomputers, Supercomputers)
Parts of Computer System (Hardware , Software, User and Data)
Information Processing Cycle (Input, Processing, Output, Storage)
Computer Hardware Categorized ( Processing Devices, Memory Devices, Input and Output Devices, Storage Devices, Bus Interconnection)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improvvisazione Teatrale e Comica: dalla teoria alla pratica</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/improvvisazione-teatrale-e-comica-dalla-teoria-alla-pratica/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/improvvisazione-teatrale-e-comica-dalla-teoria-alla-pratica/</guid>
      <description>Cos&#39;è un&#39; improvvisazione? E se si chiama IMPROVVISAZIONE perché studiarla in un corso?
Perché sono state scritte tonnellate di libri a tal riguardo?
L&#39;improvvisazione è una vera e propria Arte e come tale necessita di studio, tecnica ed esperienza. 
Non si può improvvisare senza possedere le conoscenze adatte.
Esistono due differenti forme di improvvisazione, quella &#34;muta&#34; nella quale l&#39;unico strumento comunicativo è rappresentato dal corpo e quella &#34;parlata&#34; durante la quale voce(storytelling) e corpo agiscono all&#39;unisono, quest&#39;ultima è l&#39;improvvisazione di cui ti parlerò in questo corso.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redação: Enem, vestibular, concurso.Teoria &#43; tira-dúvidas</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/reda%C3%A7%C3%A3o-enem-vestibular-concurso.teoria-tira-d%C3%BAvidas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/reda%C3%A7%C3%A3o-enem-vestibular-concurso.teoria-tira-d%C3%BAvidas/</guid>
      <description>Se você já tem professor para avaliar suas redações, e não&amp;nbsp; precisa de exercícios de reforço, aqui você tem as quase 8&amp;nbsp;horas de aulas em vídeo do curso completo (disponível na plataforma Udemy) + tira-dúvidas ilimitado comigo!

Você vai descobrir como escrever dissertações de provas mais rápido, sem decorar regras ou fórmulas.
Se você trava ou fica em &#34;branco&#34;, veja o que te espera:
tipos de dissertação
como começar a redação sem travar</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American English Pronunciation for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/american-english-pronunciation-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/american-english-pronunciation-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling with your English pronunciation? 
Do you have a strong accent when speaking English?

Do native speakers always ask you to repeat yourself?

Do you want to begin speaking with an American accent confidently?

Do you what tips and help with speaking with an American accent? 
I welcome you to this - “American English Pronunciation Training - course where I will patiently guide you through the basic techniques you need to pronounce English sounds correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arabic complete beginner course through (Byna Yadek)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-complete-beginner-course-through-byna-yadek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-complete-beginner-course-through-byna-yadek/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I&#39;m Mr.Bakoor. I have been teaching Arabic for a while. I got students form All over the world. My respect for all of them. My students liked the way I teach because It&#39;s easy, it goes step by step, they easily understand and also show improvement,&amp;nbsp; I feel so happy when I my student telling me that they are really improving in Arabic, I hope to make Arabic teaching easier for everyone who think Learning Arabic is hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combined Heat and Power (CHP) Cogeneration Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/combined-heat-and-power-chp-cogeneration-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/combined-heat-and-power-chp-cogeneration-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Combined Heat and Power (CHP) Cogeneration Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn all about the concept of CHP and cogeneration that are essential in working in the industry.

I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on cogeneration as well as how to apply it in the utility industry.

If you are currently a professional who are interested working with Cogeneration plants, you will find this course of great help to get the fundamental knowledge you need to kick start your professional career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete French Course: Learn French for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-french-course-learn-french-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-french-course-learn-french-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to learn French? Dubbed the “language of love”, French is used by over 235 million speakers daily in over 54 countries. But why should you pick French out of all the languages you could be learning?
To start, France isn’t just one of the most beautiful countries in central Europe, but a global powerhouse with significant presence in the automobile, aircraft and chemical manufacturing, the electronic, machinery, metallurgy industries, as well as tourism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete General Chemistry 20&#43; hours of lectures &amp; examples</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-general-chemistry-20-hours-of-lectures-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-general-chemistry-20-hours-of-lectures-examples/</guid>
      <description>Description:
General Chemistry is a basic course for a broad range of students from different fields of science and engineering. This course is designed to help you get a firm grasp over the most important topics in chemistry that you need to know in order to do great in your exams and classes. By the end of the course you’ll learn the principals and important concepts regarding matter, atoms, solutions, phases, chemical reactions, equilibrium, kinetics, acids and bases and so much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Tamil Course: Learn Tamil for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-tamil-course-learn-tamil-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-tamil-course-learn-tamil-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to learn Tamil? As one of the oldest classical languages in the world, Tamil is spoken by over 70 million people. But why should you pick Tamil out of all the languages you could be learning?
To start, Tamil is the official language of Tamil Nadu, India’s fourth largest state, which has seen significant economic growth and foreign investment over the last decade. The state is a leading figure in several industries, such as automobile and auto-components, engineering, pharmaceuticals and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash Course on Civil Engineering and AutoCAD: Part 3</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-3/</guid>
      <description>This incredible series-based crash course takes an amazing turn here in Part 3 as&amp;nbsp;&#34;New-age Environmental Engineering &amp;amp; Artificial Intelligence&#34; concepts are taught by Digital Marketing Legend &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34;&amp;nbsp;and Narmadha.M.
Environmental Engineering is a professional engineering discipline that takes advantage of specific scientific topics such as chemistry, biology, geography, geology, hydraulics, hydrology, microbiology, and mathematics to create solutions that will preserve and also improve the health of living organisms and increase environmental quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Differential Equations | Complete Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/differential-equations-complete-differential-equations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/differential-equations-complete-differential-equations/</guid>
      <description>Learn Differential Equation:
This course includes video lectures and text explanations of everything from differential equations and its applications, and it includes 7 quizzes (with video solutions!) and&amp;nbsp; for practice worksheet with extra practice problems, to help you test your understanding along the way. &#34;Differential Equations&#34; is arranged into the following sections:
Understanding of differential equations.
Order and degree of differential equations.
Formation of differential equation.
Variable separation method.
Substitution method of solution of differential equation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Biomedical Engineering - Nanodevices RAHBME282</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/intro-to-biomedical-engineering-nanodevices-rahbme282/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/intro-to-biomedical-engineering-nanodevices-rahbme282/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Nanodevices course, brought to you by Rahsoft. In this course we will be going over the basics and fundamentals of nanodevices and nanosensors, as well as in-depth examples and practice problems to give you a better understanding of the field. The course is taught by Dennis Fer, a Biomedical Engineering Instructor at Rahsoft, and the course advisor is Ahsan Ghoncheh, the Co-Founder and Technical Advisor at Rahsoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Heat Transfer Engineering - RAHHT1 Rahsoft</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-heat-transfer-engineering-rahht1-rahsoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-heat-transfer-engineering-rahht1-rahsoft/</guid>
      <description>Heat Transfer is one of the principle courses for all the university students who study in one of the branches of chemical engineering, mechanical engineering or materials engineering. This course which is placed at the beginning semesters of bachelor programs, is offered in two separate courses as heat transfer 1 &amp;amp; 2 each credited as 3 units. Having a full grasp over the concepts of heat transfer and fully understand the mechanisms of heat transfer in different situations is a must for any students studying the fields mentioned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japanese for French speakers : katakana</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/japanese-for-french-speakers-katakana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/japanese-for-french-speakers-katakana/</guid>
      <description>C&#39;est un cours complet pour apprendre tous les katakana, l&#39;alphabet de base japonais qui est utilisé pour écrire certaines catégories de mots tels que les mots étrangers ou les onomatopées. Grâce à des photos, des illustrations animées, une bande-son et des sous-titres en français, vous apprendrez facilement à lire le tableau entier des 46 katakana, à les prononcer parfaitement et à les écrire dans le bon ordre. Vous ne serez pas ennuyés, car à la fin de chaque section vous pourrez vérifier vos progrès avec des quiz amusants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matemáticas desde aritmética a cálculo con Python</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/matem%C3%A1ticas-desde-aritm%C3%A9tica-a-c%C3%A1lculo-con-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/matem%C3%A1ticas-desde-aritm%C3%A9tica-a-c%C3%A1lculo-con-python/</guid>
      <description>En este curso te enseñaré a usar Python como una herramienta para resolver problemas de matemáticas desde la aritmética hasta el cálculo diferencial e integral. Además de que te enseñaré a usar este lenguaje de manera muy básica. Siempre he dicho que lo mejor de un curso es ir al grano, por lo que te ayudaré a hacer ejercicios matemáticos directamente con las herramientas de Google Colaborative que nos permitirán programar en Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul: A Biography: Small Group Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/paul-a-biography-small-group-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/paul-a-biography-small-group-edition/</guid>
      <description>N. T. Wright&#39;s definitive biography of Paul reveals the apostle&#39;s lasting role in Christian history as an inventor of new paradigms for how we understand Jesus and what he accomplished. Wright celebrates Paul’s stature as one of the most effective and influential intellectuals in human history, while shedding fresh light on his writings, thoughts, and ideas. Consider these remarkable facts: Paul&#39;s writing occupy less than 90 pages in a modern translation yet they have, page per page, generated more sermons, books, monographs, and journal articles than any other writings from the ancient world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quadratic Equations &amp; Quadratic Expression</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quadratic-equations-quadratic-expression/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quadratic-equations-quadratic-expression/</guid>
      <description>Learn Quadratic Equations and Functions:
This 7 lessons course includes video lectures and text explanations of everything from quadratic equations and functions, and it includes 7 quizzes (with video solutions!) and&amp;nbsp; for practice worksheet with extra practice problems, to help you test your understanding along the way. &#34;Quadratic equations and expression&#34; is arranged into the following sections:
Basic concept of quadratic Equation
Solving a quadratic equation by different method
How many ways are there to solve a quadratic equation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 150 Most Important Irregular Verbs in English. Volume 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-150-most-important-irregular-verbs-in-english.-volume-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-150-most-important-irregular-verbs-in-english.-volume-1/</guid>
      <description>Support available in: English 
Spanish 
French

I can&#39;t wait to share with you this exciting English course based on Irregular Verbs. 
Do you feel unsure about the right conjugation when you try use irregular verbs in every day conversation?
Are you frustrated of having to memorize unending word lists? 
Then this course is for you. 
It is not a secret that Irregular Verbs are hard to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>