<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Teaching &amp; Academics on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/teaching-academics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Teaching &amp; Academics on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/teaching-academics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Archaische Astronomie 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/archaische-astronomie-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/archaische-astronomie-1/</guid>
      <description>Kennst du dich am Nachthimmel aus?

In diesem einführenden Kurs zur Archaischen Astronomie beschäftigen wir uns mit den sichtbaren Planeten und deren zyklischen Wiederkehr am Sternenhimmel.
Du weißt sicher über den Mondzyklus Bescheid. Unser Zeitbegriff &#34;Monat&#34; stammt vom synodischen Mondzyklus. Es gibt aber noch weitere 5 sichtbare Planeten, deren Zyklus du mit freiem Auge beobachten kannst: Merkur, Venus, Mars, Jupiter und Saturn. Deren Bewegung lässt sich über den Lauf eines oder mehrere Jahre ohne Hilfsmittel und mit freiem Auge beobachten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deutsch - Klare Kommunikation  A2-C1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/deutsch-klare-kommunikation-a2-c1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/deutsch-klare-kommunikation-a2-c1/</guid>
      <description>Wie kann ich klar kommunizieren, das was mir wichtig ist?
Wie können Konflikte so angesprochen werden, dass mein Gegenüber bereit ist zu kooperieren?
Lernen Sie zu formulieren was Sie möchten, anstatt nur zu sagen was sie stört.
Kann ich mich so ausdrücken, dass das was ich bin, unzweideutig mitgeteilt wird?
Neben dem Erwerb von psychosozialen Kompetenzen für den Beruf und Alltag werden im Kurshilfreiche Kommunikationsstrukturen, sowie ein differenziertes psychologisches Vokabular erlernt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Language Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/english-language-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/english-language-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>Preparing for Competitive Exams like IELTS or TOEFL and looking for more practice questions on English Grammar?
You have come to the right practice assessment course! 
Test your knowledge with this practice test created by experts who have years of experience in the field. Suitable for beginners who want to improve their understanding of written English or to improve their knowledge with explanations and timed tests.

Most questions and multiple choice and fill in the blank type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Egyptian Arabic through Cartoon movie</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-egyptian-arabic-through-cartoon-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-egyptian-arabic-through-cartoon-movie/</guid>
      <description>This is actually a new idea in teaching a foreign language , Hello everyone. I&#39;m Mr,Bakoor. I have been teaching Arabic for several years. so I have enough experience in teaching Arabic, in this course I come up with a new idea a new strategy to Egyptian Arabic this idea is you will get fun while learning Egyptian dialect. this idea will make memorization easier to, you will find it enjoyable and easy to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking for College Students: Become a Great Speaker</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-for-college-students-become-a-great-speaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 12:19:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-for-college-students-become-a-great-speaker/</guid>
      <description>Imagine speaking to a classroom or even an auditorium full of students knowing that everyone understands you, remembers your key messages and feels you are a confident speaker. Wouldn&#39;t it be great to know that you can speak to any sized audience and that you will always come across your very best?  In this Public Speaking for College Students course you will learn the following:  *How to speak with confidence inside and outside the classroom  *How to avoid the common speaking blunders made by most other college students  *How to rehearse important presentations on video  *How to make fellow students and adults remember your messages  This course is delivered primarily through spoken lecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Transformer</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 07:41:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-transformer/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in Transformer based Company? Don’t be stressed, take our Transformer based quiz and prepare yourself for your Interview.
With this Transformer based Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Transformer based questions. In Transformer based Multiple Choice Questions Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Basic Knowledge in Transformer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be an expert in English Grammar</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/be-an-expert-in-english-grammar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:52:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/be-an-expert-in-english-grammar/</guid>
      <description>The course has 14 sections. They display the different grammar rules in a funny way that depends on the animated cartoons. These 14 sections have 96 lectures. These 96 lectures have 2 hours of video content. This course takes you from level 1 to be a professional in the English grammar.  Ratings: 4.30/5
Enrollments: 72280
Coupon Code: SEPTEMBER16
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TESOL and TPRS Course (For Language Teachers)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tesol-and-tprs-course-for-language-teachers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:52:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/tesol-and-tprs-course-for-language-teachers/</guid>
      <description>Although uneducated parents can teach a languge to their children, how can educated teachers not teach a foreign language? In this course, you will learn how to teach a languge with a contemporary method but ancient.

In ancient times, people used to travel by horses or camels but then they invented cars and began to go everywhere with them. Today, we use planes. There is no doubt that cars are faster than horses, but planes are the fastest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2021 - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Do you remember the &#34;Jetsons show&#34;? 
The Jetsons fascinated me and everyone else around me. Thoughts of moving sidewalks, self-driving vehicles and robot housekeepers - fuelled my daydreams to the core. Let&#39;s now talk about the present time and the tech that is evolving.
Nowadays, I can command a robotic tool, device or tech to tell me the next day’s weather, read a e-book to me, play my preferred podcasts and even vacuum my flooring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2021 - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this superb course that will walk you through the future of content creation. Taking a leap from RoboAuthor Part 1, this Part 2 course taught by Digital Marketing Legend Srinidhi Ranganathan and MasterMind Saranya Srinidhi will continue your adventure in content writing to open a new door of opportunities that is incredibly futuristic. 
It is undoubtedly one of the most challenging tasks to create content for your digital marketing campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2021 - Part 3</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-3/</guid>
      <description>Ready to create ebooks in minutes?
Welcome to this superb course that will walk you through the future of content creation and eBook generation. Taking a leap from RoboAuthor Part 2, this Part 3 course taught by Digital Marketing Legend Srinidhi Ranganathan will continue your adventure in content writing to unlock opportunities for ultra-fast eBook writing and creation with the power of Artificial Intelligence. 
We must know that artificial intelligence will create amazing content today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10X Amazon Ebay Dropshipping Fba Wholesale 2021 Para Kazanma</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/10x-amazon-ebay-dropshipping-fba-wholesale-2021-para-kazanma/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/10x-amazon-ebay-dropshipping-fba-wholesale-2021-para-kazanma/</guid>
      <description>2021 yılında hala ticarete başlamadıysan bu kurs tam sana göre. Ben Akın Yılmaz, takım arkadaşlarımla beraber sizlerin ticaretinizi geliştirmenizi ve internet üzerinden gelir elde edebilmeniz için sizlere Udemy üzerinden Ücretisiz eğitimler hazırlıyoruz. Temel ticaret mantığını anlamak ve kendinizi e-ticaret alanında geliştirmek için lütfen bu kursa ve Akın Yılmaz kanalına göz atın. Buralarda sahip olmasını isteyeceğiniz çok kıymetli bilgiler var. Ve siz bu bilgileri edinmelisiniz. Artık kendi paranızı kazanma vaktiniz geldi. Tek yapmanız gereken aksiyon alıp artık başlamak ve ticaretinizi geliştirmek.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AP Physics 1 - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ap-physics-1-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ap-physics-1-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Master AP Physics 1 and get the score you want in this clear, concise, and in-depth course! This course will teach you everything, from kinematics to energy to momentum, and consists of lectures and practice problems for each unit. This is the first part of the entire AP Physics 1 course, covering the first portion of the curriculum units. Each unit has specific videos with hand-picked problems to supplement the lectures, making the overall learning process easy, efficient, and effective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Pronunciation Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/english-pronunciation-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/english-pronunciation-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Hi! My name is Professor G and I&#39;m an English teacher with more than 10 years of teaching experience. I previously studied French and Spanish at university, and I&#39;ve taught English in a number of countries around the world, including Brazil (Campinas), France (Paris) and Spain (Malaga). I understand the problems that language learners experience, especially when it comes to speaking the language. When I first moved to France, I had studied French for 5 years, but had very little speaking practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zero To Hero! Intro To Algebra: Variables, Fractions &amp; More</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/zero-to-hero-intro-to-algebra-variables-fractions-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/zero-to-hero-intro-to-algebra-variables-fractions-more/</guid>
      <description>In this course you will get professional maths tutoring to help you be successful at Algebra. We cover the basics of algebra such as variables, fractions, operations, cubes, roots and squares. You will get practical, step by step explanations, practice examples and demonstration lessons. A solid introduction to algebra is so important for the rest of your maths journey so join us in this course as we help you achieve your goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrivere un Dialogo - Scrittura Creativa Vol. 3</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/scrivere-un-dialogo-scrittura-creativa-vol.-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 18:00:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/scrivere-un-dialogo-scrittura-creativa-vol.-3/</guid>
      <description>Ciao! 
 In questo corso ti spiegherò come poter approcciare, nel migliore dei modi, alla composizione di un’ ottima sequenza dialogica e all’importanza che essa assume all’interno di un racconto, un romanzo o qualsivoglia opera di carattere narrativo. Considera che tra i motivi del “Blocco della pagina bianca&#34; di molti scrittori alle prime armi vi è proprio il senso di inadeguatezza o incapacità nell’affrontare la scrittura dei dialoghi e ti renderai conto che ovviare eliminando gli stessi dialoghi non rappresenta affatto una soluzione effettiva.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Il Personaggio - Scrittura Creativa Vol. 5</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/il-personaggio-scrittura-creativa-vol.-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 09:03:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/il-personaggio-scrittura-creativa-vol.-5/</guid>
      <description>Come nasce l&#39;idea per un personaggio narrativo?
A chi o a cosa ispirarsi?
Dall&#39;idea di un determinato personaggio come si giunge poi al suo inserimento in un preciso contesto narrativo?
Come rivestire uno o più personaggi di credibilità??
Queste sono solo alcune delle domande che affiorano nella mente di uno scrittore quando decide di cimentarsi nella scrittura di un &#39;opera narrativa, a prescindere dal genere che deciderà di seguire o adottare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AutoCAD Course l كورس الاوتوكاد</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/autocad-course-l-%D9%83%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%B3-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%88%D8%AA%D9%88%D9%83%D8%A7%D8%AF/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/autocad-course-l-%D9%83%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%B3-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%88%D8%AA%D9%88%D9%83%D8%A7%D8%AF/</guid>
      <description>كورس الاوتوكاد كورس هنتعلم فيه مع بعض اهم الاسس اللي لازم تكون عارفها عن الاوتوكاد
 هنتعلم مع بعض اوامر الرسم المختلفة وكذالك اوامر التعديل المختلفة
زي Filet , Extend , Scale , Alignment , Divide , match , hatch ,text , offset , move , rotate , mirror , Block and Explode 
سنتعرف على الاوامر الهامة داخل برنامج الاوتوكاد الذى لا غنى عنه فى اى تصميم او رسومات بانواعها والذى ايضاً فى حاجه له مع برامج اخرى لتوصيل الفكرة وتنفيذها بسهولة .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kamu Yönetimi Kapsamlı Kursu</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/kamu-y%C3%B6netimi-kapsaml%C4%B1-kursu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/kamu-y%C3%B6netimi-kapsaml%C4%B1-kursu/</guid>
      <description>Kamu Yönetimi dersleri, diğer bilim dalları ve derslerden farklı özellikler göstermektedir. Örneğin ülkelerin yapısı ve hiyerarşisine göre değişkenlik göstermesi sebebiyle uygulanış açıklama ve yorumları, evrensel bir dille genel bir yapı göstermediği için diğer dillerden bir uyarlama yapılamayıp, özgün çalışmalar gerektirir.
Bu kurs, bu sebeple daha önce yapılmış çalışmaların ışığında ve öğrencilerin sık karşılaştıkları veya karşılaşmak durumunda olacakları sorulara ve cevaplara çok fazla yer vererek, gerekli anlaşılır açıklamaların yapıldığı derslerden oluşmaktadır.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Armed Services Vocational Aptitude Battery ASVAB tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-armed-services-vocational-aptitude-battery-asvab-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 12:13:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-armed-services-vocational-aptitude-battery-asvab-tests/</guid>
      <description>Armed Services Vocational Aptitude Battery ASVAB tests
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily

Welcome to Our ASVAB Practice Test!Our tests are designed to help you with your ASVAB test prep and review.Each of our free ASVAB practice tests includes challenging practice questions along with detailed explanations. Whether you are preparing for a career in the Army, Navy, Air Force, or the Marines you will need to pass the ASVAB test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English language basics for beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/english-language-basics-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 12:13:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/english-language-basics-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>We make it easy for you to learn how to speak and write English fluently as a beginner learner. These English lessons will show you how to say and use almost anything in daily English conversation. Get started now with our speaking, vocabulary and grammar exercises that come with model answers. In this course, you will learn important topics and lessons in English, such as, Alphabet, numbers, saying hello, signs and symbols, telling the time, asking and answering questions about name, age, weather, classroom things, classroom instructions, days of the week, months of the year, seasons of the year, basic colors, simple shapes and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scrivere per Bambini e Ragazzi - Scrittura Creativa Vol. 2</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/scrivere-per-bambini-e-ragazzi-scrittura-creativa-vol.-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 12:13:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/scrivere-per-bambini-e-ragazzi-scrittura-creativa-vol.-2/</guid>
      <description>In questo corso di scrittura creativa per bambini e per ragazzi parlerò delle tecniche che vi sono dietro lo scrivere in base a due fattori: la fascia di età e il genere. 

In questo corso in particolar modo i nostri lettori vengono suddivisi in quattro fasce di età:
1. al di sotto dei 5 anni
2. dai 5 ai 7 anni
3. dagli 8 agli 11
4. dai 12 ai 14</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arabic: Learn Arabic Language| Online Arabic Language Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-learn-arabic-language-online-arabic-language-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 20:51:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-learn-arabic-language-online-arabic-language-course/</guid>
      <description>Marhaba (Hello and welcome)!
My name is Nezha, and welcome to Arabic 4 U!   ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
After taking this online Arabic language course, you will start to:
 Speak Arabic with Arabic speakers from around the world

 Understand Formal Arabic called Modern Standard Arabic MSA or Fusha
 Arabic speakers learn Modern Standard Arabic in school. It is used in Arabic books, Arabic news, Arabic documentaries, Arabic road signs, and Arabic formal speeches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IEC 61850 Communication Protocol Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/iec-61850-communication-protocol-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/iec-61850-communication-protocol-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>IEC61850 Communication Protocol Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn industry specific knowledge about the IEC61850 protocol standard such as that found in the utility industry.

I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge from cable component basic to calculating for simple cable installation designs.
I will teach you the basic concepts of IEC61850 standard as well as the overall IEC61850 Data Model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Digital Marketing</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-digital-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 13:08:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-digital-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Dear Students,
Are you Preparing for Interview in Digital Marketing? Don’t be stressed, Take our Digital Marketing quiz and prepare yourself for the Interview.
With this Digital Marketing Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and tricks to solve Digital Marketing based questions. Here you will get Digital Marketing based MCQ for your next Job or Exam.
In Digital Marketing Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Knowledge in the field of Digital Marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corso completo di Teatro per bambini 4-6 anni</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/corso-completo-di-teatro-per-bambini-4-6-anni/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:16:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/corso-completo-di-teatro-per-bambini-4-6-anni/</guid>
      <description>In questo corso spiegherò come poter gestire un gruppo di bambini dai 4 ai 6 anni facendo loro praticare, in modo ludico ma nello stesso tempo costruttivo e creativo, attività teatrali volte alla conoscenza di elementi fondamentali per la suddetta fascia d&#39;età. 
Gli scopi di un laboratorio teatrale destinato ai più piccini sono svariati tra cui: 
1. Favorire la socializzazione; 2. Superare eventuali timidezze; 3. Coordinare l&#39;attività motoria; 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Criminology : Fundamentals of Criminal Psychology and Law</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/criminology-fundamentals-of-criminal-psychology-and-law/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:16:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/criminology-fundamentals-of-criminal-psychology-and-law/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
What is criminology?
Criminology is a branch of sociology, which traditionally examines human behavior, interaction, and organization. However, it also ties in research and concepts from other areas of study, such as philosophy, anthropology, biology, and psychology. Criminologists examine a broad range of topics related to crime. They are dedicated to studying not only the causes of crime but the social roots and impact as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insight to Post Pandemic: Importance of Lean Six Sigma</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/insight-to-post-pandemic-importance-of-lean-six-sigma/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:16:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/insight-to-post-pandemic-importance-of-lean-six-sigma/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this ultimate course on &#34;Insight to Post Pandemic: Importance of Lean Six Sigma&#34; that contains vaulable lessons taught by &#34;Casey Ang&#34; and &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34;.
Since its introduction as a corporate strategy by Jack Welch at General Electric in 1995, Six Sigma has come a long way. Since then, it has been widely adopted in a variety of industries.
The Greek letter sigma is used by statisticians to represent the variation in a process and we all know that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angiosperm :  Flowering Plant</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/angiosperm-flowering-plant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/angiosperm-flowering-plant/</guid>
      <description>The flowering plants, also known as Angiospermae, meaning hidden seeds in Greek, are the most diverse group of land plants with 64 orders, 416 families, approximately 13,000 known genera and 300,000 known species. Like gymnosperms, angiosperms, which are also known by Magnoliophyta, are seed-producing plants.
The angiosperms dominate Earth’s surface and vegetation in more environments, particularly terrestrial habitats, than any other group of plants. As a result, angiosperms are the most important ultimate source of food for birds and mammals, including humans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build your own first Voice Assistant in Python</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-build-your-own-first-voice-assistant-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-build-your-own-first-voice-assistant-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to this class
In this project you will learn how to build your first virtual assistant VA in python in less then 90 minutes.
This is a great small project to get started (even if you have little or no prior knowledge in python) and learning opportunity.
Learning through your own little projects is the best and most enjoying way to improve your skills.
In the world of today we all already use Virtual Assistants like Alexa, Siri, Google and others more and more in our daily lifes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning &amp; Data Science A-Z: Hands-on Python 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/machine-learning-data-science-a-z-hands-on-python-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/machine-learning-data-science-a-z-hands-on-python-2021/</guid>
      <description>Are you interested in data science and machine learning, but you don&#39;t have any background, and you find the concepts confusing?
Are you interested in programming in Python, but you always afraid of coding?
I think this course is for you!
Even if you are familiar with machine learning, this course can help you to review all the techniques and understand the concept behind each term.
This course is completely categorized, and we don&#39;t start from the middle!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introductory Biology: Complete course of Biology</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introductory-biology-complete-course-of-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introductory-biology-complete-course-of-biology/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt; This course is designed to meet the requirement of the students to understand the Complete Introduction of Biology.

&amp;gt;This course presents many of the topics Found in O and A level biology.

&amp;gt;The topics are presented through PowerPoints presentation.Each body system is presented separately and there are quizzes at the end of each section.

&amp;gt;In this Course , Students will learn the introduction of Biology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nanotechnology Fundamentals - Most comperehensive NANOTECH</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/nanotechnology-fundamentals-most-comperehensive-nanotech/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 11:42:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/nanotechnology-fundamentals-most-comperehensive-nanotech/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
Nanotechnology is a field of research and innovation concerned with building &#39;things&#39; - generally, materials and devices - on the scale of atoms and molecules. A nanometre is one-billionth of a metre: ten times the diameter of a hydrogen atom. The diameter of a human hair is, on average, 80,000 nanometres. At such scales, the ordinary rules of physics and chemistry no longer apply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Path Loss 5</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-path-loss-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:28:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-path-loss-5/</guid>
      <description>You want to learn about network planning, especially the Access Network which is most fragile and ever changing part of the fixed and wireless network.

I have been working in the transmission field since last twenty years and I found that there is no basic training of the most commonly used access planning software and the new comers in Transmission planning learn this tool through hit and trial. That is why they are never able to fully utilize their potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corso completo di Teatro: esercizi pratici (Per Formatori)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/corso-completo-di-teatro-esercizi-pratici-per-formatori/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:15:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/corso-completo-di-teatro-esercizi-pratici-per-formatori/</guid>
      <description>Essere un Formatore Teatrale non è semplice, ci si ritrova ogni volta in contesti differenti, con persone di età diverse e che giungono con motivazioni più disparate. Per tali motivi ho cercato di non tralasciare alcun aspetto sul come impostare un Laboratorio Teatrale: dall&#39;organizzazione delle lezioni, alla tempistica, e poi tutti gli esercizi più importanti per fare un laboratorio teatrale, ognuno spiegato nei minimi particolari.
 A dispetto di tanto impegno per fare un laboratorio di teatro, alla fine si hanno grandi soddisfazioni: si assiste lezione dopo lezione alla crescita degli aspiranti attori, li si vede affrontare i vari ostacoli e superarli, ed io stessa dopo ogni laboratorio mi sento arricchita, è qualcosa che solo chi ha sentito il profumo di un palco può capire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Allama Iqbal Poetry Explanation Course in Urdu</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-ultimate-allama-iqbal-poetry-explanation-course-in-urdu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 20:19:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-ultimate-allama-iqbal-poetry-explanation-course-in-urdu/</guid>
      <description>Allama Muhammad Iqbal is one of the most outstanding poet-philosophers of the Indian sub-continent belonging to the modern period. His intellectual genius has reigned supreme in the arena of Islamic philosophy during the twentieth century and is likely to direct and influence the Islamic Intellectual tradition in the twenty first century as well. His sublime poetry and philosophy inspired millions of Muslims to wake up to the reality of the times and forge a destiny for themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Academic Writing course: Research &#43; Essay Writing!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ultimate-academic-writing-course-research-essay-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 20:19:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ultimate-academic-writing-course-research-essay-writing/</guid>
      <description>This course is specially developed for students who need the essential knowledge to prepare them for writing and defending their thesis/dissertation in an efficient and effective manner. I have created 17 lectures that cover all facets of thesis writing in one and a half hour!
SummaryI will start with the end in mind; how is your thesis evaluated? Based on this central question I explain my formula of success and take you by the hand from topic selection all the way up to successful thesis defence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High School Organic Chemistry 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/high-school-organic-chemistry-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/high-school-organic-chemistry-1/</guid>
      <description>Chemistry is fun when you learn from the best tutors. At Go2uni, we present you “High School Organic Chemistry 1”. We start from the basics and take a deep dive with clear examples and exercises to ensure every concept is understood.
Go2uni presents seasoned tutors with years of experience to offer you &#34;High School Organic Chemistry 1&#34;, the organic chemistry course you need to ace your exams.
This course will demystify Chemistry with tonnes of examples, work through exercises and take-home exercises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Miller Analogies Test (MAT) TOP Practical Questions</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-miller-analogies-test-mat-top-practical-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-miller-analogies-test-mat-top-practical-questions/</guid>
      <description>Hello !
Most Common Miller Analogies Test (MAT) professional Questions with your hand
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily
The Miller Analogies Test (MAT) is a standardized test used both for graduate school admissions in the United States and entrance to high I.Q. societies. Created and still published by Harcourt Assessment (now a division of Pearson Education), the MAT consists of 120 questions in 60 minutes (formerly 100 questions in 50 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware Certified Professional - VCP-DTM Practice Exams 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/vmware-certified-professional-vcp-dtm-practice-exams-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/vmware-certified-professional-vcp-dtm-practice-exams-2021/</guid>
      <description>We have created these practice exams with over 130 questions to help you prepare for the VCP-DTM exam and help you pass on your first attempt.
More information about the certifications :
VMware Desktop and Mobility certifications are designed to gauge your level of skill designing, installing, and managing a VMware Horizon with View environment deployed on a VMware vSphere implementation. The VCP-DTM 2021 certification validates a candidate’s skills in performing in-depth configuration and management of VMware Horizon environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Computer Basics Guide for Beginners: 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-computer-basics-guide-for-beginners-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-computer-basics-guide-for-beginners-2021/</guid>
      <description>The Computer Defined, Data versus Information, Classification of Computers based on how data is handled (Analog Computers, Digital Computers Hybrid Computers)
Computers for Individual Users or Personal Computers (Desktop Computers,Workstations, Laptops, Notebooks, Tablets, Handheld PCs, Smartphones)
Computers for Organizations (Network Server, Mainframes, Minicomputers, Supercomputers)
Parts of Computer System (Hardware , Software, User and Data)
Information Processing Cycle (Input, Processing, Output, Storage)
Computer Hardware Categorized ( Processing Devices, Memory Devices, Input and Output Devices, Storage Devices, Bus Interconnection)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improvvisazione Teatrale e Comica: dalla teoria alla pratica</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/improvvisazione-teatrale-e-comica-dalla-teoria-alla-pratica/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/improvvisazione-teatrale-e-comica-dalla-teoria-alla-pratica/</guid>
      <description>Cos&#39;è un&#39; improvvisazione? E se si chiama IMPROVVISAZIONE perché studiarla in un corso?
Perché sono state scritte tonnellate di libri a tal riguardo?
L&#39;improvvisazione è una vera e propria Arte e come tale necessita di studio, tecnica ed esperienza. 
Non si può improvvisare senza possedere le conoscenze adatte.
Esistono due differenti forme di improvvisazione, quella &#34;muta&#34; nella quale l&#39;unico strumento comunicativo è rappresentato dal corpo e quella &#34;parlata&#34; durante la quale voce(storytelling) e corpo agiscono all&#39;unisono, quest&#39;ultima è l&#39;improvvisazione di cui ti parlerò in questo corso.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redação: Enem, vestibular, concurso.Teoria &#43; tira-dúvidas</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/reda%C3%A7%C3%A3o-enem-vestibular-concurso.teoria-tira-d%C3%BAvidas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/reda%C3%A7%C3%A3o-enem-vestibular-concurso.teoria-tira-d%C3%BAvidas/</guid>
      <description>Se você já tem professor para avaliar suas redações, e não&amp;nbsp; precisa de exercícios de reforço, aqui você tem as quase 8&amp;nbsp;horas de aulas em vídeo do curso completo (disponível na plataforma Udemy) + tira-dúvidas ilimitado comigo!

Você vai descobrir como escrever dissertações de provas mais rápido, sem decorar regras ou fórmulas.
Se você trava ou fica em &#34;branco&#34;, veja o que te espera:
tipos de dissertação
como começar a redação sem travar</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American English Pronunciation for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/american-english-pronunciation-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/american-english-pronunciation-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling with your English pronunciation? 
Do you have a strong accent when speaking English?

Do native speakers always ask you to repeat yourself?

Do you want to begin speaking with an American accent confidently?

Do you what tips and help with speaking with an American accent? 
I welcome you to this - “American English Pronunciation Training - course where I will patiently guide you through the basic techniques you need to pronounce English sounds correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arabic complete beginner course through (Byna Yadek)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-complete-beginner-course-through-byna-yadek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-complete-beginner-course-through-byna-yadek/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I&#39;m Mr.Bakoor. I have been teaching Arabic for a while. I got students form All over the world. My respect for all of them. My students liked the way I teach because It&#39;s easy, it goes step by step, they easily understand and also show improvement,&amp;nbsp; I feel so happy when I my student telling me that they are really improving in Arabic, I hope to make Arabic teaching easier for everyone who think Learning Arabic is hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combined Heat and Power (CHP) Cogeneration Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/combined-heat-and-power-chp-cogeneration-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/combined-heat-and-power-chp-cogeneration-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Combined Heat and Power (CHP) Cogeneration Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn all about the concept of CHP and cogeneration that are essential in working in the industry.

I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on cogeneration as well as how to apply it in the utility industry.

If you are currently a professional who are interested working with Cogeneration plants, you will find this course of great help to get the fundamental knowledge you need to kick start your professional career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete French Course: Learn French for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-french-course-learn-french-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-french-course-learn-french-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to learn French? Dubbed the “language of love”, French is used by over 235 million speakers daily in over 54 countries. But why should you pick French out of all the languages you could be learning?
To start, France isn’t just one of the most beautiful countries in central Europe, but a global powerhouse with significant presence in the automobile, aircraft and chemical manufacturing, the electronic, machinery, metallurgy industries, as well as tourism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete General Chemistry 20&#43; hours of lectures &amp; examples</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-general-chemistry-20-hours-of-lectures-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-general-chemistry-20-hours-of-lectures-examples/</guid>
      <description>Description:
General Chemistry is a basic course for a broad range of students from different fields of science and engineering. This course is designed to help you get a firm grasp over the most important topics in chemistry that you need to know in order to do great in your exams and classes. By the end of the course you’ll learn the principals and important concepts regarding matter, atoms, solutions, phases, chemical reactions, equilibrium, kinetics, acids and bases and so much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Tamil Course: Learn Tamil for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-tamil-course-learn-tamil-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-tamil-course-learn-tamil-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to learn Tamil? As one of the oldest classical languages in the world, Tamil is spoken by over 70 million people. But why should you pick Tamil out of all the languages you could be learning?
To start, Tamil is the official language of Tamil Nadu, India’s fourth largest state, which has seen significant economic growth and foreign investment over the last decade. The state is a leading figure in several industries, such as automobile and auto-components, engineering, pharmaceuticals and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash Course on Civil Engineering and AutoCAD: Part 3</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-3/</guid>
      <description>This incredible series-based crash course takes an amazing turn here in Part 3 as&amp;nbsp;&#34;New-age Environmental Engineering &amp;amp; Artificial Intelligence&#34; concepts are taught by Digital Marketing Legend &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34;&amp;nbsp;and Narmadha.M.
Environmental Engineering is a professional engineering discipline that takes advantage of specific scientific topics such as chemistry, biology, geography, geology, hydraulics, hydrology, microbiology, and mathematics to create solutions that will preserve and also improve the health of living organisms and increase environmental quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Differential Equations | Complete Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/differential-equations-complete-differential-equations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/differential-equations-complete-differential-equations/</guid>
      <description>Learn Differential Equation:
This course includes video lectures and text explanations of everything from differential equations and its applications, and it includes 7 quizzes (with video solutions!) and&amp;nbsp; for practice worksheet with extra practice problems, to help you test your understanding along the way. &#34;Differential Equations&#34; is arranged into the following sections:
Understanding of differential equations.
Order and degree of differential equations.
Formation of differential equation.
Variable separation method.
Substitution method of solution of differential equation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Biomedical Engineering - Nanodevices RAHBME282</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/intro-to-biomedical-engineering-nanodevices-rahbme282/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/intro-to-biomedical-engineering-nanodevices-rahbme282/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Nanodevices course, brought to you by Rahsoft. In this course we will be going over the basics and fundamentals of nanodevices and nanosensors, as well as in-depth examples and practice problems to give you a better understanding of the field. The course is taught by Dennis Fer, a Biomedical Engineering Instructor at Rahsoft, and the course advisor is Ahsan Ghoncheh, the Co-Founder and Technical Advisor at Rahsoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Heat Transfer Engineering - RAHHT1 Rahsoft</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-heat-transfer-engineering-rahht1-rahsoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-heat-transfer-engineering-rahht1-rahsoft/</guid>
      <description>Heat Transfer is one of the principle courses for all the university students who study in one of the branches of chemical engineering, mechanical engineering or materials engineering. This course which is placed at the beginning semesters of bachelor programs, is offered in two separate courses as heat transfer 1 &amp;amp; 2 each credited as 3 units. Having a full grasp over the concepts of heat transfer and fully understand the mechanisms of heat transfer in different situations is a must for any students studying the fields mentioned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japanese for French speakers : katakana</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/japanese-for-french-speakers-katakana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/japanese-for-french-speakers-katakana/</guid>
      <description>C&#39;est un cours complet pour apprendre tous les katakana, l&#39;alphabet de base japonais qui est utilisé pour écrire certaines catégories de mots tels que les mots étrangers ou les onomatopées. Grâce à des photos, des illustrations animées, une bande-son et des sous-titres en français, vous apprendrez facilement à lire le tableau entier des 46 katakana, à les prononcer parfaitement et à les écrire dans le bon ordre. Vous ne serez pas ennuyés, car à la fin de chaque section vous pourrez vérifier vos progrès avec des quiz amusants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Matemáticas desde aritmética a cálculo con Python</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/matem%C3%A1ticas-desde-aritm%C3%A9tica-a-c%C3%A1lculo-con-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/matem%C3%A1ticas-desde-aritm%C3%A9tica-a-c%C3%A1lculo-con-python/</guid>
      <description>En este curso te enseñaré a usar Python como una herramienta para resolver problemas de matemáticas desde la aritmética hasta el cálculo diferencial e integral. Además de que te enseñaré a usar este lenguaje de manera muy básica. Siempre he dicho que lo mejor de un curso es ir al grano, por lo que te ayudaré a hacer ejercicios matemáticos directamente con las herramientas de Google Colaborative que nos permitirán programar en Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul: A Biography: Small Group Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/paul-a-biography-small-group-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/paul-a-biography-small-group-edition/</guid>
      <description>N. T. Wright&#39;s definitive biography of Paul reveals the apostle&#39;s lasting role in Christian history as an inventor of new paradigms for how we understand Jesus and what he accomplished. Wright celebrates Paul’s stature as one of the most effective and influential intellectuals in human history, while shedding fresh light on his writings, thoughts, and ideas. Consider these remarkable facts: Paul&#39;s writing occupy less than 90 pages in a modern translation yet they have, page per page, generated more sermons, books, monographs, and journal articles than any other writings from the ancient world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quadratic Equations &amp; Quadratic Expression</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quadratic-equations-quadratic-expression/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quadratic-equations-quadratic-expression/</guid>
      <description>Learn Quadratic Equations and Functions:
This 7 lessons course includes video lectures and text explanations of everything from quadratic equations and functions, and it includes 7 quizzes (with video solutions!) and&amp;nbsp; for practice worksheet with extra practice problems, to help you test your understanding along the way. &#34;Quadratic equations and expression&#34; is arranged into the following sections:
Basic concept of quadratic Equation
Solving a quadratic equation by different method
How many ways are there to solve a quadratic equation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 150 Most Important Irregular Verbs in English. Volume 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-150-most-important-irregular-verbs-in-english.-volume-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-150-most-important-irregular-verbs-in-english.-volume-1/</guid>
      <description>Support available in: English 
Spanish 
French

I can&#39;t wait to share with you this exciting English course based on Irregular Verbs. 
Do you feel unsure about the right conjugation when you try use irregular verbs in every day conversation?
Are you frustrated of having to memorize unending word lists? 
Then this course is for you. 
It is not a secret that Irregular Verbs are hard to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
