<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Esoteric Practices on </title>
    <link>/tags/esoteric-practices/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Esoteric Practices on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 20:22:08 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/esoteric-practices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hypnosis to overcome Dentist fear guided hypnosis program</title>
      <link>/hypnosis-to-overcome-dentist-fear-guided-hypnosis-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 20:22:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hypnosis-to-overcome-dentist-fear-guided-hypnosis-program/</guid>
      <description>Hypnosis to overcome Dentist fear guided hypnosis program has beed created to simulate a therapy visit with me 
Learn to change how you feel about the dentist If the thoughts of going for a dental appointment to your dentist have had you feeling anxious this course is just right for you. Because you will be using natures gift of hypnosis and being able to be hypnotized to change your thoughts and reactions to going to the dentist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oracle or Tarot Cards? Quick Start Guide: Choosing Your Deck</title>
      <link>/oracle-or-tarot-cards-quick-start-guide-choosing-your-deck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/oracle-or-tarot-cards-quick-start-guide-choosing-your-deck/</guid>
      <description>Upon completion of this course, you will be able to select the Oracle or Tarot card deck that will be your partner in giving accurate readings that flow with ease. You will know the difference between Oracle and Tarot cards and figure out which one fits your style and finally you’ll learn where to buy your new deck.
Choosing your card deck is the first step on a fun, magical and often amazing journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Antike Astrologie 2</title>
      <link>/antike-astrologie-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/antike-astrologie-2/</guid>
      <description>Dieser Kurs baut auf seiem Vorgänger Antike Astrologie 1 auf und erweitert die erste gelernte Technik mit der Methode der Elementarherrscher. Kannst du mit der Technik des Herrschers des Aszendenten (Kurs 1 ) das Generelle Lebenesthema bestimmen, so geht es hier um eine erste Timing - Technik.
Du erfährst wie du 3 grundlegende Planeten ermittelst und diese anschließend evaluierst. Dadurch wird das Leben des Horoskopstellers in 2 Hälften geteilt, die jeweils von den 3 Elementarherrscheerplaneten unterstützt werden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreaming Understand Dream Messages Remember Your Dreams 2020</title>
      <link>/dreaming-understand-dream-messages-remember-your-dreams-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dreaming-understand-dream-messages-remember-your-dreams-2020/</guid>
      <description>Dreaming Understand Dream Messages and Remember Your Dreams
5 Star Review 
I was able to use this information to sort through dreams....and understand what the dream was telling me after the hypnosis. I will keep coming back to the hypnosis sessions as I find them very helpful. I do admit I am not writing things down...but I am holding what I need to know in memory and mulling over what I am finding out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Law Of Attraction Course Updated for the 2020s</title>
      <link>/the-complete-law-of-attraction-course-updated-for-the-2020s/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-law-of-attraction-course-updated-for-the-2020s/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Law Of Attraction Course Updated for the 2020s
Master the Law of Attraction - Become Your Own Best Law of Attraction Coach - Great Life Manifestation Attract Success
You can obtain mastery of the Law of Attraction. You may have seen the movie or read the book, but this course will teach you in a systematic way how to re-condition your brain, completely, into an abundance-creating being.
TJ Walker dives deep into the secrets of the Law of Attraction.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
