<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Esoteric Practices on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/esoteric-practices/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Esoteric Practices on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/esoteric-practices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Positive Transformation Hypnotherapy | Certificate Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/positive-transformation-hypnotherapy-certificate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/positive-transformation-hypnotherapy-certificate-course/</guid>
      <description>Positive Transformation Hypnotherapy | Certificate Course
Hello everyone! I&#39;d like to welcome you to this course I created that is a complete guide for anyone who wants to learn the art of hypnotherapy, &amp;amp; use it to help induce positive mind shifts that last! I always wanted to be able to help the people around me but to do so I had to be able to help myself. This is what positive mind hypnotherapy did for me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reiki Secrets Revealed: Complete 30-Hour Certification Class</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/reiki-secrets-revealed-complete-30-hour-certification-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/reiki-secrets-revealed-complete-30-hour-certification-class/</guid>
      <description>✨✨The Complete 30+ Hour Reiki Certification: Secrets from A-Z includes over 30 hours of video lectures, including hand-drawn images of each of the Reiki symbols. Most of this course content is entirely original, with a brand-new approach to never-before-seen uses of Reiki. this is one of the most in-depth, longest, and comprehensive Reiki course you will find on the platform✨✨
Update April 2022: Thanks to student contributions, we now have an additional Reiki Handbook that is over 20,000 words long!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soundwave Healing | Solfeggio Frequency Certificate Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/soundwave-healing-solfeggio-frequency-certificate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/soundwave-healing-solfeggio-frequency-certificate-course/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Soundwave Healing!
This is an incredible short &amp;amp; sweet course on understanding all 10 of the healing frequencies that can be used in conjunction with sound therapy! This includes &amp;amp; covers the original 6 solfeggio frequencies and was made for all people who want to learn how to heal with sound waves &amp;amp; solfeggio frequencies. In this Soundwave Healing course, you will receive 10 x 10 min pure sound meditations on all of the healing frequencies (174hz - 963hz) that will be downloadable and available for commercial use in the course!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Law Of Attraction Course Updated for the 2020s</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-law-of-attraction-course-updated-for-the-2020s/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:30:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-law-of-attraction-course-updated-for-the-2020s/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Law Of Attraction Course Updated for the 2020sMaster the Law of Attraction - Become Your Own Best Law of Attraction Coach - Great Life Manifestation Attract Success
You can obtain mastery of the Law of Attraction. You may have seen the movie or read the book, but this course will systematically teach you how to re-condition your brain, completely, into an abundance-creating being.
TJ Walker dives deep into the secrets of the Law of Attraction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angel Card Reading 2022 - Transformational Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/angel-card-reading-2022-transformational-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 18:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/angel-card-reading-2022-transformational-course/</guid>
      <description>The Angels of Heaven invite you to join this transformational course, where you will learn how to tap into their higher vibrational wisdom through the power of one simple tool: Angel Cards!
Whether you want to learn how to channel guidance from the heavenly realm for yourself or for others, this course is for you.
You will enjoy a complete guide on Angel Card Readings: Including: learning spreads from beginner to advanced, getting to know 19 Archangels, tapping into your intuition for your highest good, and much more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreaming Understand Dream Messages Remember Your Dreams 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/dreaming-understand-dream-messages-remember-your-dreams-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 12:48:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/dreaming-understand-dream-messages-remember-your-dreams-2022/</guid>
      <description>Dreaming Understand Dream Messages and Remember Your Dreams in 2022
5 Star Review I was able to use this information to sort through dreams....and understand what the dream was telling me after the hypnosis. I will keep coming back to the hypnosis sessions as I find them very helpful. I do admit I am not writing things down...but I am holding what I need to know in memory and mulling over what I am finding out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kundalini Reiki 1-2-3-master teacher (all in one course)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kundalini-reiki-1-2-3-master-teacher-all-in-one-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 14:59:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kundalini-reiki-1-2-3-master-teacher-all-in-one-course/</guid>
      <description>KUNDALINI REIKI (1-2-3 MASTER TRAINING)
You will learn how to use Universal Life Force Energy Kundalini Reiki to heal yourself, your friends, family, pets, other people, animals, objects and even situations! You will learn how to take care of your mind, body, and spirit, as well as attracting loving energy and abundance into your life.
====== INCLUDED ======
This course includes all levels of Kundalini Reiki including Master. This course is all digital, which means you can go as slow or as fast as you want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Antike Astrologie 1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/antike-astrologie-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/antike-astrologie-1/</guid>
      <description>In diesem Kurs lernst du die Grundlagen der hellenistischen- römischen Astrologie. 2000 Jahre alte Prognostische Techniken werden seit ca. 20 Jahren wiederbelebt. Hier geb ich dir das Werkzeug in die Hand, damit du selbst bei dir die erste Technik anwenden kannst um in deinem Horoskop deine Lebensaufgabe zu erkennen: Die verrät dir der Herrscher deines Aszendenten - der Kurios
Ratings: 4.44/5
Enrollments: 5227
Coupon Code: 4F1A00CB61BB30F66882
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypnosis for to visit Past life or lives Guided Hypnosis</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hypnosis-for-to-visit-past-life-or-lives-guided-hypnosis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:52:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hypnosis-for-to-visit-past-life-or-lives-guided-hypnosis/</guid>
      <description>5 Star Review Great course and appreciated the bonus, feel good lecture. Instructor is easy to listen to and very good at what he does. Thank you for offering your course which has saved me many hundreds of dollars as well as my precious time from having to schedule the allotted time with a therapist. Very comfortable watching as my time allowed and going through these sessions in the privacy of my home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypnosis to overcome Dentist fear guided hypnosis program</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hypnosis-to-overcome-dentist-fear-guided-hypnosis-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 20:22:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hypnosis-to-overcome-dentist-fear-guided-hypnosis-program/</guid>
      <description>Hypnosis to overcome Dentist fear guided hypnosis program has beed created to simulate a therapy visit with me Learn to change how you feel about the dentist If the thoughts of going for a dental appointment to your dentist have had you feeling anxious this course is just right for you. Because you will be using natures gift of hypnosis and being able to be hypnotized to change your thoughts and reactions to going to the dentist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oracle or Tarot Cards? Quick Start Guide: Choosing Your Deck</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/oracle-or-tarot-cards-quick-start-guide-choosing-your-deck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/oracle-or-tarot-cards-quick-start-guide-choosing-your-deck/</guid>
      <description>Upon completion of this course, you will be able to select the Oracle or Tarot card deck that will be your partner in giving accurate readings that flow with ease. You will know the difference between Oracle and Tarot cards and figure out which one fits your style and finally you’ll learn where to buy your new deck.
Choosing your card deck is the first step on a fun, magical and often amazing journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Antike Astrologie 2</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/antike-astrologie-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/antike-astrologie-2/</guid>
      <description>Dieser Kurs baut auf seiem Vorgänger Antike Astrologie 1 auf und erweitert die erste gelernte Technik mit der Methode der Elementarherrscher. Kannst du mit der Technik des Herrschers des Aszendenten (Kurs 1 ) das Generelle Lebenesthema bestimmen, so geht es hier um eine erste Timing - Technik.
Du erfährst wie du 3 grundlegende Planeten ermittelst und diese anschließend evaluierst. Dadurch wird das Leben des Horoskopstellers in 2 Hälften geteilt, die jeweils von den 3 Elementarherrscheerplaneten unterstützt werden.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
