<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Public Relations: Become a Media Star by Pitching with Video</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/public-relations-become-a-media-star-by-pitching-with-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/public-relations-become-a-media-star-by-pitching-with-video/</guid>
      <description>Public Relations. Imagine yourself appearing on major TV news network programs, regularly. You can become the media&#39;s go-to person for your industry. Getting on major local, national and international TV news programs no longer has to be a dream for you and your organization. It can happen now.
You will learn half a dozen very specific techniques on how to get more mainstream media Public Relations coverage through the strategic use of simple, talking-head YouTube videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growth Hacking &amp; Viral Marketing: #1 Strategy Growth Hacking</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/growth-hacking-viral-marketing-#1-strategy-growth-hacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/growth-hacking-viral-marketing-#1-strategy-growth-hacking/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to grow extremely quickly without a lot of money? Do you wish your marketing investments produced exponential growth instead of petty marginal gains? Do you feel there are better ways to grow than just copying competitors? Are you looking for HUGE wins and EXPLOSIVE growth hacking? This the course for you: the definitive guide to growth hacking!
This course is for truly ambitious entrepreneurs, marketers, and product managers who want to drive real IMPACT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copywriting &amp; Content Marketing Course: Be a PRO Copywriter</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/copywriting-content-marketing-course-be-a-pro-copywriter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/copywriting-content-marketing-course-be-a-pro-copywriter/</guid>
      <description>UPSKILL YOURSELF AND ENSURE YOU&#39;RE NEVER OUT OF WORK OR OUT OF CLIENTS, WITH THE CONTENT MARKETING &amp;amp; COPYWRITING COURSE 2021. LEARN EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO KNOW TO BECOME A PROFESSIONAL CONTENT CREATOR, AND START A NEW CAREER ONLINE, OR BOOST YOUR LOCAL OR E-COMMERCE BUSINESS.
&#34;I wanted to tell you that I have a job in a digital marketing company! I&#39;m working as a copywriter and account manager for a team of developers and graphic designers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn 6 SIMPLE Steps to Make Money on TikTok App!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-6-simple-steps-to-make-money-on-tiktok-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-6-simple-steps-to-make-money-on-tiktok-app/</guid>
      <description>How would you feel like when making $10,000&#39;s just by using your smartphone?
Benefits of Making Money on TikTok App:
You can do this worldwide!
You can make money for 100% FREE!
TikTok is the most downloaded app in the world right now!
Steps are really SIMPLE!
The earning potential is HUGE!
--
While I can&#39;t guarantee you any money (by law) but let me tell you a short story from my own life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Guide to Pinterest &amp; Pinterest Growth 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-guide-to-pinterest-pinterest-growth-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 13:13:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-guide-to-pinterest-pinterest-growth-2021/</guid>
      <description>Hey there, Nick Nyxson here.
Welcome to PinHeroes.
Only Pinterest course EVER to teach you how to grow your profile on Pinterest from 0 to 1 Million monthly viewers in just short few months.
Pinterest is one of the fastest-growing social media platforms and its main appeal is its unconventional way treat the content. It is an ONLY social media platform that Not just NOT RESTRICT external content but actively encourages it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copywriting: B2B Copywriting, Content Writing, Copy Writing</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/copywriting-b2b-copywriting-content-writing-copy-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 13:13:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/copywriting-b2b-copywriting-content-writing-copy-writing/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to get more customers in this groundbreaking, definitive course on B2B copywriting and content marketing. Master the art &amp;amp; science of copywriting to push people down your funnel to become active, paying customers, instead of just &#34;leads.&#34; Generate pipeline revenue and serious financial results instead of inflating vanity metrics, such as captured &#34;emails&#34; that never convert into paying customers. This is the ultimate course on B2B copywriting and content marketing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Group Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/facebook-group-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 13:13:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/facebook-group-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>One of the easiest ways to boost engagement, build a following and become a thought leader or influencer in your market is by creating a Facebook group.
A Facebook group serves as a communication channel between you and an ever-growing community of potential customers and joint venture partners.
With a Facebook group, you’re able to take advantage of the heavy traffic that Facebook provides, and you’ll be able to connect with your audience who finds you just by entering in keywords relating to your niche.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tiktok-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 13:13:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/tiktok-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve not tried using TikTok Marketing to promote your business online, then today is the time to start!

Never before has there been an advertising platform of this magnitude that will allow you to reach an audience of billions and rapidly grow your business online at next to zero cost!

Become The Ultimate TikTok Marketing Master and join this course today to learn the same PROVEN success strategy Henry Zhang, Digital Marketing expert and world-leading trader used to build this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Guide to Tailwind - Master Pinterest with Tailwind</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-guide-to-tailwind-master-pinterest-with-tailwind/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-guide-to-tailwind-master-pinterest-with-tailwind/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Complete Guide to Tailwind - Master Pinterest with Tailwind!
The only course you will need to start with Tailwind, one of the best Pinterest Management Tools on the market (if not the best).
Tailwind is the service that will help you to manage practically all aspects of Pinterest and most importantly it allows you to create Pinterest Pins (Right from the browser), Schedule your pins and manage them, all from one convenient spot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics, GA4, GTM. How to improve your marketing?</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/google-analytics-ga4-gtm.-how-to-improve-your-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/google-analytics-ga4-gtm.-how-to-improve-your-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Description
Web analytics is the pulse of digital marketing. Everything is measured, and everything is measurable. With Google Analytics and a call tracking system, you can clearly understand who your client is, how to improve your site, and which traffic sources are the most beneficial for your business.
What will you learn in this course?
After completing this course, you will learn how to work with and get the most out of your web analytics data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Business: The Complete CPA Marketing Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/home-business-the-complete-cpa-marketing-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/home-business-the-complete-cpa-marketing-course/</guid>
      <description>Subtitles / Closed-Captions are available for ALL lectures!Even if you&#39;re a complete beginner, this course will teach you how to use CPA (Cost Per Action) to create a business that makes money while you sleep.
You&#39;ll be able to generate profits without having to sell any products, and you&#39;ll set up a legitimate online business quickly and easily.
Use CPA to Establish a Successful Online Business and Generate Consistent Income</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagram Marketing 2021: Growth and Promotion on Instagram</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/instagram-marketing-2021-growth-and-promotion-on-instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/instagram-marketing-2021-growth-and-promotion-on-instagram/</guid>
      <description>Growing on social media can sometimes be very complicated, especially if you have no prior experience and this field. But, this course has everything that you need to be able to start growing your instagram account for personnal or professional purposes. Indeed, you will learn many different things about this amazing application from scratch. If you: - Are someone interested in growing your personnal Instagram
- Want to create an Instagram account for your business - Launch an agency to promote different Instagram accounts</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile App Marketing for Absolute Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/mobile-app-marketing-for-absolute-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/mobile-app-marketing-for-absolute-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Mobile app marketing is quite important to get a huge user base and to get the ultimate revenue from a mobile app.
This course organized as
In-App Marketing (Low cost but very effective) 
Build virality into your app
How virality in the mobile app works?
Best practices of virality
More Apps
Update = $$
In-App graphical banner Ad (cross-promotional)
Push Notification (Army for better app marketing)
Why you should care about push notification?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete List Building Course: All Levels</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-list-building-course-all-levels/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-list-building-course-all-levels/</guid>
      <description>&#34;SUPER-FAST &amp;amp; TOP-SECRET, EFFECTIVE LIST BUILDING TECHNIQUES THAT I USE TO GET 10,000+ SUBSCRIBERS EACH AND EVERY MONTH! - THIS WORKS NO MATTER WHERE YOU LIVE IN THE WORLD!&#34; You can get thousands of HUNGRY BUYERS waiting for YOUR OFFERS within a FEW DAYS! I am going to reveal to you the exact strategies I have been using to build my lists and collect thousands of subscribers in no time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Digital Marketing Course for Local Businesses 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-digital-marketing-course-for-local-businesses-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-digital-marketing-course-for-local-businesses-2021/</guid>
      <description>&#34;This Digital Marketing Course is amazing. I have learned a lot of from this course. I like the explanation style of the teacher. So, please everyone join this course to change your life....&#34; Kamran
&#34;The complete content was brilliantly explained. Thank you.&#34; Riya
&#34;The course content is amazing. I have learned many new things, especially new tips and tricks in digital marketing. One thing I have to tell that the trainer is awesome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Marketing 2021. Content that Sells!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/content-marketing-2021.-content-that-sells/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/content-marketing-2021.-content-that-sells/</guid>
      <description>What is content marketing?
Content marketing is a marketing method for creating and distributing valuable, relevant, and consistent content for a specific audience.
The goal of content marketing is to help your audience cope with challenges, improve their quality of life, and to establish yourself as a trusted thought leader.

The Role of Content Marketing in 2021
The impact of the coronavirus is being felt around the world.
Shopper needs and habits are rapidly changing, which poses new challenges for marketers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/facebook-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/facebook-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Facebook is a massive traffic monster. Over 1.3 billion people are using Facebook day after day. On top of this, it continues to grow.
You really cannot afford to miss out on Facebook and its marketing potential.
This course teaches you the best ways to promote on Facebook. It also gives you step by step instructions, so you can engage in Facebook marketing with a higher than average chance of success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Messenger Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/facebook-messenger-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/facebook-messenger-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>In order to have your business succeed in the current market, it’s important that you build and maintain a strong online presence.
With customers demanding answers at all hours of the day, regardless of what they’re doing or where they are, you should consider using a Facebook Messenger Chatbot.
It&#39;s an Artificial Intelligence (AI), interactive messaging system that engages with your customers on behalf of your company, all within Facebook’s popular messenger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Ultimate Guide to YouTube Channel &amp; YouTube Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-ultimate-guide-to-youtube-channel-youtube-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-ultimate-guide-to-youtube-channel-youtube-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to TubeHeroes 1.5!
An Only Course you need to start making and growing your YouTube channel!
The YouTube industry is as big as ever was and it will only continue to grow in the coming years. And it does not matter whether you want to grow your personal following or to grow your business, YouTube is a practically essential social media platform to be active on.
But you have no idea where to start?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace your career with the Power of Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ace-your-career-with-the-power-of-artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ace-your-career-with-the-power-of-artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the eleventh course in Term 1 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Artificial intelligence (AI) is real science that deals with building intelligent machines or automated robots that can think and respond like a human being. Nevertheless, AI tech holds exceptional future opportunities in digital marketing and the trend is changing day by day. The impact of AI in digital marketing actually goes far beyond what one can ever imagine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing Course for Fitness Professionals</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-marketing-course-for-fitness-professionals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-marketing-course-for-fitness-professionals/</guid>
      <description>To succeed in the fitness industry or field, your company must stand out from the crowd and competition. That means developing and implementing a solid and proven digital marketing strategy that is powered by Artificial Intelligence (AI). Social media marketing allows you to showcase your skills and expertise while also allowing people to learn about your company. It&#39;s a great, low-cost way to get more customers. But manual implementation of the same takes a lot of time, effort and resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Futuristic Digital Marketing Course: 2021 Student Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/futuristic-digital-marketing-course-2021-student-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/futuristic-digital-marketing-course-2021-student-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the tenth course in Term 1 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
The digital marketing world is evolving day by day with the rise of new technologies. Currently, in the city of Bangalore, there has been an advent of new companies or startups which have emerged this year. As Bill Gates said–&#34;If your company isn&#39;t on the internet, your business will be out of business,&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lead Generation MASTERY with Facebook Lead &amp; Messenger Ads</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/lead-generation-mastery-with-facebook-lead-messenger-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/lead-generation-mastery-with-facebook-lead-messenger-ads/</guid>
      <description>Discover how to QUICKLY attract a CONSTANT stream of new customers with targeted FACEBOOK MESSENGER ADS, FACEBOOK LEAD GENERATION ADS, and FACEBOOK CONVERSION ADS!
Dear Students,
Hi, I’m Tomas Moravek, Internet Efficiency Awarded Digital Strategist and Professional Marketer, here to present my Facebook Lead, Messenger, and Conversion Ads Mastery Guide, so you can benefit from these POWERFULLY EFFECTIVE automated marketing tools.
Facebook Lead Ads, Messenger Ads, and Conversion Ads are vital tools for any brand, as they&#39;ll help you quickly build a subscriber base of interested potential customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New-Age Technologies For Fitness Trainers</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/new-age-technologies-for-fitness-trainers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/new-age-technologies-for-fitness-trainers/</guid>
      <description>Technology is a flourishing sector today, with a plethora of intriguing and innovative products as well as new learning opportunities. Apps and wearable technology, as well as digital fitness platforms and equipment, are among the most popular fitness technologies today. Putting aside the excitement of new developments, the convenience that technology may provide is unrivalled. Long before the pandemic, the mix of fitness technology and digital fitness was altering our market; both areas were rising at a rapid pace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Render 2.0: Transform your podcast into videos in 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/space-render-2.0-transform-your-podcast-into-videos-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/space-render-2.0-transform-your-podcast-into-videos-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the third course in Level 3 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Creative Arts, Design and Animation&#34;.
Marketers always desire to transform their podcast into videos. We also know that humans are naturally visual beings, after all.
Video adds visual ambiguity and the absence of audio&#39;s emotional depth. That&#39;s one of the reasons why the digital web is increasingly becoming the backbone of video.
In hopes of expanding their following, creators convert their work into a video for YouTube, like young actors flocking to Hollywood for more exposure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing Ultimate Course Bundle - 13 Courses in 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-marketing-ultimate-course-bundle-13-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 13:24:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-marketing-ultimate-course-bundle-13-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Digital Marketing Ultimate Course Bundle - 13 Courses in 1 (Over 27 hours of content)
In this practical hands-on training, you’re going to learn to become a digital marketing expert with this ultimate course bundle that includes 13 digital marketing courses in 1!
Blending practical work with solid theoretical training, this course takes you from the basics of Digital Marketing to mastery, giving you the training you need not just to build Sales funnels, generate leads using Email, Facebook ads, Google ads, LinkedIn and SEO but also how to build websites and create amazing videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn 10 Ways to Make MORE Money on YouTube!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-10-ways-to-make-more-money-on-youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 13:24:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-10-ways-to-make-more-money-on-youtube/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to make money on YouTube even while you are sleeping?
The work that you do today can make you money for months and years to come!
In this YouTube Audience Growth course, you&#39;ll learn at least 5 Ways to Make Money on YouTube.
You&#39;ll learn how to attract 1,000,000&#39;s of Views and Grow Your YouTube Channel Into a MONEY-MAKING MACHINE
I published some videos back in 2017 and they are still generating me money EVERY.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Traffic Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/online-traffic-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 13:24:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/online-traffic-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Whether you have a personal blog, business website, or are making money through online advertising, today&#39;s currency of success relies, almost exclusively, on the science of cultivating more significant traffic to your website.
The traffic that you bring to your website is crucial because it helps you increase your rankings on the various search engines, which is how potential customers can find your company.
Unfortunately bringing more traffic to your site these days can be a challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Referral Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/referral-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 13:24:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/referral-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’re looking to maximize exposure and profits while consistently working towards acquiring new customers, there is no better way than with referral marketing. Referral marketing is all about encouraging people in your niche to share your products and services. This can include customers, influencers and thought leaders in your market.
Ultimately, there is no easier way to better position your brand and leverage your existing customer base than to design a referral system that actively encourages sharing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction into Facebook Marketing &amp; Facebook Advertising</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-into-facebook-marketing-facebook-advertising/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-into-facebook-marketing-facebook-advertising/</guid>
      <description>&#34;The BEST, authentic, great and very precise course on Facebook Marketing and Facebook Advertising. Though the course is just 10 hours, it covers the topics beyond anyone&#39;s expectations. I would rank this course #1 because the instructor Tomas takes the systematic and a very organized approach in training the students. I will enrol for another courses because it&#39;s JUST WORTH IT. The course brilliantly and generously covers the entire topic without biases or prejudice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn 4 Steps to Make Money Online with Affiliate Marketing!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-4-steps-to-make-money-online-with-affiliate-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-4-steps-to-make-money-online-with-affiliate-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to make money online even while you are sleeping?
Would you like to spend time with your loved ones and earning money at the same time?
It happens to me all the time.
I still remember the day when I stumbled online and searched something like, &#34;How to make money online&#34;.
There was a young man from the United States who said that he can show me how to make money using the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Powerful Instagram Sales Funnel to Grow Your Business</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/powerful-instagram-sales-funnel-to-grow-your-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/powerful-instagram-sales-funnel-to-grow-your-business/</guid>
      <description>Instagram has over 700 million active users ready to discover your brand. However, there’s no clear way to drive traffic back to your website and get sales. The solution lays in building powerful Instagram sales funnel to convert someone browsing into a customer. In this class, we will discuss: How you can transition a customer from discovering your brand to following you &amp;amp; eventually purchasing from you
How to track your customer&#39;s behavior &amp;amp; retarget them until they purchase from you</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crea tu Libro de Autor para Arquitectos e Interioristas</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/crea-tu-libro-de-autor-para-arquitectos-e-interioristas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/crea-tu-libro-de-autor-para-arquitectos-e-interioristas/</guid>
      <description>Crea tu Libro de Autor para Arquitectos e Interioristas
Crear tu Libro de Autor de tus Diseños, Obras y Proyectos de Arquitectura e Interiorismo
Instructores: Arquitecto Álvaro García y Arquitecta Lucía Fernández. Contenido Actualizado: Octubre 2021 
Calificación: ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐

Descripción del Curso:
Hola, Somos Álvaro García y Lucía Fernández, arquitectos desde hace más de 15 años. Hemos realizando obras, proyectos y reformas de interior y queremos compartir contigo esta formación donde podrás hacer una auto publicación o edición de tu libro de autor, que consiste en la publicación de tu libro porfolio con tus proyectos de arquitectura, interiorismo y creatividad sin la intervención de un editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Analytics: Pricing Strategies and Price Analytics</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/marketing-analytics-pricing-strategies-and-price-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/marketing-analytics-pricing-strategies-and-price-analytics/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re looking for a complete course on pricing strategies and pricing analytics that maximize your firm revenue/profit, right?
You&#39;ve found the right Marketing Analytics: Pricing Strategies course! This course teaches you everything you need to know about different pricing strategies and how to implement it using profit maximizing price points.
After completing this course you will be able to:
Implement pricing strategies such as simple linear pricing, price bundling, giving quantity discount, price skimming, applying two part tariffs and many more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copywriting: 3 Crucial Points For Your Text To Sell Itself</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/copywriting-3-crucial-points-for-your-text-to-sell-itself/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/copywriting-3-crucial-points-for-your-text-to-sell-itself/</guid>
      <description>We can’t go a day in our life without reading something on the internet: blogposts, articles, promotional texts, etc. Who writes them? Who makes us read all of that information? A copywriter. Just image the amount of power hidden inside copywriter’s brain. When someone needs something sold – they contact a copywriter, when someone needs something promoted – they contact a copywriter. Don’t underestimate that. If you want to learn how all the things forementioned here are done, come along and let’s talk about it in the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing Strategy Course 2021. Start from scratch!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-marketing-strategy-course-2021.-start-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-marketing-strategy-course-2021.-start-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my digital marketing course!
What is digital marketing?
Digital marketing is an innovative way to attract a large audience to your online project. There are a wide variety of online marketing techniques that you can use, such as social media marketing, content marketing, email marketing, search engine optimization, affiliate marketing, inbound marketing, mobile marketing, display advertising, paid search, web analytics, conversion optimization, etc. In this digital marketing course, we will discuss how to make these marketing techniques work in sync with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sales Funnel, Email Marketing All-in-One Tool: Systeme Guide</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sales-funnel-email-marketing-all-in-one-tool-systeme-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sales-funnel-email-marketing-all-in-one-tool-systeme-guide/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Complete Online Business Marketing Tool - Guide to Systeme!
For a long time, marketers have had to piece together various tools and software tools in order to achieve their goals. But these days, marketers are constantly being confronted with new platforms, new startup companies, and old favorites that are constantly re-tooling themselves and shifting their strategies.
In this rapid-fire internet era of marketing, it can be hard for even the most seasoned professionals to keep up with everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Utreon Masterclass - Ultimate Guide to YouTube Alternative</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/utreon-masterclass-ultimate-guide-to-youtube-alternative/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/utreon-masterclass-ultimate-guide-to-youtube-alternative/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Utreon Masterclass - Ultimate Guide to YouTube Alternative!
The only course you will need to start with Utreon, one of the best and newest video hosting platforms and YouTube alternatives for aspiring content creators.
Utreon is a relatively new video hosting platform that allows you to host your channel and content and gain access to large and untapped audiences that is simply impossible to reach nowadays on YouTube. For that reason, Utreon is deemed as one of the best YouTube alternatives today where creators can reach large portions of audiences without inhuman amounts of effort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Ads &amp; Instagram Ads Course 2021 (Ready for iOS 14&#43;)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/facebook-ads-instagram-ads-course-2021-ready-for-ios-14-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/facebook-ads-instagram-ads-course-2021-ready-for-ios-14-/</guid>
      <description>FACEBOOK ADS &amp;amp; INSTAGRAM ADS &amp;amp; MESSENGER ADS ULTIMATE COURSE 2021 edition (ready for Apple iOS 14+ restrictions) - Optimise your Facebook, Instagram and Messenger ads budget, boost e-commerce sales, enjoy HOT leads from Facebook &amp;amp; Instagram, or set up as a successful freelancer…
Dearest Student,
Hi, I’m Tomas Moravek, the INTERNET EFFICIENCY AWARD Winning Digital Strategist with my Facebook, Instagram, and Messenger Ads Ultimate Mastery Course, 2021 Edition.
When you enrol on this course, you’ll be joining 450,000+ successful students who’ve learned Facebook Ads, Instagram Ads, Messenger Ads using my techniques and strategies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Influencer Content Marketing (2021 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/influencer-content-marketing-2021-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/influencer-content-marketing-2021-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the eighth course in Term 1 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Your website acts as the forefront of your business. It enables your visitors to see you in the virtual space so they can make specific assumptions and create a given brand perception.
Nevertheless, one of the most common woes for anyone running a business is getting a “lack of traffic” to any website or blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Branded TV Channel Creation (Neon Edition 2021)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/online-branded-tv-channel-creation-neon-edition-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/online-branded-tv-channel-creation-neon-edition-2021/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the seventh course in Term 3 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
You&#39;ll totally love this course.
Know that this course focussing on &#34;Online Branded TV Channel Creation (Neon 2021 Edition)&#34; created by Digital Marketing Legend &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34; can redefine inbound marketing and Online TV Channel Creation - altogether. Do you know about the growth of internet television in 2021? It&#39;s unexplained and the answer is &#39;tremendous&#39;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viral YouTube Marketing - Crash Course (2021 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/viral-youtube-marketing-crash-course-2021-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/viral-youtube-marketing-crash-course-2021-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the fifth course in Term 1 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Did you know? 
Millions of videos are uploaded to YouTube on a daily basis. YouTube seems the greatest place to grow your own brand, drive traffic to your website, and earn money from ads (leveraging AdSense) that are generated through advertisers who bid on Google and your product and service promotions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEO Strategy 2021. SEO training to TOP rank your website!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/seo-strategy-2021.-seo-training-to-top-rank-your-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/seo-strategy-2021.-seo-training-to-top-rank-your-website/</guid>
      <description>Description
Search engines have become a universal advisor and assistant to today’s internet users. We come to Google to find out different things, asking what to buy, which model, what brand etc.
Every day, Google receives 10 billion requests, and the commercial interest of a company is a big part of this 10 billion.
SEO has an enormous amount of targeted traffic, and its price is usually many times lower than that of PPC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social media marketing strategy 2021. Launch your SMM!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/social-media-marketing-strategy-2021.-launch-your-smm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/social-media-marketing-strategy-2021.-launch-your-smm/</guid>
      <description>What is social media marketing and its role in modern society?
Social media marketing is the use and management of different social media platforms to promote your brand, products, and services. It is a great tool to communicate with your existing customers and reach new ones. Social media marketing helps you drive traffic to your website, increase sales, build engagement and customer loyalty.
The use of social media is a fast-growing global trend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Marketing 2021 | Go Viral With Authentic Videos!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tiktok-marketing-2021-go-viral-with-authentic-videos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/tiktok-marketing-2021-go-viral-with-authentic-videos/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Social Savvy Insider for TikTok!
For licensing inquiries email: skyler@weresocialsavvy.com
Language: English
----------------------------------------
Hi! My name is Skyler, Co-Founder of Social Savvy LA (Digital Marketing Agency)
This is the most educational TikTok course under 2 hours on the market. Guaranteed! This course is hyper-focused on the most effective tactics of marketing through TikTok. For this course to be applied to your page, you should have an intermediate level of understanding of social media platforms and their basic functionality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Email Monetization Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/email-monetization-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/email-monetization-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Turning your email list into a passive income money maker isn’t as difficult, or time consuming as you may think.
Every day, thousands of online marketers are transforming their mailing lists into powerful cash funnels, and quite often, they don’t even have their own product line!
This course will make it easy for you to start making money with your subscriber base even if you’re just starting out.
It will show you how you can join the ranks of successful list builders quickly and easily, while increasing engagement, building your tribe and positioning yourself as a thought leader in your market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction To SEO Based Content Writing (Hindi)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-seo-based-content-writing-hindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-seo-based-content-writing-hindi/</guid>
      <description>Feel Free To Enjoy This Course And Learn One Of The Best SEO Based Content Writing Course In Language “Hindi”. So, After Completing The Course, You Will Be Enable To Write Search Engine Based Contents. And With That, You Can Increase Good Valuable Content In Any Article. After Completing The Job You Can Do Freelance Or Create Your Own Blog To Earn Good Amount Of Dollars Every Month.
 Ratings: 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masterclass in Marketing Psychology</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/masterclass-in-marketing-psychology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/masterclass-in-marketing-psychology/</guid>
      <description>This course aims to make you a Jedi of Marketing Psychology within approx. 3.5 hours. This Udemy course is to learn what works and how to get results – fast! 
In this course I will show you how to:
· How to create effective messaging for Marketing Campaigns: online(#Digital Marketing) and offline
· How to advertise products for making the right impact
· How to establish trust through body language</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn 4 STEPS to Make Money Online by Blogging!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-4-steps-to-make-money-online-by-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-4-steps-to-make-money-online-by-blogging/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to wake up in the morning, check your phone and see how much money you made while you&#39;ve been sleeping?
That&#39;s my morning routine.
Every single morning I like to check out from my phone how much money I have made last night.
But of course, things weren&#39;t always so good for me so let&#39;s go back in time back to 2015...
How Did I Learn to Make Money Blogging?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Pinterest Marketing Guide for Creatives 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-pinterest-marketing-guide-for-creatives-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-pinterest-marketing-guide-for-creatives-2021/</guid>
      <description>I believe in making your business work for YOU and not the other way. 
Join over 10.000 happy Students that are already enrolled to this course and pinning to win!
+++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++
This Pinterest Course is a Complete  Pinterest Marketing Guide for Creatives and will teach you How to Get Free Traffic From Pinterest. 
&amp;gt;&amp;gt;I have included Done-for-you Pinterest Templates that you can edit in a free Design Tool called Canva and use for your Business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Facebook Traffic Ads (Facebook CPC) Course 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-facebook-traffic-ads-facebook-cpc-course-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-facebook-traffic-ads-facebook-cpc-course-2022/</guid>
      <description>Gain more clients, maximise sales, and push more traffic to your website with the most comprehensive and current Facebook Traffic and Marketing course out there - The Complete Facebook Traffic Ads (Facebook CPC) Course 2022!
&#34;I love Tom, he is the man, he really knows what he&#39;s talking about when it comes to Facebook marketing. A true expert in the field! Don&#39;t hesitate to take this course, because I promise you that you will not be disappointed!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to sell on Instagram: marketing for online sales via DM</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-sell-on-instagram-marketing-for-online-sales-via-dm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-sell-on-instagram-marketing-for-online-sales-via-dm/</guid>
      <description>THIS COURSE IS FILLED WITH EXCLUSIVE INFORMATION THAT YOU CAN’T GOOGLE AND FIND ANYWHERE ELSE!
It’s based on valuable insights that we’ve gained from our clients’ experiences and the strategies of million-dollar IG businesses. The secret is that proper communication in Direct on Instagram is not a mainstream practice yet. So, it will become a powerful tool for boosting your sales in a short period of time. Foolproof plans are revealed in the lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEO TRAINING 2021: Complete SEO Course &#43; WordPress SEO Yoast</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/seo-training-2021-complete-seo-course-wordpress-seo-yoast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/seo-training-2021-complete-seo-course-wordpress-seo-yoast/</guid>
      <description>This is my Complete SEO Course 2021 available with up-to-date SEO information on the latest 2021 SEO strategy, like voice search, mobile SEO, video SEO, YouTube SEO, video featured snippets on Google, featured snippets on Google, image SEO, and visual search.
Dear Students,
Hi, Tomas Moravek here, Internet Efficiency 2016 Award Winning Digital Strategist, to introduce my brand new, updated, SEO MASTERY Course.
I&#39;ve put so much passion, energy, and time in to creating this SEO Training for you and I can&#39;t wait until you join my thousands of satisfied students so you can see for yourself why my strategies really work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Analytics and Retail Business Management</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/marketing-analytics-and-retail-business-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/marketing-analytics-and-retail-business-management/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re looking for a complete course on understanding Marketing Analytics and Retail Business Management to drive business decisions involving production schedules, inventory management, promotional mail optimization, store layouting, estimating right bundle price, customer valuation and many other parts of the business., right?
You&#39;ve found the right Marketing Analytics &amp;amp; Retail Business Management course! This course teaches you everything you need to know about different forecasting models, Market Basket analysis, conducting market research, marketing analytics, RFM (recency, frequency, monetary) analysis, Customer Valuation methods &amp;amp; Price Bundling analysis and how to implement these models in Excel using advanced excel tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beginner &amp; Advanced Udemy Course Creation – Unofficial</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/beginner-advanced-udemy-course-creation-unofficial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/beginner-advanced-udemy-course-creation-unofficial/</guid>
      <description>Note: This course is not sponsored by or affiliated with Udemy, Inc.
Beginner &amp;amp; Advanced Udemy Course Creation Training. Inside this Online Course you will learn how to make Udemy courses the fast, simple &amp;amp; easy way. You will also be shown how to make an amazing amount of steady and recurring passive income on Udemy.
I SHARE ALL MY SECRETS IN THIS COURSE
Learn how the “Gurus” on Udemy really make their money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEST of Facebook Ads: Facebook Ads 2021 ULTIMATE PRO Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/best-of-facebook-ads-facebook-ads-2021-ultimate-pro-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/best-of-facebook-ads-facebook-ads-2021-ultimate-pro-edition/</guid>
      <description>Upskill yourself and ensure you&#39;re never out of work or out of clients, with the BEST OF FACEBOOK ADS, INSTAGRAM ADS &amp;amp; MESSENGER ADS PRO EDITION 2021. Learn everything you need to know to become a Professional Facebook Ads Consultant, and start a new career online, or boost your local or e-commerce Business.
&#34;I love this course. All the points related to Facebook Ads were explained in-depth by Tom. You will feel pretty confident about launching Facebook Ads after finishing this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Ads B2B: Facebook Advertising&#43; Facebook Ads for B2B</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/facebook-ads-b2b-facebook-advertising-facebook-ads-for-b2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/facebook-ads-b2b-facebook-advertising-facebook-ads-for-b2b/</guid>
      <description>This is the ultimate course on business-to-business Facebook advertising!
I’ve been advertising on Facebook for over a decade. I was a VP of Marketing for a Google accelerator startup, a global marketing manager for Sony, and I’ve helped countless small businesses with digital advertising. I taught college-level digital marketing, and I studied digital marketing at the #1 ranked business school for marketing - the Kellogg School of Management. This is where the father of marketing, Philip Kotler, teaches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagram Marketing 2021 | Grow Organic Followers Naturally!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/instagram-marketing-2021-grow-organic-followers-naturally/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/instagram-marketing-2021-grow-organic-followers-naturally/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Social Savvy Insider!
***Over 10,000 students enrolled in 3 days of this course going live***
***Now 100,000+ students enrolled***
Language: English
----------------------------------------
Hi! My name is Skyler, Co-Founder of Social Savvy LA (Influencer Marketing Growth Agency)
This is the most educational course under 2 hours on the market. This course is hyper-focused on the most effective tactics of marketing through Instagram. For this course to be applied to your page, you should have an intermediate level of understanding of the platform and its basic functionality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local SEO 2021 Made Simple &amp; Fun &#43; Google Maps &amp; TripAdvisor</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/local-seo-2021-made-simple-fun-google-maps-tripadvisor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/local-seo-2021-made-simple-fun-google-maps-tripadvisor/</guid>
      <description>2021’s MOST ENJOYABLE LOCAL SEO, GOOGLE MY BUSINESS &amp;amp; TRIPADVISOR COURSE!!! THIS LOCAL SEO COURSE IS FILLED WITH QUIZZES, ANIMATED VIDEOS, ASSIGNMENTS, TEMPLATES SCREEN RECORDINGS AND OVER MY SHOULDER EXPLANATIONS!!! WATCH AS I WALK YOU THROUGH EVERYTHING YOU WILL NEED TO KNOW TO BECOME A LOCAL SEO, AND COPYWRITING PRO IN 10 EASY TO FOLLOW STEPS!!! MAX LOCAL SEO TRAFFIC &amp;amp; SALES, BOOST SEARCH RANKING, OR LAND YOUR DREAM MARKETING JOB!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Marketing 101 - How To Make The Most Of It!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/social-media-marketing-101-how-to-make-the-most-of-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/social-media-marketing-101-how-to-make-the-most-of-it/</guid>
      <description>In This Online Social Media Marketing Course You Will Learn The RIGHT Way To Do Social Media Marketing From The Expert. This Social Media Marketing Training Will Give You All The Key Skills You Need. You Will Benefit From A Great Overview Of Social Media Marketing &amp;amp; How To Make The Most Of It For Maximum Profits!
Learning These Key Skills &amp;amp; Techniques Can Help You Be Massively Successful As You Do Social Media Marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Branding &amp; Brand Management: Branding Strategy Brand Tactics</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/branding-brand-management-branding-strategy-brand-tactics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/branding-brand-management-branding-strategy-brand-tactics/</guid>
      <description>Top MBAs are expensive, time-consuming, and extremely difficult to get into. My goal with this course is to give you an MBA level of understanding branding and brand management. Learn from a former Global Brand Manager at Sony PlayStation who studied brand management at the Kellogg School of Management and has helped countless startups with their branding. If you sell marketing services, this gives you a sophisticated edge over other marketers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEST of CONTENT MARKETING, SEO &amp; COPYWRITING &#43; 23 TEMPLATES</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/best-of-content-marketing-seo-copywriting-23-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 10:00:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/best-of-content-marketing-seo-copywriting-23-templates/</guid>
      <description>LEARN CONTENT MARKETING, SEO &amp;amp; COPYWRITING WITH OUR EASY LEARNING SYSTEM - HQ VIDEO ANIMATED EXPLAINERS, QUIZZES, &amp;amp; ASSIGNMENTS THAT MAKE LEARNING FUN, FAST, &amp;amp; EASY!!! GET PRO 23 CONTENT CREATION TEMPLATES YOU CAN CUSTOMISE!!! MAX LEADS &amp;amp; SALES, BOOST SEARCH RANKING, OR LAND YOUR DREAM MARKETING JOB!!!
MASTER CONTENT MARKETING - Learn how to get your content in front of the right people - and how to rev up its engagement rate - so you get more LEADS, SALES, COMMENTS, &amp;amp; SHARES.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create your marketing calendar for busy entrepreneurs</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-create-your-marketing-calendar-for-busy-entrepreneurs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-create-your-marketing-calendar-for-busy-entrepreneurs/</guid>
      <description>If you are a digital entrepreneur, coach, consultant, affiliate marketer, blogger, or own any type of online business, You know how important marketing is for your business. And with the never-ending to-do list that we have as busy entrepreneurs, managing our marketing and planning and executing marketing campaigns and measuring the results is a top business priority but so many entrepreneurs don&#39;t have a solid system in place to plan their marketing and this is why I created this course!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sales Funnels Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sales-funnels-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sales-funnels-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you want to maximize your income so you can squeeze every possible dollar from your product launches,you absolutely need to master the art of creating high-converting sales funnels.
Because a well-constructed sales funnel that’s based on proven techniques can take a simple product launch and retain the momentum weeks, even months after the launch.
This special report was written to provide you with a step-by-step quick start blueprint to creating outstanding sales funnels that not only maximize your profits but are aimed at keeping the money rolling in long after your initial launch phase is over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Money Online for Beginners: Follow PROVEN STEPS!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-make-money-online-for-beginners-follow-proven-steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-make-money-online-for-beginners-follow-proven-steps/</guid>
      <description>Your first $1 online is the hardest. The rest will be much easier.
In this course, you&#39;ll learn the steps, mindset and the principles to making money online.
You&#39;re not going to get push buttons to riches but a solid advice from a person who has helped numerous people to make money online.
While I can&#39;t promise you results by law, I can promise to do my best to help you to succeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Marketing on Autopilot with Missinglettr</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/social-media-marketing-on-autopilot-with-missinglettr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/social-media-marketing-on-autopilot-with-missinglettr/</guid>
      <description>Did you know? The technique of automating social media activities in order to improve the results generated from social media channels is known as social media automation. It saves time and effort spent on administering social platforms, communicating with prospects, and increasing brand exposure for marketers. Let&#39;s now ask you a quick question.
Have you ever dreamt of automating your social media campaigns with a magical platform that creates, schedules and provides reports of branded social media content while you&#39;re busy doing something else?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Thumbnail Masterclass / Ultimate to Guide Thumbnails</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/youtube-thumbnail-masterclass-/-ultimate-to-guide-thumbnails/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/youtube-thumbnail-masterclass-/-ultimate-to-guide-thumbnails/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s not a secret to anyone anymore. YouTube Thumbnails matter. A lot. It&#39;s the first thing people see when browsing YouTube and it&#39;s what will make them click on your video to watch it or not. It can mean the difference between a million views and no views. YouTube thumbnails are often the most influential factor in determining whether or not viewers will watch your video. This is because it&#39;s the first thing they see when browsing YouTube and is what will make them click on it to watch or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best of Copywriting &amp; SEO: Content, Copywriting &amp; SEO Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/best-of-copywriting-seo-content-copywriting-seo-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 09:38:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/best-of-copywriting-seo-content-copywriting-seo-course/</guid>
      <description>LEARN HIGHLY PERSUASIVE SEO COPYWRITING TECHNIQUES – SEAMLESSLY BOOST YOUR SEO WHILE PUSHING YOUR CUSTOMER’S BUTTONS. WRITE FOR SALES SUCCESS WITH OUR EXPERT GUIDE FROM A PRO CONTENT CREATOR – INCLUDES EASY WALKTHROUGHS TO MAX YOUR SEO COPYWRITING RESULTS. THIS SEO &amp;amp; COPYWRITING COURSE IS COMPLETELY ANIMATED AND OPTIMISED FOR BEGINNERS TO LEARN FAST. THIS COURSE ALSO INCLUDES A PRO COPYWRITING PDF GUIDE, PDF CHECKLIST AND 23 CONTENT MARKETING TEMPLATES, SO YOU CAN CREATE CONTENT LIKE AN EXPERT, AND SELL MORE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inbound Marketing: Content Marketing, KPI &amp; Google Analytics</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/inbound-marketing-content-marketing-kpi-google-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 09:38:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/inbound-marketing-content-marketing-kpi-google-analytics/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to use inbound marketing strategies to get the best leads and most engaged customers to your site or product.
Then monitor how those leads behave on your website using Google Analytics which is a data-driven approach where you identify and set the right KPIs (Key Performance Indicators) to monitor and work on improving. Once your KPIs are heading in the right direction, so will your business.
WHY IS INBOUND MARKETING GREAT?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mit Online Marketing Dein Business aufbauen ohne Vorwissen!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/mit-online-marketing-dein-business-aufbauen-ohne-vorwissen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 09:38:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/mit-online-marketing-dein-business-aufbauen-ohne-vorwissen/</guid>
      <description>Letzte Aktualisierung: 24.9.2021
*** DER KURS WIRD LAUFEND ERWEITERT -&amp;gt; neue Inhalte jeden Monat! *** 

Digitales Marketing und insbesondere Online Marketing boomen seit einigen Jahren. Es herrscht eine Goldgräberstimmung, und genau JETZT hat es Sinn, sich mit Online Marketing auseinanderzusetzen - bevor es zu spät ist. Besonders jetzt, im Jahr 2021 explodiert der Online Traffic und die Werbepreise gehen herunter.
Der Einzelhandel, Unternehmer und Selbständige sind aufgrund der aktuellen Lage gezwungen, ihre Produkte immer mehr online zu verkaufen - und kaum jemand ist wirklich darauf vorbereitet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SELL Like HELL: Facebook Ads for E-COMMERCE Ultimate MASTERY</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sell-like-hell-facebook-ads-for-e-commerce-ultimate-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 11:41:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sell-like-hell-facebook-ads-for-e-commerce-ultimate-mastery/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Excellent Facebook Ads &amp;amp; Instagram Ads Course. Would highly recommend this course to someone who is looking to learn or for that matter even gain knowledge. No institute or a YouTube video teaches this in so much detail as much as Tomas. I haven’t come across so far a genuine course teaching material as much as you have designed. Thanks Tomas a ton.&#34; Ridhima
&#34;Best course for Facebook e-commerce ads. Really in depth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Manipulation Works in Marketing/Copywriting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-manipulation-works-in-marketing/copywriting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-manipulation-works-in-marketing/copywriting/</guid>
      <description>MARKETING OR MANIPULATING?
You probably know that marketers and copywriters do a great job of making a product (or offer) seem appealing.
The only problem is when those techniques turn into actual lies or manipulation.
As a persuasion expert, I&#39;ve catalogued all different possible types of manipulation.
And in this course, you will find out about how every single one of them is using in marketing.


LET ME TELL YOU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2021 - Part 10</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-10/</guid>
      <description>Virality is not a single attribute. It&#39;s a rule of architecture. It&#39;s not a fortunate outcome. It&#39;s sophisticated. It&#39;s art too. People are the key component of all practices in social media. That means the sort of real social buzz that can bring your content in front of a massive amount of real people is not an automated process. Although attempts to automate social buzz are nothing more than ineffective spam, there is now a real solution to the good news.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Instagram Marketing Strategies to get more Followers</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/top-10-instagram-marketing-strategies-to-get-more-followers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:50:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/top-10-instagram-marketing-strategies-to-get-more-followers/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our course, which will teach you the Top 10 secret Instagram Strategies, to get more Followers.

This Course is made for
- Entrepreneurs
- Influencer
- Businesses
- And Professionals

Who wants to gain more Followers and skyrocket their Instagram Profile?

We are DLI DIgitalLearn Interactive with a strong focus on digital entrepreneurship and over 10 years of experience in doing business online from Amazon FBA to affiliate marketing over to all kinds of Social Media Platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Youtube Business Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/youtube-business-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:47:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/youtube-business-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Youtube is the most popular video-streaming service boasting massive online traffic and constant streaming services.
And it’s the second most-visited website on the Internet with nearly 2 billion monthly users logging on to watch videos every day.
Youtube channel can maximize exposure and help your brand become recognized within your market.
It’s a great way to connect with your audience and keep them engaged for longer periods of time, while encouraging repeat traffic and views.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Engine Optimization Complete Specialization Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/search-engine-optimization-complete-specialization-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/search-engine-optimization-complete-specialization-course/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the World&#39;s best specialized SEO course ever. 
The course cover everything from theory to practical with case studies and examples. This is the only course in the world where you woll also learn about the technicalities of SEO and how to handle them. The content of this course is based on real world practices and checklists used by professionals in the SEO world.
You will learn about</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unique Selling Proposition Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/unique-selling-proposition-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/unique-selling-proposition-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>USP stands for Unique Selling Proposition (or Point) and every business needs one.
It’s easy to spot a USP once you see one in action. It’s the service or product that you offer which no other business is currently offering to their clients.
Your USP is why consumers should do business with you, versus the competition. It’ll also be the reason they keep coming back to your business.
In this course, will discover a few examples of winning USP’s so you can see what a USP is, and how to create one for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Video Production, Video Marketing, &amp; YouTube Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-video-production-video-marketing-youtube-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:43:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-video-production-video-marketing-youtube-course/</guid>
      <description>Become a filmmaker, upgrade your lifestyle, travel the world, and tap into the fastest growing, most profitable media income stream around with this POWERFUL Step-By-Step Guide to Video Production and Video Marketing... Just one well-made video could turnaround your business, bringing you a slew of new customers, boosting your sales, social media followers and sign ups, and helping you hit those all-important first page spots on Google and YouTube...
Dear Students,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified Facebook Marketing Professional | CPD Accredited</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/certified-facebook-marketing-professional-cpd-accredited/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/certified-facebook-marketing-professional-cpd-accredited/</guid>
      <description>Two Facebook Marketing Certificates for the Price of One! Finish your Udemy course and Contact us to get your Continuing Professional Development (CPD) Certificate! Check out &#34;This is How You Earn Your CPD Accrdeited Certificate!&#34; Lecture for more information!

Still, struggling to reach out easily to tons of globally scattered customers?
This is Your Ultimate Chance to Easily Reach Out To Your Targeted Business Audience &amp;amp; Boost Brand Awareness For Your Products &amp;amp; Services Without Spending Much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified Instagram Marketing Professional | CPD Accredited</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/certified-instagram-marketing-professional-cpd-accredited/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/certified-instagram-marketing-professional-cpd-accredited/</guid>
      <description>Two Instagram Marketing Certificates for the Price of One! Finish your Udemy course and Contact us to get your Continuing Professional Development (CPD) Certificate!
Are you still struggling to promote your brand to widely scattered masses &amp;amp; boost sales and profits?
To achieve your objectives, are you searching for the most proven and tested strategies.
Then, it’s time to take a breather.
As of today, We are going to spill the beans on Instagram Marketing, one of the best ways to communicate easily and reach out to your targeted business audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified YouTube Marketing Professional | CPD Accredited</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/certified-youtube-marketing-professional-cpd-accredited/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/certified-youtube-marketing-professional-cpd-accredited/</guid>
      <description>Two YouTube Marketing Certificates for the Price of One! Finish your Udemy course and Contact us to get your Continuing Professional Development (CPD) Certificate! Check out &#34;This is How You Earn Your CPD Accrdeited Certificate!&#34; Lecture for more information!

Doing business with YouTube has become the best technique for success, hungry marketers, to make the most from their marketing efforts, and if not given adequate importance to, it can prove fatal for your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Affiliate Networking Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/affiliate-networking-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/affiliate-networking-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>There’s no easier way to skyrocket your income, get your products in front of thousands of new prospects and build a recognized brand than by connecting with seasoned affiliate marketers.
Affiliates will help build momentum before, during and after your product launch, but they do much more than that.
This special report will help you quickly locate the top affiliates in your market and show you exactly what you need to do to turn influencers into dedicated marketer’s that are proud to promote your products and align with your brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Affiliate Secrets (সুপার অ্যাফিলিয়েট সিক্রেটস) Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/super-affiliate-secrets-%E0%A6%B8%E0%A7%81%E0%A6%AA%E0%A6%BE%E0%A6%B0-%E0%A6%85%E0%A7%8D%E0%A6%AF%E0%A6%BE%E0%A6%AB%E0%A6%BF%E0%A6%B2%E0%A6%BF%E0%A6%AF%E0%A6%BC%E0%A7%87%E0%A6%9F-%E0%A6%B8%E0%A6%BF%E0%A6%95%E0%A7%8D%E0%A6%B0%E0%A7%87%E0%A6%9F%E0%A6%B8-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/super-affiliate-secrets-%E0%A6%B8%E0%A7%81%E0%A6%AA%E0%A6%BE%E0%A6%B0-%E0%A6%85%E0%A7%8D%E0%A6%AF%E0%A6%BE%E0%A6%AB%E0%A6%BF%E0%A6%B2%E0%A6%BF%E0%A6%AF%E0%A6%BC%E0%A7%87%E0%A6%9F-%E0%A6%B8%E0%A6%BF%E0%A6%95%E0%A7%8D%E0%A6%B0%E0%A7%87%E0%A6%9F%E0%A6%B8-course/</guid>
      <description>এটিই সর্বপ্রথম বাংলা ভাষায় অ্যাফিলিয়েট মার্কেটিং-এর World-Class অনলাইন কোর্স -
If you have always wanted to build a profitable affiliate business but could not find a guide that explained the whole process to you, this is the answer you have been looking for.
This series of video lectures in Bengali covers everything you need to know about building an affiliate business that generates commissions every month like clockwork.

Super Affiliate Secrets Course in the Bengali Language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copywriting: Make Money From Home WRITING WORDS</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/copywriting-make-money-from-home-writing-words/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 21:40:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/copywriting-make-money-from-home-writing-words/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to make money online Writing Words?
I&#39;ve been doing that already for years and now I&#39;ll reveal to you the Best Secrets of copywriting.
Once you make money with copywriting, you&#39;ll have a lot of freedom.
You can make money...
ANYWHERE you want
ANYTIME you want
WRITING about something you love
NEVER showing your face unless you want
In a nutshell, you can simply open your laptop and start making money whenever you want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Analytics: Forecasting Models with Excel</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/marketing-analytics-forecasting-models-with-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/marketing-analytics-forecasting-models-with-excel/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re looking for a complete course on understanding Forecasting models and forecasting analytics to drive business decisions involving production schedules, inventory management, manpower planning, demand forecasting, and many other parts of the business., right?
You&#39;ve found the right Marketing Analytics: Forecasting Models with Excel! This course teaches you everything you need to know about different forecasting models and how to implement these models for devising forecasting analytics in Excel using advanced excel tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEST of Digital Marketing Essentials 2021: Learn FUN &amp; FAST</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/best-of-digital-marketing-essentials-2021-learn-fun-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 22:18:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/best-of-digital-marketing-essentials-2021-learn-fun-fast/</guid>
      <description>HI AND BIG WELCOME TO OUR INTRODUCTION TO THE ESSENTIAL OF DIGITAL MARKETING, SOCIAL MEDIA, AND SEO. MAKE SURE YOU’RE SITTING COMFORTABLY, AS YOU’RE ABOUT TO GET A COMPREHENSIVE OVERVIEW OF EVERYTHING RELATED TO DIGITAL MARKETING, SOCIAL MEDIA, AND SEO. THIS DIGITAL MARKETING COURSE IS MADE FUN! IT HAS BEEN FILLED WITH HQ ANIMATED VIDEO EXPLAINERS AND INTERACTIVE QUIZZES WITH QUESTIONS A, B, C, D.
IF YOU WANT TO BE SUCCESSFUL ONLINE TODAY, YOU NEED TO HAVE STRONG DIGITAL MARKETING SKILLS AS INTERNET BUSINESS HAS NEVER BEEN MORE COMPETITIVE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2021 - Part 12</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2021-part-12/</guid>
      <description>So, want to proofread effectively, or start a proofreading business and sell a ton of editing or writing services, right away?
Hop in.
Editing is not just the icing on the cake; it is a highly important part of the writing process. Get ready. 
Take the guesswork out of great writing with this course. See what you can accomplish with the power of these proofreading tools at your fingertips. Easily improve any text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basics of Proofreading</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/basics-of-proofreading/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/basics-of-proofreading/</guid>
      <description>Proofreaders are normally the members of the publishing team that make sure that documents look and read their best before they are sent to print. Along with being able to recognize errors in written materials, proofreaders must be able to correctly mark the documents for corrections.

However, nowadays, with the help of freelancer marketplaces anyone can become a proofreader and offer their services online.

Proofreaders can charge around $20-$50 per hour</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Page &amp; Facebook Ads Made as FUN: 10 DAYS Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/facebook-page-facebook-ads-made-as-fun-10-days-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/facebook-page-facebook-ads-made-as-fun-10-days-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Step by step Facebook ads &amp;amp; Instagram ads course for beginners (ready for ios 14.5+ restrictions) - Accept our 10 days challenge and learn how to set up Facebook business page &amp;amp; Facebook business manager. Install Facebook Pixel ready for iOS 14.5+ restrictions. Use Facebook Creator studio. Launch your first Facebook read ads &amp;amp; Facebook engagement campaigns. Generate leads with Facebook lead generation ads. This Facebook ads course includes essential info so you can prep for the Facebook Pixel API for iOS14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversion Optimization Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/conversion-optimization-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 12:58:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/conversion-optimization-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Increasing your website’s traffic is already a time-consuming task that will take up enough of your time. So, you need to make sure that traffic converts into sales, right?
There are simple ways of capturing attention, boosting conversion rates and ultimately, maximizing your profits without breaking the bank, or spending a lot of time tweaking your traffic campaigns.
The conversion boosting hacks featured in this report are ones that you can easily implement into your existing website without spending more than a couple of hours tightening up a few weak areas so that you can transform your business in just a matter of a few short days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEST of GOOGLE ADS 2021: Set Up Google Search Campaign Today</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/best-of-google-ads-2021-set-up-google-search-campaign-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 20:22:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/best-of-google-ads-2021-set-up-google-search-campaign-today/</guid>
      <description>LEARN GOOGLE ADS AND SETUP YOUR GOOGLE SEARCH CAMPAIGN TODAY!!!! LEARN HOW TO SET UP YOUR GOOGLE ADS ACCOUNT, USE GOOGLE COUPON, WRITE YOUR GOOGLE AD COPY, CREATE YOUR FIRST CAMPAIGN, AND GET YOUR ADVERTISING UP &amp;amp; RUNNING. IN THIS GOOGLE ADS COURSE YOU WILL WALK-THROUGH SETUP, CONFIGURATION, CREATING AD COPY, ADDING YOUR KEYWORDS, AND OPTIMISING YOUR ADS TO DRIVE TRAFFIC TO YOUR WEBSITE. YOU WILL LEARN HOW TO SETUP RETARGETING AND GOOGLE SHOPPING (GOOGLE MERCHANT CENTRE).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SnapChat Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/snapchat-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 12:05:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/snapchat-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Uncover the secrets to creating extremely successful marketing campaigns on Snapchat!
Snapchat is pretty much the hottest thing going these days, especially among the younger millennial crowd. The site allows users to send “Snaps”, which are pictures or videos, to their followers. These Snaps disappear after a short period of time, giving users the (somewhat false) sense that anything they do won’t last forever.
Snapchat can actually be extremely useful for your business, especially if you market to the younger crowd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>أستثمر أموالك وأربح شهرياً 25 % من رأس المال</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/%D8%A3%D8%B3%D8%AA%D8%AB%D9%85%D8%B1-%D8%A3%D9%85%D9%88%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%83-%D9%88%D8%A3%D8%B1%D8%A8%D8%AD-%D8%B4%D9%87%D8%B1%D9%8A%D8%A7%D9%8B-25-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%B1%D8%A3%D8%B3-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D8%A7%D9%84/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/%D8%A3%D8%B3%D8%AA%D8%AB%D9%85%D8%B1-%D8%A3%D9%85%D9%88%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%83-%D9%88%D8%A3%D8%B1%D8%A8%D8%AD-%D8%B4%D9%87%D8%B1%D9%8A%D8%A7%D9%8B-25-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%B1%D8%A3%D8%B3-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D8%A7%D9%84/</guid>
      <description>بهذه الدورة رح تتعلم كيف تحقق دخل سلبي أي يعني كيف تحقق دخل شهري بدون مجهود منك وبدون أي تعب وبدون أي شروطخطوات بسيطة تفعلها مرة وحده وبتحقق مصدر دخل ممكن يغنيك عن قيود الوظيفة أو ببساطة تكون مصدر دخل ثانوي لكـ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ـما بيلزمك أي خبرة سابقة بأي شيء قبل ما توخذ الدورة لأن الدورة مشروح فيها بالتفصيل أساسيات وطريقة العمل والموضوع كثير سهلـ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ــ ـ ـوالأهم من هيك مش شرط يكون معك رأس مال مشان تستثمر أموالك  !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Analytics: Customer Value and Promotion Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/marketing-analytics-customer-value-and-promotion-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/marketing-analytics-customer-value-and-promotion-strategy/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re looking for a complete course that will teach you how to calculate customer value to drive business decisions involving product pricing, acquisition cost, marketing cost, and many other parts of the business., right?
You&#39;ve found the right course Customer Valuation for Entrepreneurs and Marketers! This course teaches you everything you need to know about different methods to find customer lifetime value and how to find it in Excel using advanced excel tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unlimited Free Traffic Generation Course: Master Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/unlimited-free-traffic-generation-course-master-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/unlimited-free-traffic-generation-course-master-edition/</guid>
      <description>A grand welcome to you for choosing to learn &#34;Unlimited Free Traffic Generation Course: Master Edition&#34;.
Organic search traffic from Google and other search engines are some of the most high-converting traffic you can get. It is considered superior to banner advertisements or social media marketing, nevertheless, it takes a lot of time for the ranking factor to come in handy for the same. The search engines also keep on changing their algorithms very frequently and hence the going gets tough for digital marketers and growth hackers like you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/google-analytics-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 13:08:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/google-analytics-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>This course will teach Google Analytics from scratch. Here is the overview of what you are going to learn,
Setup Google Analytics Account
Installing Tracking Code on your website
Configure Marketing Goals
Setup Filters
UTM Parameters
Generating Reports ( Audience, Real-time, Acquisition, etc. )
Who this course is for:
Bloggers
Webmasters
Online Business Owners
Marketing Professionals
Intermediate level Digital Marketers
Beginners in Web Analytics
College Students
 Ratings: 4.39/5
Enrollments: 41912</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagram Business Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/instagram-business-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:42:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/instagram-business-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>You probably have wondered how short videos and images can be used to promote business awareness through Instagram in a bid to enhance customer experience.
It is simple. Instagram can be used to promote your business online through a number of ingenious ways that have been developed over time.
With this course you will discover a list of strategies, tools and practices that can assist you building your Instagram business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMMP Exam: Marketing Management --&gt; Practice Test 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cmmp-exam-marketing-management-practice-test-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cmmp-exam-marketing-management-practice-test-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Interview in Marketing Management ? 
Don’t be stressed, Take our Marketing Management Based Mock Test and prepare yourself for the Exam. Here you will get Marketing Management based Multiple Choice Question for your Next Exam.
What you will get in These Mock Test ? 
It contains sample questions which are likely to be asked in the Exam.
These Marketing Management based MCQ questions help you with self-study and self-assessment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing B2B: Ultimate B2B Digital Marketing Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-marketing-b2b-ultimate-b2b-digital-marketing-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-marketing-b2b-ultimate-b2b-digital-marketing-course/</guid>
      <description>ATTENTION B2B DIGITAL MARKETING STUDENTS: Learn the strategies and nitty-gritty tactical details of acquiring business customers cheaply and quickly through digital marketing and modern social media marketing. Get executive-level training from a former VP of Marketing and college instructor with Fortune 100 experience--at a fraction of the cost of an executive digital marketing training courses!This is the ultimate course on B2B digital marketing. I was a global marketing manager for Sony and a Vice President of Marketing for a Google accelerator startup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing Agency Elite Consultants Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-marketing-agency-elite-consultants-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:15:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-marketing-agency-elite-consultants-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>LEARN HOW YOU CAN GROW A SUCCESSFUL​ MARKETING AGENCY... in as little as 30 days or less as Juan pulls back the curtain on how you can get paid high monthly retainers and even if you have no prior marketing experience.
I&#39;ve done the painful leg work so that you don&#39;t have to. When I first started, I struggled to get clients because I had no confidence. I was unsure how to get results or even how to sell and close clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Online Marketing &amp; Advertising Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-online-marketing-advertising-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-online-marketing-advertising-course/</guid>
      <description>In This Online Course You Will Learn The RIGHT Way To Do Online Marketing &amp;amp; Advertising. This Course Covers ALL The Major Online Advertising Methods … Giving You Step-By-Step Instructions And A Great Overview Of Online Advertising.
Learning These Key Skills &amp;amp; Techniques Can Help You Be Massively Successful As You Do Online Marketing &amp;amp; Advertising. Once You Can Master Online Marketing &amp;amp; Advertising … Your Income Potential Is Limitless!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEST of SEO: #1 SEO Training &amp; Content Marketing Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/best-of-seo-#1-seo-training-content-marketing-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/best-of-seo-#1-seo-training-content-marketing-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>In our increasingly online world, if you want to be successful, you need the latest digital skills. In this SEO &amp;amp; CONTENT MARKETING MASTERY course, I bring you CONSTANTLY UPDATED CUTTING-EDGE STRATEGIES AND TECHNIQUES so you can THRIVE in Content Marketing and SEO. This is my brand new 2021 SEO Training and Content Marketing Course! Now UPDATED to include many more topics to give you EVEN MORE VALUE and ensure your and SEO Success, with input from multiple experts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AD’s Hacker 1.0: Growth Hacking Certification for Marketers</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ads-hacker-1.0-growth-hacking-certification-for-marketers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ads-hacker-1.0-growth-hacking-certification-for-marketers/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the third course in Term 2 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Time to set the advertising industry on fire with AD&#39;s Hacker 1.0 !!!
There is no denying that we have changed the way we work on the World Wide Web and the Internet. For presents or gifts, we no longer visit the city centre– we’re going to an eCommerce marketplace like Amazon and getting it shipped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Branding: Personal Brand Building | Fame &amp; Success!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/personal-branding-personal-brand-building-fame-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/personal-branding-personal-brand-building-fame-success/</guid>
      <description>This is the definitive course on personal branding. My name is Dekker Fraser and I was a Global Brand Manager for Sony PlayStation. I have over 100,000 students on Udemy and I was a VP of Marketing for a Google accelerator startup. I was a college marketing instructor, and I studied brand management at the #1 business school for marketing. This is where the father of marketing himself, Philip Kotler, teaches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced LinkedIn Advertising: LinkedIn Ads Advanced B2B</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/advanced-linkedin-advertising-linkedin-ads-advanced-b2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/advanced-linkedin-advertising-linkedin-ads-advanced-b2b/</guid>
      <description>This B2B LinkedIn advertising course builds on my previous one by showing you how to build more scalable full-funnel campaigns, instead of just focusing on the low-hanging fruit when it comes to lead generation. You will learn how to build an efficient lead generation campaign with the appropriate content. Learn from someone who has been doing LinkedIn advertising since 2011, has worked for companies of varying sizes (including the Fortune 100), and has a top-tier marketing MBA from Philip Kotler&#39;s school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon PPC Masterclass - The Ultimate PPC Guide</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/amazon-ppc-masterclass-the-ultimate-ppc-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/amazon-ppc-masterclass-the-ultimate-ppc-guide/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling with Amazon&#39;s Sponsored Products ads but don&#39;t know where to start? Do your existing PPC campaigns get high aCos and/or low sales volume?&amp;nbsp; Then this course is designed for you!

I will show you the biggest mistakes I see when using Amazon&#39;s Sponsored Products and teach you how to properly set up and optimise and create your campaigns. 

After years of testing and spending literally tens of thousands of dollars I&#39;ve discovered highly profitable Amazon PPC campaigns that have gone on to generate tens of thousands of dollars in sales and PROFIT.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App Marketing: Mobile App Marketing &amp; Growth Hacking</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/app-marketing-mobile-app-marketing-growth-hacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/app-marketing-mobile-app-marketing-growth-hacking/</guid>
      <description>This is the definitive course on app marketing to help with your go-to-market app launch. Please note that this is NOT just a course on app store optimization (ASO). This is a more comprehensive course on marketing your app in the market for maximum impact.
I led the mobile app marketing for a Google venture-backed startup (Series E) in Silicon Valley. In just four months, I increased downloads by 71% and mobile app revenue by 89%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence in SEO (2021 Extreme Edition)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/artificial-intelligence-in-seo-2021-extreme-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/artificial-intelligence-in-seo-2021-extreme-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the ninth course in Term 1 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Looking for the word called &#34;Popularity&#34; to come to life? It&#39;s good to be heard, of course, and everything, but is that really the point? To be able to applaud and say, yeah... I had 1,000,000 visits last year to my website... that may be amazing, but why is website traffic important to your business or any business, for that matter?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become a Product Marketing Manager | Product Management</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/become-a-product-marketing-manager-product-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/become-a-product-marketing-manager-product-management/</guid>
      <description>Learn from an experienced Silicon Valley PMM with a top MBA
Learn how to become a product marketing manager from&amp;nbsp;someone with years of&amp;nbsp;experience in product marketing at small, medium, and large software companies including Sony.&amp;nbsp;Your lead instructor received his MBA from the top marketing school in the U.S. and works in the epicenter of product&amp;nbsp;marketing in San Francisco.&amp;nbsp;
New! Free access to the top-rated book Become a Product Marketing Manager (PDF version)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Creation &amp; Content Writing for B2B Content Marketing</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/content-creation-content-writing-for-b2b-content-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/content-creation-content-writing-for-b2b-content-marketing/</guid>
      <description>ATTENTION business-to-business writers and marketers!
Do you want to learn how to develop world-class B2B content from a former VP of Marketing with Fortune 100 experience, a top-tier MBA, and college-level teaching experience? Do you want to take your content writing and content creation to the next level? This is the course for you. This course goes into the details of B2B content writing &amp;amp; content creation using case studies and real-world examples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversion Rate Optimization CRO: B2B Conversion Rate CRO</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/conversion-rate-optimization-cro-b2b-conversion-rate-cro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/conversion-rate-optimization-cro-b2b-conversion-rate-cro/</guid>
      <description>Learn B2B (business-to-business) conversation rate optimization (conversion rate optimisation / CRO) to maximize leads and paying customers. Optimize the entire growth marketing funnel using tactical and strategic conversion maximization approaches from a top MBA with Fortune 100 experience and master&#39;s level analytics training. -&amp;gt; Real examples from my own experience in driving growth for companies of various sizes including Sony and a Google-accelerator startup
-&amp;gt; Advice from my colleagues who drove growth for top companies including LinkedIn and Sephora</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing Agency: Grow Your Digital Marketing Agency</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-marketing-agency-grow-your-digital-marketing-agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-marketing-agency-grow-your-digital-marketing-agency/</guid>
      <description>This is the ultimate course on growing your digital marketing agency &amp;amp; getting more clients. I worked for a digital marketing agency for 5 years. I also worked as an independent consultant. As a global marketing manager for Sony, I worked with some of the top marketing agencies in the world including Digitas, Mediacom, and Publicis. I taught college level digital marketing and I have an MBA from the top business school for marketing--the Kellogg School of Management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Gain More Customers With Video Marketing</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-gain-more-customers-with-video-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-gain-more-customers-with-video-marketing/</guid>
      <description>In recent years, we can see the emergence of many websites on the Internet and even more intense competition between these sites. Everyone is trying to make their website better and more attractive than the competitor&#39;s, but still, everyone uses the same methods and tools to promote their business.
But many people forget about another very effective method, like video marketing, in which video is the main tool for promoting a business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Money Online With Digital Product Launch</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/make-money-online-with-digital-product-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/make-money-online-with-digital-product-launch/</guid>
      <description>take this 9 Days Journey with me to create, craft and launch your digital course product and program. start selling Instantly.

Do you want to overcome your all financial problems? and start your business online?
Have you always sought to create and launch a digital product but stuck with the process?
Are you having a hard time doing it as it requires a huge Investment, Time and Energy?
Would you prefer a better, Simpler, Easier and Faster way to launch your digital product or program?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Launch: How to Go to Market Product Marketing Plan</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/product-launch-how-to-go-to-market-product-marketing-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/product-launch-how-to-go-to-market-product-marketing-plan/</guid>
      <description>Create a breakthrough go-to-market product marketing plan in just a few days ... using this 7-step formula!
“Going to market is just the process of convincing people that your new way is better than the status quo.”
In 3,2,1…product launch, Dekker Fraser and Spencer Grover offer marketing professionals and entrepreneurs proven and cutting-edge guidance for launching new products and getting ready to go-to-market, employing the latest marketing tactics emerging from Silicon Valley and the foundational thinking from top business schools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Marketing B2B: Proven Social Media Marketing</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/social-media-marketing-b2b-proven-social-media-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/social-media-marketing-b2b-proven-social-media-marketing/</guid>
      <description>This is the ultimate course on business-to-business social media marketing. I’ve been doing B2B marketing on social media platforms like LinkedIn and Facebook for over a decade. I was a Vice President of Marketing for a Google accelerator startup, and I was a Global Marketing Manager for Sony. I also held numerous positions helping small startups with their social media marketing.
I taught college-level digital marketing, and I studied digital marketing and B2B marketing at the Kellogg School of Management, the #1-ranked business school for marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storytelling Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/storytelling-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/storytelling-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Story telling can be a powerful component in a marketing strategy. It can be the driving force behind developing, and more importantly, establishing a brand that connects and resonates with your target audience.
It’s also the easiest way to express emotions and illustrate your commitment to providing value.
There’s nothing more powerful than a carefully crafted story that fulfills the needs of your core market.
In this special course, you will learn top story-telling methods, how to best use these strategies and how you can use storytelling to strengthen your brand or launch a new one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Driving Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/traffic-driving-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/traffic-driving-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>You’ve likely heard about the power of viral sharing. When enough people share content and it goes viral, the traffic is virtually unstoppable.
And it’s targeted, FREE traffic!
When you inject viral sharing into your sales copy or funnel, you’ll immediately maximize exposure with very little work involved. Instead of spending hours setting up traffic campaigns and ads on social media networks, you motivate your visitors into doing all the work for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Marketing 2021: Strategies and Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/youtube-marketing-2021-strategies-and-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/youtube-marketing-2021-strategies-and-growth/</guid>
      <description>When you take this course, we will start you from an idea that you want to do YouTube video marketing and we will end with you crafting a professional YouTube channel as well as a strategy for how you will use it.&amp;nbsp;
Boomy and Lara are both internet marketing professionals committed to helping guide you with videos demonstrating the best and the worst in YouTube. We wanted this to be a course that you could watch while you work on your own channel, so it may take longer then the hour of video content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Content Marketing Quiz (2021 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-ultimate-content-marketing-quiz-2021-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-ultimate-content-marketing-quiz-2021-edition/</guid>
      <description>Content is truly termed as &#34;The King&#34;.
&#39;Content marketers always say that with our clients we want to build close, trusting relationships&#39;. But how many of our respected personal relationships are marked by a lack of feeling? The best way to create those genuinely meaningful relationships we all want to have with our clients is to concentrate on making stories more personally resonant, situationally important, and emotionally intelligent. Greater empathy is the real key to every goal - we have (as content marketers, and as people).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Search Engine Optimization (SEO) Quiz 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-ultimate-search-engine-optimization-seo-quiz-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-ultimate-search-engine-optimization-seo-quiz-2021/</guid>
      <description>We all know that search engine optimization (SEO) is the art and science of getting pages to rank higher in search engines like Google,&amp;nbsp;Bing,&amp;nbsp;Duckduckgo etc. Since search is one of the main ways people discover online content, ranking higher in search engines can lead to an increase in website traffic. SEO has two key objectives. The first is to help you understand what online users are looking for - so that you can create high-quality content to serve their purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
