<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music Fundamentals on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/music-fundamentals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music Fundamentals on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/music-fundamentals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Basic Theory for Guitar</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/basic-theory-for-guitar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/basic-theory-for-guitar/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to your Music Theory for Guitarists Course!
Hi there! I&#39;m Jack, and I have been teaching music for many many years, and in all of that time, the main thing I have noticed that holds students back, whether they have played for months or for decades, is a lack of an understanding of the basics of music theory. So I&amp;nbsp;have created this course to address that issue so that students will have their fundamentals down and will therefore be able to continually improve without limit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blues &amp; Rock Theory for Guitar</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/blues-rock-theory-for-guitar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/blues-rock-theory-for-guitar/</guid>
      <description>Now that we have worked our way through the basics of diatonic theory in our last course, that is to say, understanding major and minor scales and their harmonies, we’re ready to look at some styles that have strayed away from that system.
The most important influence on all the styles of popular music that break away from traditional European music, is Blues music- it doesn’t have to be your favorite thing to play or listen to, but whether you know it or not, there’s hardly a popular style in existence that doesn’t draw from it in some way or another.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
