<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Finance &amp; Accounting on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/finance-accounting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Finance &amp; Accounting on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/finance-accounting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chargeback Reason Codes in Card Payments</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/chargeback-reason-codes-in-card-payments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/chargeback-reason-codes-in-card-payments/</guid>
      <description>THE CHARGEBACK WAY OF LIFE
You may know that a merchant (or their bank, the acquirer/merchant bank), chargebacks are a nightmare.
In short, a credit card owner claims they should obtain their money back due to something that went wrong in a transaction.
Fraud, disputes over the goods, authorization errors, and many other types come in here.
Chargebacks represent difficult obstacles for both acquiring and issuing bank.
Each chargeback is usually represent by something called the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Trade Forex Market Structures And Patterns</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-trade-forex-market-structures-and-patterns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-trade-forex-market-structures-and-patterns/</guid>
      <description>Discover the secrets to trading profitably and consistently for maximum profits. This course contains powerful information that can guide you on how to exploit patterns that arise now and then in the markets. Discover when and where to trade, and when and where not to trade.
Thank you for joining our course because you are about to gain more knowledge about the formation of classic forex chart patterns and structures. It is true that they are valid and do indeed work; provided that they are used properly, at the appropriate price levels, and with the correct knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Forex- learn to trade forex by yourself</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-forex-learn-to-trade-forex-by-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-forex-learn-to-trade-forex-by-yourself/</guid>
      <description>The financial markets are not very easy to handle and to trade. The Forex market is the biggest of those with more than 2 trillion dollars exchanged on a daily basis. But, there is a way to make profit out of all those transaction with forex trading and this is the goal of this course. Indeed, if you :
- Are someone who is interested in forex trading but never actually started</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Money Laundering Concepts: AML, KYC and Compliance</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/anti-money-laundering-concepts-aml-kyc-and-compliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/anti-money-laundering-concepts-aml-kyc-and-compliance/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the course on Anti-Money Laundering (AML), where you will learn about the key issues faced by financial institutions today: Money Laundering and Terrorist Financing. This course will educate you on Money Laundering and Terrorist Financing laws, Know Your Customer, Customer Due Diligence, Economic Sanctions and Politically Exposed Persons. This is a comprehensive course that captures all relevant concepts required for training employees of an organization.
We will start the course by understanding the term Money Laundering and will then cover the process &amp;amp; impact of the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GST Returns 2021 Course (Live Working) : Get Certified Today</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/gst-returns-2021-course-live-working-get-certified-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/gst-returns-2021-course-live-working-get-certified-today/</guid>
      <description>Aim &amp;amp; Future Prospects:
The aim of the course is to help individuals, businessman, accountants, CAs and other professionals to upgrade their knowledge regarding the Goods and Services Tax by offering most of the real time practical knowledge on GST Portal in an updated and systematic approach that help them to accelerate their skills and knowledge required for self-employment &amp;amp; employment at industrial level as well.
Benefits of the course:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bookkeeping &amp; Accounting Masterclass - Beginner to Advanced</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/bookkeeping-accounting-masterclass-beginner-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/bookkeeping-accounting-masterclass-beginner-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>The course starts right from scratch, introduces the concept of Accounting, fundamental accounting terms, the accounting system of recording business transactions. Then it takes you to more complex areas of accounting like transactions affected by discounts and sales tax, prepaid and accrued transactions, and accounting adjustments like depreciation. Topics Covered:
Introduction to Accounting
Why Accounting has to follow rules and what are the accounting standards?
What are the different types of Accounting and what information is produced by each?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOREX TRADING NOMAD | HOW TO GET FUNDED BY INVESTORS IN 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/forex-trading-nomad-how-to-get-funded-by-investors-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/forex-trading-nomad-how-to-get-funded-by-investors-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>Investors are keen to meet you. The problem is that you may not have anything to offer them yet. This course takes you by the hand and teaches you one strategy that will help you make it in the world of trading or I&#39;ll give you your money back. Then your newly gained knowledge is put to the tests. Once you have successfully passed the tests, you are introduced to the investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of Fraud Prevention and Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-fraud-prevention-and-monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-fraud-prevention-and-monitoring/</guid>
      <description>WHY FRAUD PREVENTION?
Understanding how fraud is committed - and especially how it&#39;s prevented - is not easy.
There are countless techniques to take into account. Perpetrators can be of different types and use different approaches.
For anyone aiming to know more about fraud prevention - whether as a fraud monitoring professional, a payments professional, or any other type of professional that wants to master the theory and practice of fraud prevention, finding the right information is crucial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of Hedge Funds</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-hedge-funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-hedge-funds/</guid>
      <description>WHY HEDGE FUNDS?
Hedge funds are one of the most profitable types of alternative assets.
However, they are not easy to comprehend.
Fund structures, investment strategies, provisions and fees, and other elements.
And unfortunately, it&#39;s hard to find a course that covers the essentials of hedge funds.
So it becomes common for a student to:
Not be able to discern among the different investment strategies;
Not know if the provisions negotiated with an investor are helpful to the fund, or not at all;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Finance Fundamentals | Infrastructure &amp; Energy</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/project-finance-fundamentals-infrastructure-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/project-finance-fundamentals-infrastructure-energy/</guid>
      <description>Whether you are a fresh graduate or looking for a shift in your career, whether you are coming from an engineering, finance, or law background; delving into the world of Infrastructure Project finance &amp;amp; PPPs might be challenging. The problem begins at the interview stage: The lack of technical knowledge and basic skills could hurt your chances to land your dream job and break into the sector.
We have been there, too, and we completely understand your frustration!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Passive Income With Bitcoin Lending</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-make-passive-income-with-bitcoin-lending/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 10:00:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-make-passive-income-with-bitcoin-lending/</guid>
      <description>Passive Income Course Covering Everything You Need To Passively Earn Money From Bitcoin Lending!
******************************************************************************************
Discover How to Make Passive Income Online Using A 6-Step Bitcoin Lending System:
- A step-by-step video for each of the 6-Steps in the Automated System!
- Inside look at my personal accounts!
- Unlimited earnings, with a small upfront investment!
- How to do all of this without any Fees!
- This course is about results!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Altcoin Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/altcoin-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/altcoin-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve not tried using Altcoins and invest the next generation currency, then today is the time to start!

Never before has there been an technology platform of this magnitude that will allow you to reach an audience of billions and rapidly grow your business online at next to zero cost!

Become The Ultimate Altcoins Master and join this course today to learn the same PROVEN success strategy Henry Zhang , the Crypto Currency expert and world-leading trader used to build this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capital Market Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/capital-market-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/capital-market-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Capital Market Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn fundamental knowledge about capital markets that would help you in finding value within the market to maximize your earning potential.

I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on the different aspects of the capital market as well as basic analysis on the market to analyze value of investment instruments as well as noticing important trends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Financial Accounting Course in Urdu / Hindi</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/basic-financial-accounting-course-in-urdu-/-hindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/basic-financial-accounting-course-in-urdu-/-hindi/</guid>
      <description>Updated: 24/7/2019 (Ledger &amp;amp; Trial Balance)
Basic Financial Accounting Course Outline:
1. Basic Accounting Course Urdu/Hindi 2. Introduction to Basic Accounting Course
3. What you will learn in this course? 4. Importance of accounting 5. Types of transactions in accounting 6. What is Debtor and creditor? 7. What is the Accounting Equation?
8. How to record the business transaction in the accounting equation?
9. What is Double Entry system in Accounting?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Accounting-Depreciation Calculation &amp; Fixed Assets</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/financial-accounting-depreciation-calculation-fixed-assets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/financial-accounting-depreciation-calculation-fixed-assets/</guid>
      <description>Property plant and equipment, also known as plant assets, fixed assets, or depreciable assets is what we will cover.
We will discuss what property plant and equipment is and how to record property plant and equipment.  Multiple depreciation methods will be covered including the straight-line depreciation method, the double declining depreciation method, and the units of production depreciation method. We will discuss the pros and cons of each depreciation method and outline a format for structuring any deprecation problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Enterprise 2020- Two Businesses &amp; Personal in One</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-enterprise-2020-two-businesses-personal-in-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-enterprise-2020-two-businesses-personal-in-one/</guid>
      <description>This is a project-based course that will use the free trial version of QuickBooks Enterprise to track multiple business financial data as well as personal financial data in one QuickBooks Enterprise file. We will learn to generate and analyze both the balance sheet and income statement reports by class.
We will learn the difference between the QuickBooks Enterprise class tracking feature and the QuickBooks Pro class tracking feature.
The course will show how to turn on the class tracking feature in QuickBooks Enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn 27 Ways to Make Money Online with Your Smartphone!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-27-ways-to-make-money-online-with-your-smartphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 09:38:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-27-ways-to-make-money-online-with-your-smartphone/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to make money online with your smartphone? 
Do you wanna see real money-making apps that pay in 2021?
Then this course is PERFECT FOR YOU!
I created this course because every single day people ask me for the best way to get paid just by using their smartphones.
Learn just 1 strategy and you&#39;ll earn your course price back. The rest will be pure profits for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Advance Options Trading Strategies (5 Courses) 11 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/diy-advance-options-trading-strategies-5-courses-11-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:35:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/diy-advance-options-trading-strategies-5-courses-11-hours/</guid>
      <description>*** Course access includes quizzes &amp;amp; homework exercises, 1-on-1 Options Trading instructor support and LIFETIME access! ***
Hear why this is one of the TOP-NOTCH Options Trading course on Udemy:
I believe it is a good value for the money. He offers a lot of information and is willing to help.
-Dwight Douglas
The Author of this course explains in great detail what is important to become a successful options trader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aplos Not for Profit Accounting Software</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aplos-not-for-profit-accounting-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aplos-not-for-profit-accounting-software/</guid>
      <description>Learners will understand how to set up Aplos, software specifically designed for Not for Profit Organizations.
The course will show how to use free resources to optimize learning.
We will demonstrate the use of funds and tags to generate Not for Profit reports.
The course will demonstrate how to enter and track restricted resources.
We will enter month end adjusting entries.
Learners will see how to allocate expenses to programs and administrative categories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of Private Equity</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-private-equity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-private-equity/</guid>
      <description>PRIVATE EQUITY, PRIVATE KNOWLEDGE
The PE industry is one of the most lucrative ones.
It&#39;s also complex to understand, if you don&#39;t have the right guide.
A lot of techniques, knowledge and hands-on tips are not usually shared.
Usually, what would find would be generic courses with theoretical materials in terms of valuations or general job descriptions, not going into the details of fund operations, the job, or other elements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Online Multiple Currencies</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-online-multiple-currencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-online-multiple-currencies/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to get access to QuickBooks Online including a possible free 30-day trial version often offered by Intuit, the owner of QuickBooks Online.
The course will discuss accounting for multiple currencies, outlining the process in Excel to provide a more transparent look at the process. Then we will enter the transactions into QuickBooks, the software automating some of the steps required.
We will learn how to turn multicurrency on, and which accounts will be affected most by multicurrency transactions including cash account types, accounts receivable account types, and accounts payable account types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xero Not for Profit Organization</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/xero-not-for-profit-organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/xero-not-for-profit-organization/</guid>
      <description>Learners will understand how to set up Xero for a Not for Profit Organization.
The course will show how to use free resources to optimize learning.
We will demonstrate the use of category tracking to generate Not for Profit reports.
Learners will see how to create and use donation receipt forms.
We will show how to create and use pledge receipt forms.
The course will demonstrate how to enter and track restricted resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance/</guid>
      <description>We will learn how to read financial statements and how to use them for decision making.
A primary tool we will use is ratio analysis. Ratio analysis is a very useful skill in a wide area of topics, and financial analysis is a great place to learn the skill.
Ratios are necessary when measuring performance, including most any job performance. For example, we must apply ratio analysis when measuring the job performance of sports athletes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/personal-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/personal-finance/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover personal finance concepts, starting from the basics, and moving to complex topics. We will cover each step thoroughly.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop – Export Directly to Tax Software Lacerte</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-desktop-export-directly-to-tax-software-lacerte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-desktop-export-directly-to-tax-software-lacerte/</guid>
      <description>The course will discuss options for getting access to QuickBooks desktop software including a free 30-day test period offered by Intuit, the owners of QuickBooks Desktop.
Learners will know how to set up tax line mapping for a sole proprietorship and S Corporation, tax line mapping allowing users to export financial data from QuickBooks directly into tax software.
We will be using Lacerte tax software for our examples. Lacerte tax software is owned by Intuit and a 30-day free trial may be available to test out Lacerte tax software as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin For Beginners: How To Earn Bitcoin Online For Free</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/bitcoin-for-beginners-how-to-earn-bitcoin-online-for-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 11:17:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/bitcoin-for-beginners-how-to-earn-bitcoin-online-for-free/</guid>
      <description>This is a course that the Government doesn&#39;t want you to see! Bitcoin is the BEST-PERFORMING asset of the decade.
It&#39;s not a coincidence that Bitcoin has been growing over 200%/year on average!
Every smart person has already realized that Bitcoin is clearly superior compared to government money (=USD, EUR, PHP, INR, etc.)
That&#39;s why Bitcoin grows rapidly.
Smart people are trying to accumulate as much Bitcoin as possible before the rest of the population gets educated about the benefits of Bitcoin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop Multiple Currencies</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-desktop-multiple-currencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 10:06:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-desktop-multiple-currencies/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to get access to QuickBooks Desktop including a possible free 30-day trial version often offered by Intuit, the owner of QuickBooks Desktop.
The course will discuss accounting for multiple currencies, outlining the process in Excel to provide a more transparent look at the process. Then we will enter the transactions into QuickBooks, the software automating some of the steps required.
We will learn how to turn multicurrency on, and which accounts will be affected most by multicurrency transactions including cash account types, accounts receivable account types, and accounts payable account types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop vs QBO Multiple Currencies</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-desktop-vs-qbo-multiple-currencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 10:06:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-desktop-vs-qbo-multiple-currencies/</guid>
      <description>The course will start by discussing how to get access to both QuickBooks Online and QuickBooks Desktop. Intuit, the owner of QuickBooks often offers a free 30-day trial for each software package. This will be a project based course. We will enter transaction in Excel before entering them into the accounting software, QuickBooks desktop and QuickBooks Online. Excel is more transparent, making it easier to understand the process. QuickBooks will then automate the process making it more efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Inventory Management in Microsoft Excel &amp;TALLY ERP9</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-inventory-management-in-microsoft-excel-tally-erp9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-inventory-management-in-microsoft-excel-tally-erp9/</guid>
      <description>Recent Student&#39;s Reviews

*** This course is well detailed in inventory management. I really learnt how to make practical use of excel, tally ERP9 and good inventory valuation (Williams Oguamah) ***

**Yes it is a good match for me. It will help me in my career path ( Dineo ) ***

*** it was awesome to learn &amp;amp; get insights from this course (Haritha.L) ***

*** Very Helpful (JULIUS IGNACIO)***</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Out of Debt and on Budget for Your Future</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-get-out-of-debt-and-on-budget-for-your-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-get-out-of-debt-and-on-budget-for-your-future/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you will learn how to get yourself out of debt so you can build your credit score and get onto a healthy budget. Getting your personal finances under control can be intimidating and daunting if you don’t know what to do to get ahead. My goal is to give you the opportunity to learn what I learned the hard way. When I was in debt, I never thought I would get out, but I tried different things and got my finances under control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank Feeds-QuickBooks Online, Xero, Sage, Wave (Comparison)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/bank-feeds-quickbooks-online-xero-sage-wave-comparison/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/bank-feeds-quickbooks-online-xero-sage-wave-comparison/</guid>
      <description>Bank Feed Options
This course will compare and contrast the top accounting software applications, focusing on the use of bank feeds.
We will provide practice data that learners can import into the software applications.
Learners will understand the process of setting up each online software package. We will also discuss purchase options.
Most of the software applications will include a free test drive, an excellent tool for learning accounting and bank feeds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C Corporation Income Tax (Form 1120)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/c-corporation-income-tax-form-1120/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/c-corporation-income-tax-form-1120/</guid>
      <description>This course currently consists of a comprehensive problem showing the data input process of a C Corporation into tax Form 1120.
This course will put together a systematic format of entering data into a Form 1120 that will minimize errors, isolate problems as they happen, and remove the possibility of having to start the process all over again.
We will enter each M-1 adjustment individually into both the tax return and an Excel worksheet so that we fully understand how M-1 adjustments function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managerial Accounting / Cost Accounting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/managerial-accounting-/-cost-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/managerial-accounting-/-cost-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Comprehensive managerial and cost accounting course. Topics include:
· Job order costing
· Process costing
· Cost volume profit analysis
· Master Budgets
· Flexible Budgets
· Responsibility accounting
· Relevant costs
· Time value of money
This course will go into detail about each topic. We will include”
· Practice Excel files with both an answer tab and a practice tab
· Lecture PDF files that can be downloaded and reviewed without internet access</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process Costing System-Cost Accounting-Managerial Accounting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/process-costing-system-cost-accounting-managerial-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/process-costing-system-cost-accounting-managerial-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Process costing system – Cost Accounting – Managerial Accounting
We will start by introducing managerial accounting or cost accounting topics that apply to companies that manufacture using either a job cost system or a process cost system.
The course will describe classifications for costs and the importance of being able to classify costs in different ways.
We will list and describe an outline of the process costs go through as they flow through the accounting process in a manufacturing company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate TallyPrime With GST Step By Step Guide - 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ultimate-tallyprime-with-gst-step-by-step-guide-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ultimate-tallyprime-with-gst-step-by-step-guide-2021/</guid>
      <description>Recent Student&#39;s Reviews

***Clearly understand what is tally prime in this full lecture.Thank you so much sir.(Rizwan Mohamed Y)***

***Covers every chapter, step by step learning for everyone (Vivekanandan Jayakumar)***

*** 1. Short and crisp to the point and no beating around the bush.
2. Very clear explanation with relevant examples
Course updated to the latest version
3. Those who are well aware of accounting concepts and manual accounting, may choose to skip section 2&amp;amp;3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Trading Momentum Based Strategies1- Technical Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/stock-trading-momentum-based-strategies1-technical-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 21:16:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/stock-trading-momentum-based-strategies1-technical-analysis/</guid>
      <description>In this course we will discuss multiple momentum oscillator, which measures both the speed as well as the rise or fall of price movements of a stocks.
Relative Strength Index (or RSI), Stoch, William %R, TSI &amp;amp; MFL are one of the top Technical Analysis Indicator. In this Course these technical indicators are not only shown as merely a indicator but a Complete System for trading.
RSI, Stoch, William %R, TSI &amp;amp; MFL is used by professional to identify the trend, Selling or Buying conditions through Reversal, divergences or simple Buy and sell techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data science for algorithmic trading</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/data-science-for-algorithmic-trading/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/data-science-for-algorithmic-trading/</guid>
      <description>It is with pride that I offer this data science course for algorithmic trading. It is the fruit of several years of work in the field to truly understand all the subtleties of the world of quantitative finance.

Using libraries will allow you to do complex mathematical calculations applied to finance in just a few lines of code. We will see how to create an algorithm for trading from data import to automatic positions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Finance</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-finance/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Introduction to Finance Course by TSI! This is a course that is designed for complete beginners— no experience is required. If you are interested in finance, then you have come to the right place. We start off by introducing finance as well as clearing up a lot of the common misconceptions people have regarding the field. We then cover money and inflation. Then we cover loans and interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Governmental Accounting 200 Capital Projects &amp; Debt Service</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/governmental-accounting-200-capital-projects-debt-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/governmental-accounting-200-capital-projects-debt-service/</guid>
      <description>The course will focus on larger capital projects and the use of a capital project fund and debt service fund to track them.
We will cover governmental accounting objective, which will be a review from governmental accounting 100.
The course will discuss what capital assets are and how they are recorded in governmental accounting, comparing governmental accounting to for-profit accounting.
Students will learn to record transactions for the issuance of bonds used to finance capital projects, recording transactions at the government-wide level and in the capital project fund, debts service fund, and general fund.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partnership Income Tax (Form 1065)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/partnership-income-tax-form-1065/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/partnership-income-tax-form-1065/</guid>
      <description>This course currently consists of a comprehensive problem showing the data input process of a Partnership into tax Form 1065.
This course will put together a systematic format of entering data into a Form 1065 that will minimize errors, isolate problems as they happen, and remove the possibility of having to start the process all over again.
We will enter each M-1 adjustment individually into both the tax return and an Excel worksheet so that we fully understand how they work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accounting–Financial Accounting Total-Beginners to Advanced</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/accountingfinancial-accounting-total-beginners-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:43:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/accountingfinancial-accounting-total-beginners-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Recently updated with A LOT of added content.
Includes downloadable e-book in multiple formats so you can open it on your tablet or Kindle - Formats (EPUB, MOBI, PDF).
This course is an excellent supplement for students or anybody who wants to learn accounting and also have something they can refer back to in the future. Udemy generally provides lifetime access to the course.
Many accounting students do not receive a physical book, they get to keep from their school, and even if they did, the information could become dated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrencies: complet practical course on crypto trading</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cryptocurrencies-complet-practical-course-on-crypto-trading/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cryptocurrencies-complet-practical-course-on-crypto-trading/</guid>
      <description>Have you witnessed all the profits that have been made by the various cryptocurrencies without knowing how to profit from them? Reassure yourself, it will not happen to you anymore. this course was created in order to allow everyone to know how it is possible to integrate the market of cryptocurrencies and it is accessible to all! At the end of the course, you will not only be able to buy your first cryptocurrency but you will also have a good base on how to trade or invest in this market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audit - Financial Statement</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/audit-financial-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/audit-financial-statement/</guid>
      <description>Audit-Financial Accounting will discuss, in detail, the auditing process of financial statements.
The course will start by discussing what an audit is, as well as what the terms attest engagement and assurances services mean.
We will discuss the audit environment, the general format of a public accounting firm, and the general format of an audit team that would conduct the procedures related to an audit. The course will also discuss regulations and regulatory institutions related to the audit process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Options Trading MasterClass: Options Trading In Simple Terms</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/options-trading-masterclass-options-trading-in-simple-terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/options-trading-masterclass-options-trading-in-simple-terms/</guid>
      <description>In this Options Trading course, President of Capstone Financial &amp;amp; Author of &#34;Options Trading Strategies for Monthly Income&#34; David J. Melilli will educate you on every aspect of options trading. David will implement his unique options trading process utilizing his extensive knowledge in the area of options trading. David has spent over fifteen years in the options trading arena. This options trading course is taught in an easy to understand, user friendly manner that will excite and help build the confidence to master options trading and it has been designed to educate and enhance every individual that wants to really develop the skills required in the world of options trading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relevant Costs - Managerial Accounting Decisions &amp; Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/relevant-costs-managerial-accounting-decisions-scenarios/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/relevant-costs-managerial-accounting-decisions-scenarios/</guid>
      <description>Apply relevant cost methods to common managerial decisions.
Managers often need to make decisions that are not routine, not part of the normal day to day process, and that can have a long-term effect on the organization. Individuals often need to make similar decisions and can apply similar tools when making decisions of a large dollar amount that can affect multiple years.
Although the specifics of each decision differ, the concept of relevant costs helps us put together a process for gathering and analyzing data, picking up the information that matters, and removing all the excess data that does not matter to our decision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tally Erp 9 &#43; Tally Prime &#43; GST  2021 - Certificate Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tally-erp-9-tally-prime-gst-2021-certificate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 22:18:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/tally-erp-9-tally-prime-gst-2021-certificate-course/</guid>
      <description>Complete Tally Course from Zero to Hero in Tally Erp 9 + Tally Prime with Advance GST Course
Get Constant Growth in your career/Business with Advance Tally GST Online Course
Best Seller Course
What you’ll learn in this Tally Erp9 + Tally Prime Online Training
Accounting of Any Company with GST Independently in Tally Erp9 &amp;amp; Tally Prime
From Manual Accounting to Advance GST Reports in Tally Erp9 &amp;amp; Tally Prime</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tally Prime Erp &#43;GST 2021 : Certificate Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tally-prime-erp-gst-2021-certificate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 22:18:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/tally-prime-erp-gst-2021-certificate-course/</guid>
      <description>--**New in Tally Prime Erp with GST **--
-&amp;gt;Better Control Over Cash Flow
-&amp;gt;Enhanced Business Efficiency
-&amp;gt;Tax Compliance Made Easy

From the Bestseller of Tally Erp9 with GST
Best Rated for Eway Bill
Best Rated for GST Returns

Complete Tally Course from Zero to Hero in Tally Prime Erp with Advance GST Course
Get Constant Growth in your career/Business with Advance Tally PRIME GST Online Course
Best Seller Course</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wave Accounting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/wave-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/wave-accounting/</guid>
      <description>This course will use free accounting software which is an excellent tool to practice with.
This course will jump right into bank feeds and how to use them.
Many accounting software courses will spend a lot of time talking about how a full-service accounting system works. We do recommend spending time learning the full accounting process, and we do have courses that do just that.
However, many small businesses want to get right down to data input as fast as possible, and others already have a good understanding of the system and want to focus specifically on bank feeds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Financial Accounting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/advanced-financial-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/advanced-financial-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Advanced financial accounting will focus heavily on intercorporate acquisitions and investments in other entities.
Why learn advanced accounting?
Even if we do not work in an area that applies advanced accounting concepts directly, learning them is very useful, because it refines our skills on the understanding of double-entry accounting, its concepts, and practical application.
Advanced financial accounting is also a standardized topic often found on exams like the CPA exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consumer Lending Risk Management Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/consumer-lending-risk-management-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/consumer-lending-risk-management-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Have you wondered what a consumer lending risk management professional does on a daily basis? Do you want to explore the world of consumer lending, which is closely tied with millions of people&#39;s lives? This introductory course, Consumer Lending Risk Management Fundamentals - A Beginner&#39;s Guide, will walk you through: Consumer lending products and ecosystem
Risk management types and framework
Risk management practices in consumer lending
Risk management throughout credit life cycle</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #1 Introduction &amp; Financial Statements</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance-#1-introduction-financial-statements/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance-#1-introduction-financial-statements/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover the core concepts of corporate finance.
You will know the differences and similarities between the field of finance, accounting, and economics. Accounting is generally using past data to construct the financial statements in accordance with accounting standards. The financial statements are critical to the field of corporate finance but the the focus is different. Corporate finance will generally use data from the financial statements to make forecasts about future performance driving decision making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #4 Leverage &amp; Break-Even Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance-#4-leverage-break-even-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance-#4-leverage-break-even-analysis/</guid>
      <description>In this course we will cover the concepts of leverage and break-even analysis from a corporate finance perspective.
Leverage is a critical component of decision making in corporate finance and is an area of debate as to the optimal amount of leverage. Finding the best level of leverage may allow a business to grow much faster.
We will discuss the concepts of operating leverage, financial leverage, and combined leverage and include practical practice problems related to these critical concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Payment Dispute Resolution</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-payment-dispute-resolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-payment-dispute-resolution/</guid>
      <description>WHY DISPUTE RESOLUTION?
Payment disputes are an important issue to solve, either as a merchant, cardholder or bank.
There are many reasons for disputes, and multiple methods for dispute resolution. All of these can affect the results of a dispute for the different parties involved.
In order to be effective at dispute resolution, it&#39;s important to understand not just the reasons for disputes, but also the mechanisms for their resolution, and the consequences of each.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop Not for Profit Organizations</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-desktop-not-for-profit-organizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-desktop-not-for-profit-organizations/</guid>
      <description>QuickBooks Desktop Not for Profit Organizations will provide the tools to enter data into QuickBooks for a not for profit organization.
This QuickBooks course will consist of three comprehensive practice problems. One problem will be for a charitable organization, one for a health care organization, and one for a not for profit school.
We will learn how to set up a QuickBooks file for a not for profit organization.
The course will show how to create a chart of accounts and items list for a not for profit organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swing Trading Ninja: 12 Hour Complete Swing Trading Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/swing-trading-ninja-12-hour-complete-swing-trading-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 12:58:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/swing-trading-ninja-12-hour-complete-swing-trading-strategy/</guid>
      <description>*** Course access includes quizzes &amp;amp; homework exercises, 1-on-1 instructor support and LIFETIME access! ***
This is best strategy I ever find in my life for swing trader. This is incredible. This milloin dollar startegy. I can say here &#34;knowledge is power&#34;.
-Suhit Kalubarme
it was a great match . I am learning a lot and enjoying class. Working on paper trades as class goes on and see things that I am learning daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #5 Financing Decisions</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance-#5-financing-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance-#5-financing-decisions/</guid>
      <description>This course will discuss company financing decisions from a corporate finance perspective.
Financing is often a critical component to company growth, optimal financing allowing companies to grow much faster while mitigating risk.
We will consider general financing patterns of a corporation.
Financing options can be broken down into short-term financing needs and long-term financing need. To determine financing needs, a company will often have to estimate future sales, future sales allowing them to estimate production levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #6 Management of Current Assets</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance-#6-management-of-current-assets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance-#6-management-of-current-assets/</guid>
      <description>This course will discuss how to manage current assets from a corporate finance perspective.
It will include many example problems, some in presentation format, some using Excel worksheets. Each Excel problem will include a downloadable Excel workbook having at least two tabs, one with the answer, another with a preformatted worksheet you can populate along with the step-by-step instructional videos.
Current asset classes we will consider include cash, accounts receivable, inventory, and marketable securities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Capital Free Financial Planner Application</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/personal-capital-free-financial-planner-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/personal-capital-free-financial-planner-application/</guid>
      <description>Personal Capital is currently a free software that can connect to financial institutions, pulling in financial asset and liability balances, as well as transaction detail, into one location.
The strong areas of benefit of using Personal Capital software are its ability to provide net worth or balance sheet information, investment management information, and planning tools such as retirement planning and other large planning goals.
The Personal Capital software also downloads transaction detail and allows for the categorization or assigning of accounts and tags that can then be used to generate an income statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income: 27 Ways to Earn Passive Income Online</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/passive-income-27-ways-to-earn-passive-income-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/passive-income-27-ways-to-earn-passive-income-online/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to earn money even while you are sleeping?
Do you want to earn money automatically once you&#39;ve set up the systems?
Then this is the right course for you.
I have been earning passive income already for years and I have helped 1,000&#39;s of people worldwide to do the same through my YouTube channel, Udemy courses and blogs.
Earning passive income works in the following way (in a nutshell):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calcul stochastique pour le trading Forex</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/calcul-stochastique-pour-le-trading-forex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 17:04:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/calcul-stochastique-pour-le-trading-forex/</guid>
      <description>Aujourd&#39;hui, Médaillon, le fond le plus profitable du monde fait en moyenne plus de 60% de gain annuel. Mais comment? Ils sont spécialiser dans la finance quantitative, le trading algorithmique et la mathématisation des processus financier. Ici, dans cette formation, nous allons nous intéresser au calcul stochastique. Nous allons voir qu&#39;elles sont les méthodes de bases du calcul stochastique, voir comment l&#39;appliquer au indice boursier et au forex. 
L&#39;idée principale de cette formation est de voir les bénéfices que l&#39;on peut avoir en combinant deux disciplines très utilisées en finance quantitative: le calcul stochastique et le machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data science pour le trading algorithmique (2020)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/data-science-pour-le-trading-algorithmique-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 17:04:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/data-science-pour-le-trading-algorithmique-2020/</guid>
      <description>C&#39;est avec plaisir que je vous offre ce cours de data science pour le trading algorithmique. C&#39;est le fuit de plusieurs années de travail dans de nombreux domaines pour comprendre les subtilités du monde de la finance quantitative.

Nous utiliserons des librairies python qui nous permettrons de faire facilement des algorithmes mathématiques très complexes appliqués à la finance avec peu de code. Le fil conducteur de cette formation sera la création d&#39;un algorithme profitable avec plus de 50% de gain annuel sur me NASDAQ 100.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MASTERCLASS: &#39;Inversión en Fondos Mutuos&#39;</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/masterclass-inversi%C3%B3n-en-fondos-mutuos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/masterclass-inversi%C3%B3n-en-fondos-mutuos/</guid>
      <description>Si usted considera que los métodos tradicionales de ahorro que le ofrecen las entidades bancarias de su país no son lo suficientemente buenas para usted debido a su baja rentabilidad y a la creciente inflación, pero a su vez considera que aún no está preparado para dar el gran salto a las inversiones en las bolsas de valores, puesto que ha oído hablar de que es muy riesgoso y que requiere de mucha preparación, entonces esta Masterclass gratuita es adecuada para usted, mi nombre es Jean Pierre Chayña Salas (Economista de profesión) y le mostraré que es posible invertir y sacarle dinero al mercado financiero de forma indirecta jugando bajo sus propios términos y condiciones, aprovechando los beneficios de la banca tradicional y del mercado de valores a través de su banca por Internet BBVA y todo esto desde la comodidad de su casa y ¿Cómo lo haremos?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #11 Capital Budgeting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance-#11-capital-budgeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance-#11-capital-budgeting/</guid>
      <description>This course will show how to make capital budgeting decisions from a corporate finance perspective.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.
Capital budgeting decisions involve planning for projects and future cash flows extending more then one year into the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Trading Ninja: 12 Hours DIY Day Trading Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/day-trading-ninja-12-hours-diy-day-trading-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/day-trading-ninja-12-hours-diy-day-trading-strategy/</guid>
      <description>*** Course access includes quizzes &amp;amp; homework exercises, 1-on-1 instructor support and LIFETIME access! ***
Hear why this is one of the TOP-NOTCH Day Trading course on Udemy:
very practical course , I already made more than 10000$ from 100$ using this course principles . I would like to thank the author for such a good effort. I would like to recommend everyone this course who is struggling in the forex market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Economics: Microeconomics and Macroeconomics</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-economics-microeconomics-and-macroeconomics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:28:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-economics-microeconomics-and-macroeconomics/</guid>
      <description>SearchEcon Economics overview provides an Introduction to Economics. This course can help your Introduction to Economics courses. We provide an overview of Microeconomics and Macroeconomics. This overview of Economics can also be helpful for business and government leaders who wish to learn the basics of Economics.
We try to provide real world examples throughout the course to help you understand Economic concepts. We also try to provide relatable examples that help connect and understand the concepts that we are reviewing in Economics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standard Costing And Variance Analysis Full Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/standard-costing-and-variance-analysis-full-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:15:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/standard-costing-and-variance-analysis-full-course/</guid>
      <description>Administrative and cost management tools
The course will introduce subject management topics to be covered throughout the course, comparing management accounting and accounting so that we are in the right frame of mind as we move forward.
The study will explain and analyze general costs and cost variance analyzes, providing an overview of the cost analysis concepts that we will go into in detail in later sections.
We will explain the analysis of sales differences, discuss when they can be used and how to calculate sales variations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IIA-CIA-Part2 Practice Test Prep Exam</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/iia-cia-part2-practice-test-prep-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/iia-cia-part2-practice-test-prep-exam/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the pratice Tests: IIA-CIA-Part2 Certified Internal Auditor - Part 2, Conducting the Internal Audit Engagement.
I prepared the pratice tests to help you prepare for the real IIA-CIA-Part2 exam, you will test your knowledge with hours of simulated questions and answers giving great chances for you to improve your performance when taking the exam.
Our pratice Tests covers all references:
 I. Managing the Internal Audit Activity
 II.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Income Tax Complete Certification Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/indian-income-tax-complete-certification-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/indian-income-tax-complete-certification-course/</guid>
      <description>Do you find it difficult to understand the Income Tax laws?
Or are you struggling with filing your own income tax return?
Many a time we hear people saying that they don’t understand tax, they are not aware of when tax is to be deducted (TDS), they find it difficult to apply for their own PAN number or they find it difficult to file their return of income.
So, friends to simplify all your problems and giving you an excellent clarity of all concepts, we have made this course on “Income Tax” presented by Direct and Corporate Tax expert CA Natasha Shah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Credit and Credit Repair from Scratch</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-about-credit-and-credit-repair-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-about-credit-and-credit-repair-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>Sadly, many people get into a debt spiral that soon goes out of control. They have trouble keeping their head above water, and soon they fall under as the weight of debt drags them down.

Thankfully, credit can be managed and all it takes is having the ability to change how one lives their life. By implementing the lessons explained in this course, an individual will be able to take their credit and repair it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aprende las bases para invertir en la bolsa</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aprende-las-bases-para-invertir-en-la-bolsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aprende-las-bases-para-invertir-en-la-bolsa/</guid>
      <description>En este curso aprenderás a leer los 3 estados financieros más importantes que reportan las empresas que cotizan en la bolsa americana (empresas públicas.) Estos son el estado de ingresos, la hoja de balance y el flujo de caja. Con el conocimiento ganado podrás reconocer si ha mejorado o empeorado el desempeño de una empresa pública. De esta forma, sabrás si es conveniente invertir en la empresa analizada. Estaremos usando Yahoo Finanzas para analizar los estados financieros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin 101 - Complete Intro to Bitcoin, Blockchain &amp; Crypto</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/bitcoin-101-complete-intro-to-bitcoin-blockchain-crypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/bitcoin-101-complete-intro-to-bitcoin-blockchain-crypto/</guid>
      <description>In this course, we dive deep into one of the most revolutionary assets of all time... Bitcoin. We dig into how Bitcoin&#39;s underlying technology, blockchain work. With no technical knowledge required, you will learn how the blockchain works, and why it is being called the &#34;next generation of the internet.&#34; Next, we take a closer look at the fundamentals of Bitcoin, and what makes it the most important cryptocurrency in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Trading for Beginners 2021 (CLICK-BY-CLICK)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cryptocurrency-trading-for-beginners-2021-click-by-click/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cryptocurrency-trading-for-beginners-2021-click-by-click/</guid>
      <description>Cryptocurrencies may feel confusing if you are a complete beginner... Not anymore!
I&#39;ll show you how cryptocurrency trading works in a SIMPLE &amp;amp; EASY&amp;nbsp;way.
I&#39;ve educated over 350,000 people on Udemy and I&#39;d love to help you next.
After helping so many people, I&#39;ve realized that cryptocurrencies don&#39;t need to be complicated.
When you learn a few simple concepts, you&#39;re already ahead of 99.9% of the population. 1,000&#39;s of beginners have learned about Bitcoin &amp;amp; cryptocurrencies for the first time of their life through my Udemy &amp;amp; YouTube videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Futures Trading Mastery 2021 | FREE Top 45 Trading Signals!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/futures-trading-mastery-2021-free-top-45-trading-signals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/futures-trading-mastery-2021-free-top-45-trading-signals/</guid>
      <description>My exclusive course teaches you how to start a successful futures trading business from scratch with zero experience. As one of the world’s 10 years veteran traders, I, Henry Zhang, will personally teach you the same proven strategy I used to build my trading empire from nothing.

Start a lucrative and sustainable trading business today with this complete A-Z guide designed to help everyone from beginners to existing traders looking to increase profits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Reporting Automation with Google Sheets</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/master-reporting-automation-with-google-sheets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/master-reporting-automation-with-google-sheets/</guid>
      <description>Learn to solve any business modeling task you might ever experience!
Have you ever felt that you&#39;re regularly repeating some tasks in Google Sheets or Excel?
Have you ever thought about the time you would save if you would automate those tasks?

All the work you&#39;re doing in a repetitive manner in Google Sheets or Excel could be automated.&amp;nbsp;It requires no coding skills, add-ons, or special tools - all you need to know is how to execute advanced formula combinations that will do all the automation for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Short Course on Ripple Cryptocurrency</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-short-course-on-ripple-cryptocurrency/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-short-course-on-ripple-cryptocurrency/</guid>
      <description>*** Course access&amp;nbsp;includes&amp;nbsp;quizzes &amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;homework exercises, 1-on-1 instructor support&amp;nbsp;(Ripple Cryptocurrency) and&amp;nbsp;LIFETIME&amp;nbsp;access! ***
Hear why this is one of the TOP-NOTCH&amp;nbsp;Ripple Cryptocurrency course&amp;nbsp;on Udemy:
Very informative indeed! Last lecture on Ripple charts was very helpful. Thanks.
-Raghbir Bhullar
I enjoyed learning about a different cryptocurrency than Bitcoin, but I would have liked more information on buying and selling Ripple. The instructor explained how to open accounts on two platforms. What is the difference between the two?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not-for-Profit Accounting-Charities, Colleges, &amp; Health Care</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/not-for-profit-accounting-charities-colleges-health-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/not-for-profit-accounting-charities-colleges-health-care/</guid>
      <description>Not for Profit Accounting-Charities, Colleges, &amp;amp; Health Care will cover accounting principles related to not for profit organizations.
Our concentration will be on nongovernmental not-for-profit organizations. However, we will discuss the differences between nongovernmental not for profit organization and governmental not-for-profit organizations. We will also discuss accounting concepts for both governmental and nongovernmental organizations related to health care and colleges.
The course will start by introducing what a not for profit organization is.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
