<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Finance &amp; Accounting on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/finance-accounting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Finance &amp; Accounting on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/finance-accounting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Accounting-Statement of Cash Flows</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/accounting-statement-of-cash-flows/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/accounting-statement-of-cash-flows/</guid>
      <description>Statement of cash flows creation and analysis. We will introduce the statement of cash flows and discuss its purpose and uses. Understanding how to create a statement of cash flows provides us with a much deeper understanding of accounting and how the financial statements are constructed. To build a statement of cash flows, we will use concepts of accrual accounting needed to create the balance sheet and income statement. We will apply our understanding of accrual concepts to analyze cash flows, creating a cash flow statement from accrual financial reports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Altcoin Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/altcoin-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/altcoin-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve not tried using Altcoins and invest the next generation currency, then today is the time to start!
Never before has there been an technology platform of this magnitude that will allow you to reach an audience of billions and rapidly grow your business online at next to zero cost!
Become The Ultimate Altcoins Master and join this course today to learn the same PROVEN success strategy Henry Zhang , the Crypto Currency expert and world-leading trader used to build this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank Feeds-QuickBooks Online, Xero, Sage, Wave (Comparison)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bank-feeds-quickbooks-online-xero-sage-wave-comparison/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bank-feeds-quickbooks-online-xero-sage-wave-comparison/</guid>
      <description>Bank Feed Options
This course will compare and contrast the top accounting software applications, focusing on the use of bank feeds.
We will provide practice data that learners can import into the software applications.
Learners will understand the process of setting up each online software package. We will also discuss purchase options.
Most of the software applications will include a free test drive, an excellent tool for learning accounting and bank feeds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #16 Convertible Bonds &amp; Warrants</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#16-convertible-bonds-warrants/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#16-convertible-bonds-warrants/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover convertible securities. We will discuss convertible bonds, warrants, &amp;amp; derivative securities.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.
Convertible securities are securities that can be converted from one asset type into another asset type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crypto-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crypto-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>Cryptocurrency is an online form of payment that can be traded for goods or services, just like fiat money.
Cryptocurrencies are usually developed by teams who build in various mechanisms for issuance, usually depending on that decentralized system
Entrepreneurs have begun to utilize cryptocurrency to further their business and increase profits. In fact, since cryptocurrencies are both investment opportunities and new financial instruments, there has never been a better time to get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Accounting – Inventory Costs</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-inventory-costs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-inventory-costs/</guid>
      <description>We cover inventory costs and cost flows, including what is included in the cost of inventory and how to account for inventory freight costs, inventory insurance costs, and discount. We also discuss inventory flow assumptions including specific identification, first in first out (FIFO), last in first out (LIFO), and weighted average methods. FIFO, LIFO and weighted average methods will be discussed using both a periodic inventory system and a perpetual inventory system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Accounting-Debits &amp; Credits-Accounting Transaction</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-debits-credits-accounting-transaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-debits-credits-accounting-transaction/</guid>
      <description>Includes downloadable e-book in multiple formats so you can open it on your tablet or Kindle - Formats (EPUB, MOBI, PDF). Accounting Instruction Reference #100 is a book that sells on Amazon and is available in Kindle, Paperback, and audiobook format. Often times when we receive a book that is published on Amazon it is exciting until we find it is only in PDF format. The e-book we provide is in a format you can use on a tablet and Kindle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Create a NFT Collection and Sell Your NFTs on Opensea</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-create-a-nft-collection-and-sell-your-nfts-on-opensea/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-create-a-nft-collection-and-sell-your-nfts-on-opensea/</guid>
      <description>More than 40,000 students from 153 countries enrolled in our courses
More than 1000 Reviews on Our Courses
&#34;it is very clear and ı am enjoying.well educated&#34;&#34;Excellent, Straight to the point&#34;&#34;t&#39;s something I wanted to learn for a long time, thanks a lot! Can&#39;t wait for the second and third parts of this course..&#34;
&#34;Good tutor with good tutorials.&#34;&#34;Great Explanation. Studied a lot. Thanks&#34;
Subscribe and enjoy the content of this course FOREVER!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Cost QuickBooks Online vs QuickBooks Desktop–Contractor</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/job-cost-quickbooks-online-vs-quickbooks-desktopcontractor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/job-cost-quickbooks-online-vs-quickbooks-desktopcontractor/</guid>
      <description>This QuickBooks Job Costing course will provide the resources for learners to develop a solid understanding of job costing concepts and the tools QuickBooks provides to create an effective job costing system.
We will provide backup files for the desktop version so learners can jump forward in the practice problem or rework any component of the problem. The use of backup files is not a requirement of the course, however.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop Multiple Currencies</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-multiple-currencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-multiple-currencies/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to get access to QuickBooks Desktop including a possible free 30-day trial version often offered by Intuit, the owner of QuickBooks Desktop.
The course will discuss accounting for multiple currencies, outlining the process in Excel to provide a more transparent look at the process. Then we will enter the transactions into QuickBooks, the software automating some of the steps required.
We will learn how to turn multicurrency on, and which accounts will be affected most by multicurrency transactions including cash account types, accounts receivable account types, and accounts payable account types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Online Bank Reconciliation</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-bank-reconciliation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-bank-reconciliation/</guid>
      <description>If we are a business owner who would like more assurance about our books, a business professional who would like to advance our career by learning the importance of bank reconciliations, or an accounting student who would like to see the critical internal control of bank reconciliations applies to real work software, this QuickBooks course is a course for us. Why choose this course?
The bank reconciliation process is the second biggest internal control for most companies and one both large and small companies can, and should, implement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Online Multiple Currencies</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-multiple-currencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-multiple-currencies/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to get access to QuickBooks Online including a possible free 30-day trial version often offered by Intuit, the owner of QuickBooks Online.
The course will discuss accounting for multiple currencies, outlining the process in Excel to provide a more transparent look at the process. Then we will enter the transactions into QuickBooks, the software automating some of the steps required.
We will learn how to turn multicurrency on, and which accounts will be affected most by multicurrency transactions including cash account types, accounts receivable account types, and accounts payable account types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Residential Rental Property Tax Preparation 2021-2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/residential-rental-property-tax-preparation-2021-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/residential-rental-property-tax-preparation-2021-2022/</guid>
      <description>This course will focus on tax preparation related to rental real property.
We will look at each new concept from multiple angles, starting with a presentation discussing the topic and then looking at examples to better understand the concepts in action.
The example section will use tax forms to work problems and an accounting equation method using Excel so learners will understand the impact on the actual tax return and visualize the concepts using a tax formula.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistique et probabilité pour la finance quantitative</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/statistique-et-probabilit%C3%A9-pour-la-finance-quantitative/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/statistique-et-probabilit%C3%A9-pour-la-finance-quantitative/</guid>
      <description>Vous avez déjà des connaissances en finance et vous voulez les approfondir pour les monétiser et les diversifier ?
Vous avez déjà des connaissances en trading et vous voulez apprendre le trading/la finance quantitative ?
Vous êtes simplement une personne curieuse qui veut s&#39;intéresser à ce sujet ?
Si vous répondez à au moins une de ces questions, je vous souhaite la bienvenue à ce cours. Toutes les applications du cours seront réalisées à l&#39;aide de Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete NFT Course: Become an NFT Creator &amp; Investor</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-nft-course-become-an-nft-creator-investor/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-nft-course-become-an-nft-creator-investor/</guid>
      <description>Ever since Bitcoin forced most people to learn about cryptocurrencies in recent years, there hasn’t been any other technology that garnered as much attention as NFTs. Running on the same blockchain technology as most cryptocurrencies, it’s like crypto, but for another purpose.
This course shows you how NFTs work and their connection with blockchain technology. You&#39;ll learn the theoretical aspect of the new technology and what function it serves in real life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two QuickBooks File-Business &amp; Personal vs One File For Both</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/two-quickbooks-file-business-personal-vs-one-file-for-both/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/two-quickbooks-file-business-personal-vs-one-file-for-both/</guid>
      <description>QuickBooks Pro Desktop 2019, comparing two methods of tracking both business and personal records, one using two QuickBooks Desktop 2019 files, and one using a sing file to track both business and personal financial data using QuickBooks class tracking feature. We will work with hands-on practical practice problems together under both methods, compare the results, and discuss the pros and cons of each approach. The course will start with the method of using two separate QuickBooks files for business and personal records because this is the most widely recommended method and provides the greatest separation of business and personal data which is usually a good thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xero Accounting Software</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/xero-accounting-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/xero-accounting-software/</guid>
      <description>This course will start at the basics, assuming you know nothing about the software or accounting.
We will then go through the purchasing process, the downloading process, and the installation process. Xero often offers a free 30 day trial which is a perfect tool to practice with. The first half of the course will be dedicated to navigating the software, getting a feel for the major components of the software, and the primary accounting cycles such as the customer section or revenue cycle, the vendor section or payments cycle, and the employee section or payroll cycle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accounting–Financial Accounting Total-Beginners to Advanced</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/accountingfinancial-accounting-total-beginners-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/accountingfinancial-accounting-total-beginners-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Recently updated with A LOT of added content.
Includes downloadable e-book in multiple formats so you can open it on your tablet or Kindle - Formats (EPUB, MOBI, PDF).
This course is an excellent supplement for students or anybody who wants to learn accounting and also have something they can refer back to in the future. Udemy generally provides lifetime access to the course.
Many accounting students do not receive a physical book, they get to keep from their school, and even if they did, the information could become dated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audit - Financial Statement</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/audit-financial-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/audit-financial-statement/</guid>
      <description>Audit-Financial Accounting will discuss, in detail, the auditing process of financial statements.
The course will start by discussing what an audit is, as well as what the terms attest engagement and assurances services mean.
We will discuss the audit environment, the general format of a public accounting firm, and the general format of an audit team that would conduct the procedures related to an audit. The course will also discuss regulations and regulatory institutions related to the audit process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance/</guid>
      <description>We will learn how to read financial statements and how to use them for decision making.
A primary tool we will use is ratio analysis. Ratio analysis is a very useful skill in a wide area of topics, and financial analysis is a great place to learn the skill.
Ratios are necessary when measuring performance, including most any job performance. For example, we must apply ratio analysis when measuring the job performance of sports athletes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cost Accounting and Artificial Intelligence Tools (2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cost-accounting-and-artificial-intelligence-tools-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cost-accounting-and-artificial-intelligence-tools-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Cost Accounting and Artificial Intelligence Tools (2022)&#34;.
Ready to learn the basics of cost accounting with a glimpse of Artificial Intelligence technology usage in accounting?
Cost accounting is an important aspect of an accounting policy that calculates the total cost of producing an item or providing a service by looking at all costs within the supply chain. It is done for the purpose of planning the budget and evaluating productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel Accounting Problem</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-accounting-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-accounting-problem/</guid>
      <description>This course will walk through a comprehensive accounting problem using Microsoft Excel in a step-by-step process. You may also use another spreadsheet software like Google Sheets.
Learners will learn how to navigate Microsoft Excel as well as how to create a well-designed accounting worksheet, complete with a general journal, trial balance, general ledger, subsidiary ledgers for accounts receivable, accounts payable, &amp;amp; inventory, financial statements and much more.
Excel is a very good tool to learn accounting because it is much more transparent than a database program, like accounting software, QuickBooks being a common example of accounting software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Statement Analysis – Ratio Analysis</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-statement-analysis-ratio-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-statement-analysis-ratio-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Learn tools to analyze financial statements, including vertical analysis, horizontal analysis, and ratio analysis.
This course will provide resources such as downloadable PDF files and preformatted Excel spreadsheet to help understand and apply the concepts.
We will list and describe the tools for financial statement analysis, including vertical analysis, horizontal analysis, and ratio analysis.
Below is more detail about the concepts we will learn.
This course will help us understand, calculate, and analyze horizontal analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managerial Accounting / Cost Accounting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/managerial-accounting-/-cost-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/managerial-accounting-/-cost-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Comprehensive managerial and cost accounting course. Topics include:
· Job order costing
· Process costing
· Cost volume profit analysis
· Master Budgets
· Flexible Budgets
· Responsibility accounting
· Relevant costs
· Time value of money
This course will go into detail about each topic. We will include”
· Practice Excel files with both an answer tab and a practice tab
· Lecture PDF files that can be downloaded and reviewed without internet access</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not-for-Profit Accounting-Charities, Colleges, &amp; Health Care</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/not-for-profit-accounting-charities-colleges-health-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/not-for-profit-accounting-charities-colleges-health-care/</guid>
      <description>Not for Profit Accounting-Charities, Colleges, &amp;amp; Health Care will cover accounting principles related to not for profit organizations.
Our concentration will be on nongovernmental not-for-profit organizations. However, we will discuss the differences between nongovernmental not for profit organization and governmental not-for-profit organizations. We will also discuss accounting concepts for both governmental and nongovernmental organizations related to health care and colleges.
The course will start by introducing what a not for profit organization is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income: 27 Ways to Earn Passive Income Online</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/passive-income-27-ways-to-earn-passive-income-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/passive-income-27-ways-to-earn-passive-income-online/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to earn money even while you are sleeping?
Do you want to earn money automatically once you&#39;ve set up the systems?
Then this is the right course for you.
I have been earning passive income already for years and I have helped 1,000&#39;s of people worldwide to do the same through my YouTube channel, Udemy courses and blogs.
Earning passive income works in the following way (in a nutshell):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover personal finance concepts, starting from the basics, and moving to complex topics. We will cover each step thoroughly.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop Not for Profit Organizations</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-not-for-profit-organizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-not-for-profit-organizations/</guid>
      <description>QuickBooks Desktop Not for Profit Organizations will provide the tools to enter data into QuickBooks for a not for profit organization.
This QuickBooks course will consist of three comprehensive practice problems. One problem will be for a charitable organization, one for a health care organization, and one for a not for profit school.
We will learn how to set up a QuickBooks file for a not for profit organization.
The course will show how to create a chart of accounts and items list for a not for profit organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APICS Certified Supply Chain Professional CSCP Practice Exam</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/apics-certified-supply-chain-professional-cscp-practice-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/apics-certified-supply-chain-professional-cscp-practice-exam/</guid>
      <description>Certified Supply Chain Professional (CSCP) Practice Exams
Get a passing grade in your CSCP exam on the first try
The questions in these practice exams are designed so you understand where your gaps are and how ready you are for the real one. The first three practice exams elaborate on the knowledge area and the other two exams are designed to determine your level of readiness.
If you are reading this sentence right now, you are in one of two groups of supply chain professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forex Trading Complete Course - &#39;Zero Experience Required&#39;</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/forex-trading-complete-course-zero-experience-required/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/forex-trading-complete-course-zero-experience-required/</guid>
      <description>In This Complete Forex Video Course, You&#39;ll Learn everything About Forex Trading. Starting from the very beginning I&#39;ll take you step by step with more than 8 hours of extensive video learning content and transform you into a profitable forex trader. you will not need any other courses to start trading forex and become a successful forex trader. You Can jump-start your forex trading immediately after completing this course. I&#39;ll give you also profitable trading strategies from a real trader that will put you in the minority of successful forex traders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Forex- learn to trade forex by yourself</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-forex-learn-to-trade-forex-by-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-forex-learn-to-trade-forex-by-yourself/</guid>
      <description>The financial markets are not very easy to handle and to trade. The Forex market is the biggest of those with more than 2 trillion dollars exchanged on a daily basis. But, there is a way to make profit out of all those transaction with forex trading and this is the goal of this course. Indeed, if you :
- Are someone who is interested in forex trading but never actually started</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Capital Free Financial Planner Application</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-capital-free-financial-planner-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-capital-free-financial-planner-application/</guid>
      <description>Personal Capital is currently a free software that can connect to financial institutions, pulling in financial asset and liability balances, as well as transaction detail, into one location.
The strong areas of benefit of using Personal Capital software are its ability to provide net worth or balance sheet information, investment management information, and planning tools such as retirement planning and other large planning goals.
The Personal Capital software also downloads transaction detail and allows for the categorization or assigning of accounts and tags that can then be used to generate an income statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The complete introduction to cryptocurrencies trading</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-introduction-to-cryptocurrencies-trading/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-introduction-to-cryptocurrencies-trading/</guid>
      <description>Cryptocurrencies trading and investing can sometimes be very hard to learn especially if you have no experience in this field. But, this course have everything that you need to be able to start your trading journey with more risky financial assets that are cryptocurrencies by learning the basis of this type of this financial product If you :
- Are in school and want to learn how to trade properly</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin For Beginners: How To Earn Bitcoin Online For Free</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bitcoin-for-beginners-how-to-earn-bitcoin-online-for-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bitcoin-for-beginners-how-to-earn-bitcoin-online-for-free/</guid>
      <description>This is a course that the Government doesn&#39;t want you to see! Bitcoin is the BEST-PERFORMING asset of the decade.
It&#39;s not a coincidence that Bitcoin has been growing over 200%/year on average!
Every smart person has already realized that Bitcoin is clearly superior compared to government money (=USD, EUR, PHP, INR, etc.)
That&#39;s why Bitcoin grows rapidly.
Smart people are trying to accumulate as much Bitcoin as possible before the rest of the population gets educated about the benefits of Bitcoin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earn Bitcoin on Your Phone WORLDWIDE Even While You Sleep</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/earn-bitcoin-on-your-phone-worldwide-even-while-you-sleep/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/earn-bitcoin-on-your-phone-worldwide-even-while-you-sleep/</guid>
      <description>This may be the most valuable Udemy course that you have ever seen!
The mobile apps that I reveal to you in this course have made me more money than most people earn in their lifetimes working full-time 9-5 jobs!
Why do I share this course for so cheap price?
I want that all 8 BILLION people will start using Bitcoin because it&#39;s making the world a better place for you, me and for every single person on this planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple and Strong Forex Swing Trading Strategy in the world</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/simple-and-strong-forex-swing-trading-strategy-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/simple-and-strong-forex-swing-trading-strategy-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Forex swing trade : use swing trading strategy to be better trader ,A Simple Forex Swing Trading Strategies That Work here its a Simple and Strong Forex Swing Trading Strategy in the world
Gain the ability to Make Money in Stock market, commodity,Forex, cryptocurrency and other tradable instruments using Price action, the Safest way by taking this course! Get your answers from two Certified &amp;amp; experienced Market experts to every single question you have related to the learning you do in this course including TimeFrame, Indicators, studying Charts, Use candlestick trading, understand the trading strategy how it work with historical date of the strategy from ( 2017 till jun 2020) and the results, and many more topics that are added every month!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Financial Accounting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-financial-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-financial-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Advanced financial accounting will focus heavily on intercorporate acquisitions and investments in other entities.
Why learn advanced accounting?
Even if we do not work in an area that applies advanced accounting concepts directly, learning them is very useful, because it refines our skills on the understanding of double-entry accounting, its concepts, and practical application.
Advanced financial accounting is also a standardized topic often found on exams like the CPA exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aplos Not for Profit Accounting Software</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aplos-not-for-profit-accounting-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aplos-not-for-profit-accounting-software/</guid>
      <description>Learners will understand how to set up Aplos, software specifically designed for Not for Profit Organizations.
The course will show how to use free resources to optimize learning.
We will demonstrate the use of funds and tags to generate Not for Profit reports.
The course will demonstrate how to enter and track restricted resources.
We will enter month end adjusting entries.
Learners will see how to allocate expenses to programs and administrative categories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Governmental Accounting 200 Capital Projects &amp; Debt Service</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/governmental-accounting-200-capital-projects-debt-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/governmental-accounting-200-capital-projects-debt-service/</guid>
      <description>The course will focus on larger capital projects and the use of a capital project fund and debt service fund to track them.
We will cover governmental accounting objective, which will be a review from governmental accounting 100.
The course will discuss what capital assets are and how they are recorded in governmental accounting, comparing governmental accounting to for-profit accounting.
Students will learn to record transactions for the issuance of bonds used to finance capital projects, recording transactions at the government-wide level and in the capital project fund, debts service fund, and general fund.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Governmental Accounting 300 Proprietary &amp; Fiduciary Funds</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/governmental-accounting-300-proprietary-fiduciary-funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/governmental-accounting-300-proprietary-fiduciary-funds/</guid>
      <description>Governmental Accounting 300 Proprietary &amp;amp; Fiduciary Funds will focus in on the accounting for proprietary and fiduciary funds.
We recommend first taking Governmental Accounting 100 and Governmental Accounting 200 or have equivalent experience before taking this course.
The course will provide an overview of governmental accounting. As we move through the course, we will focus on areas of governmental accounting that are different from for-profit accounting.
We will consider what proprietary funds are and when a proprietary would be used within governmental accounting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process Costing System-Cost Accounting-Managerial Accounting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/process-costing-system-cost-accounting-managerial-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/process-costing-system-cost-accounting-managerial-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Process costing system – Cost Accounting – Managerial Accounting
We will start by introducing managerial accounting or cost accounting topics that apply to companies that manufacture using either a job cost system or a process cost system.
The course will describe classifications for costs and the importance of being able to classify costs in different ways.
We will list and describe an outline of the process costs go through as they flow through the accounting process in a manufacturing company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Value of Money &amp; Capital Budgeting - Present Value</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-value-of-money-capital-budgeting-present-value/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-value-of-money-capital-budgeting-present-value/</guid>
      <description>Time value of money and capital budgeting decision is an excellent course for anybody who needs to consider longer-term decisions that require us to understand the time value of money. We will learn the time value of money concepts like present value and future value using multiple methods, including formulas, tables, and Excel functions. We will format the data in many ways and have many examples using Excel to calculate present value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wave Accounting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/wave-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/wave-accounting/</guid>
      <description>This course will use free accounting software which is an excellent tool to practice with.
This course will jump right into bank feeds and how to use them.
Many accounting software courses will spend a lot of time talking about how a full-service accounting system works. We do recommend spending time learning the full accounting process, and we do have courses that do just that.
However, many small businesses want to get right down to data input as fast as possible, and others already have a good understanding of the system and want to focus specifically on bank feeds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #1 Introduction &amp; Financial Statements</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#1-introduction-financial-statements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#1-introduction-financial-statements/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover the core concepts of corporate finance.
You will know the differences and similarities between the field of finance, accounting, and economics. Accounting is generally using past data to construct the financial statements in accordance with accounting standards. The financial statements are critical to the field of corporate finance but the the focus is different. Corporate finance will generally use data from the financial statements to make forecasts about future performance driving decision making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Governmental Accounting 100</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/governmental-accounting-100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/governmental-accounting-100/</guid>
      <description>Governmental accounting, including fund accounting financial transactions, focusing on the general fund and government-wide activities.
We will work through many example problems as we learn the material, posting transactions to a trial balance, so we can see how accounts behave. Many governmental accounts are new to many learners, and we will be using different accounting methods than just an accrual method. Posting transactions and seeing a trial balance will be very helpful in learning the material and is something lacking in most courses on the subject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relevant Costs - Managerial Accounting Decisions &amp; Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/relevant-costs-managerial-accounting-decisions-scenarios/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/relevant-costs-managerial-accounting-decisions-scenarios/</guid>
      <description>Apply relevant cost methods to common managerial decisions.
Managers often need to make decisions that are not routine, not part of the normal day to day process, and that can have a long-term effect on the organization. Individuals often need to make similar decisions and can apply similar tools when making decisions of a large dollar amount that can affect multiple years.
Although the specifics of each decision differ, the concept of relevant costs helps us put together a process for gathering and analyzing data, picking up the information that matters, and removing all the excess data that does not matter to our decision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xero Not for Profit Organization</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/xero-not-for-profit-organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/xero-not-for-profit-organization/</guid>
      <description>Learners will understand how to set up Xero for a Not for Profit Organization.
The course will show how to use free resources to optimize learning.
We will demonstrate the use of category tracking to generate Not for Profit reports.
Learners will see how to create and use donation receipt forms.
We will show how to create and use pledge receipt forms.
The course will demonstrate how to enter and track restricted resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Trading for Beginners (Learn CLICK-BY-CLICK)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cryptocurrency-trading-for-beginners-learn-click-by-click/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cryptocurrency-trading-for-beginners-learn-click-by-click/</guid>
      <description>Cryptocurrencies may feel confusing if you are a complete beginner... Not anymore!
I&#39;ll show you how cryptocurrency trading works in a SIMPLE &amp;amp; EASY way.
I&#39;ve educated over 350,000 people on Udemy and I&#39;d love to help you next.
After helping so many people, I&#39;ve realized that cryptocurrencies don&#39;t need to be complicated.
When you learn a few simple concepts, you&#39;re already ahead of 99.9% of the population. 1,000&#39;s of beginners have learned about Bitcoin &amp;amp; cryptocurrencies for the first time of their life through my Udemy &amp;amp; YouTube videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profitable Forex Candlestick Trading Strategy - Forex Trader</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/profitable-forex-candlestick-trading-strategy-forex-trader/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/profitable-forex-candlestick-trading-strategy-forex-trader/</guid>
      <description>REVEALED The Most Powerful and EASIEST Forex Japanese Candlestick Patterns Strategy
Start Forex Trading Today and learn from an expert, Forex trader
Are you Looking to Start in Forex Trading and you don&#39;t know how? or you haven&#39;t find something that actually work ?
don&#39;t worry you are in the right place!!
I will take you in this 4 hours and half course step by step from basics till you gone to be a pro Forex trader including anything you need to start in the world of Forex trading the right and proper way, all you need just a cup of coffee and be focused that all, and believe me at the end of the course you gone to know the information i give you its high quality not like majority of fibs you hearing online !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bitcoin-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bitcoin-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>Never before has there been an technology platform of this magnitude that will allow you to reach an audience of billions and rapidly grow your business online at next to zero cost!
Become The Ultimate Bitcoin Master and join this course today to learn the same PROVEN success strategy Henry Zhang , the Crypto Currency expert and world-leading trader used to build this course.
In just 1 hours, Henry will explain in SIMPLE terms how to harness Bitcoin and other crypto currencies to skyrocket your campaign success rates and keep the conversions coming in thick and fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corp Finance #12 Capital Budgeting &amp; Investment Risk Tools</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corp-finance-#12-capital-budgeting-investment-risk-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corp-finance-#12-capital-budgeting-investment-risk-tools/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover the use of risk assessment tools as they relate to capital budgeting and investment decisions and how to use them.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corp Finance #17 Merger, Acquisition &amp; Foreign Currency</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corp-finance-#17-merger-acquisition-foreign-currency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corp-finance-#17-merger-acquisition-foreign-currency/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover mergers, acquisitions &amp;amp; foreign currency.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.
We will discuss what acquisitions and mergers are and how they may be structured, including cash acquisitions and stock for stock acquisitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corp. Finance #14 Financing-Commons Stock &amp; Preferred Stock</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corp.-finance-#14-financing-commons-stock-preferred-stock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corp.-finance-#14-financing-commons-stock-preferred-stock/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover corporate financing options using common stock and preferred stock.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.
When thinking about financing options for a corporation we can break them into the two main groups of debt financing and equity financing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #11 Capital Budgeting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#11-capital-budgeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#11-capital-budgeting/</guid>
      <description>This course will show how to make capital budgeting decisions from a corporate finance perspective.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.
Capital budgeting decisions involve planning for projects and future cash flows extending more then one year into the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #15 Dividend Policy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#15-dividend-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#15-dividend-policy/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover corporate dividend policy.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.
Dividends represent earnings that a corporation distributes to owners. Dividends for a corporation can be compared do withdrawals from a sole proprietorship or partnership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #4 Leverage &amp; Break-Even Analysis</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#4-leverage-break-even-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#4-leverage-break-even-analysis/</guid>
      <description>In this course we will cover the concepts of leverage and break-even analysis from a corporate finance perspective.
Leverage is a critical component of decision making in corporate finance and is an area of debate as to the optimal amount of leverage. Finding the best level of leverage may allow a business to grow much faster.
We will discuss the concepts of operating leverage, financial leverage, and combined leverage and include practical practice problems related to these critical concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #5 Financing Decisions</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#5-financing-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#5-financing-decisions/</guid>
      <description>This course will discuss company financing decisions from a corporate finance perspective.
Financing is often a critical component to company growth, optimal financing allowing companies to grow much faster while mitigating risk.
We will consider general financing patterns of a corporation.
Financing options can be broken down into short-term financing needs and long-term financing need. To determine financing needs, a company will often have to estimate future sales, future sales allowing them to estimate production levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #6 Management of Current Assets</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#6-management-of-current-assets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#6-management-of-current-assets/</guid>
      <description>This course will discuss how to manage current assets from a corporate finance perspective.
It will include many example problems, some in presentation format, some using Excel worksheets. Each Excel problem will include a downloadable Excel workbook having at least two tabs, one with the answer, another with a preformatted worksheet you can populate along with the step-by-step instructional videos.
Current asset classes we will consider include cash, accounts receivable, inventory, and marketable securities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #7 Short Term Financing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#7-short-term-financing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#7-short-term-financing/</guid>
      <description>This course will discuss short term financing options from a corporate finance perspective.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.
Learners will understand accounts payable and trade credit as options from the perspective of short-term financing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #9 Valuation-Bond, Common /Preferred Stock</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#9-valuation-bond-common-/preferred-stock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#9-valuation-bond-common-/preferred-stock/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover the valuation of financial assets including bonds, common stock, and preferred stock.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel Accounting 1–Transactions for Common Data Input Forms</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-accounting-1transactions-for-common-data-input-forms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-accounting-1transactions-for-common-data-input-forms/</guid>
      <description>In this course we will build an accounting system starting with a blank Excel worksheet, creating a general journal, a general ledger, a trial balance, subledgers, and financial statements.
For each new step in the process, you will have access to a downloadable Excel Workbook, containing at least two tabs, one with the answer, the new steps having been completed, the other starting out where the prior presentation left off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel Accounting 3 – Enter First Month of Transactions</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-accounting-3-enter-first-month-of-transactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-accounting-3-enter-first-month-of-transactions/</guid>
      <description>In this course we will enter common financial transactions for the first month of operations into an accounting system set up using an Excel worksheet.
Learners will learn how to navigate Microsoft Excel as well as how to use a well-designed accounting worksheet, complete with a general journal, trial balance, general ledger, subsidiary ledgers for accounts receivable, accounts payable, &amp;amp; inventory, financial statements and much more.
Excel is a very good tool to learn accounting because it is much more transparent than a database program, like accounting software, QuickBooks being a common example of accounting software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel Accounting 5–Bank Reconciliations-Month 1 &amp; 2</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-accounting-5bank-reconciliations-month-1-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-accounting-5bank-reconciliations-month-1-2/</guid>
      <description>This course will focus on creating bank reconciliations after two months of financial data was entered into an accounting system using Excel.
For most new steps in the process, you will have access to a downloadable Excel Workbook containing at least two tabs, one with the answer, the new steps completed, the other starting where the prior presentation left off.
We will create a bank reconciliation for the first and second months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance #1 Goals, Planning, &amp; Time Value of Money</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance-#1-goals-planning-time-value-of-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance-#1-goals-planning-time-value-of-money/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover the core introductory concepts related to personal finance.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.
We will discuss what personal finance is and what the differences between personal finance, corporate finance, economics, and accounting are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance #2–Financial Statements &amp; Budgeting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance-#2financial-statements-budgeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance-#2financial-statements-budgeting/</guid>
      <description>This course will focus on personal financial statements, a fundamental tool for personal financial planning.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.
Financial statements are the core tool we used to measure our current financial position as well as our past performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance #3–Financial Services &amp; Bank Reconciliation</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance-#3financial-services-bank-reconciliation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance-#3financial-services-bank-reconciliation/</guid>
      <description>This course will focus on the importance of performing the bank reconciliation process and how to complete a bank reconciliation.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Masterclass: Bitcoin, Altcoins, NFTs, DeFi, Metaverse</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crypto-masterclass-bitcoin-altcoins-nfts-defi-metaverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:33:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/crypto-masterclass-bitcoin-altcoins-nfts-defi-metaverse/</guid>
      <description>Cryptos are taking over the digital currency sector by storm, with digital currencies already being termed the money of the future. Many traders take advantage of Bitcoin to earn passive income and diversify their investments in the process.
By taking this course, you’ll learn about the fundamentals of cryptocurrency and the blockchain which will teach you how Cryptos fit into the whole digital currency story.
Firstly, you’ll start by learning the general introduction to money and the background and history of Bitcoin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Finance Fundamentals | Infrastructure &amp; Energy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-finance-fundamentals-infrastructure-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:33:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-finance-fundamentals-infrastructure-energy/</guid>
      <description>Whether you are a fresh graduate or looking for a shift in your career, whether you are coming from an engineering, finance, or law background; delving into the world of Infrastructure Project finance &amp;amp; PPPs might be challenging. The problem begins at the interview stage: The lack of technical knowledge and basic skills could hurt your chances to land your dream job and break into the sector.
We have been there, too, and we completely understand your frustration!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Accounting – Closing Process</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-closing-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-closing-process/</guid>
      <description>The financial accounting closing process is the final step in the accounting cycle. We will learn why the closing process in needed and be able to perform the closing process multiple ways. In addition to instructional video, this course will include downloadable
• Downloadable PDF Files
• Excel Practice Files
• Multiple Choice Practice Questions
• Short Calculation Practice Questions
• Discussion Questions
The PDF files allow us to download reference information we can use offline and as a guide to help us work through the material.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Accounting-Adjusting Entries &amp; Financial Statement</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-adjusting-entries-financial-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-adjusting-entries-financial-statement/</guid>
      <description>Adjusting entries, posting adjusting entries to a worksheet, financial statement creation from an adjusted trial balance, and reversing entries will be covered in this course.
The adjusting entry process is a fundamental bookkeeping and accounting process but is often the accounting process most misunderstood. Because of the name of accounting adjusting entry process we are led to believe that we are adjusting errors made by the accounting department. In other words, we may get the idea that the adjusting process would not be needed if the accounting department did their work perfectly through the period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Accounting-Depreciation Calculation &amp; Fixed Assets</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-depreciation-calculation-fixed-assets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-depreciation-calculation-fixed-assets/</guid>
      <description>Property plant and equipment, also known as plant assets, fixed assets, or depreciable assets is what we will cover.
We will discuss what property plant and equipment is and how to record property plant and equipment. Multiple depreciation methods will be covered including the straight-line depreciation method, the double declining depreciation method, and the units of production depreciation method. We will discuss the pros and cons of each depreciation method and outline a format for structuring any deprecation problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Receivables &amp; The Allowance vs The Direct Write Off Methods</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/receivables-the-allowance-vs-the-direct-write-off-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/receivables-the-allowance-vs-the-direct-write-off-methods/</guid>
      <description>We will discuss receivables, focusing on accounts receivable and notes receivable, reviewing the accounts receivable cycle, the journal entries for recording accounts receivable, and related subsidiary ledgers. We will discuss bad debt and valuing of accounts receivable using two methods, the allowance method and the direct write off method. The accounts receivable account represents money owed to the company but there will be times when the company cannot collect on the account receivables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank Reconciliations &amp; Cash Internal Controls</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bank-reconciliations-cash-internal-controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bank-reconciliations-cash-internal-controls/</guid>
      <description>We will discuss internal controls including what they are, why they are useful, and the objectives of internal controls. We will then move to internal controls specific to cash including bank reconciliations. Bank reconciliations are important controls for both large and small companies. After the double entry accounting system itself, the bank reconciliation is one of the most important internal controls. The bank reconciliation will compare the bank statement to the cash book balance as of a point in time and reconcile the difference between the two.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Accounting – Subsidiary Ledgers &amp; Special Journals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-subsidiary-ledgers-special-journals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-subsidiary-ledgers-special-journals/</guid>
      <description>We record transactions using special journals and track accounts receivable by customer and accounts payable by vendor using subsidiary ledger. We should have a good understanding of debits and credits before this course and we have courses covering debits and credits. We can construct an accounting system where we record every financial transaction using debits and credits in a general journal, posting each journal entry to the general ledger, making the trial balance form the general ledger, and the financial statements from the trial balance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Accounting &amp; Excel–Comprehensive Accounting Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-excelcomprehensive-accounting-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-excelcomprehensive-accounting-course/</guid>
      <description>If we are a business owner or accounting professional who would like to get a better understanding of what our accounting software is doing
Or
An accounting student or student in general that would like to get a better understanding of what our accounting textbook is doing
This course is a course for us.
Business owners, accounting professionals, and accounting students often have the same problem with accounting. . .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop vs QBO Multiple Currencies</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-vs-qbo-multiple-currencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-vs-qbo-multiple-currencies/</guid>
      <description>The course will start by discussing how to get access to both QuickBooks Online and QuickBooks Desktop. Intuit, the owner of QuickBooks often offers a free 30-day trial for each software package. This will be a project based course. We will enter transaction in Excel before entering them into the accounting software, QuickBooks desktop and QuickBooks Online. Excel is more transparent, making it easier to understand the process. QuickBooks will then automate the process making it more efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Financial Planning Course- Beginners to advanced</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-financial-planning-course-beginners-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-financial-planning-course-beginners-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the complete Personal Financial Planning Course...!!!
This course covers managing your money as well as saving and investing. It encompasses budgeting, inflation, net worth, insurance, CIBIL Scores, Credit Card, loans, financial planning thumb rules, power of compounding, financial goals, risk profile, asset allocation, mutual fund &amp;amp; shares investments, retirement planning, tax planning, etc.
Also included in this course is an Excel spreadsheet like a cash flow statement, know your worth- Networth statement, Loan calculator, All in one Financial Goal Calculator Template, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency &amp; Bitcoin for Beginners in Plain English.</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cryptocurrency-bitcoin-for-beginners-in-plain-english./</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cryptocurrency-bitcoin-for-beginners-in-plain-english./</guid>
      <description>The Latest Cryptocurrency Course on Udemy, no old and out of date content. - Let me make you a promise...
If you DON&#39;T learn everything you want about Cryptocurrency, Crypto Trading, Blockchain, DeFi, Ethereum, N FTs and more in the first 30 days of this course then you can have your MONEY BACK ..... and you get to keep your free copy of my Cryptocurrency Book just for trying this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Analysis Certification Course with live trades</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/technical-analysis-certification-course-with-live-trades/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/technical-analysis-certification-course-with-live-trades/</guid>
      <description>This course is created only for the knowledge purpose and from the application of this knowledge you will be a step forward to your career as a technical analyst or an investor or a day trader.
By taking this course you can get a basic understanding of the market how to have a view of a trader and get an edge in market with the help of Technical analysis and study of charts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop Pro-Personal Tax Tracking Tricks</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-pro-personal-tax-tracking-tricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-pro-personal-tax-tracking-tricks/</guid>
      <description>Use QuickBooks to track personal tax item as well as business expenses easily, so that we have more of our year-end tax preparation materials in one place that is well organized. Tracking personal tax-related items in a business QuickBooks account is actually a highly controversial topic in the world of accounting and bookkeeping, the conventional wisdom being that we should separate any personal items from the business files as much as possible, whether they be tax related or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop vs. Excel</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-vs.-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-vs.-excel/</guid>
      <description>Would we like to run our business better using accounting software? Would we like to better understand accounting concepts, how they apply to accounting software, and work accounting problems MUCH faster?
Would we like to advance our career by increase our skills with business software?
This comprehensive QuickBooks &amp;amp; Excel course can help to achieve these goals
Why choose this course?
Current video content means all QuickBooks lectures are done recently as of this post rather than adding a few new videos to content from prior years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Token Engineering for Web3 Platforms</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-token-engineering-for-web3-platforms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 21:50:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-token-engineering-for-web3-platforms/</guid>
      <description>Everyone knows that web3 platforms are decentralized…but what really enables decentralization…tokens…
The distribution of value and control in the decentralized ecosystem is primarily driven by various kinds of tokens.
Tokens are often touted as investment opportunities but the primary role of tokens on web3 platforms is to capture the value generated by the platforms and distribute value and control among the network participants to incentivize them so that they behave in a way that contributes to the smooth functioning and growth of the ecosystem itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xero Cloud Accounting Basic to Pro Complete Course 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/xero-cloud-accounting-basic-to-pro-complete-course-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 21:50:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/xero-cloud-accounting-basic-to-pro-complete-course-2022/</guid>
      <description>This course takes you from beginners level and gives enough knowledge so you feel comfort while using Xero , this training program is ideal for Freelancers , who want to learn how Bookkeeping , accounting and payroll work is performed on clients projects practically
About This Training
This Xero Cloud Accounting Training Comes with scenario-based activities covering in practical assignments. This course covers essential accounting skills and you will get a certificate upon completion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Accounting – Payroll</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-payroll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-payroll/</guid>
      <description>This financial accounting and payroll class will cover payroll topics including payroll legislation, payroll calculations, and entering payroll journal entries.
Because payroll is becoming more complex and more of a specialized field it is difficult to find content that puts it all together in one spot like this course does. We will discuss payroll legislation, going over a wide variety of laws that influence payroll. Because payroll is such a broad topic and because it overlaps with other areas of business like human resources many laws influence the processing of payroll.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See 27 Ways to Make Money Online with Your Smartphone!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/see-27-ways-to-make-money-online-with-your-smartphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:57:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/see-27-ways-to-make-money-online-with-your-smartphone/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to make money online with your smartphone? Do you wanna see real money-making apps that pay in 2021?
Then this course is PERFECT FOR YOU!
I created this course because every single day people ask me for the best way to get paid just by using their smartphones.
Learn just 1 strategy and you&#39;ll earn your course price back. The rest will be pure profits for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accounting Interview Questions: Go from ZERO to HERO</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/accounting-interview-questions-go-from-zero-to-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 20:03:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/accounting-interview-questions-go-from-zero-to-hero/</guid>
      <description>This interview exams sets are designed in a way for the candidate to prepare for the accounting position interview. This course will provide you the basic understanding of how accounting works and will help you build the base foundation of the accounting so that you can crack the any accounting interview. Accounting is one of the most important skills for people pursuing a career in Finance.
It helps you understand whether a business is profitable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFT Meisterkurs - Das große Non-Fungible Token Komplettpaket</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/nft-meisterkurs-das-gro%C3%9Fe-non-fungible-token-komplettpaket/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 20:03:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/nft-meisterkurs-das-gro%C3%9Fe-non-fungible-token-komplettpaket/</guid>
      <description>Suchst du nach einer vollständigen Schritt-für-Schritt-Anleitung um Non-fungible Tokens (NFTs) zu prägen (minten), zu kaufen &amp;amp; zu verkaufen? Dann ist dieser NFT Meisterkurs genau das richtige für dich! Ich nehme dich mit in die NFT-Welt und zeige dir alle wichtigen Grundlagen, um NFTs zu verstehen und mit ihnen Geld zu verdienen.
Auf dich warten 2,5+ Stunden Videomaterial, 30+ Lektionen, Begleitdokumente und Quizze. Du erhältst zudem persönliche Beratung von mir und erhöhst deine Lernerfahrung durch immer neue Lektionen, aktuelle Inhalte und vieles mehr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anti-Money Laundering Concepts: AML, KYC and Compliance</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/anti-money-laundering-concepts-aml-kyc-and-compliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 13:36:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/anti-money-laundering-concepts-aml-kyc-and-compliance/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the course on Anti-Money Laundering (AML), where you will learn about the key issues faced by financial institutions today: Money Laundering and Terrorist Financing. This course will educate you on Money Laundering and Terrorist Financing laws, Know Your Customer, Customer Due Diligence, Economic Sanctions and Politically Exposed Persons. This is a comprehensive course that captures all relevant concepts required for training employees of an organization.
We will start the course by understanding the term Money Laundering and will then cover the process &amp;amp; impact of the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency  Secret Trading Strategy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cryptocurrency-secret-trading-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:57:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cryptocurrency-secret-trading-strategy/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Cryptocurrency Secret Trading Strategy Course, in This Course I Teach You How to You Can Predict the Next Market Move With High Accuracy. This Course Is for All Kinds of Person Who Are Interested in Trading.
So let&#39;s introduce with our chapters
Section 01) What&#39;s Needed to Get Started
In this chapter I will teach you basic usage of trading view for use these strategy perfectly.
Section 02 ) Top 3 Supertrend Trading Strategy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Metaverse verstehen &amp; investieren: Die Metaverse Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/metaverse-verstehen-investieren-die-metaverse-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:57:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/metaverse-verstehen-investieren-die-metaverse-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Spätestens seit Facebook sich Ende Oktober 2021 in Meta umbenannt hat, ist es in aller Munde: das Metaverse oder Metaversum. Aber was wissen wir eigentlich wirklich darüber außer, dass wir in Zukunft vielleicht noch mehr im Internet sein werden als ohnehin schon und das 24/7 - so jedenfalls die Vorstellung - mit einer VR-Brille auf dem Kopf. Aber ist es so einfach? Ist das Metaverse das nächste &#34;große Ding&#34; oder handelt es sich hier nur um eine geniale Marketingstrategie des größten Social Media Unternehmens der Welt?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Enterprise-Classes-Responsibility Accounting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-enterprise-classes-responsibility-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:30:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-enterprise-classes-responsibility-accounting/</guid>
      <description>This course is a project-based course using the free trial version of QuickBooks Enterprise, practicing the feature of class tracking for both the balance sheet and profit and loss, the class tracking feature applied to responsibility accounting.
We will learn how to download the free trial version of QuickBooks Enterprise and set up a new company file to work in.
The course will show how to turn on the class tracking feature and discuss the differences between class tracking for the QuickBooks Pro version of the software and the QuickBooks Enterprise version.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Enterprise - Two Businesses &amp; Personal in One</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-enterprise-two-businesses-personal-in-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 20:40:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-enterprise-two-businesses-personal-in-one/</guid>
      <description>This is a project-based course that will use the free trial version of QuickBooks Enterprise to track multiple business financial data as well as personal financial data in one QuickBooks Enterprise file. We will learn to generate and analyze both the balance sheet and income statement reports by class.
We will learn the difference between the QuickBooks Enterprise class tracking feature and the QuickBooks Pro class tracking feature.
The course will show how to turn on the class tracking feature in QuickBooks Enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sage 300 people ,payroll and hr, employees management 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sage-300-people-payroll-and-hr-employees-management-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:10:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sage-300-people-payroll-and-hr-employees-management-2022/</guid>
      <description>The purpose of the basic Training is to provide you with the necessary skills that will enable you to take full ownership of the payroll function. You will be able to complete an entire pay run on the Sage 300 People system and reconcile input, etc. to ensure accurate payroll data. you will learn to manage employees information such as earnings, deductions, taxable benefits, company contributions and leave .Apply for leave , manage their claims , manage their own personal details like bank accounts and next of kin information , View current and previous payslips and tax certificates and print selected reports , complete a performance review ,start a free workflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accounting, Financial Accounting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/accounting-financial-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 17:02:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/accounting-financial-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Hello there and welcome to the Best support Financial Accounting Course on Udemy (Learn Finance and Accounting the Easy Way)! I am gonna take you right the way through out the course so you&#39;ll see my course will help you understand underlying principles and concepts relating to financial accounting and technical proficiency in the use of double-entry accounting techniques including the preparation of the basic financial statements.
After taking this course you will understand how to create, analyze and forecast an income statement, balance sheet and cash flow statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABA CTFA Certified Trust and Financial Advisor Practice Exam</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aba-ctfa-certified-trust-and-financial-advisor-practice-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aba-ctfa-certified-trust-and-financial-advisor-practice-exam/</guid>
      <description>What Exactly Is Certification?
Certification is an amazing pathway to getting a high paying career in some of the best jobs in the world without spending thousands of dollars attending a four-year college.
Get Ready To Prepare Like You’ve Never Prepared Before
As we often say at AFAQ Formations, work smarter not harder. You are about to see a study guide that took hours of hard collection work, expert preparation, and constant feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accounting for Beginners: Financial Accounting Made Easy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/accounting-for-beginners-financial-accounting-made-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/accounting-for-beginners-financial-accounting-made-easy/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever had an Accounting Professor which just rambled and rambled, making Accounting sound like a different language ? Or have you ever tried going on to YouTube to take Accounting classes but just got lost within the sea of information ?
Trust me, I know how that feels. I too went through the same frustration during my Undergraduate and Graduate Studies listening to Professor talk and talk while I was confused within the 1st 10 minutes of class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Budgeting for Beginners in this Post Pandemic World</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-budgeting-for-beginners-in-this-post-pandemic-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-budgeting-for-beginners-in-this-post-pandemic-world/</guid>
      <description>The world is getting more and more uncertain in this post pandemic environment, with many big companies going bankrupt and many jobs being less secured. Aside from that, as we were not taught financial literacy in school, many families has declared themselves bankrupt. It is truly a scary time. Having said that, those who saved money are less impacted and they are doing a little better at this very uncertain time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Step by Step Guide to Get Out of Debt Easily</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-step-by-step-guide-to-get-out-of-debt-easily/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-step-by-step-guide-to-get-out-of-debt-easily/</guid>
      <description>I know its a very difficult time for many families including for us right now as businesses are recording losses and many are losing their jobs during this period. Personally when I walk around, I notice many shops closing up and I see worried faces among grocery buyers as the illusion of &#39;job security&#39; is shattered. In our instinct, among the questions running in our heads is &#34;How do I gain more control on my finances ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CPA Auditing and Attestation (AUD) Practice Exams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cpa-auditing-and-attestation-aud-practice-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cpa-auditing-and-attestation-aud-practice-exams/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to crush the CPA Auditing and Attestation Exam and get certified?
Today is a competitive world and the smartest, best, and most qualified get paid a lot of money to work in amazing fields. But you don’t need a college degree, certification is an amazing path that opens up new opportunities and shows employers that you are the cream of the crop. We know that AICPA certification will add some flair to that resume and help you get amazing new roles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance fundamentals for beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance-fundamentals-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance-fundamentals-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>We keep hearing about financial terms all the time in the news, in conversations, and in almost every kind of media that reaches us. But most of the time we just filter out that information as noise due to the tiresome jargon. What if you just spend a couple of hours and get a basic framework to start making sense of that noise? The main objective of this course is to create awareness about the bigger picture of the finance ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance/Budgeting Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance/budgeting-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance/budgeting-basics/</guid>
      <description>In this course we will cover the basics on how to create and balance a budget. Save for the future, retire, and adjust your mindset for future financial success. 6 in 10 Americans don&#39;t have enough saved to cover an emergency. After this course, you will have the foundation built to keep you from becoming one of them. This course has helped over 1,000 students on Udemy take control of their finances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tally ERP9 With GST Step By Step Guide From Basic to Advance</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tally-erp9-with-gst-step-by-step-guide-from-basic-to-advance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tally-erp9-with-gst-step-by-step-guide-from-basic-to-advance/</guid>
      <description>Recent Student&#39;s Reviews
***This Course Is Very Useful And Helpful To Me, I Teach To Tally Program In This Your All Videos. Thank You - Zaid Saiyed***
***It Was Really Amazing Session Where I Brushed Up All My Concepts In A Very Simple Method - Keshvi Balodia***
***I Have Really Enjoyed With This Course And It Is An Amazing Course. The Practical Example I Did Myself And It Is So Worth - Jasmin***</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain &amp; NFTs (Basics): Smart Contracts to QR NFTs</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/blockchain-nfts-basics-smart-contracts-to-qr-nfts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 21:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/blockchain-nfts-basics-smart-contracts-to-qr-nfts/</guid>
      <description>This course will be on the development of Blockchain and Cryptocurrency Technology through the SOLIDITY language. Solidity is a curly-bracket language influenced by Object-Oriented languages including JavaScript and is designed to target the Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM). In this course, you will be taught to create smart contracts for uses such as voting, crowdfunding, blind auctions, and multi-signature wallets using the SOLIDITY language.
Upon successful completion of the course, each student will show tangible evidence of growth and maturity in the following areas: 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate CAMS Practice Tests | ACAMS 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-cams-practice-tests-acams-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 21:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-cams-practice-tests-acams-2022/</guid>
      <description>What is CAMS Exam?
Certified Anti-Money Laundering Specialist (CAMS) is the gold standard in AML certifications which is widely recognized and accepted by financial institutions, Banks, governments and international law enforcement agencies, with more than 40,000 CAMS graduates worldwide. The certification helps to land / boost your career in the field of Financial Crime Compliance.
With the recent spike in higher salaries for AML/CFT practitioners, a CAMS holder earns 42% more compared to non-CAMS certified counterpart!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Altcoins - Investing In Altcoins &amp; ICOs!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/altcoins-investing-in-altcoins-icos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 21:27:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/altcoins-investing-in-altcoins-icos/</guid>
      <description>I truly believe Cryptocurrency is the opportunity of a lifetime to participate in wealth redistribution. It is the time that anyone; no matter your level of knowledge or investment; to generate incredible returns with your own money, whilst investing in projects that fits with your values. I also strongly believe that “Blockchain” - the technology that underpins Cryptocurrencies will radically change our lives for the better in ways no one can fathom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Company Registration In UK~ Make paypal &amp; Stripe Business</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/company-registration-in-uk~-make-paypal-stripe-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 16:38:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/company-registration-in-uk~-make-paypal-stripe-business/</guid>
      <description>Earn in many ways by selling this skill on fiverr &amp;amp; register companies for people in UK who are mostly dropshipping. (This training in Urdu/Hindi only enroll if you understand the language)Whatsapp Group Access &amp;amp; lifetime mentorship is only for students who enroll through my website.
Register a company in UK
Buying a virtual address
Buying UK number from Pakistan
Opening a bank account in UK
VPS (Virtual private Server)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Changes to accounting Industry &amp; CFO Trends 2022 Beyond</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/10-changes-to-accounting-industry-cfo-trends-2022-beyond/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/10-changes-to-accounting-industry-cfo-trends-2022-beyond/</guid>
      <description>Technology and Innovations in Business models has disrupted so many industries in recent years. Taxi service, travel, banking and shopping have been radically transformed by technology and innovation. These industries have been turned upside down and reshaped in just a few years.
The same is true for the accounting industry. Accounting is no longer a person at a desk opening mail and processing invoices. A majority of invoices are sent electronically, and many are automatically paid through a processing system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of IAS 16  - Property Plant &amp; Equipments</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentals-of-ias-16-property-plant-equipments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentals-of-ias-16-property-plant-equipments/</guid>
      <description>IAS 16 establishes principles for recognizing property, plant, and equipment as assets, measuring their carrying amounts, and measuring the depreciation charges and impairment losses to be recognized in relation to them. Property, plant, and equipment are tangible items that:
· are held for use in the production or supply of goods or services, for rental to others, or for administrative purposes; and
· are expected to be used during more than one period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Analysis and Financial Modeling using MS Excel</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-analysis-and-financial-modeling-using-ms-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 19:20:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-analysis-and-financial-modeling-using-ms-excel/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re looking for a complete course on understanding Financial Analysis and Financial Modeling using MS Excel to drive business decisions, right?
You&#39;ve found the right Financial Analysis using MS Excel course! Financial Analysis and Financial analytics provides scientific support to decision-making concerning a firm&#39;s money related matters. This course addresses the topic of Financial analysis with a practical focus, focusing especially on demystifying analytics for finance managers, financial analysts from both statistical and computing point of view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop – Export Directly to Tax Software Lacerte</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-export-directly-to-tax-software-lacerte/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 18:10:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-export-directly-to-tax-software-lacerte/</guid>
      <description>The course will discuss options for getting access to QuickBooks desktop software including a free 30-day test period offered by Intuit, the owners of QuickBooks Desktop.
Learners will know how to set up tax line mapping for a sole proprietorship and S Corporation, tax line mapping allowing users to export financial data from QuickBooks directly into tax software.
We will be using Lacerte tax software for our examples. Lacerte tax software is owned by Intuit and a 30-day free trial may be available to test out Lacerte tax software as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABA Certified Regulatory Compliance Manager Practice Exams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aba-certified-regulatory-compliance-manager-practice-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 19:15:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aba-certified-regulatory-compliance-manager-practice-exams/</guid>
      <description>What Exactly Is Certification?
Certification is an amazing pathway to getting a high paying career in some of the best jobs in the world without spending thousands of dollars attending a four-year college.
Get Ready To Prepare Like You’ve Never Prepared Before
As we often say at AFAQ Formations, work smarter not harder. You are about to see a study guide that took hours of hard collection work, expert preparation, and constant feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrencies: complet practical course on crypto trading</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cryptocurrencies-complet-practical-course-on-crypto-trading/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 19:15:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cryptocurrencies-complet-practical-course-on-crypto-trading/</guid>
      <description>Have you witnessed all the profits that have been made by the various cryptocurrencies without knowing how to profit from them? Reassure yourself, it will not happen to you anymore. this course was created in order to allow everyone to know how it is possible to integrate the market of cryptocurrencies and it is accessible to all! At the end of the course, you will not only be able to buy your first cryptocurrency but you will also have a good base on how to trade or invest in this market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Inventory Management in Microsoft Excel &amp;TALLY ERP9</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-inventory-management-in-microsoft-excel-tally-erp9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-inventory-management-in-microsoft-excel-tally-erp9/</guid>
      <description>Recent Student&#39;s Reviews
*** This course is well detailed in inventory management. I really learnt how to make practical use of excel, tally ERP9 and good inventory valuation (Williams Oguamah) ***
**Yes it is a good match for me. It will help me in my career path ( Dineo ) ***
*** it was awesome to learn &amp;amp; get insights from this course (Haritha.L) ***
*** Very Helpful (JULIUS IGNACIO)***</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Risk Measurement: A Beginner&#39;s Guide to Process Metrics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/risk-measurement-a-beginners-guide-to-process-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/risk-measurement-a-beginners-guide-to-process-metrics/</guid>
      <description>A risk measure is used in financial mathematics to calculate the amount of an asset or collection of assets (traditionally cash) that should be kept in reserve. The goal of this reserve is for the regulator to accept the risks that financial institutions, such as banks and insurance firms, take. Convex and coherent risk measurement has received a lot of attention in recent years.
In this course:
We will talk about how risk and uncertainty are measured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACAMS|CAMS Exam Practice Exams 2022 (&#43;detailed explanations)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/acamscams-exam-practice-exams-2022-detailed-explanations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 21:29:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/acamscams-exam-practice-exams-2022-detailed-explanations/</guid>
      <description>What is CAMS Exam?
Certified Anti-Money Laundering Specialist (CAMS) is the gold standard in AML certifications which is widely recognized and accepted by financial institutions, Banks, governments and international law enforcement agencies, with more than 40,000 CAMS graduates worldwide. The certification helps to land / boost your career in the field of Financial Crime Compliance.
With the recent spike in higher salaries for AML/CFT practitioners, a CAMS holder earns 42% more compared to non-CAMS certified counterpart!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forex strategies for algorithmic trading 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/forex-strategies-for-algorithmic-trading-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 21:29:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/forex-strategies-for-algorithmic-trading-2022/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to create quantitative FOREX strategies to earn up to 60%/YEAR ?
You already have some trading knowledge and you want to learn about quantitative trading/finance?
You are simply a curious person who wants to get into this subject to monetize and diversify your knowledge?
If you answer at least one of these questions, I welcome you to this course. All the applications of the course will be done using Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Online vs. Excel</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-vs.-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 21:29:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-vs.-excel/</guid>
      <description>Would we like to run our business better using accounting software?
Would we like to better understand accounting concepts, how they apply to accounting software, and work accounting problems MUCH faster?
Would we like to advance our career by increase our skills with business software?
This comprehensive QuickBooks Online &amp;amp; Excel course can help to achieve these goals
Why choose this course? Current video content means all QuickBooks lectures are done recently as of this post rather than adding a few new videos to content from prior years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Analysis Mastery for Financial Markets.</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/technical-analysis-mastery-for-financial-markets./</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 21:10:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/technical-analysis-mastery-for-financial-markets./</guid>
      <description>This course is set out for you to gain expertise in technical analysis in a very simple way . This course allows its learners to move from beginner to advanced level in a step-by-step method as outlined below:
The course introduces the candlesticks and its patterns explaining the learners about the language of the financial markets and develops their skill to not only read but understand the market.
Following this , the course explains the key chart patterns that are essential for any trader to know in order to trade efficiently and exposes learners to some of the key indicators which are used by many professionals to make informed trading decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixed Income Securities: Become a Bond Analyst &amp; Investor</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fixed-income-securities-become-a-bond-analyst-investor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 21:10:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fixed-income-securities-become-a-bond-analyst-investor/</guid>
      <description>Investing in bonds has a lot of financial benefits for investors. It provides a regular stream of income and widens their investment portfolio. Bonds also carry low market volatility.
It is a safe investment plan which allows investors to preserve and increase their capital. Investing in top-quality government bonds doesn&#39;t come with a default risk for investors.
This course is for investors and individuals who show interest in widening their scope on the fundamentals of fixed-income instruments and exploring the structures and features of the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete and Special Bitcoin Trading Course In The World</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-and-special-bitcoin-trading-course-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 21:06:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-and-special-bitcoin-trading-course-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Bitcoin Trading: Trade Bitcoins &amp;amp; Cryptocurrency course 2021 PAID VERSION In this Bitcoin Trading Course, you gone to learn what it&#39;s Bitcoin, and the History of Bitcoin, when it start and why people they using Bitcoin WHO is Satoshi Nakamoto.
And you gone to understand all the basics about Bitcoin Wallet and what its the types of Bitcoins wallets you can use, plus How to get Bitcoin and and how to change Bitcoin to usd and what its Bitcoin Mining And you gone to learn why all the Cryptocurrency and Altcoin they follow Bitcoin and what its the Market Cap of Bitcoin plus the Daily Trading Volume in Bitcoin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trading Algorithmique avec Python: Analyse Technique</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/trading-algorithmique-avec-python-analyse-technique/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 21:27:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/trading-algorithmique-avec-python-analyse-technique/</guid>
      <description>Vous avez déjà des connaissances en python et vous voulez monétiser et diversifier vos connaissances ?
Vous avez déjà des connaissances en trading et vous voulez apprendre le trading algorithmique ?
Vous êtes tout simplement une personne curieuse qui souhaite s&#39;intéresser à ce sujet ?
Si vous répondez à au moins une de ces questions, je vous souhaite la bienvenue dans ce cours. Pour les débutants en python, pas de panique, il existe un cours de python (petit mais condensé) pour maîtriser ces connaissances en python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Payroll Management in Excel &amp;TALLY ERP9 &amp;TallyPrime</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-payroll-management-in-excel-tally-erp9-tallyprime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 13:34:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-payroll-management-in-excel-tally-erp9-tallyprime/</guid>
      <description>Recent Student&#39;s Reviews
*** This is a wonderful course for learning about payroll and how that is to me maintained on Tally ERP. All my doubts about maintaining payroll on Tally got cleared after doing this course - Ayushi ***
*** Good &amp;amp; Detailed EXplanation about every topics - Ujjawal Kumar ***
*** About this course is easy understand payroll process in Excel &amp;amp; Tally and help develop my knowledge - Shijith ***</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAMS certification: A Beginner&#39;s Guide Anti-Money Laundering</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cams-certification-a-beginners-guide-anti-money-laundering/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 18:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cams-certification-a-beginners-guide-anti-money-laundering/</guid>
      <description>Do you possess the necessary expertise to spot suspicious transactions?
If you answered yes, then the Certified Anti-Money Laundering Specialist (CAMS) certification is a highly sought-after way to start or enhance your career in the Anti-Money Laundering and Counter-Terrorism Financing Sector. And, if you&#39;re still wondering if the CAMS is worthwhile, the answer is emphatically yes.
So, let&#39;s get started on a rewarding and reputable career as an Anti-Money Laundering Professional.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency/Bitcoin - Made Easy (First Timer&#39;s Guide)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cryptocurrency/bitcoin-made-easy-first-timers-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 13:29:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cryptocurrency/bitcoin-made-easy-first-timers-guide/</guid>
      <description>Updated: January 2022
With technologies moving fast into the future, we should also start our education and take part in this amazing new digital technology revolution.
People that have reached financial success always do 3 things: 1. Research new business ventures and investment possibilities,
2. Stay on top of what is happening on the market,
3. Predict where the future is heading in terms of technologies and innovations.
So if you want answers to the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geld verdienen mit NFT - Sammeln, kaufen, verkaufen &amp; Gaming</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/geld-verdienen-mit-nft-sammeln-kaufen-verkaufen-gaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 12:27:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/geld-verdienen-mit-nft-sammeln-kaufen-verkaufen-gaming/</guid>
      <description>Die Welt der NFTs und der digitalen Kunst revolutioniert die Welt und zieht immer mehr Künstler, Gamer und Investoren in ihren Bann. NFTs geben Künstlern die Macht, auch langfristig am Erfolg ihrer Arbeit teilzuhaben.
NFTs können jedoch wenig verwirrend sein. Was sind sie? Warum redet jeder über sie? Was bewirken sie? Welche Technologie steckt dahinter? Und: Kann auch ich damit Geld verdienen?
Das sind alles Fragen, die ich mit dir gemeinsam in diesem NFT-Kurs beantworten möchte.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Passive Income With Bitcoin Lending</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-make-passive-income-with-bitcoin-lending/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 16:49:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-make-passive-income-with-bitcoin-lending/</guid>
      <description>Passive Income Course Covering Everything You Need To Passively Earn Money From Bitcoin Lending!
******************************************************************************************
Discover How to Make Passive Income Online Using A 6-Step Bitcoin Lending System:
- A step-by-step video for each of the 6-Steps in the Automated System!
- Inside look at my personal accounts!
- Unlimited earnings, with a small upfront investment!
- How to do all of this without any Fees!
- This course is about results!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accounting Principles</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/accounting-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 17:47:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/accounting-principles/</guid>
      <description>Accounting is very important subject that convert all financial events of the business into figures which allow managers and other users to report, analyze, and take decisions that help to read the financial position of a business and project future results.
I built this course using multiple reliable resources in Accounting. The content is based on U.S. GAAP Accounting standards, I also used my own knowledge and experience which I earned throughout my career for more than 15 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bilanzanalyse mit Excel</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bilanzanalyse-mit-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 17:15:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bilanzanalyse-mit-excel/</guid>
      <description>Allgemein
&#34;Die Bilanz muss immer aufgehen&#34; - Der klassische Spruch aus der Finanzabteilung bzw. Rechnungswesen.
Es ist schon relativ herausfordernd, die klassischen Kennzahlen einer Bilanz zu lesen, zu verstehen und zu interpretieren. Dabei passiert es oft, dass mehrere Excel-Dateien verwendet werden und immer wieder mit kopieren und einfügen die Daten regelrecht zu &#34;sammeln&#34;.
Das muss nicht sein. Sie können wunderbar nur 1 Excel-Datei für Ihre Bilanzanalyse verwenden inkl. Cashflow, GuV, ROI und der dazugehörigen Kennzahlen-Analyse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aprende Análisis Técnico de Figuras - Chartismo</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprende-an%C3%A1lisis-t%C3%A9cnico-de-figuras-chartismo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 12:36:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprende-an%C3%A1lisis-t%C3%A9cnico-de-figuras-chartismo/</guid>
      <description>A lo largo de este curso vamos a aprender todo acerca del Análisis Técnico principalmente enfocándonos en el Análisis Chartista basándonos principalmente en el Precio y Volumen para poder Analizar e Identificar patrones y figuras como: los Triángulos, Hombros Cabezas Hombro, Doble/Triple Techo/Suelo y muchas otras figuras para poder ganar dinero en los mercados financieros tanto para Acciones, Forex, Criptomonedas, Materias Primas o cualquier otro activo bursátil. No requiere experiencia previa ya que empezamos desde los conceptos mas básicos hasta un nivel mas avanzado.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>أساسيات المحاسبة المالية</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%A3%D8%B3%D8%A7%D8%B3%D9%8A%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D8%AD%D8%A7%D8%B3%D8%A8%D8%A9-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%8A%D8%A9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 17:51:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%A3%D8%B3%D8%A7%D8%B3%D9%8A%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D8%AD%D8%A7%D8%B3%D8%A8%D8%A9-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%8A%D8%A9/</guid>
      <description>انت فى الصريق الصحيح لتطوير مهاراتك لتصبح محترف فى المحاسبة كل ما تحتاجه فى كورس واحد تم تصميم المحتوى التدريبي لهذا الكورس على اساس احتياجات سوق العمل و يتميز هذا الكورس بربط الاطار النظرى للمحاسبة بالواقع العملى و المستندات الفعلية المستخدمة فى الشركات الكورس بنظام سؤال و جواب لتسهيل طريقة الشرحو يتناول الكورس اجابات هذه الاسئلة على سبيل المثال وليس الحصر ما هي المحاسبة؟
ما هي الجوانب الأساسية في المحاسبة ؟</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Statement analysis</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-statement-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 15:34:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-statement-analysis/</guid>
      <description>عالم تحليل الاداء المالي للشركات وعالم الاستثمار قد يكون فيه بعض الغموض لشريحة واسعة من الناس, لهذا السبب قررنا انشاء كورس &#34;تحليل القوائم المالية&#34; حتى يكون بمقدورك تحليل سلوك الشركات المالي بشكل سليم.
الكورس هو كورس استثماري يهدف إلى ممارسة وفهم عالم الاستثمار طويل الأجل من خلال دراسة وتحليل البيانات المالية للشركات لفهم سلوك الشركة المالي
الكورس سيعطيك خريطة الطريق للاستثمار الأنسب ولفهم كيفية عمل الشركات &#34;وراء الكواليس&#34;.
ميزة أخرى كبيرة للكورس، ليست فقط في الاستثمار ، ولكن من حيث أنها تفتح لك عالما جديدا ، وجهة نظر أخرى حول السلوك المالي لحياتك, لا سيما ان كنت صاحب بيزنس او شخص يريد ان يتعلم موضوع التحليل المالي للشركات لاي سبب كان.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January- a month of sales : Economic Analysis</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/january-a-month-of-sales-economic-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 21:20:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/january-a-month-of-sales-economic-analysis/</guid>
      <description>THIS COURSE IS CURRENT AS AT 4th January 2022
The course includes a WORKBOOK.
A new section has been added about...you!
Black Friday Economics looks at the Economics behind Black Friday - but also the Ethics.
We look at:
1. Black Friday history
2. Pricing policy - not just &#39;sale price; but the strategies within the strategies!
3. Black Friday &#39;traps&#39;
4. The psychology behind deals - you are welcome to share your own personal experiences!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The complete forex course from scratch to professional</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-forex-course-from-scratch-to-professional/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 17:13:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-forex-course-from-scratch-to-professional/</guid>
      <description>The complete Forex trading course from scratch to professional (Step by step with live trading example) + Free Template And Indicators
(((((( student feedback
-Kavindra Lakshitha -
Good Teacher with an amazing strategy. I brushed up my knowledge perfectly from his course. Thank you Thomas. Thank you Udemy.
-Chathuranga prabash Ananda-
I have learnt many things about forex and mt4 and also a new strategy...Thank you so much for giving us this opportunity to become online entrepreneur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Simple Bitcoin Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-simple-bitcoin-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 13:43:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-simple-bitcoin-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>(Don&#39;t buy this course. Buy Bitcoin and HODL)
Wherever you turn, Bitcoin seems to be there. It is in the spotlight especially after the world&#39;s richest man joined the frenzy.
What is it?
Why are people going crazy about it?
How did it all start?
Satoshi Nakamoto, the mysterious internet figure gave birth to Bitcoin in 2008 as a way to escape the global financial system. What was ridiculed in the earlier days is now a trillion-dollar asset in market capitalization!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masterclass de NFT: Aprende desde cero</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/masterclass-de-nft-aprende-desde-cero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 13:12:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/masterclass-de-nft-aprende-desde-cero/</guid>
      <description>Bienvenido a la revolución del arte, el mundo del Arte Digital, Cripto Arte y NFTs llegó para quedarse. Después de que el 11 de marzo de 2021 un NFT se subastara por 69 millones de dólares, muchas personas se preguntan qué es el Criptoarte y cómo se hace.
Aquí aprenderás paso a paso, cómo crear una obra digital de cripto arte y convertirla a NFT o token no fungible.
Conoce el potencial de los NFT y cómo están impactando al mundo actualmente.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aprende Análisis Técnico Avanzado Ondas Elliott y Fibonacci</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprende-an%C3%A1lisis-t%C3%A9cnico-avanzado-ondas-elliott-y-fibonacci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 19:17:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprende-an%C3%A1lisis-t%C3%A9cnico-avanzado-ondas-elliott-y-fibonacci/</guid>
      <description>A lo largo de este curso vamos a ver todo lo relacionado al uso del Análisis Técnico de una forma Avanzada basándonos en la Teoría de las Ondas de Elliott y en Fibonacci para poder analizar activos de nuestro interés de una manera profesional para poder hacer Trading y operaciones en cualquier tipo de mercado tanto de Criptomonedas, Acciones, Forex, Futuros, para poder ganar dinero en el mercado de manera consistente.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kripto Paralarda Haber Analizi Ve Ön Satışlar</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kripto-paralarda-haber-analizi-ve-%C3%B6n-sat%C4%B1%C5%9Flar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kripto-paralarda-haber-analizi-ve-%C3%B6n-sat%C4%B1%C5%9Flar/</guid>
      <description>Bu kurs kripto para borsasında haber analizi ve ön satışlar ile ilgili önemli bütün bilgileri barındırıyor. Haber analizlerini hangi haberlere ağırlık vererek incelemeyi ve bu haberlere de en kolay ve hızlı yoldan ulaşarak gelir elde etmek amacımızdır. Boğa ve ayı sezonlarında haber analizi ile al sat yaparken en çok nelere dikkat etmeleri gerektiklerini ve nasıl hareket etmeleri gerektiğini öğretmek amacımızdır.
Haber analizi yaparken hangi haberin fiyata etki edeceğini, hangi haberin fiyata etki etmeyeceğini öğrenmek.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>فوركس بالعربي</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D9%81%D9%88%D8%B1%D9%83%D8%B3-%D8%A8%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B9%D8%B1%D8%A8%D9%8A/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D9%81%D9%88%D8%B1%D9%83%D8%B3-%D8%A8%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B9%D8%B1%D8%A8%D9%8A/</guid>
      <description>أي شخص مهتم بالتداول في الفوركس ويريد أن يبدأ بشكل صحيح من خلال تعلم الفوركس بإحترافية بدلاً من بدء التداول بشكل عشوائي ، ليست هناك حاجة إلى خبرة تداول سابقة سواء في الفوركس أو البورصة.
من خلال الكورس يمكنك الإستيعاب الكامل لمبادئ ومصطلحات الفوركس ، التعرف على معظم عمليات الفوركس وفهم آلية عملها ، القدرة على بدء التداول ووضع أستراتيجية للمتاجرة وأخيراً التعرف على المخاطر المحتملة في التداول.
يبدأ الكورس بمقدمة عن المدرب ومحتويات الكورس</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Trade Forex Market Structures And Patterns</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-trade-forex-market-structures-and-patterns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 00:29:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-trade-forex-market-structures-and-patterns/</guid>
      <description>Discover the secrets to trading profitably and consistently for maximum profits. This course contains powerful information that can guide you on how to exploit patterns that arise now and then in the markets. Discover when and where to trade, and when and where not to trade.
Thank you for joining our course because you are about to gain more knowledge about the formation of classic forex chart patterns and structures. It is true that they are valid and do indeed work; provided that they are used properly, at the appropriate price levels, and with the correct knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Course on Blockchain and Crypto Currency</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-course-on-blockchain-and-crypto-currency/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:46:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-course-on-blockchain-and-crypto-currency/</guid>
      <description>If you are new to cryptocurrencies and blockchain then you may have some questions in mind such as:
What are bitcoin and ethereum blockchains?
How are blocks interlinked with each other in blockchain?
Understanding these questions might be overwhelming but this course will help you understand all the complex topics.I have divided this course into 10 different sections and you will have a very good understanding of blockchain and cryptocurrency after this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking: You Can Give Great Financial Presentations</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-you-can-give-great-financial-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:36:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-you-can-give-great-financial-presentations/</guid>
      <description>Public Speaking. Imagine giving a financial presentation and your audience is following you closely, understanding your key points and remembering the most important numbers and trends. Would you like to be able to give a financial presentation knowing that you will appear confident and relaxed, and that your audience can clearly understand your key takeaways? In this How to Give Financial Presentations Public Speaking course you will learn the following: *How to avoid the most common blunders in financial presentations that make most audience members zone out *How to use PowerPoint effectively *How to get audiences to understand complex financial concepts *How to get your audience to remember your most important numbers and messages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Der große Börsenhandel Ratgeber: Investieren leicht gemacht</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/der-gro%C3%9Fe-b%C3%B6rsenhandel-ratgeber-investieren-leicht-gemacht/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/der-gro%C3%9Fe-b%C3%B6rsenhandel-ratgeber-investieren-leicht-gemacht/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Eine Investition in Wissen bringt die besten Zinsen.&#34; - Benjamin Franklin Was sind deine finanziellen Ziele?
Willst du dein traditionelles Einkommen aufbessern?
Planst du einen frühen Ruhestand?
Und strebst du letztendlich nach finanzieller Freiheit?
Auf dem Weg zum finanziellen Erfolg gibt es nur wenige Dinge, die so wichtig sind wie ein gründliches Verständnis davon, wo und wie man investiert. Lass dein Geld nicht auf der Bank liegen, nur weil dir der Aktienmarkt zu kompliziert erscheint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Algorithmic Trading with Python: Technical Analysis Strategy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/algorithmic-trading-with-python-technical-analysis-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/algorithmic-trading-with-python-technical-analysis-strategy/</guid>
      <description>You already have knowledge in python and you want to monetize and diversify your knowledge?
You already have some trading knowledge and you want to learn about algorithmic trading?
You are simply a curious person who wants to get into this subject?
If you answer at least one of these questions, I welcome you to this course. For beginners in python, don&#39;t panic there is a python course (small but condensed) to master this python knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of Hedge Funds</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentals-of-hedge-funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentals-of-hedge-funds/</guid>
      <description>WHY HEDGE FUNDS?
Hedge funds are one of the most profitable types of alternative assets.
However, they are not easy to comprehend.
Fund structures, investment strategies, provisions and fees, and other elements.
And unfortunately, it&#39;s hard to find a course that covers the essentials of hedge funds.
So it becomes common for a student to:
Not be able to discern among the different investment strategies;
Not know if the provisions negotiated with an investor are helpful to the fund, or not at all;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of Private Equity</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentals-of-private-equity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentals-of-private-equity/</guid>
      <description>PRIVATE EQUITY, PRIVATE KNOWLEDGE
The PE industry is one of the most lucrative ones.
It&#39;s also complex to understand, if you don&#39;t have the right guide.
A lot of techniques, knowledge and hands-on tips are not usually shared.
Usually, what would find would be generic courses with theoretical materials in terms of valuations or general job descriptions, not going into the details of fund operations, the job, or other elements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate TallyPrime With GST Step By Step Guide - 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-tallyprime-with-gst-step-by-step-guide-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-tallyprime-with-gst-step-by-step-guide-2021/</guid>
      <description>Recent Student&#39;s Reviews
***All lectures were amazing and easily understandable.
one important thing i like most is that downloadable link of Tally Prime is available and we can easily practice all the examples side by side while watching the lectures - Simpi Garg***
***Clearly understand what is tally prime in this full lecture.Thank you so much sir.(Rizwan Mohamed Y)***
***Covers every chapter, step by step learning for everyone (Vivekanandan Jayakumar)***</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Finance and Financial Modeling</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/business-finance-and-financial-modeling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/business-finance-and-financial-modeling/</guid>
      <description>Uplatz provides this comprehensive course on Business Finance and Financial Modeling. The Business Finance course will help get familiarized with the concepts of Corporate Finance, how to raise funds for your business, how to manage the funds, along with risk management. The Financial Modeling course will equip you with the methodology, tools, and techniques used in Financial Modeling, how to develop models for financial forecasting, how to manage the cash flow appropriately, and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cost &amp; Management Accounting Certification Training 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cost-management-accounting-certification-training-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cost-management-accounting-certification-training-2021/</guid>
      <description>Costing, as defined by the Institute of Cost and Works Accountants, England is basically “The technique and process of ascertaining costs.” It can also be described as classifying, recording and appropriate allocation of expenditure for the determination of the costs of products or services, and for presentation of suitably arranged data for the purposes of control, and guidance of management.
Cost Accounting is a method of accounting wherein all the costs involved in performing any process, project or product are noted and analyzed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Accounting &amp; Reporting Certification</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-reporting-certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-reporting-certification/</guid>
      <description>Uplatz provides this comprehensive training on Financial Accounting &amp;amp; Reporting.
This Financial Accounting &amp;amp; Financial Reporting course will demonstrate the key accounting concepts and principles to be able to prepare financial statements and unlock critical insights into business performance and potential. You will explore how financial advisors, managers, analysts, and entrepreneurs leverage accounting to drive strategic decision-making. The Financial Accounting course will help you master the functional and technical skills needed to analyze financial statements and disclosures for use in financial analysis, and learn how accounting standards and managerial incentives affect the financial reporting process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to beat the Forex market quick and effective!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-beat-the-forex-market-quick-and-effective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-beat-the-forex-market-quick-and-effective/</guid>
      <description>My name is Destin Brown, a 21-year-old entrepreneur. Been trading forex for 2 years, have been through multiple programs and found they only provide you with common information and most gurus or teachers charge an arm and a leg for this sort of information. Most times it gets confusing trying to figure out which pattern is which or what the overall trend in the market is, but I am here to eliminate all of that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CFA level 1, Ethics and Standards of Professional Conduct</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cfa-level-1-ethics-and-standards-of-professional-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cfa-level-1-ethics-and-standards-of-professional-conduct/</guid>
      <description>If you have come to this page looking for a quick solution to ace this topic then rest assured this course is for you.
A deep dive into the Code of Ethics and Standards of Professional Conduct for CFA level 1. In this course we cover
Code of Ethics and Standards of Professional conduct
Guidance for Standards I- VII
Ethical Decision Making Framework
Global Investment Performance Standards
Practice questions with answers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CFA Level 2, Ethics and Standards of Professional Conduct</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cfa-level-2-ethics-and-standards-of-professional-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cfa-level-2-ethics-and-standards-of-professional-conduct/</guid>
      <description>A comprehensive course covering Code of Ethics and Standards of Professional conduct for CFA level 2. In this course we cover
Code of Ethics and Standards of Professional conduct
Guidance for Standards I-VII
Application of the Code and Standards
Practice questions with answers
This course simplifies the theoretical concepts in short easy to follow videos. It summarises the key points for effective retention. The content is power packed with examples and is designed to help you score on this topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CFA Level 3, Ethics and Standards of Professional Conduct</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cfa-level-3-ethics-and-standards-of-professional-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cfa-level-3-ethics-and-standards-of-professional-conduct/</guid>
      <description>A deep dive into Code of Ethics and Standards of Professional Conduct for CFA level 3. In this course we cover
Code of Ethics and Standards of Professional Conduct
Guidance for Standards I-VII
Application of the Code and Standards
Asset Manager Code
Professionalism in Investment Industry
Global Investment Performance Standards
Practice questions with answers
This course simplifies the theoretical concepts in short easy to follow videos. It summarises the key points for effective retention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data science for algorithmic trading</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/data-science-for-algorithmic-trading/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/data-science-for-algorithmic-trading/</guid>
      <description>It is with pride that I offer this data science course for algorithmic trading. It is the fruit of several years of work in the field to truly understand all the subtleties of the world of quantitative finance.
Using libraries will allow you to do complex mathematical calculations applied to finance in just a few lines of code. We will see how to create an algorithm for trading from data import to automatic positions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tally Erp 9 &#43; Tally Prime &#43; GST  2021 - Certificate Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tally-erp-9--tally-prime--gst-2021-certificate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tally-erp-9--tally-prime--gst-2021-certificate-course/</guid>
      <description>Complete Tally Course from Zero to Hero in Tally Erp 9 + Tally Prime with Advance GST Course
Get Constant Growth in your career/Business with Advance Tally GST Online Course
Best Seller Course
What you’ll learn in this Tally Erp9 + Tally Prime Online Training
Accounting of Any Company with GST Independently in Tally Erp9 &amp;amp; Tally Prime
From Manual Accounting to Advance GST Reports in Tally Erp9 &amp;amp; Tally Prime</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Option Day Trading with Chart Pattern Trading Tools</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/stock-option-day-trading-with-chart-pattern-trading-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/stock-option-day-trading-with-chart-pattern-trading-tools/</guid>
      <description>Can you make 10% in ten minutes trading stock options with Chart Pattern Trading? No one but you knows the answer to that question.
What we do promise is that you will learn the tools in this course to make make 10% in ten minutes on a regular basis. Those tools include how to use our exclusive Waves of Profits software, how to control Fear and Greed, journaling, and identifying patterns of success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chargeback Reason Codes in Card Payments</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/chargeback-reason-codes-in-card-payments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/chargeback-reason-codes-in-card-payments/</guid>
      <description>THE CHARGEBACK WAY OF LIFE
You may know that a merchant (or their bank, the acquirer/merchant bank), chargebacks are a nightmare.
In short, a credit card owner claims they should obtain their money back due to something that went wrong in a transaction.
Fraud, disputes over the goods, authorization errors, and many other types come in here.
Chargebacks represent difficult obstacles for both acquiring and issuing bank.
Each chargeback is usually represent by something called the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GST Returns 2021 Course (Live Working) : Get Certified Today</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gst-returns-2021-course-live-working-get-certified-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gst-returns-2021-course-live-working-get-certified-today/</guid>
      <description>Aim &amp;amp; Future Prospects:
The aim of the course is to help individuals, businessman, accountants, CAs and other professionals to upgrade their knowledge regarding the Goods and Services Tax by offering most of the real time practical knowledge on GST Portal in an updated and systematic approach that help them to accelerate their skills and knowledge required for self-employment &amp;amp; employment at industrial level as well.
Benefits of the course:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bookkeeping &amp; Accounting Masterclass - Beginner to Advanced</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bookkeeping-accounting-masterclass-beginner-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bookkeeping-accounting-masterclass-beginner-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>The course starts right from scratch, introduces the concept of Accounting, fundamental accounting terms, the accounting system of recording business transactions. Then it takes you to more complex areas of accounting like transactions affected by discounts and sales tax, prepaid and accrued transactions, and accounting adjustments like depreciation. Topics Covered:
Introduction to Accounting
Why Accounting has to follow rules and what are the accounting standards?
What are the different types of Accounting and what information is produced by each?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOREX TRADING NOMAD | HOW TO GET FUNDED BY INVESTORS IN 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/forex-trading-nomad-how-to-get-funded-by-investors-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/forex-trading-nomad-how-to-get-funded-by-investors-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>Investors are keen to meet you. The problem is that you may not have anything to offer them yet. This course takes you by the hand and teaches you one strategy that will help you make it in the world of trading or I&#39;ll give you your money back. Then your newly gained knowledge is put to the tests. Once you have successfully passed the tests, you are introduced to the investors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of Fraud Prevention and Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentals-of-fraud-prevention-and-monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentals-of-fraud-prevention-and-monitoring/</guid>
      <description>WHY FRAUD PREVENTION?
Understanding how fraud is committed - and especially how it&#39;s prevented - is not easy.
There are countless techniques to take into account. Perpetrators can be of different types and use different approaches.
For anyone aiming to know more about fraud prevention - whether as a fraud monitoring professional, a payments professional, or any other type of professional that wants to master the theory and practice of fraud prevention, finding the right information is crucial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capital Market Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/capital-market-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/capital-market-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Capital Market Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn fundamental knowledge about capital markets that would help you in finding value within the market to maximize your earning potential.
I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on the different aspects of the capital market as well as basic analysis on the market to analyze value of investment instruments as well as noticing important trends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Financial Accounting Course in Urdu / Hindi</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basic-financial-accounting-course-in-urdu-/-hindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basic-financial-accounting-course-in-urdu-/-hindi/</guid>
      <description>Updated: 24/7/2019 (Ledger &amp;amp; Trial Balance)
Basic Financial Accounting Course Outline:
1. Basic Accounting Course Urdu/Hindi 2. Introduction to Basic Accounting Course
3. What you will learn in this course? 4. Importance of accounting 5. Types of transactions in accounting 6. What is Debtor and creditor? 7. What is the Accounting Equation?
8. How to record the business transaction in the accounting equation?
9. What is Double Entry system in Accounting?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY Advance Options Trading Strategies (5 Courses) 11 Hours</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/diy-advance-options-trading-strategies-5-courses-11-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:35:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/diy-advance-options-trading-strategies-5-courses-11-hours/</guid>
      <description>*** Course access includes quizzes &amp;amp; homework exercises, 1-on-1 Options Trading instructor support and LIFETIME access! ***
Hear why this is one of the TOP-NOTCH Options Trading course on Udemy:
I believe it is a good value for the money. He offers a lot of information and is willing to help.
-Dwight Douglas
The Author of this course explains in great detail what is important to become a successful options trader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Out of Debt and on Budget for Your Future</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-get-out-of-debt-and-on-budget-for-your-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-get-out-of-debt-and-on-budget-for-your-future/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you will learn how to get yourself out of debt so you can build your credit score and get onto a healthy budget. Getting your personal finances under control can be intimidating and daunting if you don’t know what to do to get ahead. My goal is to give you the opportunity to learn what I learned the hard way. When I was in debt, I never thought I would get out, but I tried different things and got my finances under control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C Corporation Income Tax (Form 1120)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/c-corporation-income-tax-form-1120/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/c-corporation-income-tax-form-1120/</guid>
      <description>This course currently consists of a comprehensive problem showing the data input process of a C Corporation into tax Form 1120.
This course will put together a systematic format of entering data into a Form 1120 that will minimize errors, isolate problems as they happen, and remove the possibility of having to start the process all over again.
We will enter each M-1 adjustment individually into both the tax return and an Excel worksheet so that we fully understand how M-1 adjustments function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stock Trading Momentum Based Strategies1- Technical Analysis</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/stock-trading-momentum-based-strategies1-technical-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 21:16:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/stock-trading-momentum-based-strategies1-technical-analysis/</guid>
      <description>In this course we will discuss multiple momentum oscillator, which measures both the speed as well as the rise or fall of price movements of a stocks.
Relative Strength Index (or RSI), Stoch, William %R, TSI &amp;amp; MFL are one of the top Technical Analysis Indicator. In this Course these technical indicators are not only shown as merely a indicator but a Complete System for trading.
RSI, Stoch, William %R, TSI &amp;amp; MFL is used by professional to identify the trend, Selling or Buying conditions through Reversal, divergences or simple Buy and sell techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Finance</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-finance/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Introduction to Finance Course by TSI! This is a course that is designed for complete beginners— no experience is required. If you are interested in finance, then you have come to the right place. We start off by introducing finance as well as clearing up a lot of the common misconceptions people have regarding the field. We then cover money and inflation. Then we cover loans and interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partnership Income Tax (Form 1065)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/partnership-income-tax-form-1065/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/partnership-income-tax-form-1065/</guid>
      <description>This course currently consists of a comprehensive problem showing the data input process of a Partnership into tax Form 1065.
This course will put together a systematic format of entering data into a Form 1065 that will minimize errors, isolate problems as they happen, and remove the possibility of having to start the process all over again.
We will enter each M-1 adjustment individually into both the tax return and an Excel worksheet so that we fully understand how they work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Options Trading MasterClass: Options Trading In Simple Terms</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/options-trading-masterclass-options-trading-in-simple-terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/options-trading-masterclass-options-trading-in-simple-terms/</guid>
      <description>In this Options Trading course, President of Capstone Financial &amp;amp; Author of &#34;Options Trading Strategies for Monthly Income&#34; David J. Melilli will educate you on every aspect of options trading. David will implement his unique options trading process utilizing his extensive knowledge in the area of options trading. David has spent over fifteen years in the options trading arena. This options trading course is taught in an easy to understand, user friendly manner that will excite and help build the confidence to master options trading and it has been designed to educate and enhance every individual that wants to really develop the skills required in the world of options trading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tally Prime Erp &#43;GST 2021 : Certificate Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tally-prime-erp-gst-2021-certificate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 22:18:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tally-prime-erp-gst-2021-certificate-course/</guid>
      <description>--**New in Tally Prime Erp with GST **--
-&amp;gt;Better Control Over Cash Flow
-&amp;gt;Enhanced Business Efficiency
-&amp;gt;Tax Compliance Made Easy
From the Bestseller of Tally Erp9 with GST
Best Rated for Eway Bill
Best Rated for GST Returns
Complete Tally Course from Zero to Hero in Tally Prime Erp with Advance GST Course
Get Constant Growth in your career/Business with Advance Tally PRIME GST Online Course
Best Seller Course
What you’ll learn in this Tally Erp9 Online Training</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consumer Lending Risk Management Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/consumer-lending-risk-management-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/consumer-lending-risk-management-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Have you wondered what a consumer lending risk management professional does on a daily basis? Do you want to explore the world of consumer lending, which is closely tied with millions of people&#39;s lives? This introductory course, Consumer Lending Risk Management Fundamentals - A Beginner&#39;s Guide, will walk you through: Consumer lending products and ecosystem
Risk management types and framework
Risk management practices in consumer lending
Risk management throughout credit life cycle</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Payment Dispute Resolution</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-payment-dispute-resolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-payment-dispute-resolution/</guid>
      <description>WHY DISPUTE RESOLUTION?
Payment disputes are an important issue to solve, either as a merchant, cardholder or bank.
There are many reasons for disputes, and multiple methods for dispute resolution. All of these can affect the results of a dispute for the different parties involved.
In order to be effective at dispute resolution, it&#39;s important to understand not just the reasons for disputes, but also the mechanisms for their resolution, and the consequences of each.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swing Trading Ninja: 12 Hour Complete Swing Trading Strategy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/swing-trading-ninja-12-hour-complete-swing-trading-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 12:58:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/swing-trading-ninja-12-hour-complete-swing-trading-strategy/</guid>
      <description>*** Course access includes quizzes &amp;amp; homework exercises, 1-on-1 instructor support and LIFETIME access! ***
This is best strategy I ever find in my life for swing trader. This is incredible. This milloin dollar startegy. I can say here &#34;knowledge is power&#34;.
-Suhit Kalubarme
it was a great match . I am learning a lot and enjoying class. Working on paper trades as class goes on and see things that I am learning daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calcul stochastique pour le trading Forex</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/calcul-stochastique-pour-le-trading-forex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 17:04:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/calcul-stochastique-pour-le-trading-forex/</guid>
      <description>Aujourd&#39;hui, Médaillon, le fond le plus profitable du monde fait en moyenne plus de 60% de gain annuel. Mais comment? Ils sont spécialiser dans la finance quantitative, le trading algorithmique et la mathématisation des processus financier. Ici, dans cette formation, nous allons nous intéresser au calcul stochastique. Nous allons voir qu&#39;elles sont les méthodes de bases du calcul stochastique, voir comment l&#39;appliquer au indice boursier et au forex. L&#39;idée principale de cette formation est de voir les bénéfices que l&#39;on peut avoir en combinant deux disciplines très utilisées en finance quantitative: le calcul stochastique et le machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data science pour le trading algorithmique (2020)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/data-science-pour-le-trading-algorithmique-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 17:04:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/data-science-pour-le-trading-algorithmique-2020/</guid>
      <description>C&#39;est avec plaisir que je vous offre ce cours de data science pour le trading algorithmique. C&#39;est le fuit de plusieurs années de travail dans de nombreux domaines pour comprendre les subtilités du monde de la finance quantitative.
Nous utiliserons des librairies python qui nous permettrons de faire facilement des algorithmes mathématiques très complexes appliqués à la finance avec peu de code. Le fil conducteur de cette formation sera la création d&#39;un algorithme profitable avec plus de 50% de gain annuel sur me NASDAQ 100.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MASTERCLASS: &#39;Inversión en Fondos Mutuos&#39;</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/masterclass-inversi%C3%B3n-en-fondos-mutuos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/masterclass-inversi%C3%B3n-en-fondos-mutuos/</guid>
      <description>Si usted considera que los métodos tradicionales de ahorro que le ofrecen las entidades bancarias de su país no son lo suficientemente buenas para usted debido a su baja rentabilidad y a la creciente inflación, pero a su vez considera que aún no está preparado para dar el gran salto a las inversiones en las bolsas de valores, puesto que ha oído hablar de que es muy riesgoso y que requiere de mucha preparación, entonces esta Masterclass gratuita es adecuada para usted, mi nombre es Jean Pierre Chayña Salas (Economista de profesión) y le mostraré que es posible invertir y sacarle dinero al mercado financiero de forma indirecta jugando bajo sus propios términos y condiciones, aprovechando los beneficios de la banca tradicional y del mercado de valores a través de su banca por Internet BBVA y todo esto desde la comodidad de su casa y ¿Cómo lo haremos?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Trading Ninja: 12 Hours DIY Day Trading Strategy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/day-trading-ninja-12-hours-diy-day-trading-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/day-trading-ninja-12-hours-diy-day-trading-strategy/</guid>
      <description>*** Course access includes quizzes &amp;amp; homework exercises, 1-on-1 instructor support and LIFETIME access! ***
Hear why this is one of the TOP-NOTCH Day Trading course on Udemy:
very practical course , I already made more than 10000$ from 100$ using this course principles . I would like to thank the author for such a good effort. I would like to recommend everyone this course who is struggling in the forex market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Economics: Microeconomics and Macroeconomics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-economics-microeconomics-and-macroeconomics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:28:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-economics-microeconomics-and-macroeconomics/</guid>
      <description>SearchEcon Economics overview provides an Introduction to Economics. This course can help your Introduction to Economics courses. We provide an overview of Microeconomics and Macroeconomics. This overview of Economics can also be helpful for business and government leaders who wish to learn the basics of Economics.
We try to provide real world examples throughout the course to help you understand Economic concepts. We also try to provide relatable examples that help connect and understand the concepts that we are reviewing in Economics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standard Costing And Variance Analysis Full Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/standard-costing-and-variance-analysis-full-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:15:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/standard-costing-and-variance-analysis-full-course/</guid>
      <description>Administrative and cost management tools
The course will introduce subject management topics to be covered throughout the course, comparing management accounting and accounting so that we are in the right frame of mind as we move forward.
The study will explain and analyze general costs and cost variance analyzes, providing an overview of the cost analysis concepts that we will go into in detail in later sections.
We will explain the analysis of sales differences, discuss when they can be used and how to calculate sales variations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IIA-CIA-Part2 Practice Test Prep Exam</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/iia-cia-part2-practice-test-prep-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/iia-cia-part2-practice-test-prep-exam/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the pratice Tests: IIA-CIA-Part2 Certified Internal Auditor - Part 2, Conducting the Internal Audit Engagement.
I prepared the pratice tests to help you prepare for the real IIA-CIA-Part2 exam, you will test your knowledge with hours of simulated questions and answers giving great chances for you to improve your performance when taking the exam.
Our pratice Tests covers all references:
I. Managing the Internal Audit Activity
II. Planning the Engagement</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indian Income Tax Complete Certification Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/indian-income-tax-complete-certification-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/indian-income-tax-complete-certification-course/</guid>
      <description>Do you find it difficult to understand the Income Tax laws?
Or are you struggling with filing your own income tax return?
Many a time we hear people saying that they don’t understand tax, they are not aware of when tax is to be deducted (TDS), they find it difficult to apply for their own PAN number or they find it difficult to file their return of income.
So, friends to simplify all your problems and giving you an excellent clarity of all concepts, we have made this course on “Income Tax” presented by Direct and Corporate Tax expert CA Natasha Shah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Credit and Credit Repair from Scratch</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-about-credit-and-credit-repair-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-about-credit-and-credit-repair-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>Sadly, many people get into a debt spiral that soon goes out of control. They have trouble keeping their head above water, and soon they fall under as the weight of debt drags them down.
Thankfully, credit can be managed and all it takes is having the ability to change how one lives their life. By implementing the lessons explained in this course, an individual will be able to take their credit and repair it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aprende las bases para invertir en la bolsa</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprende-las-bases-para-invertir-en-la-bolsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aprende-las-bases-para-invertir-en-la-bolsa/</guid>
      <description>En este curso aprenderás a leer los 3 estados financieros más importantes que reportan las empresas que cotizan en la bolsa americana (empresas públicas.) Estos son el estado de ingresos, la hoja de balance y el flujo de caja. Con el conocimiento ganado podrás reconocer si ha mejorado o empeorado el desempeño de una empresa pública. De esta forma, sabrás si es conveniente invertir en la empresa analizada. Estaremos usando Yahoo Finanzas para analizar los estados financieros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin 101 - Complete Intro to Bitcoin, Blockchain &amp; Crypto</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bitcoin-101-complete-intro-to-bitcoin-blockchain-crypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bitcoin-101-complete-intro-to-bitcoin-blockchain-crypto/</guid>
      <description>In this course, we dive deep into one of the most revolutionary assets of all time... Bitcoin. We dig into how Bitcoin&#39;s underlying technology, blockchain work. With no technical knowledge required, you will learn how the blockchain works, and why it is being called the &#34;next generation of the internet.&#34; Next, we take a closer look at the fundamentals of Bitcoin, and what makes it the most important cryptocurrency in the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Futures Trading Mastery 2021 | FREE Top 45 Trading Signals!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/futures-trading-mastery-2021-free-top-45-trading-signals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/futures-trading-mastery-2021-free-top-45-trading-signals/</guid>
      <description>My exclusive course teaches you how to start a successful futures trading business from scratch with zero experience. As one of the world’s 10 years veteran traders, I, Henry Zhang, will personally teach you the same proven strategy I used to build my trading empire from nothing.
Start a lucrative and sustainable trading business today with this complete A-Z guide designed to help everyone from beginners to existing traders looking to increase profits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Reporting Automation with Google Sheets</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-reporting-automation-with-google-sheets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-reporting-automation-with-google-sheets/</guid>
      <description>Learn to solve any business modeling task you might ever experience!
Have you ever felt that you&#39;re regularly repeating some tasks in Google Sheets or Excel?
Have you ever thought about the time you would save if you would automate those tasks?
All the work you&#39;re doing in a repetitive manner in Google Sheets or Excel could be automated.&amp;nbsp;It requires no coding skills, add-ons, or special tools - all you need to know is how to execute advanced formula combinations that will do all the automation for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Short Course on Ripple Cryptocurrency</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-short-course-on-ripple-cryptocurrency/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-short-course-on-ripple-cryptocurrency/</guid>
      <description>*** Course access&amp;nbsp;includes&amp;nbsp;quizzes &amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;homework exercises, 1-on-1 instructor support&amp;nbsp;(Ripple Cryptocurrency) and&amp;nbsp;LIFETIME&amp;nbsp;access! ***
Hear why this is one of the TOP-NOTCH&amp;nbsp;Ripple Cryptocurrency course&amp;nbsp;on Udemy:
Very informative indeed! Last lecture on Ripple charts was very helpful. Thanks.
-Raghbir Bhullar
I enjoyed learning about a different cryptocurrency than Bitcoin, but I would have liked more information on buying and selling Ripple. The instructor explained how to open accounts on two platforms. What is the difference between the two?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
