<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music Production on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/music-production/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music Production on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/music-production/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Complete Cubase Megacourse: Beginner to Expert</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-cubase-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-cubase-megacourse-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Learn music production with Cubase!
Create like a pro!
Have you ever wanted to create your own music? In the era of digital audio, this can be easily achieved! Maybe you want to record your song ideas and show them off on social media, or perhaps you want to hone your musical skills to pursue a career in the music industry. Whether you’re already a musician or a complete beginner creating and editing music is not only for the pros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ableton Workflow Masterclass - How To Make A Track A Day.</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ableton-workflow-masterclass-how-to-make-a-track-a-day./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ableton-workflow-masterclass-how-to-make-a-track-a-day./</guid>
      <description>Calling all passionate, aspiring and existing music producers!!! A must-buy comprehensive guide on how to master Music Production and the music industry from a mastering engineer, Mentor and a label owner.
This course shows that you don&#39;t need the technical skills or music theory knowledge to be proficient in Music Production.
A 30-day money back guarantee if you are not satisfied with the 20 hours of content!!! Sit back and relax whilst you learn some of the best kept producer secrets in the industry, along with never before shared knowledge about Music Production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ableton Live: Complete EDM Music Production in 3 Hours</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ableton-live-complete-edm-music-production-in-3-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ableton-live-complete-edm-music-production-in-3-hours/</guid>
      <description>Charlie Atom&#39;s Course to learn to make music in less than 3 hours!
Yeah! And not only samples, you will learn music making tricks so you can use music theory without spending years studing scales or composition.
Are you a DJ? Are you a music lover? Are you a professional music producer? This is your course. Even so you will learn from the beginning, as a professional you will learn some unique techniques I&#39;ve develop to make your music very fast and understand music theory in a very simplified way that is helpful for electronic and pop music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music Production - Succeed With Ableton Live</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/music-production-succeed-with-ableton-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 20:24:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/music-production-succeed-with-ableton-live/</guid>
      <description>Omar Meho is an artist from the United Kingdom. He is a Label Owner, Music Production/ DJ Teacher, Mastering Engineer and International Resident in Ibiza, France, U.K &amp;amp; Dubai. He has played in some of the biggest clubs in the U.K Including Egg LDN, Fabric, The Arch, The Cause &amp;amp; Much more. He has played festivals in front of 12,500 people and has support on his tracks from some of the biggest DJ&#39;s in the world including Marco Carola, East End Dubs, Chris Stussy, Jamie Jones, Adam Beyer And More.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rock Music Production For TV/Film &amp; Video Games</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/rock-music-production-for-tv/film-video-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/rock-music-production-for-tv/film-video-games/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the COMPLETE Rock Music Production For TV/Film &amp;amp; Video Games Guide!
This is a course created for the typical individual who is willing to take their musical journey and grow it into something greater. Whether you are a practicing musician, guitarist, or ambitious producer, this lesson is excellent for you.
As music producers, we are continuously striving for greater, fresher, and more distinct tones - we want to attain the same level of power,</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
