<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Creativity on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/creativity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Creativity on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:47 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/creativity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Simple Independent Film Screenwriting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/simple-independent-film-screenwriting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/simple-independent-film-screenwriting/</guid>
      <description>By independent director, producer and screenwriter Hank Orion. In this course we will dive deep into writing screenplay specifically for independent films. We will talk about stuff they don&#39;t teach you at film school. Some of the topics we will cover in this course are:
Screenplay Format And What Software To Use
Character Research
How To Write A Good Backstory
Writing A Solid Beginning, Middle And An End
How To Write Great Act I</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unleash Your Creative Mind</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/unleash-your-creative-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/unleash-your-creative-mind/</guid>
      <description>**Course Updated - June 2022**
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; COURSE REGULARLY UPDATED: NEW TIPS, MORE LESSONS &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; CERTIFIED COACH, SPEAKER AND TRAINER &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; OVER 180,000 STUDENTS IN TOTAL &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
I am sure you have heard it once if not many times that CREATIVITY - Worth Its Weight in Gold.
Being creative is a very desirable trait in modern society. Before the modern information age creativity was not something the average person really needed in order to be a productive member of society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innovation 1.0: Learn To Think Creatively Like Walt Disney</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/innovation-1.0-learn-to-think-creatively-like-walt-disney/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/innovation-1.0-learn-to-think-creatively-like-walt-disney/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the course titled &#34;Innovation 1.0: Learn To Think Creatively Like Walt Disney&#34;
What would Walt Disney think?
Although Disney has been gone for a long, you know that his company is still at the forefront of technological evolution. Frankly speaking, it was his marketing genius that set him and his company apart from everybody else on the planet. Now, I would like to re-incarnate Walt Disney into this course and put forth ideas from his perspective, imagining him to be your business coach, after all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to FAQ the coder&#39;s brain?</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-faq-the-coders-brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:10:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-faq-the-coders-brain/</guid>
      <description>Are you a coder? How is your personality connected with coding? Can you become a coder having non-technical background?
What is paradigm shift?
Learn neuroplasticity for developing a creative mind.
Why do you need art to become creative?
Gain insights from merging of technology with art.
Highly sensitive people are the most passionate and creative. How to develop your sensitivity and sensuality to become more creative? &#34;Creativity is intelligence having fun&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Creativity Course: Unleash Your Innovation Now!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-creativity-course-unleash-your-innovation-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:16:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-creativity-course-unleash-your-innovation-now/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Creativity Course: Unleash Your Innovation Now!
Turn Your Creative Energies On Daily. You Are the Source of Innovation, Creative Writing and New Ideas
Creativity is innate to all human beings. You can quickly build, refine, improve and strengthen your creativity and innovation muscles. Creativity is not something allocated to only a few of life&#39;s lottery winners. Instead, it is a habit that can be built by anyone--if they know the process and are willing to do a little work each day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Day Journaling Challenge</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/7-day-journaling-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 17:15:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/7-day-journaling-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Journaling is a powerful mindfulness tool that helps us self-reflect and catch various streams of thoughts and emotions. When we write things down, we literally transfer our thoughts out of our minds on paper. Our opinions are shaped, we untangle messy strings of ideas in our mind and create a logical flow of things with each sentence. As a result, we gain clarity on what we think and how we really feel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corso completo di sceneggiatura: scrivere un Film</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-completo-di-sceneggiatura-scrivere-un-film/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 12:00:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-completo-di-sceneggiatura-scrivere-un-film/</guid>
      <description>-Sei un appassionato di cinema e hai sempre sognato di poter un giorno scrivere per esso?
-Ti chiedi spesso cosa ci sia dietro lo scorrere delle immagini che vediamo al cinema?
-Ti è capitato mai di esclamare: &#34;HO UNA VOGLIA MATTA DI SCRIVERE UNA STORIA PER UN FILM...CREDO POTREI RIUSCIRCI....MA ... NON SAPREI DA DOVE INIZIARE!!&#34;...?
Beh...se le tue risposte alle mie domande sono affermative allora sei l&#39;alunno giusto nell&#39;aula virtuale giusta!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intelligence quotient IQ Test Questions and Answers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/intelligence-quotient-iq-test-questions-and-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:36:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/intelligence-quotient-iq-test-questions-and-answers/</guid>
      <description>TEST YOUR INTELLGENCE Intelligence quotient IQ Test Questions and Answers
2021 Measure students, employees, humans, scientists and child&#39;s intelligence, PSYCHOMETRIC and Personality
An intelligence quotient (IQ) is a total score derived from a set of standardized tests or subtests designed to assess human intelligence. The abbreviation &#34;IQ&#34; was coined by the psychologist William Stern for the German term Intelligenzquotient, his term for a scoring method for intelligence tests at University of Breslau he advocated in a 1912 book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screenwriting: Writing a Selling Story with Your Bare Hands</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/screenwriting-writing-a-selling-story-with-your-bare-hands/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 17:04:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/screenwriting-writing-a-selling-story-with-your-bare-hands/</guid>
      <description>Oh, you want to be a screenwriter? Then come along to learn how to become one. This course focuses on conjuring your ideas, structuralizing your plot and turning it into a selling script.
This course will make your search for ideas less menacing, showing you how and where to find them. If inspiration doesn’t come willingly, you’ll learn how to call upon it and brainstorm ideas.
You will learn key elements of a movie script, as much as key steps for turning your idea into a story, and story into a plot for your script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Secrets for Improving Screenwriting Skills Summary</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/top-5-secrets-for-improving-screenwriting-skills-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 17:04:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/top-5-secrets-for-improving-screenwriting-skills-summary/</guid>
      <description>I’m sure you really want to write something to put on silver-screen and be proud that it’s your story hundreds of thousands of people are talking about. Well, you can either just go at it and encounter lots upon lots of difficulties and mistakes, or you can learn everything you need to know first and get at it like a pro. The choice is yours, but I would really advice the second option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Song Tantra - Songwriting from the Soul!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-song-tantra-songwriting-from-the-soul/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-song-tantra-songwriting-from-the-soul/</guid>
      <description>In this course I teach you a special vocal technique that opens the voice and creative flow! My technique connects you to the creative energy from your soul, so you can create beautiful music that will entrance audiences to you and your music. I have personally have studied singing and sung professionally for over 20 years, graduated cum la mentored with pro- songwriters who write for celebrities and learn their songwriting techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
