<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Creativity on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/creativity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Creativity on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 16:01:27 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/creativity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Screenwriting: Writing a Selling Story with Your Bare Hands</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/screenwriting-writing-a-selling-story-with-your-bare-hands/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 16:01:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/screenwriting-writing-a-selling-story-with-your-bare-hands/</guid>
      <description>Oh, you want to be a screenwriter? Then come along to learn how to become one. This course focuses on conjuring your ideas, structuralizing your plot and turning it into a selling script.
This course will make your search for ideas less menacing, showing you how and where to find them. If inspiration doesn’t come willingly, you’ll learn how to call upon it and brainstorm ideas.
You will learn key elements of a movie script, as much as key steps for turning your idea into a story, and story into a plot for your script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Secrets for Improving Screenwriting Skills Summary</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/top-5-secrets-for-improving-screenwriting-skills-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 16:01:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/top-5-secrets-for-improving-screenwriting-skills-summary/</guid>
      <description>I’m sure you really want to write something to put on silver-screen and be proud that it’s your story hundreds of thousands of people are talking about. Well, you can either just go at it and encounter lots upon lots of difficulties and mistakes, or you can learn everything you need to know first and get at it like a pro. The choice is yours, but I would really advice the second option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Song Tantra - Songwriting from the Soul!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-song-tantra-songwriting-from-the-soul/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-song-tantra-songwriting-from-the-soul/</guid>
      <description>In this course I teach you a special vocal technique that opens the voice and creative flow! My technique connects you to the creative energy from your soul, so you can create beautiful music that will entrance audiences to you and your music. 
I have personally have studied singing and sung professionally for over 20 years, graduated cum la mentored with pro- songwriters who write for celebrities and learn their songwriting techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intelligence quotient IQ Test Questions and Answers</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/intelligence-quotient-iq-test-questions-and-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 20:12:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/intelligence-quotient-iq-test-questions-and-answers/</guid>
      <description>TEST YOUR INTELLGENCE 
Intelligence quotient IQ Test Questions and Answers
2021 Measure students, employees, humans, scientists and child&#39;s intelligence, PSYCHOMETRIC and Personality

An intelligence quotient (IQ) is a total score derived from a set of standardized tests or subtests designed to assess human intelligence. The abbreviation &#34;IQ&#34; was coined by the psychologist William Stern for the German term Intelligenzquotient, his term for a scoring method for intelligence tests at University of Breslau he advocated in a 1912 book.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>