<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Science on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/data-science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Science on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/data-science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence in Digital Marketing - Gold Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/artificial-intelligence-in-digital-marketing-gold-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/artificial-intelligence-in-digital-marketing-gold-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the first course in Term 1 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Artificial Intelligence in Digital Marketing - Gold Edition.
Artificial Intelligence has transformed the virtual panorama, inclusive of Google’s RankBrain personalising suggestions by Amazon. Artificial Intelligence (AI) is hastily turning into important in the daily happenings of the virtual global, with marketing and advertising and marketing being no exception. The idea of AI may also bring to thoughts 60’s sci-fi with futuristic robots, however it’s definitely approximately so much greater.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence in Web Design (Special Edition)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/artificial-intelligence-in-web-design-special-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/artificial-intelligence-in-web-design-special-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Level 2 of the series &#34;MBA in Creative Arts, Design and Animation&#34;.
Artificial Intelligence in Web Design (Special Edition)
What is this 2021 Special Edition Website Design course all about?
Website design is the art and science of building the look, feel, and how a website functions in a nutshell. This course is having clear, concise, and easy to use website design technologies and will ultimately lead to a better user experience for your custom audience or clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning- From Basics to Advanced</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/machine-learning-from-basics-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/machine-learning-from-basics-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>If you are looking to start your career in Machine learning then this is the course for you. This is a course designed in such a way that you will learn all the concepts of machine learning right from basic to advanced levels.
This course has 5 parts as given below:
Introduction &amp;amp; Data Wrangling in machine learning Linear Models, Trees &amp;amp; Preprocessing in machine learning Model Evaluation, Feature Selection &amp;amp; Pipelining in machine learning Bayes, Nearest Neighbors &amp;amp; Clustering in machine learning SVM, Anomalies, Imbalanced Classes, Ensemble Methods in machine learning For the code explained in each lecture, you can find a GitHub link in the resources section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence Music Creation (2021 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/artificial-intelligence-music-creation-2021-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/artificial-intelligence-music-creation-2021-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the fifth course in Level 2 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Creative Arts, Design and Animation&#34;.
Giant Tech firms have developed AI software that can compose music on its own. So, the machines will be composing soundtracks using Artificial Intelligence. This game-changing course focuses on &#34;Artificial Intelligence Music Creation (2021 Edition)&#34;  introduces you to new-age technologies in Artificial Intelligence music creation to help you become a music star in no time with the power of automagical music-making tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Processing for Text Summarization</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/natural-language-processing-for-text-summarization/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 21:16:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/natural-language-processing-for-text-summarization/</guid>
      <description>The area of ​​Natural Language Processing (NLP) is a subarea of ​​Artificial Intelligence that aims to make computers capable of understanding human language, both written and spoken. Some examples of practical applications are: translators between languages, translation from text to speech or speech to text, chatbots, automatic question and answer systems (Q&amp;amp;A), automatic generation of descriptions for images, generation of subtitles in videos, classification of sentiments in sentences, among many others!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning &amp; Deep Learning in Python &amp; R</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/machine-learning-deep-learning-in-python-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/machine-learning-deep-learning-in-python-r/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re looking for a complete Machine Learning and Deep Learning course that can help you launch a flourishing career in the field of Data Science, Machine Learning, Python, R or Deep Learning, right?
You&#39;ve found the right Machine Learning course!
After completing this course you will be able to:
· Confidently build predictive Machine Learning and Deep Learning models using R, Python to solve business problems and create business strategy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spatial Analysis &amp; Geospatial Data Science in Python</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/spatial-analysis-geospatial-data-science-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/spatial-analysis-geospatial-data-science-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Geospatial data science is a subset of data science that focuses on spatial data and its unique techniques. In this, we are going to perform spatial analysis and trying to find insights from spatial data. In this course, we lay the foundation for a career in Geospatial Data Science. You will get hands-on Geopy, Plotly etc.. the workhorse of Geospatial data science Python libraries.

The topics covered in this course widely touch on some of the most used spatial technique in Geospatial data science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/docker-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 22:18:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/docker-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Containerization of the applications is going on in the full swing across the IT industry. Docker&#39;s course covers the fundamental concepts of Docker containers. Along with the concepts it also covers the most useful commands related to container management, image management, and Dockerfile. After studying this course one would be ready to dive deeper into the world of container orchestration. Docker&#39;s course becomes the necessary prerequisite for learning Docker Swarm and Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide to Careers in Data Science - Interview Hacks (2021)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/guide-to-careers-in-data-science-interview-hacks-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 07:41:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/guide-to-careers-in-data-science-interview-hacks-2021/</guid>
      <description>Want to start your career in Data Science? Then this course is for YOU!
This complete guide is designed to answer all your queries regarding careers in Data Science such as:
Efficient job search
4 Mantras for Guaranteed Success
Educational Requirements
Creating an Outstanding Resume
Why choose a career in Data Science
Is Data Science for YOU?
Interview Questions and Answers
Do&#39;s and Don&#39;ts of Preparation
Job Titles in Data Science</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python and Data Handling for Everyone 2021 Mastery Bootcamp</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-and-data-handling-for-everyone-2021-mastery-bootcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 10:29:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-and-data-handling-for-everyone-2021-mastery-bootcamp/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to the Python and Data Handling for Everyone 2021 Mastery Bootcamp.
Data science is a huge field, and one of the promising fields that is spreading in a fast way, also, it is one of the very rewarding, and it is increasing in expansion day by day, due to its great importance and benefits, as it is the future.
Data science enables companies to measure, track, and record performance metrics for facilitating and enhancing decision making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python-Introduction to Data Science and Machine learning A-Z</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-introduction-to-data-science-and-machine-learning-a-z/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-introduction-to-data-science-and-machine-learning-a-z/</guid>
      <description>Learning how to program in Python is not always easy especially if you want to use it for Data science. Indeed, there are many of different tools that have to be learned to be able to properly use Python for Data science and machine learning and each of those tools is not always easy to learn. But, this course will give all the basics you need no matter for what objective you want to use it so if you :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Analysis Real world use-cases- Hands on Python</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/data-analysis-real-world-use-cases-hands-on-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 12:58:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/data-analysis-real-world-use-cases-hands-on-python/</guid>
      <description>This is the first course that gives hands-on Data Analysis Projects using Python..


Can you start right now?
A frequently asked question of Python Beginners is: &#34;Do I need to become an expert in Python coding before I can start working on Data Analysis Projects?&#34;
The clear answer is: &#34;No!
You just require some Python Basics like data types, simple operations/operators, lists and numpy arrays that you can learn from my Free Python course &#39;Basics Of Python&#39;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Processing [ Building Real World Projects]</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/natural-language-processing-building-real-world-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/natural-language-processing-building-real-world-projects/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to your first steps into the world of Natural Language Processing!
This course will guide you through the world of Natural Language Processing through hands-on tutorials with real world examples.
We will start off with the basics of Natural Language Processing, and work towards developing our very own application. By the end of this course, we will build an application that predicts what people think of any topic based on what people have said about it on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning pour le trading de A à Z</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/machine-learning-pour-le-trading-de-a-%C3%A0-z/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/machine-learning-pour-le-trading-de-a-%C3%A0-z/</guid>
      <description>Cette formation vous propose un large choix d&#39;algorithme permettant d&#39;appréhender les variations des marchés financier, nous créerons également un robot trader à l&#39;aide d&#39;un algorithme de Deep Reinforcement Learning.

La data science est en pleine expansion est s&#39;insère jour après jour dans tous les secteurs. La finance est l&#39;un des secteurs les plus enclins à l&#39;arrivée de la data science car depuis la crise de 2008 le secteur financier à un besoin croissant de quantifier les risques, mais aussi de pricer (prévoir les variations des actifs financiers) les différents actifs sur lesquelles les acteurs de la finance investissent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning (application en finance)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/reinforcement-learning-application-en-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 17:04:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/reinforcement-learning-application-en-finance/</guid>
      <description>Cette formation vous propose un cours complet concernant les algorithmes de Depp Q Learning. Vous aborderez la théorie dans un premier temps qui vous permettra d&#39;appréhendez au mieux la seconde plus appliquée.

L&#39;apprentissage par renforcement est une discipline de plus en plus utilisée dans le monde réelle. C&#39;est pourquoi, la formation met l&#39;accent sur les aspects intuitifs, les principales librairies du renforcement learning et notamment Open AI Gym.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SVM for Beginners: Support Vector Machines in R Studio</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/svm-for-beginners-support-vector-machines-in-r-studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/svm-for-beginners-support-vector-machines-in-r-studio/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re looking for a complete Support Vector Machines course that teaches you everything you need to create a SVM model in R, right?
You&#39;ve found the right Support Vector Machines techniques course!
How this course will help you?
A Verifiable Certificate of Completion is presented to all students who undertake this Machine learning advanced course.
If you are a business manager or an executive, or a student who wants to learn and apply machine learning in Real world problems of business, this course will give you a solid base for that by teaching you some of the advanced technique of machine learning, which are Support Vector Machines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Neural Networks in Python: CNN Computer Vision</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/convolutional-neural-networks-in-python-cnn-computer-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 20:51:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/convolutional-neural-networks-in-python-cnn-computer-vision/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re looking for a complete Convolutional Neural Network (CNN) course that teaches you everything you need to create a Image Recognition model in Python, right?
You&#39;ve found the right Convolutional Neural Networks course!
After completing this course you will be able to:
Identify the Image Recognition problems which can be solved using CNN Models.
Create CNN models in Python using Keras and Tensorflow libraries and analyze their results.
Confidently practice, discuss and understand Deep Learning concepts</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python for Data Science &amp; Machine Learning from A-Z</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-for-data-science-machine-learning-from-a-z/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-for-data-science-machine-learning-from-a-z/</guid>
      <description>Learn Python for Data Science &amp;amp; Machine Learning from A-Z
In this practical, hands-on course you’ll learn how to program using Python for Data Science and Machine Learning. This includes data analysis, visualization, and how to make use of that data in a practical manner. Our main objective is to give you the education not just to understand the ins and outs of the Python programming language for Data Science and Machine Learning, but also to learn exactly how to become a professional Data Scientist with Python and land your first job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fraud Analytics in Banking and Credit using Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fraud-analytics-in-banking-and-credit-using-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fraud-analytics-in-banking-and-credit-using-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>In general, fraud can be defined as some illegal or criminal thing done by any person who intended to deceive in financial organizations or personal profit. So the processes of analyzing such illegitimate transactions done by anyone like buyer or customer are caught and only the legal transactions are allowed to be made. As fraud is increasing in day to day life so to analyze frauds that are occurring in the organizations or companies these frauds are analyzed using some quantitative science to understand the fraud, through BI (Business Intelligence), and then we have to develop effective fraud detection solutions through data science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MatPlotLib for Python Developers - Advanced</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/matplotlib-for-python-developers-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/matplotlib-for-python-developers-advanced/</guid>
      <description>We will be covering all the advanced level concepts in the course by the virtue of the sample questions which have been included to help the trainees on getting a precise view of the topics. You will get to learn about all the advanced-level topics and will also learn how to leverage them to draft solutions for plotting-based problems. Once you are done with this unit, you will be able to work proficiently with all the aspects of Matplotlib.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
