<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Engineering on </title>
    <link>/tags/engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Engineering on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nanotechnology Fundamentals - Most comperehensive NANOTECH</title>
      <link>/nanotechnology-fundamentals-most-comperehensive-nanotech/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nanotechnology-fundamentals-most-comperehensive-nanotech/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
Nanotechnology is a field of research and innovation concerned with building &#39;things&#39; - generally, materials and devices - on the scale of atoms and molecules. A nanometre is one-billionth of a metre: ten times the diameter of a hydrogen atom. The diameter of a human hair is, on average, 80,000 nanometres. At such scales, the ordinary rules of physics and chemistry no longer apply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Path Loss 5</title>
      <link>/learn-path-loss-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:28:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-path-loss-5/</guid>
      <description>You want to learn about network planning, especially the Access Network which is most fragile and ever changing part of the fixed and wireless network.

I have been working in the transmission field since last twenty years and I found that there is no basic training of the most commonly used access planning software and the new comers in Transmission planning learn this tool through hit and trial. That is why they are never able to fully utilize their potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combined Heat and Power (CHP) Cogeneration Fundamentals</title>
      <link>/combined-heat-and-power-chp-cogeneration-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/combined-heat-and-power-chp-cogeneration-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Combined Heat and Power (CHP) Cogeneration Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn all about the concept of CHP and cogeneration that are essential in working in the industry.

I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on cogeneration as well as how to apply it in the utility industry.

If you are currently a professional who are interested working with Cogeneration plants, you will find this course of great help to get the fundamental knowledge you need to kick start your professional career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash Course on Civil Engineering and AutoCAD: Part 3</title>
      <link>/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-3/</guid>
      <description>This incredible series-based crash course takes an amazing turn here in Part 3 as&amp;nbsp;&#34;New-age Environmental Engineering &amp;amp; Artificial Intelligence&#34; concepts are taught by Digital Marketing Legend &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34;&amp;nbsp;and Narmadha.M.
Environmental Engineering is a professional engineering discipline that takes advantage of specific scientific topics such as chemistry, biology, geography, geology, hydraulics, hydrology, microbiology, and mathematics to create solutions that will preserve and also improve the health of living organisms and increase environmental quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Biomedical Engineering - Nanodevices RAHBME282</title>
      <link>/intro-to-biomedical-engineering-nanodevices-rahbme282/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/intro-to-biomedical-engineering-nanodevices-rahbme282/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Nanodevices course, brought to you by Rahsoft. In this course we will be going over the basics and fundamentals of nanodevices and nanosensors, as well as in-depth examples and practice problems to give you a better understanding of the field. The course is taught by Dennis Fer, a Biomedical Engineering Instructor at Rahsoft, and the course advisor is Ahsan Ghoncheh, the Co-Founder and Technical Advisor at Rahsoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Heat Transfer Engineering - RAHHT1 Rahsoft</title>
      <link>/introduction-to-heat-transfer-engineering-rahht1-rahsoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/introduction-to-heat-transfer-engineering-rahht1-rahsoft/</guid>
      <description>Heat Transfer is one of the principle courses for all the university students who study in one of the branches of chemical engineering, mechanical engineering or materials engineering. This course which is placed at the beginning semesters of bachelor programs, is offered in two separate courses as heat transfer 1 &amp;amp; 2 each credited as 3 units. Having a full grasp over the concepts of heat transfer and fully understand the mechanisms of heat transfer in different situations is a must for any students studying the fields mentioned.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
