<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Engineering on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Engineering on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:06 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Cryptography</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-cryptography/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-cryptography/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in Cryptography? Don’t be stressed, take our Cryptography based quiz and prepare yourself for your Interview. 
With this Cryptography based Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Cryptography based questions. In these Cryptography based Multiple Choice Questions Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Basic Knowledge in Cryptography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Cyber Security</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-cyber-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-cyber-security/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in Cyber Security? Don’t be stressed, take our Cyber Security based quiz and prepare yourself for your Interview.
With this Cyber Security based Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Cyber Security based questions. In Cyber Security based Multiple Choice Questions Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Basic Knowledge in Cyber Security .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power Engineering Arc Flash Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/power-engineering-arc-flash-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/power-engineering-arc-flash-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Power Engineering Arc Flash Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn how to do an arc flash analysis and developing an Arc Flash Safety Program for your business.

I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on Arc Flash as well as the hazards associated with it and how to do Arc Flash Mitigation.

If you are engineer, electrical worker or safety profession, you will find this course of great help to get the fundamental knowledge you need to kick start your professional career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Ethical Hacking</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-ethical-hacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 09:38:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-ethical-hacking/</guid>
      <description>Dear Students,
Are you Preparing for Interview in Ethical Hacking? Don’t be stressed, take our Ethical Hacking quiz and prepare yourself for the Interview.
With this Ethical Hacking Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Ethical Hacking based questions. Here you will get Ethical Hacking based MCQ for your next Job or exam. In Ethical Hacking Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Knowledge in the field of Ethical Hacking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Petroleum Institute API PRACTICE QUESTIONS</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/american-petroleum-institute-api-practice-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/american-petroleum-institute-api-practice-questions/</guid>
      <description>The American Petroleum Institute (API) is the largest U.S. trade association for the oil and natural gas industry. It claims to represent nearly 600 corporations involved in production, refinement, distribution, and many other aspects of the petroleum industry.
The association describes its mission as to promote safety across the industry globally and influence public policy in support of a strong, viable U.S. oil and natural gas industry. API&#39;s chief functions on behalf of the industry include advocacy, negotiation and lobbying with governmental, legal, and regulatory agencies; research into economic, toxicological, and environmental effects; establishment and certification of industry standards; and education outreach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>Preparing for Machine learning Interview? Don’t be stressed, take our Machine learning based quiz questions and prepare your self for the interview. With this Machine learning Quiz Questions, we are going to you build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Machine learning questions. Here you will get Machine learning General Multiple Choice Questions and Answers for your next job or exam. In Machine learning Multiple Choice Questions based practice tests, there will be a series of practice tests wherein you can test your Basic Machine learning concepts on every Topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultrasonic Testing Level 1 Training</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ultrasonic-testing-level-1-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:50:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ultrasonic-testing-level-1-training/</guid>
      <description>This course teaches you how to perform ultrasonic inspection from beginning to end.
The course provides you with Level 1 training in the fundamentals of Ultrasonic Testing methods. It will introduce you to the basic concepts and principles and includes hands-on training using Ultrasonic Testing equipment settings and functions.The Ultrasonic theories presented will provide the knowledge of Ultrasonic Testing required and enable you to work with individuals qualified and certified to gain needed experience for qualification as Level 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Electrical Engineering</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-electrical-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 21:16:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-electrical-engineering/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in Electrical Engineering? Don’t be stressed, take our Electrical Engineering based quiz and prepare yourself for your Interview. 
With this Electrical Engineering based Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Electrical Engineering based questions. In Electrical Engineering based Multiple Choice Questions Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Basic Knowledge in Electrical Engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simplilearn Arduino</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/simplilearn-arduino/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/simplilearn-arduino/</guid>
      <description>Arduino is an open-source computer hardware/software platform for building digital devices and interactive objects that can sense and control the physical world around them. In this class you will learn how the Arduino platform works in terms of the physical board and libraries and the IDE (integrated development environment).
Upon completing this course, you will be able to: 1. Outline the composition of the Arduino development board 2. Describe what it means to program the board&#39;s firmware 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on D.C. Machines</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-d.c.-machines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 22:18:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-d.c.-machines/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in D.C. Machines based Company? Don’t be stressed, take our D.C. Machines based quiz and prepare yourself for your Interview.
With this D.C. Machines based Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve D.C. Machines based questions. In D.C. Machines based Multiple Choice Questions Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Basic Knowledge in D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Transformer</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 07:41:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-transformer/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in Transformer based Company? Don’t be stressed, take our Transformer based quiz and prepare yourself for your Interview.
With this Transformer based Quiz, we are going to build your confidence by providing tips and trick to solve Transformer based questions. In Transformer based Multiple Choice Questions Quiz, there will be a series of practice tests where you can test your Basic Knowledge in Transformer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IEC 61850 Communication Protocol Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/iec-61850-communication-protocol-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/iec-61850-communication-protocol-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>IEC61850 Communication Protocol Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn industry specific knowledge about the IEC61850 protocol standard such as that found in the utility industry.

I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge from cable component basic to calculating for simple cable installation designs.
I will teach you the basic concepts of IEC61850 standard as well as the overall IEC61850 Data Model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build your own first Voice Assistant in Python</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-build-your-own-first-voice-assistant-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-build-your-own-first-voice-assistant-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to this class
In this project you will learn how to build your first virtual assistant VA in python in less then 90 minutes.
This is a great small project to get started (even if you have little or no prior knowledge in python) and learning opportunity.
Learning through your own little projects is the best and most enjoying way to improve your skills.
In the world of today we all already use Virtual Assistants like Alexa, Siri, Google and others more and more in our daily lifes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nanotechnology Fundamentals - Most comperehensive NANOTECH</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/nanotechnology-fundamentals-most-comperehensive-nanotech/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 11:42:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/nanotechnology-fundamentals-most-comperehensive-nanotech/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
Nanotechnology is a field of research and innovation concerned with building &#39;things&#39; - generally, materials and devices - on the scale of atoms and molecules. A nanometre is one-billionth of a metre: ten times the diameter of a hydrogen atom. The diameter of a human hair is, on average, 80,000 nanometres. At such scales, the ordinary rules of physics and chemistry no longer apply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Path Loss 5</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-path-loss-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:28:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-path-loss-5/</guid>
      <description>You want to learn about network planning, especially the Access Network which is most fragile and ever changing part of the fixed and wireless network.

I have been working in the transmission field since last twenty years and I found that there is no basic training of the most commonly used access planning software and the new comers in Transmission planning learn this tool through hit and trial. That is why they are never able to fully utilize their potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Combined Heat and Power (CHP) Cogeneration Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/combined-heat-and-power-chp-cogeneration-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/combined-heat-and-power-chp-cogeneration-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Combined Heat and Power (CHP) Cogeneration Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn all about the concept of CHP and cogeneration that are essential in working in the industry.

I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on cogeneration as well as how to apply it in the utility industry.

If you are currently a professional who are interested working with Cogeneration plants, you will find this course of great help to get the fundamental knowledge you need to kick start your professional career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash Course on Civil Engineering and AutoCAD: Part 3</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-3/</guid>
      <description>This incredible series-based crash course takes an amazing turn here in Part 3 as&amp;nbsp;&#34;New-age Environmental Engineering &amp;amp; Artificial Intelligence&#34; concepts are taught by Digital Marketing Legend &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34;&amp;nbsp;and Narmadha.M.
Environmental Engineering is a professional engineering discipline that takes advantage of specific scientific topics such as chemistry, biology, geography, geology, hydraulics, hydrology, microbiology, and mathematics to create solutions that will preserve and also improve the health of living organisms and increase environmental quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Biomedical Engineering - Nanodevices RAHBME282</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/intro-to-biomedical-engineering-nanodevices-rahbme282/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/intro-to-biomedical-engineering-nanodevices-rahbme282/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Nanodevices course, brought to you by Rahsoft. In this course we will be going over the basics and fundamentals of nanodevices and nanosensors, as well as in-depth examples and practice problems to give you a better understanding of the field. The course is taught by Dennis Fer, a Biomedical Engineering Instructor at Rahsoft, and the course advisor is Ahsan Ghoncheh, the Co-Founder and Technical Advisor at Rahsoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Heat Transfer Engineering - RAHHT1 Rahsoft</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-heat-transfer-engineering-rahht1-rahsoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-heat-transfer-engineering-rahht1-rahsoft/</guid>
      <description>Heat Transfer is one of the principle courses for all the university students who study in one of the branches of chemical engineering, mechanical engineering or materials engineering. This course which is placed at the beginning semesters of bachelor programs, is offered in two separate courses as heat transfer 1 &amp;amp; 2 each credited as 3 units. Having a full grasp over the concepts of heat transfer and fully understand the mechanisms of heat transfer in different situations is a must for any students studying the fields mentioned.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
