<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>User Experience Design on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/user-experience-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in User Experience Design on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:33:44 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/user-experience-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Figma UI/UX Web Design &amp; Animation with 5 Projects (2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/figma-ui/ux-web-design-animation-with-5-projects-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:33:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/figma-ui/ux-web-design-animation-with-5-projects-2022/</guid>
      <description>UPDATED JUNE 2022
Hello, Creative Minds,
Figma is a free, online UI tool to create, collaborate, prototype, and hand off. It’s currently the industry’s leading interface design tool and companies such as Notion, Zoom, Uber are using Figma.
In this course, you will learn the process of web design in Figma, which starts at the product brief and ends with a beautiful design.
We will start everything from scratch and I will share all the techniques and shortcuts that increase your workflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe XD 2022 Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-xd-2022-ultimate-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-xd-2022-ultimate-guide/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone and welcome to Adobe XD 2022 Ultimate Guide.
In this video we&#39;re going over a course overview of what we&#39;re going to be learning throughout the course.
So in Section two, we&#39;re going to talk about Adobe Creative Cloud plans.
So cover individuals, business students and teachers, schools and universities.
Next, we&#39;ll talk about how to create a free creative cloud account.
And then we&#39;ll talk about Adobe Creative Cloud Web and how to install Adobe XD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Guide to Product Design: Design Thinking Approach</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-guide-to-product-design-design-thinking-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-guide-to-product-design-design-thinking-approach/</guid>
      <description>**Course Updated - June 2022**
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; COURSE REGULARLY UPDATED: NEW TIPS, MORE LESSONS &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; CERTIFIED COACH, SPEAKER AND TRAINER &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; OVER 180,000 STUDENTS IN TOTAL &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
The world finally understands the essential role of design. Products look better than ever, interfaces feel intuitive, and companies are hiring designers at an increasing rate. But, the designer’s role has been changing over the last few years. It’s no longer enough to iterate and understand your user, instead of in today’s world, designers should be able to do both – identify problems and build solutions, which will increase their worth by at least 10 times for any company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Figma Megacourse: UI/UX Design Beginner to Expert</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-figma-megacourse-ui/ux-design-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-figma-megacourse-ui/ux-design-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>This course is constantly being revised and updated with new lessons.
Have you ever wanted to design your own app, website or blog? These days, we use them without a second thought. They have become an integral part of both the human experience and the financial market. It’s easy to come up with a new idea for a viral new app, but not as easy to make that app a reality - or so you might think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course on Design Thinking and Product Development</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/course-on-design-thinking-and-product-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 21:29:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/course-on-design-thinking-and-product-development/</guid>
      <description>Crisp and straight to the point lectures!
This course will cover the following topics.
· Design thinking
- You will learn about the 5 stages of Design thinking process: Empathize, Define, Ideate, Prototype &amp;amp; Test
· Challenges faced during successful Product development
· Characteristics of Product development
· Cost &amp;amp; Duration of product development
· Case study on Electronic brakeforce distribution system
· Difference between Agile, Design thinking Design sprint</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming A UX Writer</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/becoming-a-ux-writer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 12:27:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/becoming-a-ux-writer/</guid>
      <description>UX writing is the verbal user communication within digital interfaces. It appears in apps, websites, and all other kinds of digital products that users interact with – and, as such, it is an integral part of the user experience. For writers and designers, however, UX writing is much more than that: Since big tech companies have become increasingly aware of the importance of UX writing, the young discipline offers promising job opportunities, exciting tasks, and a great career outlook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn User Experience Design from A-Z: Adobe XD UI/UX Design</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-user-experience-design-from-a-z-adobe-xd-ui/ux-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 13:19:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-user-experience-design-from-a-z-adobe-xd-ui/ux-design/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Learn User Experience Design from A-Z: Adobe XD UI UX Design
Where you’re going to learn how to get started with User Experience and User Interface Design (UX/UI) Design and how to land your first job as a UX Designer even if you have no prior knowledge or experience.
In this practical, hands-on course our main objective is to give you the education not just to understand the ins and outs of UX and UI Design, but also to learn exactly how the web development industry works, the different roles within a team, how color psychology and color schemes work , so you can learn first hand exactly how to design websites and mobile apps in Adobe XD and create an amazing user experience as a UX &amp;amp; UI Designer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
