<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Advertising on </title>
    <link>/tags/advertising/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Advertising on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:52:12 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/advertising/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Facebook Traffic Ads (Facebook CPC) Course 2021</title>
      <link>/the-complete-facebook-traffic-ads-facebook-cpc-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:52:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-facebook-traffic-ads-facebook-cpc-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Gain more clients, maximise sales, and push more traffic to your website with the most comprehensive and current Facebook Traffic and Marketing course out there - The Complete Facebook Traffic Ads (Facebook CPC) Course 2021!
&#34;I love Tom, he is the man, he really knows what he&#39;s talking about when it comes to Facebook marketing. A true expert in the field! Don&#39;t hesitate to take this course, because I promise you that you will not be disappointed!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SELL Like HELL: Facebook Ads for E-COMMERCE Ultimate MASTERY</title>
      <link>/sell-like-hell-facebook-ads-for-e-commerce-ultimate-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 17:04:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sell-like-hell-facebook-ads-for-e-commerce-ultimate-mastery/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Excellent Facebook Ads &amp;amp; Instagram Ads Course. Would highly recommend this course to someone who is looking to learn or for that matter even gain knowledge. No institute or a YouTube video teaches this in so much detail as much as Tomas. I haven’t come across so far a genuine course teaching material as much as you have designed. Thanks Tomas a ton.&#34; Ridhima
&#34;Best course for Facebook e-commerce ads. Really in depth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Online Marketing &amp; Advertising Course</title>
      <link>/complete-online-marketing-advertising-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-online-marketing-advertising-course/</guid>
      <description>In This Online Course You Will Learn The RIGHT Way To Do Online Marketing &amp;amp; Advertising. This Course Covers ALL The Major Online Advertising Methods … Giving You Step-By-Step Instructions And A Great Overview Of Online Advertising.
Learning These Key Skills &amp;amp; Techniques Can Help You Be Massively Successful As You Do Online Marketing &amp;amp; Advertising. Once You Can Master Online Marketing &amp;amp; Advertising … Your Income Potential Is Limitless!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AD’s Hacker 1.0: Growth Hacking Certification for Marketers</title>
      <link>/ads-hacker-1.0-growth-hacking-certification-for-marketers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ads-hacker-1.0-growth-hacking-certification-for-marketers/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the third course in Term 2 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Time to set the advertising industry on fire with AD&#39;s Hacker 1.0 !!!
There is no denying that we have changed the way we work on the World Wide Web and the Internet. For presents or gifts, we no longer visit the city centre– we’re going to an eCommerce marketplace like Amazon and getting it shipped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon PPC Masterclass - The Ultimate PPC Guide</title>
      <link>/amazon-ppc-masterclass-the-ultimate-ppc-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/amazon-ppc-masterclass-the-ultimate-ppc-guide/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling with Amazon&#39;s Sponsored Products ads but don&#39;t know where to start? Do your existing PPC campaigns get high aCos and/or low sales volume?&amp;nbsp; Then this course is designed for you!

I will show you the biggest mistakes I see when using Amazon&#39;s Sponsored Products and teach you how to properly set up and optimise and create your campaigns. 

After years of testing and spending literally tens of thousands of dollars I&#39;ve discovered highly profitable Amazon PPC campaigns that have gone on to generate tens of thousands of dollars in sales and PROFIT.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
