<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Development on </title>
    <link>/tags/personal-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal Development on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/personal-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to be a good PR</title>
      <link>/how-to-be-a-good-pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-be-a-good-pr/</guid>
      <description>This course is presented by me: Alhassan Ahmed younes Ahmed a good PR in many teams. You will gain a lot of knowledge from my experience in this committee. You will learn how to pass any interview in this field, how to complete any form in registering in any team.

You will learn all of the information of this topic in student activities.

You will learn how to make deals from zero to hero, and I will help you with some important contact numbers of some people are very famous around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Become a Firefighter!</title>
      <link>/how-to-become-a-firefighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-become-a-firefighter/</guid>
      <description>Learn how a career as a firefighter can provide you with financial stability, allowing you to give back to your community and make you excited to come to work. Firefighting is a rewarding career that offers great opportunity for growth and advancement, amazing medical benefits and a high level of job satisfaction. This course will teach you how to prepare for your new career full of thrills and excitement while helping your community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning to Religion to reduce STRESS</title>
      <link>/turning-to-religion-to-reduce-stress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/turning-to-religion-to-reduce-stress/</guid>
      <description>Notice: Please do NOT enrol on this course on impulse, thinking you might watch it later. Maybe show an interest on impulse, yes, but before you enrol, watch the Preview videos, read the Course Description and then make a decision. If you then enrol then please start the course as soon as possible. Watch the lectures, look at the workbooks and join in the discussions. Joining my courses is a serious business and I want you to get the most out of your study – but I also want you to enjoy the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beat Procrastination in Turbulent Covid Era</title>
      <link>/beat-procrastination-in-turbulent-covid-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/beat-procrastination-in-turbulent-covid-era/</guid>
      <description>Procrastination is one of the principle boundaries obstructing you from getting up, settling on the correct choices, and carrying on with the fantasy life you&#39;ve considered.

Ongoing investigations have shown that individuals regret more the things they haven&#39;t done than the things they have done. Furthermore, sensations of disappointment and blame coming about because of botched freedoms will in general remain with individuals any longer.

Some of the time every one of our chances appear to be on our fingertips, however we can&#39;t contact them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fully Accredited Professional EFT Tapping Certification</title>
      <link>/fully-accredited-professional-eft-tapping-certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fully-accredited-professional-eft-tapping-certification/</guid>
      <description>This IAOTH, UK accredited EFT Tapping certification is a masterclass that will enable you to help an endless number of people (including yourself).
This concise programme is designed, keeping in mind that you may not have any prior knowledge about Art Therapy, and you want to learn despite your busy schedule. So we have tried to avoid jargon as much as possible and simplified concepts and terminology for you. for EFT is found extremely useful for a wide range of conditions/situations e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stress Management - For Relief From Stress of Life &amp; Work</title>
      <link>/stress-management-for-relief-from-stress-of-life-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stress-management-for-relief-from-stress-of-life-work/</guid>
      <description>Stress Management: Stress can weigh you down until you can hardly think straight! Beat it Today with this Comprehensive Stress Management Course filled with Cutting-Edge Tools &amp;amp; Strategies - Feel better TODAY! Created by Master Therapist &amp;amp; Multiple Award-Winning Educator Prof. Paul J. Cline Ed.D ... Get His 35+ years of Expertise in Helping others Beat Stress ... Condensed down into this Training.
Here Are Just A Few Of the Skills You Will Gain:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness para desarrollar la inteligencia emocional</title>
      <link>/mindfulness-para-desarrollar-la-inteligencia-emocional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mindfulness-para-desarrollar-la-inteligencia-emocional/</guid>
      <description>Te enseño herramientas efectivas y sencillas de aplicar en tu rutina diaria, invirtiendo sólo entre 5 a 15 minutos al día tus emociones no serán más un obstáculo en la consecución de tus metas, tampoco volverás a sentir la culpa o vergüenza de tus impulsos y reacciones emocionales. 
Tu también puedes gozar de relaciones empáticas, satisfactorias y sin tantas fricciones. Poder solucionar de manera asertiva y consciente las diferencias con tus seres queridos, colegas, clientes y colaboradores es posible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Repair - Auto Repair &amp; Tuning - Auto Technician Training</title>
      <link>/car-repair-auto-repair-tuning-auto-technician-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/car-repair-auto-repair-tuning-auto-technician-training/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
One of the things that I find most interesting about automotive technology is how it advances and changes. It is also interesting that ideas from many years ago often return to favour. In this course I have therefore concentrated on core technologies, in other words how the technology works, rather than giving too many examples from specific vehicles. However, I have included some examples of Formula 1 technology, arguably the pinnacle of automotive engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nomad Lifestyle: LIVE YOUR DREAM &amp; Travel the World</title>
      <link>/digital-nomad-lifestyle-live-your-dream-travel-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/digital-nomad-lifestyle-live-your-dream-travel-the-world/</guid>
      <description>IS IT POSSIBLE TO LIVE YOUR DREAM LIFE WITHOUT WORKING SO HARD? DOES IT HAVE TO TAKE SO MUCH EFFORT, STRESS, AND ENERGY TO HAVE A LIFE THAT DEEPLY FULFILS YOU? HONOR AND TRUST YOUR PROCESS, AND SURRENDER TO THE MAGIC OF LIFE!!! BEING A DIGITAL NOMAD MEANS LIVING LIFE 100% ON YOUR OWN TERMS!!!
From leaving behind the corporate life of a consistent and often capped salary, saying goodbye to cubicles, a regular work commute and the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Master Your Origin Challenge</title>
      <link>/how-to-master-your-origin-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-master-your-origin-challenge/</guid>
      <description>This course includes:
1 hours of on-demand video instruction
7 video sections
Over 30 downloadable exercises &amp;amp; resources
Downloadable book chapter
Full lifetime access
Access on mobile and TV
Certificate of completion

What you’ll learn:
Learn who and what you are and why.
Discover the “origin programming” done by your parents, etc. during your first 18 years of life.
Identify which of your traits and relationship characteristics come from your origin programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Stop Fear Spiritually</title>
      <link>/how-to-stop-fear-spiritually/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-stop-fear-spiritually/</guid>
      <description>Do you still allow fear to stop you from taking developmental steps?
If you have struggled to put that business idea that has been in your heart for many years&amp;nbsp;to work, then you&#39;re dwelling in the cage of fear.
&amp;nbsp;A wise man once said a child is born without fear except for the ones he&#39;s taught by society&amp;nbsp;as he grows up.
I want you to understand that everyone has the tendency to have fear but those who are great&amp;nbsp;achievers in our society have found a way to consistently kill it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview Success</title>
      <link>/interview-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/interview-success/</guid>
      <description>This course is for anyone wanting to do better at Job interviews and successfully get a Job offer in the career you want!
Created by practising Recruitment professionals with decades of experience in Business and Executive Recruitment from both Corporate leadership and Recruitment Agency backgrounds, we know what interviewers are looking for and what it takes to stand out - the competition is tougher than ever and we will help you shine!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Brain Training Course - Neuroplasticity -</title>
      <link>/the-complete-brain-training-course-neuroplasticity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-brain-training-course-neuroplasticity/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Brain Training Course - Neuroplasticity -
Brain Training for the Modern Smart Phone Era! You Can Train Your Brain to Think More Clearly and Creatively
Brain training is essential if you want do you live up to your full potential as a human being. Your brain is your most important organ, therefore it is essential that you train it for peak performance.
Like it or not, every single day your brain is being trained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Miraculous Faith</title>
      <link>/the-miraculous-faith/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-miraculous-faith/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling to overcome a problem or a challenge in your life, business, or marriage? Do you want simple-to-understand and easy-to-apply descriptions or explanations of the Christian faith that will help you solve those nagging problems in your life, business, or marriage?
If those questions apply to you, then this course, ‘The Miraculous Faith: Principles of Christian Faith Manifestation: How to make miracles through faith’ is just the right one for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PNL: Conversación transformacional &amp; Negociación efectiva</title>
      <link>/pnl-conversaci%C3%B3n-transformacional-negociaci%C3%B3n-efectiva/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pnl-conversaci%C3%B3n-transformacional-negociaci%C3%B3n-efectiva/</guid>
      <description>Los seres humanos hemos concebido la idea de que existen variables que están fuera de la gestión individual, por tal motivo se ha exteriorizado la responsabilidad de aquellos pilares transformándonos en víctima de factores externos configurados en paradigmas (política, economía, ciencia y religión) encarnados en autoridades dueñas de conocimientos, reglas y mandamientos que han configurado las estructuras mentales por las cuales construimos nuestras experiencias y realidades.
Sin embargo, gracias a la era de la información y a consecuencia de la conectividad producida por el mismo fenómeno, estamos comenzando a cambiar la percepción del tiempo y el conocimiento desde un paradigma lineal e inamovible a otro holístico y constituidos por millares de posibilidades.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
