<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Development on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/personal-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal Development on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/personal-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nomad Lifestyle: Live Your Dream &amp; Travel the World</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-nomad-lifestyle-live-your-dream-travel-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-nomad-lifestyle-live-your-dream-travel-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Is It Possible to Live your Dream Life Without Working so Hard?
Does it have to take so much effort, stress, and energy to have a life that deeply fulfils you? Honor and trust your process, and surrender to the magic of life!!! Being a digital nomad means living life 100% on your own terms!!!
From leaving behind the corporate life of a consistent and often capped salary, saying goodbye to cubicles, a regular work commute and the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>This course was designed to show even absolute beginners how to become more confident when speaking in public. It includes 5 preformatted lessons packed with easy to understand information.
Discover how to be more confident when speaking in public!
Do you know what one of the easiest ways to become a successful public speaker is? Well it is really easy and that is to study other successful speakers.
Why not learn from the best?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>No matter what business or industry you’re involved in, learning how to effectively manage your time is one of the most important skills that will set you on the path towards ongoing success.
This course will help you get more done in less time by levelling up your productivity score quickly and easily.
The strategies contained in this course are designed to help you learn to value your time, make informed decisions about the kind of work you’re focused on and ultimately, beat the clock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Motivation Course: Motivation for Your Success</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-motivation-course-motivation-for-your-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-motivation-course-motivation-for-your-success/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Motivation Course: Motivation for Your SuccessMotivation for Your Personal Development and Personal Success - Take Action Today for a Successful and Meaningful Future
You can have all the knowledge in the world, but without motivation, you cannot use your knowledge to live a more meaningful, purposeful and enjoyable life. Motivation is the key to living a successful life.
In this course you will learn how motivation is a skill that you can build.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10x your Productivity with Time Management</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/10x-your-productivity-with-time-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/10x-your-productivity-with-time-management/</guid>
      <description>Time…..the most scarce resource of life. Whatever job you do, you feel scarcity of only one thing i.e time. This scarcity does not differentiate rich or poor, black or white, tall or short, it&#39;s equal for everyone.
Even the most powerful person on earth has faced this scarcity.
In This Course I&#39;ll Teach You:
How to have Time Freedom. When you have time freedom you can focus your time on setting and achieving the biggest goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy parents happy kids parenting course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/happy-parents-happy-kids-parenting-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/happy-parents-happy-kids-parenting-course/</guid>
      <description>This course will nurture a better, peaceful atmosphere at home. Enhance your well-being of you as a parent and, in turn, the well-being of your children that will enrich the quality of your relationship with your child/children. This course will create more room for understanding and less room for tension and conflicts, by promote healthier coping skills and constructive responses, to not only your children but people around you. This course will help you regulate and manage your own emotions, by providing techniques for feeling more grounded and in control of situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>P.O.W.E.R Resume System: Proven system to get job interviews</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/p.o.w.e.r-resume-system-proven-system-to-get-job-interviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/p.o.w.e.r-resume-system-proven-system-to-get-job-interviews/</guid>
      <description>**Course Updated - June 2022**
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; COURSE REGULARLY UPDATED: NEW TIPS, MORE LESSONS &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; CERTIFIED COACH, SPEAKER AND TRAINER &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; OVER 180,000 STUDENTS IN TOTAL &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
Did you know it’s ONLY for 6 seconds any recruiting manager looks at your resume and that’s why it is a must to have a unique resume to catch the utmost attention of the employer within that 6-second span of time? It’s not easy to present your career in an easy-to-read way that does justice to your experience and is attractive enough to ignite the urge in the recruiter to perk up and reach the phone to make a call to you for an interview.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Zen Methodology Secrets To Habit Formation</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-zen-methodology-secrets-to-habit-formation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-zen-methodology-secrets-to-habit-formation/</guid>
      <description>The Zen Methodology Secrets To Habit Formation
If you lies in any of the below point:- . Procrastinate when we have difficult work to do. · Avoid exercise and seek the comforts of the Internet.
· Eat unhealthy food and gain too much weight. · Become overwhelmed, stressed out, full of anxiety. · Put off meeting new people because we’re afraid. · Avoid pursuing our dreams, building a business, finding our fulfilling careers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management for Personal &amp; Professional Productivity</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-for-personal-professional-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-for-personal-professional-productivity/</guid>
      <description>Hi ! I’m Pradeep Prajapati, your Instructor for this course. I know you are facing problems in your life for managing the most valuable asset of your life, and that asset is your time. In this course you will learn This course lays a common frame of understanding by exploring what people believe about time management, enumerating the benefits of time management, formally defining the term time management, briefly going over the history of time management, and showing how time management can lead to success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management for Professionals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-for-professionals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-for-professionals/</guid>
      <description>&#34;I must govern the clock, not be governed by it.&#34;
But how many of us can realize this dream? Not many, right? In today&#39;s fast-paced, hyper-connected world, you are not alone if you feel that there simply isn&#39;t enough time to get everything done at work. Even if we put in extra time, it seems like more tasks pile up and some even get lined up for the weekend, when we expect to have some uninterrupted time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quit your smartphone addiction with(in) 30 days challenges</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quit-your-smartphone-addiction-within-30-days-challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quit-your-smartphone-addiction-within-30-days-challenges/</guid>
      <description>This course is by no means a course in treating nomophobia, which is the term for the fear of losing one&#39;s phone, and an abbreviation for No More Phone (NoMoPhone/Phobia). It is merely a set of activities that anyone can do in an attempt to control and reduce the use and abuse of time spent on a smartphone. The average time spent online is around 7 hours per day, and most of it is done via a smartphone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rational Thinking</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/rational-thinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/rational-thinking/</guid>
      <description>The way you think influences the way you feel and behave. Irrational thoughts will lead to emotional distress and behavioral problems. Rational thoughts will help you experience positive emotions or negative, yet adaptive emotions. We all experience both types of thoughts - rational and irrational. But few know how to identify and separate them, so often they rule our life. Learn how to identify your irrational thinking patterns and make them more rational, through rational emotive behavior therapy (REBT).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Success Mindset Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/success-mindset-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/success-mindset-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>Most of people spent quite a bit of time thinking about what constitutes success, how they will achieve it, and how good they&#39;ll feel when they achieve their goals.
In this course you will learn 5 key steps that will help you reach your goals and accomplish what you’ve set out to do.
Learn how to nurture a mindset of success to become an unstoppable entrepreneur.
Success Mindset Course For EVERY Level</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unshakable self confidence for busy entrepreneurs</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/unshakable-self-confidence-for-busy-entrepreneurs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/unshakable-self-confidence-for-busy-entrepreneurs/</guid>
      <description>Raise your hand if the online entrepreneurship space is making you doubt yourself and question everything you do! We have good and bad news for you, fellow busy entrepreneur.
The bad news is: This happens to all of us. and will keep happening (sad but true!)
The good news is: You can totally fight it and beat it every. Single. Time!
And we came together and created this course to share with you our best tips, strategies, and solutions to go from constantly doubting yourself and your business to having unshakable self confidence and beat that self doubt every single time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking for Parents - Teach Your Kids to Present 1Hr</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-for-parents-teach-your-kids-to-present-1hr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-for-parents-teach-your-kids-to-present-1hr/</guid>
      <description>Public Speaking for Parents - Teach Your Kids to Present - learn in less than 1Hour
You can teach your child or kid to become a confident and strong public speaker. Public speaking and presentation skills are essential for success in most careers, yet they are rarely taught in public or private schools.
TJ Walker has taught public speaking skills to top CEOs, presidents of countries, prime ministers, and business visionaries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Life Transformation and Personal Growth Plan Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-life-transformation-and-personal-growth-plan-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-life-transformation-and-personal-growth-plan-guide/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you will learn the Life Transformation Techniques for personal Development, Personal Transformation, and Finding Your Life Purpose. In just 10-minutes a day, The Personal Life Transformation Masterclass will help revolutionize your life by improving your mindset, goals, and personal and professional productivity. You&#39;ll unlock the potential concentration, confidence, and optimism you need to start moving forward again and again. Once you&#39;ve mastered mentioned areas completely, you&#39;ll feel unstoppable and have total belief in your ability to achieve incredible results with ease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Confidence &amp; Self Esteem: Confidence Via Self-Awareness</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/self-confidence-self-esteem-confidence-via-self-awareness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/self-confidence-self-esteem-confidence-via-self-awareness/</guid>
      <description>Boost your confidence and self-esteem in just a few seconds and for the long-term. Then use confidence as a tool to achieve more and improve your life.
- Scientific research about confidence and performance
- Authoritative literature on confidence - Law of attraction
- Positive affirmations to boost confidence
- Listening to your internal dialog and realigning it to boost your confidence
- Getting positive reinforcement from your relationships - Conquering your fear of failure</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assertiveness Training &amp; Assertive Communication Improvement</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/assertiveness-training-assertive-communication-improvement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/assertiveness-training-assertive-communication-improvement/</guid>
      <description>Learn assertive communication that helps you and the person with whom you are communicating. After you master assertive communication, learn to use it in various professional scenarios, including negotiation.
We communicate every day. Why not learn how to be more open, transparent, and get people on our side with our communication? That&#39;s exactly what happens when you are assertive. You define your boundaries not by being rude or authoritarian, but by being transparent and honest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effective Time Management Skills For A Productivity Boost</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/effective-time-management-skills-for-a-productivity-boost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/effective-time-management-skills-for-a-productivity-boost/</guid>
      <description>This course approaches time management from 3 unique angles:
Time management in a single day
Time management in a week
Time management in your life to make sure that the tasks you work on are the right ones for your overall life direction, because if you are working on the wrong tasks, then all that time is mismanaged and wasted
Try this course and its unique approach which ends at you looking at the bigger picture of your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn to drive a car: real world driving &amp; exam preparation</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-to-drive-a-car-real-world-driving-exam-preparation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-to-drive-a-car-real-world-driving-exam-preparation/</guid>
      <description>Driving can be a daunting task if you lack the experience or the knowledge. Learners commonly feel unconfident when they step into the car next to their examiner for their final exam and make unnecessary mistakes because of it. This often results in insecurity, which drags on into their future driving time.Our lessons are packed with tips, tricks and how-to&#39;s to help you enjoy driving. Whether you simply want to improve your driving skills, become a more confident driver or want to pass that driving exam, this is your course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn To Focus: Meditation &amp; Mindfulness For ADHD</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-to-focus-meditation-mindfulness-for-adhd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-to-focus-meditation-mindfulness-for-adhd/</guid>
      <description>ADD and ADHD can make it hard to focus &amp;amp; get things done. You have lots of mental energy (that&#39;s why you&#39;re so smart!) but you have a hard time directing it to one thing at a time. Many people go through their entire lives in this scatter-brained state, jumping from thing to thing, never fully concentrating on, or actually enjoying, anything. This can lead to major school &amp;amp; career problems (not paying attention in class, not paying attention at work, not caring about what you&#39;re working on, bouncing from job to job, career to career, etc), and problems becoming a successful adult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mind Power - Change Your Thought Process To Change Your Life</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mind-power-change-your-thought-process-to-change-your-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mind-power-change-your-thought-process-to-change-your-life/</guid>
      <description>**Course Updated - June 2022**
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; COURSE REGULARLY UPDATED: NEW TIPS, MORE LESSONS &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; CERTIFIED COACH, SPEAKER AND TRAINER &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; OVER 180,000 STUDENTS IN TOTAL &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
To have a breakthrough in YOUR happiness and emotional well-being... All you have to Do is CHANGE YOUR BELIEF SYSTEM/THOUGHT PROCESS
Have you ever thought about what causes someone to persist when another would give up?
What causes a person to focus and utilize all their resources towards a goal?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Clarity Compass: Finding &amp; Following my Unique Purpose</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/my-clarity-compass-finding-following-my-unique-purpose/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/my-clarity-compass-finding-following-my-unique-purpose/</guid>
      <description>Do you feel frustrated because you outgrew your current situation and are so ready for a change but don’t know where to start? You’re struggling to figure out what you really desire to pursue next in life because you’re overwhelmed &amp;amp; procrastinating any decision because you’re stuck overthinking?
Then this is for you.
My Clarity Compass is a bite sized video online course that will help you to reflect on what you really want in life, what makes you happy &amp;amp; to make a decision with confidence on what you want to pursue next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passions of the soul. Resurrection</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/passions-of-the-soul.-resurrection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/passions-of-the-soul.-resurrection/</guid>
      <description>Passions make us suffer and can ruin our life.
Create a better understanding of human passions.
Intense feelings of passionate love affect the brain in the same way as drugs like cocaine.
How to transit from passionate love to compassionate?
Gain a deeper insight into chemistry, lust and obsession.
Why is chemistry not the same as compatibility?
Learn about neuroscience of chemistry, lust, love and hatred.
Self-love, self- esteem and self- compassion are the keys for psychological well- being and mental health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Obvious Secrets To Success No One Knows</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-obvious-secrets-to-success-no-one-knows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-obvious-secrets-to-success-no-one-knows/</guid>
      <description>This training will DIRECTLY Answer the following questions:
How to get more money! How to lose weight and live longer! How to build great relationships! And much more! In addition, you will learn a step-by-step system on how to overcome your challenges and reach your full potential! What decisions do you make?
What is your Reality? And is it real?
What is Commitment actually about?
The Secret Sauce: Action!
This is a step-by-step course for understanding what it takes to succeed and then walks you through 4 simple steps to implement that understanding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Time Management and Productivity (Bonus Free eBook)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-time-management-and-productivity-bonus-free-ebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-time-management-and-productivity-bonus-free-ebook/</guid>
      <description>Make the most of EVERY second, because when it is gone, you can NEVER have it back!
Wouldn’t it be absolutely liberating if you could decrease your hours and increase your productive output at the same time?
Is life not too short to waste your precious seconds on unproductive endeavors, feeling stressed, overwhelmed and asking yourself how it is all worthwhile?
Are you tired of feeling tired, overworked and on the verge of burning out because you have too much to do and to little time in which to do it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypnosis for Natural Easy Childbirth  Hypnosis Program</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hypnosis-for-natural-easy-childbirth-hypnosis-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hypnosis-for-natural-easy-childbirth-hypnosis-program/</guid>
      <description>Hypnosis for Natural Easy Childbirth Hypnosis Program this has been created to simulate a complete collection of private hypnosis sessions with me as your guiding Hypnotherapist
Childbirth is one of the most natural experiences any woman can ever have and has to have been the first ever most precious of human experiences. All fears and most of the pain that you may have heard about giving birth or being in labor are created by those people who gave birth with fear in their minds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser Focus Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/laser-focus-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/laser-focus-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>We live in an era of information overload. We are bombarded with media, technology, entertainment, and notifications every day. It seems there are hundreds of people and things competing for your attention at any given time.
There is no wonder why in the last few years, our attention spans have become shorter and our ability to focus has decreased.
Not being able to focus can have a negative effect on how successful we are at work and in our personal lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop Panic Attacks Today with EFT</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/stop-panic-attacks-today-with-eft/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/stop-panic-attacks-today-with-eft/</guid>
      <description>Panic attacks effect so many people today resulting in sickness and lost days at work and can effect people from all walks of life from business men who head up huge corporations to their workers both male and female housewives and children attending school.
The good news is it is only a reaction to a past experience where your mind is continuously working looking out to protect you from what frightened you in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Persuasion in Business Communications</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/persuasion-in-business-communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/persuasion-in-business-communications/</guid>
      <description>Persuasion is the most powerful tool any business executive, manager, or leader can have. With strong persuasion skills, any goal is achievable. Without strong persuasion skills, not much happens and careers and businesses stall.
This course is filled with practical, step-by-step processes that anyone in the workplace can use to persuade colleagues, bosses, customers, clients and prospects on what to do.
You can persuade people to endorse your plan, become a customer, validate your idea, hire your firm or approve your budget, once you know and practice the skills of persuasion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leading Effective Meetings - You Can Lead Effective Meetings</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/leading-effective-meetings-you-can-lead-effective-meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/leading-effective-meetings-you-can-lead-effective-meetings/</guid>
      <description>Leading Effective Meetings. Imagine yourself leading effective meetings that people in your organization actually look forward to attending. Meetings don&#39;t have to be dry, boring, tedious, time-wasting affairs.
In this course, you will learn the specific skills and mindset needed for leading effective meetings. You will master the following:
How to plan meetings more effectively
how to set a meeting agenda
How to instantly engage everyone in a meeting within the first 3 minutes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pursue Top 1% Career: Become The No. 1 Success Magnet</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pursue-top-1-career-become-the-no.-1-success-magnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:33:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pursue-top-1-career-become-the-no.-1-success-magnet/</guid>
      <description>**Course Updated - June 2022**
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; COURSE REGULARLY UPDATED: NEW TIPS, MORE LESSONS &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; CERTIFIED COACH, SPEAKER AND TRAINER &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; OVER 180,000 STUDENTS IN TOTAL &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
Are you not able to convert job interviews into job offers? Or your appraisals into promotions?
Do you have all of the required qualifications, yet are not able to create an unforgettable impression?
Are you looking for a key that will unlock success in your life?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Independent Film Screenwriting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/simple-independent-film-screenwriting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/simple-independent-film-screenwriting/</guid>
      <description>By independent director, producer and screenwriter Hank Orion. In this course we will dive deep into writing screenplay specifically for independent films. We will talk about stuff they don&#39;t teach you at film school. Some of the topics we will cover in this course are:
Screenplay Format And What Software To Use
Character Research
How To Write A Good Backstory
Writing A Solid Beginning, Middle And An End
How To Write Great Act I</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management Mastery: 10X Your Time, Join the New Rich</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-mastery-10x-your-time-join-the-new-rich/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-mastery-10x-your-time-join-the-new-rich/</guid>
      <description>Time management is essential for the growth and success of any individual. The majority of the world&#39;s billionaires or successful people have excellent time management skills. They use their limited time so productively that the rest of the population finds it hard to emulate.
Good time management skills aren&#39;t about the amount of time available to implement a task. It&#39;s about making the little time you have to be as productive as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goal Setting For Success: Plan And Achieve Your Goals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/goal-setting-for-success-plan-and-achieve-your-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/goal-setting-for-success-plan-and-achieve-your-goals/</guid>
      <description>Are you a student, struggling at setting and achieving your goals?
This goal setting course will quickly allow you to start setting personal and professional goals to boost your success.
If you are a studente you can start seeing a path to the success you hope for: you will be able to develop a goal setting mindset, find out what you want in life and create a concrete action plan to reach your targets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stress-free Effective Learning for Adults: Crush your goals!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/stress-free-effective-learning-for-adults-crush-your-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/stress-free-effective-learning-for-adults-crush-your-goals/</guid>
      <description>This course on how to learn is designed with life-long learning in mind for you to become a superlearner. Taking a holistic approach, we will explore the different areas and techniques that will make your study sessions engaging, avoid procrastination, and make study fun and stress-free.
The course is targeted for both students and people seeking adult education help, who work and want to increase their productivity and develop their career further.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comunicación Asertiva y Empática</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/comunicaci%C3%B3n-asertiva-y-emp%C3%A1tica/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/comunicaci%C3%B3n-asertiva-y-emp%C3%A1tica/</guid>
      <description>Te ha pasado ¿Qué no logras crear confianza en un negocio? o te preguntas muy seguido ¿por qué no me entiendo con un compañero(a) de trabajo? o incluso has pensado que algo pasa contigo ¿por qué no atraes la relación de pareja que esperas?, en este curso podrás responderte a ti mism@ estos interrogantes, porque vas a potencializar tus habilidades comunicativas, las cuales te permitan crear lazos de confianza y empatía, en tus negocios, en las relaciones con los compañeros del trabajo, en los vínculos afectivos y en todas tus interacciones interpersonales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering The Interview</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mastering-the-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mastering-the-interview/</guid>
      <description>The interview is one of the key elements of the job search process.
As with any skill, we can get better at it with preparation and practice. So in this course, you will explore how to prepare for an interview and become familiar with the types of questions to expect, as well as the questions you should think about asking.
Some people are natural at selling themselves to hiring managers. Others aren’t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unleash Your Creative Mind</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/unleash-your-creative-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/unleash-your-creative-mind/</guid>
      <description>**Course Updated - June 2022**
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; COURSE REGULARLY UPDATED: NEW TIPS, MORE LESSONS &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; CERTIFIED COACH, SPEAKER AND TRAINER &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; OVER 180,000 STUDENTS IN TOTAL &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
I am sure you have heard it once if not many times that CREATIVITY - Worth Its Weight in Gold.
Being creative is a very desirable trait in modern society. Before the modern information age creativity was not something the average person really needed in order to be a productive member of society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Couples Counseling | Learn to Live happy with Life Partner</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/couples-counseling-learn-to-live-happy-with-life-partner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/couples-counseling-learn-to-live-happy-with-life-partner/</guid>
      <description>Happy Couple Relationship is basic ambition of Life Partners, however this relationship is very sensitive and needs extra attention from Life Partners to make the relationship happy and smooth.
Couples who do not give proper attention for effective management of Marriage Relationship are likely to go into deep conflicts which may result into divorce or at-least toward prolonged resentment.
This Couples Counseling course is designed for those Couples who have been facing difficulty in maintaining the healthy relationship with life partners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brain Computer Interfacing via spiking neuromorphic networks</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/brain-computer-interfacing-via-spiking-neuromorphic-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/brain-computer-interfacing-via-spiking-neuromorphic-networks/</guid>
      <description>This exciting course contains two parts. The first part introduces you to the fundamentals of brain functioning prior to Brain-Computer Interfacing in the second part.
The first part of the course aims to provide students with an introduction to the core ideas of the brain involving inculcating happiness and well-being to manage stress, anxiety, and depression. Further acquainting them with the significance of positive thinking, courage, and determination, the meaning of life, gratitude, and compassion in life in the first part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Up Creativity in Your Child</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fire-up-creativity-in-your-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fire-up-creativity-in-your-child/</guid>
      <description>**Course Updated - June 2022**
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; COURSE REGULARLY UPDATED: NEW TIPS, MORE LESSONS &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; CERTIFIED COACH, SPEAKER AND TRAINER &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; OVER 180,000 STUDENTS IN TOTAL &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------
What if I told you your child has special powers and latent abilities just waiting to be unleashed?? Sounds interesting?? Let’s go ahead and learn what this is all about…
Let me ask you a few questions? Do children today use their imaginations as much as we did when we were kids?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Coaching: ZERO TO HERO Life Coach certificate Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/life-coaching-zero-to-hero-life-coach-certificate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/life-coaching-zero-to-hero-life-coach-certificate-course/</guid>
      <description>Many people often mistake a life coach for a mental health professional, such as a psychiatrist or a therapist. This misconception often leads people to believe they do not need a life coach since they feel as though nothing is wrong with their mental health. However, a life coach is designed to help improve a person’s professional and personal life by working with them to achieve their goals. You will discover the meaning of life coaching and how life coaching services can be utilized to achieve their goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LIFE CRAFTING: The System to Make a Masterpiece of Your Life</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/life-crafting-the-system-to-make-a-masterpiece-of-your-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/life-crafting-the-system-to-make-a-masterpiece-of-your-life/</guid>
      <description>What Is Life Crafting?
Life Crafting means skillfully shaping 5 key areas of your life incrementally over your lifetime, in line with a vision of what your life can be by knowing what you are going to do, then learning and practicing your skills using a clear recipe vs. living by random trial, and error. This is Making a Masterpiece of Your Life. This is Life-as-a-Craft.
Life-as-a-Craft
‘Life-as-a-Craft’ is a framework based on the practices found in master workshops across the world, applied to practicing ‘life’ as a defined &#39;craft&#39; the way that someone learns and practices textile weaving, woodworking, or any other trade, occupation, and profession; (i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neuroplasticity: Discover How To Rewire Your Anxiety</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/neuroplasticity-discover-how-to-rewire-your-anxiety/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/neuroplasticity-discover-how-to-rewire-your-anxiety/</guid>
      <description>The human brain is capable of integrating intricate and diverse inputs from multiple sensory systems simultaneously in order to rapidly comprehend and assess the information for planning and execution of complex actions. These and other cognitive functions are performed by the vastly interconnected neural networks formed by the roughly 100 billion neurons of the brain. The precise patterns of connectivity among neurons within these networks determines their function, and through experience, these connectivity patterns change over time to enable acquisition of new skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Persuasion: Give a Persuasive Presentation</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/persuasion-give-a-persuasive-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 20:12:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/persuasion-give-a-persuasive-presentation/</guid>
      <description>Persuasion can be possible in every presentation you give. Imagine that every time you speak, your audience not only understands you but is persuaded by your arguments and ideas. Wouldn&#39;t it be great to know that when you speak, people will be convinced of the vision you have? You can become the master of persuasion.
In this How to Give a Persuasive Speech course you will learn the following: * How to be more persuasive in every presentation * Excel at all aspects or presentation persuasion</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master the Art Of Self-Confidence – Unshakable Confidence</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-the-art-of-self-confidence-unshakable-confidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-the-art-of-self-confidence-unshakable-confidence/</guid>
      <description>In this you will get learn the power of Confidence and How you can make your personality more strong and powerful. This course focuses on the benefits of strong and consequences of low confidence.
In this course I will share with you some of my best strategies for becoming more confident. The great thing about this course is that you can complete it in 30 minutes and most of the strategies I discuss can be implemented straight away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self Care: The Boundary Bundle</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/self-care-the-boundary-bundle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/self-care-the-boundary-bundle/</guid>
      <description>The Boundary Bundle
Boundaries are limits that we set with ourselves, family, friends, co-workers and the world around us to protect ourselves. Boundaries are how we express what we will or will not tolerate. They are how we protect and manage our time and energy.
Boundaries are sometimes disregarded, we all experience boundary pushers. Most of the time, people are not trying to push our limits. Most of the time, these violations occur because we haven’t voiced what our needs are or what our wants are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Become a Facilitator: 7 Effective Skills</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-become-a-facilitator-7-effective-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-become-a-facilitator-7-effective-skills/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever felt like the task of becoming a leader and leading people to success is impossible? Well, it is no secret that the task may seem quite daunting and out of the realms of our possibilities. Well, the beauty of life is that nothing is impossible and with courage and willpower one can overcome their greatest fears and lead people to greatness.
That is one of the main functions of a Facilitation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master the Art of Making Actionable To Do List</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-the-art-of-making-actionable-to-do-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-the-art-of-making-actionable-to-do-list/</guid>
      <description>A to-do list is nothing but a list of tasks you need to complete in a certain period of time.
It’s a very simple, efficient and extremely popular productivity tool, the only problem is that you can find a lot of conflicting advice online on whether to-do lists work or not, and whether you should keep them in your productivity tool belt at all. To-do lists are an efficient tool to boost your productivity but the Problem is we dont know How to Make an Effective To-do List and Moreover Build a discipline to stick to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automate your Job-Search with LoopCV in 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/automate-your-job-search-with-loopcv-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/automate-your-job-search-with-loopcv-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Automate your Job-Search with LoopCV in 2022&#34;.
Just imagine, how much time do you spend applying to jobs and all you get is a rejection letter after a week or a month&#39;s time?
Let&#39;s get this right as we elaborate on this problem faced by every job-seeker out there.
Do you actually spend a lot of time applying to a job, only to wait for weeks without any kind of positive feedback or response from recruiters and hiring managers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing a Career based on Passion in 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/choosing-a-career-based-on-passion-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/choosing-a-career-based-on-passion-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>Ready to experience &#34;Choosing a Career based on passion in 2022&#34;?
Welcome, my name is Srinidhi Ranganathan. My fans fondly call me &#34;Digital Marketing Legend&#34;. Teaming up with Saranya and Sai Manoj, I have now put this training course &#34;Choosing a career based on passion&#34; together to help people pursue their passion and achieve the success that will follow with happiness in their lives.
While pursuing your passion or what we call &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>P.O.W.E.R. : Proven Interview System to crack your DREAM job</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/p.o.w.e.r.-proven-interview-system-to-crack-your-dream-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/p.o.w.e.r.-proven-interview-system-to-crack-your-dream-job/</guid>
      <description>**Course Updated - May 2022**
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; COURSE REGULARLY UPDATED: NEW TIPS, MORE LESSONS &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; CERTIFIED COACH, SPEAKER AND TRAINER &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; OVER 180,000 STUDENTS IN TOTAL &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
Preparing for an interview takes a lot more than Googling a list of common interview questions. You have to make a great first impression, you will have to have a great knowledge of your target company and its product, and, of course, know exactly how to convey that you&#39;re the perfect fit for the job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 6 steps to unlock your confidence</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-6-steps-to-unlock-your-confidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-6-steps-to-unlock-your-confidence/</guid>
      <description>we will learn about importance of having goals in life and the extent of their impact on self confidence and moving with specific and steady steps towards goals and how to overcome challenges and obstacles and the importance of approaching the successful and imitating their steps and confidence in our capabilities and ideas and changing the negative ones to positive to reach the desired success. failure dose not reflect the person, his thoughts, or his feelings, but it is just an unsuccessful step and must be retried many times to reach the desired goal, And as we know that one of the most important causes of loss of self-confidence, which turns against progress and success, is the crippling beliefs that are not helpful to us, but also affect our feelings because they are a major reason for the existence of negative thoughts that we get used to with time and in most studies, the existence of these beliefs consists in childhood and because they remain with us It is not a small period in our life, it also takes a not small period to change it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innovation 1.0: Learn To Think Creatively Like Walt Disney</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/innovation-1.0-learn-to-think-creatively-like-walt-disney/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/innovation-1.0-learn-to-think-creatively-like-walt-disney/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the course titled &#34;Innovation 1.0: Learn To Think Creatively Like Walt Disney&#34;
What would Walt Disney think?
Although Disney has been gone for a long, you know that his company is still at the forefront of technological evolution. Frankly speaking, it was his marketing genius that set him and his company apart from everybody else on the planet. Now, I would like to re-incarnate Walt Disney into this course and put forth ideas from his perspective, imagining him to be your business coach, after all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memory: 3 Ways of Memorising Like a Spy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/memory-3-ways-of-memorising-like-a-spy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/memory-3-ways-of-memorising-like-a-spy/</guid>
      <description>Our brain is really stubborn at times. It doesn’t want to remember certain things, it doesn’t want to cope with the fact that you just have to remember certain information. Lucky us – this problem can be solved.
This course is about Memory, about memorizing like a spy, so that’s exactly what we are going to do. We are going to learn how to Memory like a spy. Spies have to remember a lot, their life depends on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Method 333 To Learn &amp; Strengthen Your Emotional Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/method-333-to-learn-strengthen-your-emotional-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 21:50:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/method-333-to-learn-strengthen-your-emotional-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>This course takes a radically different approach to emotional intelligence.
This course is about you, how to free yourself from the negative force that opposes the positive change of emotions that no teaching or technique mentions due to ignorance or to keep hidden from the mass.
This is a practical course based on true deep spirituality to acquire the ability to know how to express and control your emotions, which is essential and acquire the ability to understand, interpret, and respond to the emotions of others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autocoaching: Aumenta tus Fortalezas, Mejora tus Debilidades</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/autocoaching-aumenta-tus-fortalezas-mejora-tus-debilidades/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/autocoaching-aumenta-tus-fortalezas-mejora-tus-debilidades/</guid>
      <description>¿Te has dado cuenta de que en las últimas décadas ha subido mucho el interés por el crecimiento personal y el bienestar?
Teorías, cursos, libros, training. Muchísimos recursos a nuestro alcance, pero…los resultados no son todo lo exitosos que esperamos.
Las investigaciones demuestran que la mayoría de la gente cuando pasa por un fracaso o un revés emocional, olvida lo que han aprendido y cae en los viejos hábitos y el malestar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10x Your Social Skills &amp; Connect With People</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/10x-your-social-skills-connect-with-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/10x-your-social-skills-connect-with-people/</guid>
      <description>**Course Updated - May 2022**
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; COURSE REGULARLY UPDATED: NEW TIPS, MORE LESSONS &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; CERTIFIED COACH, SPEAKER AND TRAINER &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; OVER 180,000 STUDENTS IN TOTAL &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
The first step is increasing your skill in dealing with people. 85 percent of your success in life is going to be determined by your social skills, by your ability to interact positively and effectively with others and to get them to cooperate with you in helping you to achieve your goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know Yourself Much Better: Cues From Friedrich Nietzsche</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/know-yourself-much-better-cues-from-friedrich-nietzsche/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:57:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/know-yourself-much-better-cues-from-friedrich-nietzsche/</guid>
      <description>Knowing yourself is a journey. A discovery about who you are as a person. The real YOU. This journey of self-discovery is unpredictable. You must face your vulnerabilities, insecurities, and even deepest fears. And why is this important?
Aristotle answers. “Knowing yourself is the beginning of all wisdom”. Gaining mastery over others could be perceived to be a strength. But gaining mastery over yourself is true power. People who have realized this simple but profound fact have gone on to achieve great things in life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Steps To Adopting Healthy, Healthy Habits!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/7-steps-to-adopting-healthy-healthy-habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 20:03:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/7-steps-to-adopting-healthy-healthy-habits/</guid>
      <description>Stop Settling For Just Surviving
Are you tired of feeling worn out and out of shape?
Constantly running, feeling like life didn&#39;t used to be like this.
If you’re finding yourself nodding along to all this, you’re not alone…
What would your life be like if you were truly brimming with energy and addicted to feeling good ….NATURALLY?
By focusing on your diet and mindset you can lift your life:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management &amp; Productivity Masterclass- Beat Overwhelm</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-productivity-masterclass-beat-overwhelm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 20:03:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-productivity-masterclass-beat-overwhelm/</guid>
      <description>Objective 1: Learn Time Management Fundamentals
Objective 2: Learn how to get all your thoughts out of your mind and on paper or in software
Objective 3: Learn the Time Management 80/20 Rule
Objective 4: Can you really Multi-task?
Objective 5: Learn from Elon Musk and Warren Buffet time management tools
Objective 6: Learn how to take back your day and get the most done
FACT 1: Despite time tracking apps, hints and tips being available, only 17% of people track their own time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storytelling With Imagery For Persuasion &amp; Personal Brand</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/storytelling-with-imagery-for-persuasion-personal-brand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 20:40:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/storytelling-with-imagery-for-persuasion-personal-brand/</guid>
      <description>Learn storytelling in two ways:
1) The traditional story arch and all the important story elements
2) Create creative imagery with your writing and vocal presentation that inspires emotions in your audience, becomes memorable, and leaves a lasting and impactful lesson and impression.
USE EMOTIONS FOR PERSUASION
People make decisions emotionally much more than logically. That&#39;s why great storytelling is about painting a picture in someone&#39;s mind and making them see things your way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Control Your Subconscious Mind: Neuroscience Hidden Secrets</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/control-your-subconscious-mind-neuroscience-hidden-secrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 15:08:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/control-your-subconscious-mind-neuroscience-hidden-secrets/</guid>
      <description>**Course Updated - May 2022**
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; COURSE REGULARLY UPDATED: NEW TIPS, MORE LESSONS &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; CERTIFIED COACH, SPEAKER AND TRAINER &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; OVER 180,000 STUDENTS IN TOTAL &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
Congratulations! You just found the Top 1% Course on Controlling Your Subconscious Mind to help you live the FUTURE you really want.
DISCOVER the 9 step Neuroscience Blueprint to Control Your Subconscious Mind. Learn the basic foundations of neuroscience and the brain and how can you control your brain to take actions automatically towards your desired future and not for survival.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical Ho&#39;oponopono Workshop</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/practical-hooponopono-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 15:08:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/practical-hooponopono-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to unleash your potential beyond your wildest dreams?If so, this course can truly help...Please ask yourself these questions:- Are your health conditions optimal?- Do you have financial independence?- Are your relationships loving and nurturing?- Is your career (or business) truly thriving?- Are you actually happy and at peace?- Are you fulfilling all your innermost dreams?If you answered no to any of these questions, this course is for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Invaluable Benefits of integrity</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-invaluable-benefits-of-integrity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-invaluable-benefits-of-integrity/</guid>
      <description>Act confident: the best way to develop courage in front of an audience is to act as if you already have it. It also helps to take a few deep breaths before you begin speaking, to get the oxygen flowing to your brain. Stand tall, look your audience in the eyes, and don&#39;t fidget.
About Mehreen Siddiqui &amp;amp; Alexis Lenihan
Mehreen Siddiqui is a Certified High Performance Coach and John Maxwell Trainer and Facilitator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women and Digital Inclusion</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/women-and-digital-inclusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/women-and-digital-inclusion/</guid>
      <description>The ability to access and use the internet effectively is central to women’s digital inclusion. • When women gain meaningful access and participate in evolving knowledge societies, it is not only women that benefit, but the whole economy. • Promoting internet access for women is much more than an issue of gender equality; it is an essential part of the economic, social and political development of the countries.
It is vital to find ways to empower women to participate in designing, building and leading our shared digital future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management &amp; Productivity for Effective Time Management</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-productivity-for-effective-time-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:57:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-productivity-for-effective-time-management/</guid>
      <description>Three reasons to TAKE THIS COURSE right now! The unique reasons for taking this course are: Complete, Concise, Confident Overview of Personal Productivity Hacks and Time Management Course especially if you want a certification to prove it - You will be confident that you have a complete overview of Time Management &amp;amp; Personal Productivity as the experts intended it, because I only teach accurately based on the expert teachings of the pros like Brian Tracy and Tony Robbins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Daily Joy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-daily-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 20:40:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-daily-joy/</guid>
      <description>I’m a strong believer that your day is your life. Yet so many people feel stuck and frustrated living their days on repeat and doing the same things. And I used to be one of those people!
For years I felt trapped because my days were all the same, and my routine left me bored and unfulfilled. I had had enough and I decided I wasn&#39;t going to live my life on repeat anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to FAQ the coder&#39;s brain?</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-faq-the-coders-brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:10:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-faq-the-coders-brain/</guid>
      <description>Are you a coder? How is your personality connected with coding? Can you become a coder having non-technical background?
What is paradigm shift?
Learn neuroplasticity for developing a creative mind.
Why do you need art to become creative?
Gain insights from merging of technology with art.
Highly sensitive people are the most passionate and creative. How to develop your sensitivity and sensuality to become more creative? &#34;Creativity is intelligence having fun&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Método 333 - Aprende y Fortalece Tu Inteligencia Emocional.</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/m%C3%A9todo-333-aprende-y-fortalece-tu-inteligencia-emocional./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:10:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/m%C3%A9todo-333-aprende-y-fortalece-tu-inteligencia-emocional./</guid>
      <description>Este curso adopta un enfoque radicalmente diferente de la inteligencia emocional.
Este curso se trata de ti, de cómo liberarte de la fuerza negativa que se opone al cambio positivo de las emociones que ninguna enseñanza o técnica menciona por desconocimiento de las mismas o por mantenerlo oculto a la masa.
Este es un curso práctico basado en la verdadera espiritualidad profunda para adquirir la capacidad de saber expresar y controlar tus emociones, lo cual es fundamental, y adquirir la capacidad de comprender, interpretar y responder a las emociones de los demás.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personalentwicklung für (zukünftige) Führungskräfte</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personalentwicklung-f%C3%BCr-zuk%C3%BCnftige-f%C3%BChrungskr%C3%A4fte/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:10:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personalentwicklung-f%C3%BCr-zuk%C3%BCnftige-f%C3%BChrungskr%C3%A4fte/</guid>
      <description>Würdest du gerne deine Fähigkeiten in der Personalführung verbessern und bist Führungskraft oder eine Person mit Verantwortung? Dieser Kurs bietet dir das notwendige Hintergrundwissen mit vielen Praxisbeispielen zum schnellen Durchstarten. Zielgruppe sind (zukünftige) Führungskräfte, Projektleiter/innen, Personen mit Leitungsfunktionen oder einfach alle Menschen mit Verantwortung im Job.
Ich habe sowohl wissenschaftliche Inhalte als auch meine eigene Erfahrungen als Trainer, Coach und Führungskraft in diesen Lektionen eingebaut. Dadurch erhaltet ihr einen guten Überblick über das die wichtigsten Instrumente der Personalentwicklung, was eure Professionalität als Personalentwickler/in oder/und Führungskraft ausbaut und festigt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Journaling Course: Build Self-Awareness Habits</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-journaling-course-build-self-awareness-habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:10:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-journaling-course-build-self-awareness-habits/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Journaling Course: Build Self-Awareness HabitsLearn the Journaling Habit - Increase Self-awareness Improve Note-Taking Skills Avoid Procrastination Organize Your Life
You can lead a more fulfilled life, a more productive life, and a happier life through the practice of daily journaling. Journaling can seem intimidating to those who have not started the process, but it is easy to begin and maintain once you understand the basics.
From Albert Einstein to Marie Curie, many of the greatest innovators in history or committed practitioners of journaling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become A Tower Crane Operator</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/become-a-tower-crane-operator/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 17:02:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/become-a-tower-crane-operator/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the tallest machines in the world.
I would like to take this moment to thank God for blessing me with this career for 6 years. Thank you for providing me with everything I need and more. Thank you for the places I have seen. Thank you for the people I have met. Thank you for the opportunity to pursue more of my dreams.
I pray the students who take this course have understanding, have courage and are blessed in the pursuit of their new career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Counselling and Negotiation Skills for Management</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/counselling-and-negotiation-skills-for-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 17:02:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/counselling-and-negotiation-skills-for-management/</guid>
      <description>You might mirror that when you last encountered an issue, assuming you had the option to talk about it with somebody whom you trusted, you felt much improved. The individual whom you trusted in may have proposed specific strides to deal with the issue, which you might not have considered. Now and again the audience can direct you to look inwards and track down arrangements. Thusly, offering one&#39;s inconveniences to a believed individual can help the singular feel more fit for confronting what is going on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habilidades Sociales - Dobla tu Confianza y Autoestima</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/habilidades-sociales-dobla-tu-confianza-y-autoestima/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 17:02:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/habilidades-sociales-dobla-tu-confianza-y-autoestima/</guid>
      <description>Más de 23,000 estudiantes de 153 países inscritos en Nuestros Cursos
Curso Mejor Valorado en Udemy sobre Habilidades Sociales Apéndice con Hábitos Diarios.
============================================================
¿Te gustaría Saber...
Cómo Obtener la mejor versión social de tí mismo?
Cómo Comenzar interacciones de una forma natural?
Cómo Cómo desarrollar y potenciar tus habilidades sociales?
Cómo Aumentar tu confianza y autoestima?
Cómo Usar tu lenguaje corporal para ser más atractivo?
Cómo Pensar desde la abundancia y destruir el miedo al rechazo?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acing Time Management &amp; Productivity: Your ultimate Program</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/acing-time-management-productivity-your-ultimate-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/acing-time-management-productivity-your-ultimate-program/</guid>
      <description>WHY THIS COURSE on Productivity and Time Management?
Are you here because you feel you are always behind with your work and that makes you feel stressed? Well congratulations for wanting to do something about it, as opposed to waiting for things to change.
This course will allow you to not only get back on top of your To-do list, but also will ensure you never get overwhelmed by your workload, which is really the main goal: You managing your to-do list and not Your list managing you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Willpower Course - Build Self Control &amp; Good Habits</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-willpower-course-build-self-control-good-habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-willpower-course-build-self-control-good-habits/</guid>
      <description>Complete Willpower Course - Build Self Control &amp;amp; Good Habits
Build the Strong Willpower Habit - Improve Self Control - Self Discipline - Weight Loss - Build Strong New Habits
You can gain power over your own life. You can build the willpower muscle that allows you to live life on your own terms. Imagine if you had the willpower you need to maintain the healthy diet you deserve, to exercise properly, and stay focused on your professional and personal life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Seekers Guide to Resume Writing and Interview Skills</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/job-seekers-guide-to-resume-writing-and-interview-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/job-seekers-guide-to-resume-writing-and-interview-skills/</guid>
      <description>Are you entering the job market for the first time or looking for a complete change in career?
Did you previously enroll in courses that promise it will help you land your dream job but then you figure out it is just a basic information that actually everybody know about it? Don&#39;t worry you have come to the right place
This course is based only on practical strategies and real-life experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post pandemic love. The undoing effect</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/post-pandemic-love.-the-undoing-effect/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/post-pandemic-love.-the-undoing-effect/</guid>
      <description>The current pandemic has made an impact not only on physical well-being and mortality,, but also on our mental health. Recent studies have shown increases in the prevalence of depression and anxiety as well as increases in post-traumatic stress disorder and substance abuse worldwide.
Many people all over the globe have already experienced different kind of challenges like loss of closed ones, loss of job, loss of business, financial problems, relationship problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Accelerated Inner Peace Formula</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-accelerated-inner-peace-formula/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-accelerated-inner-peace-formula/</guid>
      <description>Wouldn’t it be amazing to know how to work with your own energy, to have the tools to heal your own pain, and finally experience that sweet Inner Peace?
In this course, I’ll show you the 4-step process for Inner Peace Making.
If you’re tired of going around in circles with your own healing,
And you’re struggling to understand &amp;amp; dissolve your patterns and your blocks
Yet you feel this deep calling to open, heal and release these blocks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Telecommuting Course - Remote Work - Work Life</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-telecommuting-course-remote-work-work-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-telecommuting-course-remote-work-work-life/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Telecommuting Course - Remote Work - Work Life
Telecommuting - Remote Working - Tools for Working from Home - Better Organization for Work Live Balance &amp;amp; Productivity
Telecommuting and remote working from home can be a great way to live a professional life if you plan accordingly and learn this new way of doing business.
The recent public health crisis has forced millions of executives around the globe out of their offices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Writing: How to become a Travel Writer</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/travel-writing-how-to-become-a-travel-writer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/travel-writing-how-to-become-a-travel-writer/</guid>
      <description>This course will take you from beginner writer to a career as a travel writer or digital nomad. There are many assignments and quizzes to help you to solidify your knowledge. I have been a travel writer for over 30 years now and I have interviewed other travel writers for this class. Learn from the pros and change your life to a life of adventure for money! There are no requirements to taking this course, just a willingness to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to SOAR into your Confidence for Busy Moms in Transition</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-soar-into-your-confidence-for-busy-moms-in-transition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-soar-into-your-confidence-for-busy-moms-in-transition/</guid>
      <description>Having struggled with my confidence, self-worth, identity, and desire to have my own money, I know exactly how it feels to feel powerless. I mean I remember just feeling completely lost with the thoughts that I was only ever going to be identified as mum.
I wanted to find Ella back again, I knew she was there somewhere and she wanted more for herself, she wanted to be able to take herself out again with her own money, wanted to be confident enough to demand her value in the corporate world once again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical Anger Management: Manage the Anger in You &amp; Others</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/practical-anger-management-manage-the-anger-in-you-others/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 21:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/practical-anger-management-manage-the-anger-in-you-others/</guid>
      <description>Are you suffering from anger issues? Or know someone who is, and need to deal with it?
The ZandaX Anger Management course is written for anyone for whom anger plays a significant part in their life, whether in themselves or others.
If you, a friend or loved one suffers from anger issues, the situation needs to be resolved, and we show you how.
Just think how much your life will improve when you&#39;re able to deal with the anger that&#39;s affecting you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ClickBank Affiliate Masterclass : Comprehensive Training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/clickbank-affiliate-masterclass-comprehensive-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 17:17:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/clickbank-affiliate-masterclass-comprehensive-training/</guid>
      <description>ClickBank Affiliate Masterclass : Comprehensive Training
5 courses in 1 - Clickbank, Affiliate Landing Pages, Winning Mindset, Wealth Creation and Financial Attraction
Listen up we together decided to team up creating one of the best and most amazing hands on training on Udemy period and I want you to be part of this. This exclusive class gives is actually 5 classes in total that been combined to make you the money making machine you always dreamed of becoming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 10 Laws for Personal Success - The Complete Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-10-laws-for-personal-success-the-complete-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 16:26:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-10-laws-for-personal-success-the-complete-course/</guid>
      <description>The 10 Laws for Personal Success - The Complete Course
Personal success...it can be yours. You can achieve your goals in life, have a great career, build strong relationships, and live your life‘s purpose. Nobody was born with personal success; it is a function of applying skills in a systematic way throughout life.
TJ Walker is one of the top personal development trainers in the world and coaches people on the elements of personal success, personal development, and personal transformation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>تدريب الأزواج ( كيف تنقذ حياتك الزوجية ؟</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%AA%D8%AF%D8%B1%D9%8A%D8%A8-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A3%D8%B2%D9%88%D8%A7%D8%AC-%D9%83%D9%8A%D9%81-%D8%AA%D9%86%D9%82%D8%B0-%D8%AD%D9%8A%D8%A7%D8%AA%D9%83-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B2%D9%88%D8%AC%D9%8A%D8%A9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 16:26:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%AA%D8%AF%D8%B1%D9%8A%D8%A8-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A3%D8%B2%D9%88%D8%A7%D8%AC-%D9%83%D9%8A%D9%81-%D8%AA%D9%86%D9%82%D8%B0-%D8%AD%D9%8A%D8%A7%D8%AA%D9%83-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B2%D9%88%D8%AC%D9%8A%D8%A9/</guid>
      <description>كيفية تحديد المشكلات التي تواجهك مع شريك الحياة بدقة
تغيير المفاهيم الخاطئة الشائعة عن العلاقات الزوجية
الاعتراف بالصفات السيئة وتحجيمها
اصلاح جوهر الذات لاصلاح جوهر العلاقة وامتلاك قيم ترتقي بعلاقتك بشريك الحياة
وصفة النجاح في العلاقة بشريك الحياة
إعادة الاتصال بشريك الحياة بفعالية
تمرينات عملية في أربعة عشر يوما من الحب بإخلاص
الاسئلة الشائعة الخاصة بالعلاقة الحميمة
إدارة العلاقة Ratings: 4.38/5
Enrollments: 2407
Coupon Code: BBDE3D517C9796DD5ACF
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurship &amp; Personality</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/entrepreneurship-personality/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 20:24:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/entrepreneurship-personality/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to become a self-confident inspired entrepreneur?
Learn what drives and motivates entrepreneurs to succeed.
Discover if it is right to follow a passion, and when it becomes an obsession.
Gain a deeper insight into the topic of intuition, and why entrepreneurs do need it.
Analyze intuition in decision-making, and categorize it as a part of tacit knowledge. Gain ideas on how to tap into your intuition.
It is important to be true to yourself and practice authentic connections in spite of the fear of judgment and rejection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are you privacy savvy? A Beginner&#39;s Guide to Privacy Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/are-you-privacy-savvy-a-beginners-guide-to-privacy-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 22:09:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/are-you-privacy-savvy-a-beginners-guide-to-privacy-basics/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that Facebook Messenger, Skype, WhatsApp, Zoom, or other applications you use to connect with your family, friends, and colleagues record what you are chatting, talking and capture the data you present? They don’t share your private data; at least, they try to protect your data from hackers. However, these organizations use your data for analytics, which age group using which applications, topics in your conversations, etc.
The Privacy Act defines personal information as any recorded information about an identifiable individual, including race, national or ethnic origin, color, religion, age or marital status.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dare to Lead: How to Become a Next Generation Leader</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/dare-to-lead-how-to-become-a-next-generation-leader/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 20:10:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/dare-to-lead-how-to-become-a-next-generation-leader/</guid>
      <description>**Course Updated - April 2022**
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; COURSE REGULARLY UPDATED: NEW TIPS, MORE LESSONS &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; CERTIFIED COACH, SPEAKER AND TRAINER &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; OVER 180,000 STUDENTS IN TOTAL &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
Let me ask you a question… How would you like to be able to learn to lead? If the answer is YES, then listen real close to what I say. In this course, I have explained the entire process that can create a fantastic leader who is loved and respected by others when integrated into your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Political Savvy: Maximizing Your IMPACT in the Organization</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/political-savvy-maximizing-your-impact-in-the-organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 20:10:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/political-savvy-maximizing-your-impact-in-the-organization/</guid>
      <description>Make the most of your opportunity to make a meaningful contribution where you work - and show your talent and leadership ability in the process!
This course is focused on a &#34;must-have&#34; skill for all those wishing to succeed in the organizational setting – the ability to influence effectively. The intent is to empower you to move your creative and productive ideas forward in your organization, and in doing so, enhance your stature and career potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Self-Discipline Course - Control Your Own Life</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-self-discipline-course-control-your-own-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 20:10:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-self-discipline-course-control-your-own-life/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Self-Discipline Course - Control Your Own Life
You can gain greater self-discipline.
Imagine going through life daily on your terms. You are in control. Life doesn’t simply happen to you, you have the self-discipline to create the life as you have always envisioned it.
Personal development expert TJ Walker will teach you his revolutionary Selfie Speak Programming techniques for helping you master complete self discipline in the easiest and most time efficient manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Creativity Course: Unleash Your Innovation Now!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-creativity-course-unleash-your-innovation-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:16:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-creativity-course-unleash-your-innovation-now/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Creativity Course: Unleash Your Innovation Now!
Turn Your Creative Energies On Daily. You Are the Source of Innovation, Creative Writing and New Ideas
Creativity is innate to all human beings. You can quickly build, refine, improve and strengthen your creativity and innovation muscles. Creativity is not something allocated to only a few of life&#39;s lottery winners. Instead, it is a habit that can be built by anyone--if they know the process and are willing to do a little work each day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Resume and CV Writing Course: Get the Ideal Job</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-resume-and-cv-writing-course-get-the-ideal-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 16:16:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-resume-and-cv-writing-course-get-the-ideal-job/</guid>
      <description>Kathryn Troutman, Resume Expert - Instructor - The Complete Resume and CV Writing Course: Get the ideal Job
TJ Walker, Presentation Coach; Interview Preparation Instructor
Learn the Art and Science of Resume and CV Writing - Job Search Skills, LinkedIn and Interview Skills
Part 1 - CV and Resume Writing - Kathryn gives real examples of career changers - Before &amp;amp; AFter, Keywords and how to match
Part 2 - COVID-19 JObs - Kathryn interprets the jobs; analyzes the qualifications; give insight about the position</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Organization Masterclass - Organize - Decluttering</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-organization-masterclass-organize-decluttering/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:15:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-organization-masterclass-organize-decluttering/</guid>
      <description>Complete Organization Masterclass - Organize - Decluttering
Organize for a Peak Performance Life - Improve Organization Skills Time Management Personal Productivity Decluttering
You can live a well organized life! Imagine if every aspect of your home, your office, your health, and your life were well organized?
You can make this happen. Organization can become part of your self identity.
Self development expert TJ Walker is a master at developing organization habits and individuals and organizations around the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Brain Training Course - Neuroplasticity -</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-brain-training-course-neuroplasticity-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:15:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-brain-training-course-neuroplasticity-/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Brain Training Course - Neuroplasticity -Brain Training for the Modern Smart Phone Era! You Can Train Your Brain to Think More Clearly and Creatively
Brain training is essential if you want do you live up to your full potential as a human being. Your brain is your most important organ, therefore it is essential that you train it for peak performance.
Like it or not, every single day your brain is being trained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Happiness Course: Become Happier Now!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-happiness-course-become-happier-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:15:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-happiness-course-become-happier-now/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Happiness Course: Become Happier Now!Happiness Can Be Yours! Learn Happiness Habits to Build Your Personal Success and Enhance Personal Development Today
Your happiness can be chosen. You only get one life, why not make the most of it and learn how to be happy on a daily basis?
Negative habits practiced on a daily basis create but unhappy, unfulfilled life. The positive habits practiced on a daily basis will create a happy life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Skills - Increase Your Earning Potential</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/job-skills-increase-your-earning-potential/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 19:20:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/job-skills-increase-your-earning-potential/</guid>
      <description>Most of us spend many years acquiring academic qualifications in the quest of finding rewarding career that allows us to lead a comfortable life. Surely, it is important to have academic qualifications, but if you want to have a rewarding career, it must be backed by appropriate job skills and competencies. The world of employment has always been very competitive and globalization with changes in our ways of working are making it even more complex.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence (AI) Tools For Job Seekers (2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-ai-tools-for-job-seekers-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-ai-tools-for-job-seekers-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience the technology covering &#34;Artificial Intelligence (AI) Tools For Job Seekers&#34;.
Do you want to teach your students how they can create a resume super-fast to beat the competition? Or, are you actually looking to learn the practical concepts of the entire process of job-seeking all by yourself? You have come to the right place.
We must understand that people cannot live without progressive technologies, because they have become an integral part of our daily lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Use LazyApply To Automate Your Job Search?</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-use-lazyapply-to-automate-your-job-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-use-lazyapply-to-automate-your-job-search/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the world-changing course that contains a new-age experience of &#34;How To Use LazyApply To Automate Your Job Search?&#34;. Let&#39;s get this straight to the point now.
This is a world of competition. Consider how much time you spend applying for employment only to receive a rejection letter a week or a month later. You must be already aware of the problems and challenges that every job applicant like you face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Nonverbal Communication Course - Body Language</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-nonverbal-communication-course-body-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-nonverbal-communication-course-body-language/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Nonverbal Communication Course - Body Language
Nonverbal Communication for Business, Public Speaking and Life - Display Confidence and High Self Esteem
Nonverbal communication can be the most memorable and most powerful way of communicating with other human beings. Whether you are meeting one-on-one with a friend, sitting in a business meeting, or giving a presentation, you need to know ho to use nonverbal communication to your benefit.
Here is what Udemy students say about this course:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Masterclass: How to get free Subscribers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-masterclass-how-to-get-free-subscribers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-masterclass-how-to-get-free-subscribers/</guid>
      <description>Get your own step-by-step, day-by-day plan of how to grow your YouTube channel fast. See what I did day by day to get fast growth. I&#39;ll share my analytics, actually see how a YouTube creator grows their channel fast!
So many YouTube course creators only have channels about growing YouTube channels... so all they know is how to grow a channel about making YouTube. So, if you want to make a successful vlog or other YouTube channel niche, the information from these channel creators isn&#39;t coming from their own real-world learnings!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Growth Mindset Course - The Mindset for Success</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-growth-mindset-course-the-mindset-for-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-growth-mindset-course-the-mindset-for-success/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Growth Mindset Course - The Mindset for Success
Build a Growth Mindset for Your Organization and Yourself - Leadership for Life Success - Learn Habits to be Successful
The happiest, most fulfilled, and most successful people in the world all have one thing in common: a growth mindset.
A growth mindset, in contrast with a fixed mindset, is essential for any individual who wants to have a meaningful life filled with positive change and growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contented Career Mom</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/contented-career-mom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 18:10:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/contented-career-mom/</guid>
      <description>Are you a mother on maternity leave who is feeling anxious about returning to work - wishing you could be focused on enjoying this time with your baby?
Wouldn’t it be amazing to breeze through your final weeks of maternity leave, relaxing and enjoying time with your baby, whilst confident that you already have a practical plan in place to prepare everything for your successful return to work?
I’ll take the guesswork out of how to tackle the transition, by teaching you my proven 30-day return to work method: leaving you feeling calmer, more confident and in control - as well as freeing up plenty of time for you to enjoy your final weeks of maternity leave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified Diploma Course In Ancestral Healing Level-1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-diploma-course-in-ancestral-healing-level-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-diploma-course-in-ancestral-healing-level-1/</guid>
      <description>Namaskar,
Welcome To Vidya Retreat.
This is our exclusive certified course, which is completely designed by famous Author Dr. Himani. She owns the copyright of this course. Kindly write us in inbox only to get a personal certificate, not in Q &amp;amp; A section. Every 30 days we issue all certificates. Ancestral healing is the procedure of exposing and healing acquired wounds and traumas passed down by our ancestors. Anybody investigating their heritage will discover both positives and negatives that go through the bloodlines from one generation to the next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Chakra Healing and Balancing - Certificate Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-chakra-healing-and-balancing-certificate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-chakra-healing-and-balancing-certificate-course/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Guide to Diagnosing, Balancing &amp;amp; Aligning Your Chakras
Is This Course for You?
It’s for you, if you feel stuck and overwhelmed with everyday challenges of the modern world – this course will give you a whole new (ancient) perspective.
It’s for you, if you notice recurring patterns in your relationships, work and health that you just don’t know how to break – this course will shed light on the truth behind those negative cycles so you can take the first step towards healing them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOP G1 driver’s license Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/top-g1-drivers-license-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/top-g1-drivers-license-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>G1 Test Practice: Free ON “Drive Test” G1 Practice Test 2021
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily
Our G1 Practice Test with multiple choice questions, is intended to help you prepare for the Ontario G1 practice test and learners driver’s test that is required before you can get your Canadian driver’s license.
This free practice Written G1 driving test is a lesson that is essential for getting your Ontario driver’s license at your local licensing office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uygulamanın Gücü ile başarıya götüren ufak adımlar</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/uygulaman%C4%B1n-g%C3%BCc%C3%BC-ile-ba%C5%9Far%C4%B1ya-g%C3%B6t%C3%BCren-ufak-ad%C4%B1mlar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/uygulaman%C4%B1n-g%C3%BCc%C3%BC-ile-ba%C5%9Far%C4%B1ya-g%C3%B6t%C3%BCren-ufak-ad%C4%B1mlar/</guid>
      <description>Kişisel gelişim ile ilgili onlarca makale, kitap ve video içerikler bulunuyor. Ama başkalarının kişisel gelişimlerine yardımcı olacak adımları atmalarını sağlayacak kaynaklar son derece sınırlı.
Bu eğitimle ilgili yapmak istediğim şey insanların bir eğitim yada alışkanlık gibi sebeplerle ilgili bir konuda aksiyon almak istemesiyle o aksiyonun tamamlanma süresi arasında maruz kaldığı koşulları iyileştirmektir.
Eğitim içeriğinde yer alan konular.
Hazırlık
Nasıl Başlamalı
Ortaya çıkarma
Somutlaştırma
Elindekilerle uygula
Kararlılık
Başlamak kolaydır.
Kararlılık
Sürdürülebilir olmak</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career Coaching: TOP 5 Secrets of Effcient Sessions</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/career-coaching-top-5-secrets-of-effcient-sessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/career-coaching-top-5-secrets-of-effcient-sessions/</guid>
      <description>Hello, everyone! Thanks for paying attention to this lection about Career Coaching!
Our world today is one that celebrates being busy. Being busy is something that we strive for, despite the feeling of overwhelm - the feeling of having no time like you’re drowning. Surely, being busy is a sign of success?
Well, not necessarily. You can be busy, but be in a job that you hate. One that makes you dread each morning, or you’re sat at your desk each day, bored and unfulfilled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find your Unique Memory Personality – Intro to Online Test</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/find-your-unique-memory-personality-intro-to-online-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 21:29:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/find-your-unique-memory-personality-intro-to-online-test/</guid>
      <description>Do you know your Unique Memory Personality?
Do you know how you personally learn and remember the easiest and fastest way?
Do you know which of our 12 Secret Memory Languages works best for you?
This course is for you if you are busy and want a fast introduction to your Memory Personality. If you want the advanced Master Class search on Udemy &#34;Next-Generation Memory, Learning &amp;amp; Communication Improvement&#34;.
Hi, I’m Dan Agervig Hansen; Educational &amp;amp; Corporate trainer and coach for 25 years, 3x Best-Selling Author, and creator of the Memory Personality Typology and the 12 Secret Languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heal your broken heart with EFT</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/heal-your-broken-heart-with-eft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/heal-your-broken-heart-with-eft/</guid>
      <description>If you have had a relationship breakdown, Ended or a divorce this experience will teach you how to let go the trapped emotions that feel like physical pain we call heartache
To do this I will be teaching you a technique called EFT Emotional Freedom Technique, now this technique can look funny or even stupid to some people but it does work and I have been using it one to one with clients for many years with great success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morning and Evening Routines for Your ADHD Child</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/morning-and-evening-routines-for-your-adhd-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/morning-and-evening-routines-for-your-adhd-child/</guid>
      <description>WHAT WILL YOU LEARN IN THIS COURSE?
Is the morning rush choking you?
Are you fed up with being up till midnight with your child because they won’t go to bed?
Are you beyond exhausted?
As a mother of an ADHD child, you know how difficult the morning and evening rush can be. You know that traditional parenting methods don&#39;t work at best, and backfire at worst. You need specialist ADHD tools to support your ADHD child to unlock their potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Citizenship Test Your Immigration Dream</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/canadian-citizenship-test-your-immigration-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 21:10:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/canadian-citizenship-test-your-immigration-dream/</guid>
      <description>Canadian Citizenship Test Your Immigration Dream
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily
Canadian-Citizenship Practice Test Canadian Symbols Modern Canada Canada’s Economy Justice System and History The Canadian Citizenship Test is a test, administered by the Department of Immigration, Refugees and Citizenship Canada, that is required for all applicants for Canadian citizenship who are aged between 14 and 64 and who meet the basic requirements for citizenship.
The exam is commonly written, however in a few cases it might be oral and take vicinity inside the form of an interview with a citizenship officer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACCREDITED How to Structure the First 4 ADHD Coach Sessions</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/accredited-how-to-structure-the-first-4-adhd-coach-sessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 16:17:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/accredited-how-to-structure-the-first-4-adhd-coach-sessions/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to &#34;ACCREDITED How to Structure the First 4 ADHD Coach Sessions.&#34; This course is accredited by the International Association of Therapists, (IAOTH).
In this IAOTH UK accredited certification course, you will learn how to retain Your ADHD clients long-term and become the expert in the ADHD coaching field. In this course you will be empowered with clear ADHD coaching tools that sets you apart as the expert in the ADHD coaching field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neuroplasticity And CBT Complete Certification Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/neuroplasticity-and-cbt-complete-certification-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 22:17:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/neuroplasticity-and-cbt-complete-certification-course/</guid>
      <description>CBT is an intensive, short-term, problem-oriented approach. It was designed to be quick, practical and goal-oriented and to provide people with long-term skills to keep them healthy. The focus of cbt is on the problems that come up in a person’s day-to-day life. cbt helps people to look at how they interpret and evaluate what is happening around them and the effects these perceptions have on their emotional experience.
Childhood experiences and events, while not the focus of cbt, may also be reviewed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neuroplasticity Ultimate Certification Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/neuroplasticity-ultimate-certification-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 22:17:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/neuroplasticity-ultimate-certification-course/</guid>
      <description>Neuroplasticity can be defined as brain’s ability to change, remodel and reorganize for purpose of better ability to adapt to new situations. Despite the fact that the concept of neuroplasticity is quite new, it is one of the most important discoveries in neuroscience. The fact is that neural networks are not fixed, but occurring and disappearing dynamically throughout our whole life, depending on experiences. While we repeatedly practice one activity such as a sequence of movements or a mathematical problem, neuronal circuits are being formed, leading to better ability to perform the practiced task with less waste of energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Memory Athlete&#39;s Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-memory-athletes-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 23:34:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-memory-athletes-guide/</guid>
      <description>This course will take you through the wonderful world of memory improvement, introducing you to the challenges that memory athletes face, the methods they use, what their memory workouts look like, and how you can become a practitioner of the memory sport yourself.
It is a practical and useful guide for anyone who wants to explore the world of this sport and learn the advanced techniques used by memory athletes to achieve amazing performance with their minds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>German Productivity Hacks</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/german-productivity-hacks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 11:27:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/german-productivity-hacks/</guid>
      <description>Germans are supposed to be highly productive and efficient but why is that? It&#39;s a combination of typical productivity hacks &amp;amp; habits which are hard wired into our culture and a bunch of strange habits which are sometimes counterproductive. But even those habits help us to succeed at the end of the day.
This course will both educate and entertain you: Learn how Germans work and why they are productive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Freelancing : To Grow Quickly at Marketplace&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-freelancing-to-grow-quickly-at-marketplaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 13:12:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-freelancing-to-grow-quickly-at-marketplaces/</guid>
      <description>This course is meant to teach the tips and tricks of freelancing in the simplest and effective way. The do`s and don`ts are discussed, about which a freelancer must be aware of. The introduction of different types of freelance marketplaces is given in this course. Web portals like Freelancer, Upwork, Fiverr, Fivesquid, and 99 Design are introduced and discussed in detail so that a trainee could effectively make money by using these portals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Course Creation: How to Create Your Own Online Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/online-course-creation-how-to-create-your-own-online-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 21:27:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/online-course-creation-how-to-create-your-own-online-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to create your very own online course(s) but didn&#39;t know where to start? Ever wondered how to publish your own online courses on online learning websites like Udemy and more? Have you ever wanted to learn how to do so in a simple and direct manner without breaking the bank? Well now you can, with my Online Course Creation: How to Create Your Own Online Course course!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management 4 Tweens &amp; Teens</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-4-tweens-teens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 12:24:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-4-tweens-teens/</guid>
      <description>In this class students will learn time management skills that will aid them to be much more productive and to minimize stress (if not eliminate it) around schoolwork, and chores. They will leave this course having learned how to manage their time effectively, no longer entertaining distractions, cutting out multitasking and procrastination. Students will learn how to manage their planners, to be organized, how to prioritize, to be strategic and consistent, and to re-frame their perspective regarding chores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Manifestation - 12 Universal Laws</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-manifestation-12-universal-laws/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 12:41:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-manifestation-12-universal-laws/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling to manifest your goals? Are you unclear about how the law of attraction works? Do you feel like you&#39;re doing everything right but still not getting the results you want? What if I told you that you are manifesting, but not what you want?
That&#39;s because you may be unaware of the 12 universal laws that govern the universe. These laws operate in tandem with the law of attraction and affect your ability to manifest certain desires.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness para desarrollar la inteligencia emocional</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mindfulness-para-desarrollar-la-inteligencia-emocional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 18:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mindfulness-para-desarrollar-la-inteligencia-emocional/</guid>
      <description>Te enseño herramientas efectivas y sencillas de aplicar en tu rutina diaria, invirtiendo sólo entre 5 a 15 minutos al día tus emociones no serán más un obstáculo en la consecución de tus metas, tampoco volverás a sentir la culpa o vergüenza de tus impulsos y reacciones emocionales. Tu también puedes gozar de relaciones empáticas, satisfactorias y sin tantas fricciones. Poder solucionar de manera asertiva y consciente las diferencias con tus seres queridos, colegas, clientes y colaboradores es posible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bible: 7 Lessons From The Book Of Jude Plus The Why..</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bible-7-lessons-from-the-book-of-jude-plus-the-why../</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 15:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bible-7-lessons-from-the-book-of-jude-plus-the-why../</guid>
      <description>The Book of Jude is one of the shortest books of the New Testament. Written by the brother of our Lord Jesus and the brother of James; the book appears just before the book of Revelation in our bibles. Its size must not be mistaken for its potency - small in size yet packs a very big punch. Although the book mirrors much of the content in 2 Peter it provides many unique features of its own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life Coach: The Complete Life Coach Certification Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/life-coach-the-complete-life-coach-certification-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 13:29:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/life-coach-the-complete-life-coach-certification-course/</guid>
      <description>A life coach helps others define how they want to improve themselves, helps them develop a plan to do so and holds them accountable to implement the plan. Their role is actually quite simple. They help us answer three questions: What do I want to change about myself, How do I change, How do I commit to changing, Whether it’s being a better lawyer, a leader or manager or whether it’s more personal, such as getting in shape, losing weight, being a better parent, change starts with identifying what you want to change about yourself, figuring out how to get from here to there and making that change a reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organize your online business for busy entrepreneurs</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/organize-your-online-business-for-busy-entrepreneurs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2022 13:29:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/organize-your-online-business-for-busy-entrepreneurs/</guid>
      <description>Still working like a charm in 2022!
Join over 70,000 students from 190+ countries worldwide taking my courses today!
no fluff, no filler content, just straight to the point course that you can start and actually finish in 1 day!
A hard drive full of unfinished projects, a head that&#39;s spinning from too many things you need to get done, and everything around you seems like a huge mess?
It is time to get organized the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Productivity Powers Unleashed (2021 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/productivity-powers-unleashed-2021-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/productivity-powers-unleashed-2021-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the thirteenth course in Term 3 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Paul J. Meyer once said that &#34;Productivity is never an accident. It is always the result of a commitment to excellence, intelligent planning, and focused effort&#34;. The reality is it can be hard to stay productive at work or at home. We know the benefits of productivity. Being productive and efficient will help your company improve and maximize the use of human capital resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership Strategies Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/leadership-strategies-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 12:27:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/leadership-strategies-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>Everyone has had the experience of working for a not-so-great boss.
While it’s common for people to be promoted into management when they excel in non-leadership positions, the truth is that a lot of the people who get those promotions don’t have leadership skills they need to effectively manage their team
However, those skills can be easily learn.
In this course, you will discover five essential leadership skills you need to successfully manage a team, and how to set yourself up for long-term success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking For Startups! - Cure Stage Fright &amp; Anxiety</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-for-startups-cure-stage-fright-anxiety/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 12:27:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-for-startups-cure-stage-fright-anxiety/</guid>
      <description>&#34;I got on stage to speak for 45 minutes but after 15 minutes I was done. I could hardly remember exactly what I said. All I knew was that after those few minutes I was still shaking and trembling. Eyes were on me not knowing whether to clap or not. All I wanted was for the nightmare to be over! It did.&#34;
Fast forward to today. I speak to audiences around the world in person and via video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified Authentic Living Coach - Specialist training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-authentic-living-coach-specialist-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 16:29:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-authentic-living-coach-specialist-training/</guid>
      <description>Isn&#39;t it just so easy to follow the crowd? It seems it takes guts sometimes to be yourself.. This course is for the people that want to stand out and be themselves regardless of what the &#39;norm&#39; is. Your power is in your uniqueness and being authentic is a part of that. If you cant be true to yourself who can you be true to right? This course shows you how to pull your true self back to the forefront of your mind and helps you coaches to do the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habitually Better: Building habits to be your best self!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/habitually-better-building-habits-to-be-your-best-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 16:29:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/habitually-better-building-habits-to-be-your-best-self/</guid>
      <description>Join the journey to become habitually better!
Pursuing long term goals does not have to be a long shot. It does not have to take an inordinate amount of will power either.
Join the journey to craft a focussed, effortless and satisfying path towards your future.
I have struggled with habit formation, and I empathize with you. Having seen how that powerful habits are and how some people face challenges in utilizing them, I believe that it should be made reachable to everyone and I would like to share this course as a humble guidance to those who are going through a similar journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Corinthians: 16 Life Changing Lessons</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/1-corinthians-16-life-changing-lessons/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 17:47:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/1-corinthians-16-life-changing-lessons/</guid>
      <description>How To Win: If there was a Book in the Bible that illustrates how a Christian should live in an overtly worldly setting, then 1 Corinthians speaks volumes and offers numerous tactics to help us navigate such terrain.
After starting the Church (Acts 18) the people continued many of their worldly practices alongside their Christian walk. There was division, selfishness, promiscuity, immorality on one side, and extreme living - abstinence from marriage, food, etc on the other side of the spectrum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curso Runas Wicca – Runas de las Brujas</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-runas-wicca-runas-de-las-brujas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 17:47:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-runas-wicca-runas-de-las-brujas/</guid>
      <description>Las Runas Wicca o Runas de la Bruja son un conjunto de símbolos mágicos utilizados para la adivinación, las lecturas evolutivas y también utilizadas como oráculos. A estas runas también se las conoce como Runas o Piedras Gitanas o incluso como Runas Modernas. Son bien diferentes de las runas nórdicas o runas vikingas, y puede considerarse que su sistema simbólico o de lectura es un tanto más simple, y, por ende, más fácil de aprender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Day Journaling Challenge</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/7-day-journaling-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 17:15:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/7-day-journaling-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Journaling is a powerful mindfulness tool that helps us self-reflect and catch various streams of thoughts and emotions. When we write things down, we literally transfer our thoughts out of our minds on paper. Our opinions are shaped, we untangle messy strings of ideas in our mind and create a logical flow of things with each sentence. As a result, we gain clarity on what we think and how we really feel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Productivity Plan &amp; Execute Effectively, Getting things done</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/productivity-plan-execute-effectively-getting-things-done/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 16:53:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/productivity-plan-execute-effectively-getting-things-done/</guid>
      <description>Research shows that a large number of professionals fail to execute their action plan successfully. The problem often isn’t with planning but with executing the planning. It is very important to take a well-structured approach to implement and execute what is planned.
The Art of Being Productive: Planning &amp;amp; Effective Execution is an online course, that will help professionals to overcome their most challenging execution obstacles on a working day and execute their tasks effectively to achieve better results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide to understanding and assessing personality</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/guide-to-understanding-and-assessing-personality/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 19:59:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/guide-to-understanding-and-assessing-personality/</guid>
      <description>Gain a deeper understanding about personality, approaches and psychological assessment that will be useful in your everyday life to interact effectively with people who are around and implement your life, career goals as well as in career counseling.
Explore the puzzle of personality Recognize how unique you are.
Spark your inspiration by identifying your strengths and talents.
Learn why personality matters.
Boost your brain plasticity by learning theories. Create a better understanding of personality assessment evolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA RECETTE pour réussir vos entretiens d&#39;embauche (2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/la-recette-pour-r%C3%A9ussir-vos-entretiens-dembauche-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 19:59:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/la-recette-pour-r%C3%A9ussir-vos-entretiens-dembauche-2022/</guid>
      <description>Vous en avez assez de ne jamais être rappelé après un entretien d’embauche ? Cela vous frustre de passer beaucoup de temps à vous préparer pour au final être dépassé par d’autres candidats.
Vous avez l’impression de ne pas être assez convaincant face aux recruteurs et de perdre vos moyens lors d’un entretien d’embauche ? Cette formation est faite pour vous.
Pas besoin de visionner en boucle de longues vidéos sur internet qui restent très théoriques, pas besoin de lire des dizaines d’articles qui donnent tous les mêmes conseils que vous connaissez déjà.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Educa ed Allena la tua Voce</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/educa-ed-allena-la-tua-voce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 17:51:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/educa-ed-allena-la-tua-voce/</guid>
      <description>Hai problemi nel farti comprendere senza dover ripeterei volte la stessa cosa detta?
Ti senti insicuro dei tuoi mezzi di parola e voce? Parli col timore di non esser capito?
Quando comunichi hai problemi nel far comprendere pensieri ed emozioni?
Vorresti avere una migliore articolazione ?
Bene! Sei proprio nell&#39;aula virtuale giusta!
In questo corso troverai un approccio all&#39;utilizzo e allo sviluppo della voce del tuto differente da quello classico che muove le prime mosse da esercizi sulla vocalizzazione, sicuro fondamentali ma solo dopo aver acquisito piena conoscenza degli organi addetti alla fonazione.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heal from the Narcissist with Ho&#39;oponopono</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/heal-from-the-narcissist-with-hooponopono/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 17:51:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/heal-from-the-narcissist-with-hooponopono/</guid>
      <description>Hello and Welcome to my course:
&#34;Heal from The Narcissist with Ho&#39;oponopono&#34;
Learning The Ho&#39;oponopono Prayer/mantra will not only re-program negative subconscious triggers but will also re-wire the subconscious to before The Narcissist got hold of you.
The Narcissist secretly works with your &#34;Inner child&#34; and your &#34;Inner critic&#34; adding more cognitive damage to your development, leaving you stuck in illusion and confusion (for years)
Ho&#39;oponopono helps you rewire your subconscious programming to 0 (When you were born) before your belief system and subconscious were conditioned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Case Interview: Most Common Job Interview Questions - Answer</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/case-interview-most-common-job-interview-questions-answer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 22:42:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/case-interview-most-common-job-interview-questions-answer/</guid>
      <description>Case interviews are merely a glimpse into someone&#39;s life. We&#39;ll give you a challenge to tackle and evaluate your abilities to approach it, devise a strategy, incorporate feedback, and discover new ways of thinking. There is no correct response; we simply want to hear yours. This course will provide you with an understanding of what you need to know to ace the case interview, as well as a solid basis on which to build the remainder of your preparation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innovation &amp; Personality</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/innovation-personality/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 13:19:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/innovation-personality/</guid>
      <description>Learn more how to identify, evaluate and motivate innovative people to boost innovation in your organization.
Discover how to boost your own individual innovativeness.
Explore the innovator’s persona. It might be challenging to identify whether a person is an innovator or not. However, several personality traits are closely related to the innovative personality.
Innovative people usually express a strong desire for autonomy, are imaginative, curious, energetic, and confident. They are open to new experiences having flexible mindset and propensity to successfully generate ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Method Acting , Characterisation &amp; Monologue Mastery</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-method-acting-characterisation-monologue-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 13:19:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-method-acting-characterisation-monologue-mastery/</guid>
      <description>In this course you will learn top monologues from legendary male characters.Master the Acting Craft with the tools and Knowledge used by A-List Stars Method Acting Method Acting is the key to your mastery of the Acting Craft. With this course, you learn to become a memorable actor. Take full control of your acting career. Increase your confidence superpower with every audition. Become an authentic and masterful Method Actor who is truly versatile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Goal Setting: How to Create The Future You Want Today</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/smart-goal-setting-how-to-create-the-future-you-want-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 13:19:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/smart-goal-setting-how-to-create-the-future-you-want-today/</guid>
      <description>Great Course - The course contains lot of tools and techniques which will definitely drives towards setting of goal which is single most virtue for successful living. thanks... - Anusha (Student)
It leads you somewhere...Most people just act for the sake of it. That&#39;s wrong. If you don&#39;t know where you are going, you won&#39;t be able to walk that way. Once you know where you&#39;re going you can put all of the necessary effort needed into achieving that goal and THIS COURSE is your perfect companion to do so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management Success</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 13:19:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-success/</guid>
      <description>Like many people I struggled with Time Management and Productivity for many years. It was an immense area of frustration for me because I tried all the strategies which, worked for a while; then everything seemed to go back to how it was.
I desperately searched for a lasting change.
I found it about 12 months ago when I instituted new thinking patterns and actions into my everyday living. I can honestly say that right now, my productivity has increased and I feel in control of my time and activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Awesome Professional Brand through Impactful Emails</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/building-awesome-professional-brand-through-impactful-emails/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 15:56:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/building-awesome-professional-brand-through-impactful-emails/</guid>
      <description>Description
Emails: In a professional setting, email is the most significant communication channel. Improving your email writing is a great strategy to strengthen and improve your professional brand. Email writing is an important communication skill that most of us overlook. Emails can be a blessing in disguise, allowing you to send a short message to get your point across, or they can be a curse, causing both the sender and the receiver severe headaches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Interviewing Skills - Master Basic Interviewing Skills</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basic-interviewing-skills-master-basic-interviewing-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 19:14:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basic-interviewing-skills-master-basic-interviewing-skills/</guid>
      <description>Basic Interviewing Skills - Master Basic Interviewing Skills:Mastering the Interview - You Can Ace the Job Interview - Never Be Nervous Again - Get the Job
Nothing is more important in gaining new employment than the job interview. It is an opportunity to demonstrate your command of your field, a vision for the future, why your experience, education, and knowledge are ideal for the position you are going for.
You will also learn how to answer tricky interview questions as well as what questions you should post to the person who is interrogating you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Achieve Goals Using Less Willpower</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-achieve-goals-using-less-willpower/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 21:15:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-achieve-goals-using-less-willpower/</guid>
      <description>In this course, I will take you on a step-by-step journey to have more willpower and use it far more efficiently than ever before. So by the end of this course, you will know exactly how to tackle difficult goals AND goal achievement will become easier for the rest of your life.
You Will Shift Your Mindset, Goal Strategies, and Energy Levels to Achieve Any Goal.
You will:
Learn about leading scientific discoveries</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fit for Work</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fit-for-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 22:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fit-for-work/</guid>
      <description>Today, more than ever before, a focus on wellness and wellbeing is the new norm for the workplace. This is mainly due to the wave of employees currently entering the job market; the millennials and Gen Zs. With good reason, these employees are looking for work environments that cater to their flexible, yet wellness-focused lifestyles. Of course, at its core, the concept of workplace wellness is for everyone. From top-level management to C-level employees, every individual can gain from a better working environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go For Gold</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/go-for-gold/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 22:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/go-for-gold/</guid>
      <description>Managing employee performance facilitates the effective delivery of an organization’s goals and there is clear evidence that using performance management programs, systems or tools leads to improved business and organizational results. As a result, an effective performance management system or tool is essential for managing and evaluating staff, developing their competencies, improving organizational performance, and eventually achieve winning business outcomes.
Performance management is essentially a management tool that helps managers monitor and evaluate employees&#39; work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Method Acting, Characterisation &amp; Monologue Mastery</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-method-acting-characterisation-monologue-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 19:17:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-method-acting-characterisation-monologue-mastery/</guid>
      <description>&#34;By the strength of her personality and her ability to foretell the future, Joan convinced the King of France to grant her an armed force. In return, she led her small band of followers to take on and defeat the might of the English. Her conviction ensured her a place at the forefront of France&#39;s military history.&#34;
&#34;A study found that Every Year 63% of Actresses and 48% of Actors struggle with anxiety</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neuroplasticity: Teach Your Brain  To Work 3 Times Faster</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/neuroplasticity-teach-your-brain-to-work-3-times-faster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/neuroplasticity-teach-your-brain-to-work-3-times-faster/</guid>
      <description>If you have never imagined what living life on autopilot is, this may be because you are going all autopilot and not realizing it. Being conscious about our lives is the least we can do to actually live the better life.
So, what does neuroplasticity have to do with it? Pretty easy. Neuroplasticity helps our brain to get out of the ‘comfort zone’, of sorts. It helps us learn new things, thus expanding our brain broad and wide for everything new the world can offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Australian Citizenship Test  The Dream</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/australian-citizenship-test-the-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/australian-citizenship-test-the-dream/</guid>
      <description>Welcome ! get Ready for Certificate of Australian Citizenship CAC
Get ready to say &#34;I am Australian.&#34;
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily
2021 Australian Citizenship Test
Congratulations on choosing to become an Australian citizen. It takes courage, endeavor and commitmentto live in a new country and participate fully as a citizen. We value your contribution to our peaceful anddemocratic society. Australian citizenship is an important step in your migration story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EFT Your Dentist</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/eft-your-dentist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 12:27:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/eft-your-dentist/</guid>
      <description>It is estimated that nearly seventy five percent of adults in the United States experience some amount of fear with regarding going to the dentist. Of that percentage, about five to ten percent of those people have a strong enough fear to be considered sufferers of a dental phobia. If you are one of those people you are in the right place.
I am going to take you through a complementary and alternative method known as Emotional Freedom Techniques or EFT/tapping for short.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corso completo di sceneggiatura: scrivere un Film</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-completo-di-sceneggiatura-scrivere-un-film/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 12:00:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corso-completo-di-sceneggiatura-scrivere-un-film/</guid>
      <description>-Sei un appassionato di cinema e hai sempre sognato di poter un giorno scrivere per esso?
-Ti chiedi spesso cosa ci sia dietro lo scorrere delle immagini che vediamo al cinema?
-Ti è capitato mai di esclamare: &#34;HO UNA VOGLIA MATTA DI SCRIVERE UNA STORIA PER UN FILM...CREDO POTREI RIUSCIRCI....MA ... NON SAPREI DA DOVE INIZIARE!!&#34;...?
Beh...se le tue risposte alle mie domande sono affermative allora sei l&#39;alunno giusto nell&#39;aula virtuale giusta!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raviver Son Amour De Soi, Son Estime De Soi Et Ses Relations</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/raviver-son-amour-de-soi-son-estime-de-soi-et-ses-relations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 12:00:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/raviver-son-amour-de-soi-son-estime-de-soi-et-ses-relations/</guid>
      <description>Vous manquez d&#39;estime de vous et souhaitez savoir comment développer l&#39;amour de soi ? Vous aimeriez apprendre à vous aimer davantage pour pouvoir mieux réussir dans vos relations ?
Alors vous êtes au bon endroit ! Apprenez à redécouvrir votre amour-propre et votre estime de vous, travaillez sur vous-même, aimez-vous davantage et réussissez dans vos relations personnelles dans ce cours de développement personnel en ligne.
Accompagné de l&#39;expert en développement personnel Alain Wolf, vous apprendrez dans ce cours pour apprendre à s&#39;aimer en ligne à vivre avec confiance et à raviver la flamme dans une relation importante de votre vie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EFT Your PTSD and Trauma</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/eft-your-ptsd-and-trauma/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 20:41:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/eft-your-ptsd-and-trauma/</guid>
      <description>This course covers what trauma is and how to heal from it. If you have lived through a trauma or know someone who has this course is for you. Life is traumatic. Whether you have survived a fire, flood, hurricane, mass shooting, abuse, other natural disaster or watched the news or social media, been yelled at or watched a scary movie – you have been traumatized. Even if you don’t think you have experienced trauma, you have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art Therapy: Personal Development and Self Healing with Art</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/art-therapy-personal-development-and-self-healing-with-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 14:13:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/art-therapy-personal-development-and-self-healing-with-art/</guid>
      <description>Have you always been interested in Art Therapy and wanted to learn more about Self Reflection and Self Care through Art but you just didn&#39;t know where to start?
Maybe you have started creating Art at home but don&#39;t really feel supported during your creative process. Then my Complete Art Therapy Course with over 30 Art Therapy exercises for Beginners to Advanced is right for you!
Welcome to &#34; The Complete Art Therapy Certificate Course for Self Healing &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FATHERHOOD MASTERY - How to be a Good Dad</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fatherhood-mastery-how-to-be-a-good-dad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 06:56:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fatherhood-mastery-how-to-be-a-good-dad/</guid>
      <description>Do you feel you can be a better father for your children?
Are you about to become a first time Dad?
The most fulfilling part of live is bring our children into the world, watching and guiding them as they grow. But many times we are conflicted in how we teach them and what behaviors we show them as they grow.
Your instructors, Ricky Shetty, father of three beautiful children under 6, and Scott Paton, with two sons over 25, share their wisdom and knowledge of raising their children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Deal With Tough Times | Problem Solving Skills</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-deal-with-tough-times-problem-solving-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:36:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-deal-with-tough-times-problem-solving-skills/</guid>
      <description>This Course is related to problem solving skills which will guide you that how you can deal with Tough Times without getting into depression by helping you through personality growth and Personality Development , It will become a key factor in your success through comprehensive information on problem solving techniques, This course will guide you that how you can get out of Tough Times Or at-least how to manage the difficult situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intelligence quotient IQ Test Questions and Answers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/intelligence-quotient-iq-test-questions-and-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:36:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/intelligence-quotient-iq-test-questions-and-answers/</guid>
      <description>TEST YOUR INTELLGENCE Intelligence quotient IQ Test Questions and Answers
2021 Measure students, employees, humans, scientists and child&#39;s intelligence, PSYCHOMETRIC and Personality
An intelligence quotient (IQ) is a total score derived from a set of standardized tests or subtests designed to assess human intelligence. The abbreviation &#34;IQ&#34; was coined by the psychologist William Stern for the German term Intelligenzquotient, his term for a scoring method for intelligence tests at University of Breslau he advocated in a 1912 book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screenwriting: Writing a Selling Story with Your Bare Hands</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/screenwriting-writing-a-selling-story-with-your-bare-hands/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 17:04:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/screenwriting-writing-a-selling-story-with-your-bare-hands/</guid>
      <description>Oh, you want to be a screenwriter? Then come along to learn how to become one. This course focuses on conjuring your ideas, structuralizing your plot and turning it into a selling script.
This course will make your search for ideas less menacing, showing you how and where to find them. If inspiration doesn’t come willingly, you’ll learn how to call upon it and brainstorm ideas.
You will learn key elements of a movie script, as much as key steps for turning your idea into a story, and story into a plot for your script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Secrets for Improving Screenwriting Skills Summary</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/top-5-secrets-for-improving-screenwriting-skills-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 17:04:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/top-5-secrets-for-improving-screenwriting-skills-summary/</guid>
      <description>I’m sure you really want to write something to put on silver-screen and be proud that it’s your story hundreds of thousands of people are talking about. Well, you can either just go at it and encounter lots upon lots of difficulties and mistakes, or you can learn everything you need to know first and get at it like a pro. The choice is yours, but I would really advice the second option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time management and life management to increase productivity</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-and-life-management-to-increase-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-and-life-management-to-increase-productivity/</guid>
      <description>Every second is important and precious in our lives, and if we spend it in the wrong manner, we risk losing what strive and seek for. So, don&#39;t lose any second or minute on trivial things which might make regret later.
If you don&#39;t know yet the importance of time and how can you invest it in the correct way, you are in the right place. Because I designed this course to suit every person who is looking for ways to manage his time more effectively and feels that he is always busy and does not have free time, and it is suitable for every person who does not know how to balance his studies or work with his personal life and always feels that he does not have enough time to do everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aviation : Passenger service and handling</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aviation-passenger-service-and-handling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aviation-passenger-service-and-handling/</guid>
      <description>Ever wonder what it takes to work at one of the airlines industry&#39;s most visible airport position?
The first actual step on the path of getting a job is spending time on researching and gathering as much information as you can about this job to gain confidence which will enable you to overcome any nervous anxiety about the recruitment process. This course; Passenger Service and Handling is meant to help you make that first step of getting your dreams job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best GMAT Math Prep Course to Score 360&#43; in GMAT-2021- Oct</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/best-gmat-math-prep-course-to-score-360-in-gmat-2021-oct/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/best-gmat-math-prep-course-to-score-360-in-gmat-2021-oct/</guid>
      <description>Hi Students, here I am going to tell you how our course is different from others
1. Our Course is designed through White Board Animated Videos, So you can avoid seeing the face of Trainer, which improves your attention.
2. Your trainer is an expert with 15 years of Experience in teaching GMAT.
3. You will gets the best Techniques as per GMAT Exam Standards in 2021.
4. Here you see how to apply the learned techniques in Real GMAT Test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Best Course For Learning about Collaboration/ Teamwork</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-best-course-for-learning-about-collaboration/-teamwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-best-course-for-learning-about-collaboration/-teamwork/</guid>
      <description>Our course would be recommended as one of the best to learn about teamwork. Our course help students to learn the best ways of how to incorporate teamwork in themselves and in their regular behavior towards others.
The good qualities nurtured by our tutors to students have allowed them to become proud leaders with the best qualities of leadership such as discipline and enthusiasm.
·If you were to ask a student from our course as to what is teamwork he/she would reply with an answer saying that the concept of teamwork can be defined as a group&#39;s collective effort to accomplish a shared purpose or complete a task most successfully and productively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master And Overcome Remote Work Information Overload</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-and-overcome-remote-work-information-overload/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 13:13:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-and-overcome-remote-work-information-overload/</guid>
      <description>About The Course
This dynamic and unique course offers a different perspective on the nature of remote work, how it differs from face-to-face work and what you can do to make the most of it. Drawing from psychological research, the history of office-based work and the latest technologies in productivity, this is a practical guide on how to beat information overload at remote distances.
The lectures in this course cover not only psychological, technological and productivity issues, but also the social factors that can make remote work a challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beating Anxiety: Learn The Hidden Secrets Of Beating Anxiety</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/beating-anxiety-learn-the-hidden-secrets-of-beating-anxiety/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/beating-anxiety-learn-the-hidden-secrets-of-beating-anxiety/</guid>
      <description>Don&#39;t LIVE With Anxiety ... Learn How To Beat It! Anxiety Has Horrible Plans For You ... Don&#39;t Go Along With It ... Gain The Tools To Fight Back &amp;amp; WIN!
This Course Give You The Hidden Skills Know Only To A Few ... Learn How To Beat Anxiety ... Don&#39;t Let Anxiety Beat You!
You Are About To Discover…
1) Discover How To Beat Back Anxiety &amp;amp; Worry ... Get Your Life Back!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beating Depression: The Hidden Secrets Of Beating Depression</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/beating-depression-the-hidden-secrets-of-beating-depression/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/beating-depression-the-hidden-secrets-of-beating-depression/</guid>
      <description>In This Online Course on Depression You Will Learn How You Can Transform Your LIFE By BEATING DEPRESSION! This Self-Help Course Covers ALL The Major Skills You Need To BEAT DEPRESSION, And Get Your LIFE Back! Depression Is HORRIBLE … And NOBODY Should Have To Live With It. Unfortunately … We Were NEVER Taught HOW To Beat Depression … NOW You WILL Have Those Skills With This One Simple Course!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motivation Mastery: Discover The Secrets Of Motivation</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/motivation-mastery-discover-the-secrets-of-motivation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/motivation-mastery-discover-the-secrets-of-motivation/</guid>
      <description>Motivation Is THE Key Life Skill .... Without it ... You Can&#39;t Get The Slightest Thing Done! How Do The MOST Motivated People Get So Motivated? ... FIND OUT!
Learn The Science Of Motivation ... In Ways That Make It Fast, Simple &amp;amp; Easy!
Get Ready To Discover …
1) What Motivation Is &amp;amp; How To Use It In Powerful Ways
2) Learn About “The Mind Games Of Motivation”
3) Discover How To Eliminate The Things That DE-Motivate You</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Success Rituals: The Ultimate Path To Success</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/success-rituals-the-ultimate-path-to-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/success-rituals-the-ultimate-path-to-success/</guid>
      <description>In This Success Ritual Online Training Course You Will Learn How To Take Your LIFE &amp;amp; CAREER To The Next Level. This Course Covers ALL The Major Success Rituals You Need To Be Massively Successful … Giving You The Key Tools, Strategies &amp;amp; Techniques You Need Make Your Life &amp;amp; Career Take Off! Learn How To Realize Your FULL Potential!
Learning These Key Success Ritual Skills &amp;amp; Techniques Can Help You Be Massively Successful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Communication-Introduce Yourself With Confidence</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-communication-introduce-yourself-with-confidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-communication-introduce-yourself-with-confidence/</guid>
      <description>Imagine that every time you introduce yourself, you know you are coming across as completely confident, comfortable and memorable. You will never again have to worry about what to say or how you come across.
How to Introduce Yourself In this &#34;How to Introduce Yourself&#34; course you will learn how to avoid the awkwardness and tediousness displayed when many people introduce themselves. You will be taught how to appear to be confident, comfortable and relaxed when standing to introduce yourself, and you will know how to say something interesting and memorable to the other people in the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking for Women</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-for-women/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-for-women/</guid>
      <description>Public Speaking - Imagine that every time you speak, people are in awe of your confidence and actually remember your messages and key ideas. Wouldn&#39;t you love to be able to stand up and speak to any crown, anytime, and know that you are coming across your very best, and that people understand you and remember your messages? In this Public Speaking for Women course you will learn the following: *How to speak with confidence *How to tell stories *How to avoid the most common Public Speaking blunders that affect both men and women public speakers *How to get your audience to understand you and remember your messages This course is delivered primarily through spoken lecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Personal Development Course - 22 Courses in 1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-personal-development-course-22-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-personal-development-course-22-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>*Update - A 50-Questions Master Quiz has been added! :)
If You Only Buy ONE Course This Year … It GOT To Be This One!
With over 54 hours of video content, 283 lectures, downloadable resources and bonuses - this is one of the most comprehensive personal development courses available! You&#39;ll also get access to:
Lifetime Access to course updates
Fast &amp;amp; Friendly Support in the Q&amp;amp;A section
Udemy Certificate of Completion Ready for Download</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond common sense: A scientific positive parenting course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/beyond-common-sense-a-scientific-positive-parenting-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/beyond-common-sense-a-scientific-positive-parenting-course/</guid>
      <description>Parenting is not easy and children (unfortunately) do not come with a manual. Although parenting advice can be found anywhere, it is often difficult to determine the quality of these parenting tips. This course aims to provide you with high-quality knowledge and skills on positive parenting, fully based on scientific findings.
Gain Science-Based Knowledge and Master Skills to be a Positive Light in Children’s Life
· Learn about Positive Parenting based on the Self-Determination Theory</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First impression hack - cheat based on scientific evidence!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/first-impression-hack-cheat-based-on-scientific-evidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/first-impression-hack-cheat-based-on-scientific-evidence/</guid>
      <description>You’ll never get a second chance to make a great first impression.Summary of the courseIn other words, when you meet someone for the first time, you need to be on top of your game from the very beginning. The key is to build rapport. Rapport is the lubricant for social communication. When rapport is established, communication barriers go down and you will have the opportunity to make a lasting connection. This practice is used actively by the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) to get interviewees to open up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking: A tactical approach</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-a-tactical-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-a-tactical-approach/</guid>
      <description>This course was born from frustration! Frustration that no one seems to be able to do what they’re teaching when it comes to speaking and communication. Everyone is either trying to teach you how to be a motivational speaker or some BS on overcoming your fears. In other words, it’s all self-help. But what does facing your fears and embracing your passion have to do with your regional sales report? Or a meeting with five people?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career Change: The 5 Key Skills To Change Your Career</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/career-change-the-5-key-skills-to-change-your-career/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/career-change-the-5-key-skills-to-change-your-career/</guid>
      <description>This is a step by step course on HOW TO CHANGE YOUR CAREER!
Welcome to this 2 hour course that will teach you the five key skills that high achievers use to change their careers!
My name is Paul and I&#39;ll be your instructor. :-) I&#39;m a Career Coach, Finance Director &amp;amp; ex PriceWaterhouseCoopers Consultant.
I guarantee that this course will help you change careers - or your money back, no questions asked!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motivation: You Can Become a Motivational Speaker</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/motivation-you-can-become-a-motivational-speaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/motivation-you-can-become-a-motivational-speaker/</guid>
      <description>Motivation. Motivational Speaking: You Can Become a Motivational Speaker Imagine yourself speaking on the stage in front of hundreds or thousands of people. Your words are inspiring and motivating your audience to make changes and take positive actions. You can lead from the platform!
How to Be a Motivational Speaker - Motivation
In this &#34;How to be a Motivational Speaker&#34; Motivation course you will learn the fundamentals of how to structure a motivational speech and how to run a motivational speaking business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win at Job Interviews for High Potential Candidates</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/win-at-job-interviews-for-high-potential-candidates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/win-at-job-interviews-for-high-potential-candidates/</guid>
      <description>In many High Profile, Consultancy, Leadership and Strategic roles, employers are looking not only for High performers but also for candidates who are High Potentials to advance and significantly contribute to an organisation and potentially advance to Senior Executive Leadership roles based on their evidenced Behavioral and Competency skill set. If you want to get on a fast Management or a High Potential training track within top organisations you need to demonstrate how you excel in key areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking: Give a Great Retirement Speech!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-give-a-great-retirement-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-give-a-great-retirement-speech/</guid>
      <description>Public Speaking: you can go out with a bang by delivering a fantastic retirement speech. Imagine giving your retirement speech and every one of your colleagues feels as though you are personally speaking to them and thanking them in a meaningful way. Wouldn&#39;t it be nice to end your career on a high note by giving a retirement speech where you hit all the right notes? In this How to Give a Retirement Speech Public Speaking course you will learn the following: *How to give a great retirement speech *How to plan stories for your speech *How to practice your speech on video *How to use the right amount of emotion and retain composure This public speaking course is delivered primarily through spoken lecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Psychology for Stress and Leadership</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-psychology-for-stress-and-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-psychology-for-stress-and-leadership/</guid>
      <description>This isn&#39;t a managing program, it&#39;s psychology. It&#39;s about YOU. Your thoughts, blocks, obstacles, stressors, and how they affect you and the people you care for. Within every craft there is always a mental side of performance, and leadership is not different.
There are many ways stress can be viewed in our normal day-to-day struggle, but I’ll do my best to try not to treat it like a superficial topic, and while I wrote this with the intention of it being clear and practical, this is not a how-to guide or a tutorial on deep breathing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win at Job Interviews for Recent Graduates</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/win-at-job-interviews-for-recent-graduates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/win-at-job-interviews-for-recent-graduates/</guid>
      <description>This course is for anyone wanting to do better at Job interviews and successfully get a Job offer in the career you want!
This course is not just about getting any job, its about getting the job that will set you firmly on your career path with your ideal brand name and chosen professional direction.
Ideal for Recent Graduates and people with relatively little professional working experience.
Fulfilling your career ambitions is a daily mission, and Winning at critical job interviews for that job you want is just the start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goal Setting Mastery</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/goal-setting-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/goal-setting-mastery/</guid>
      <description>Setting Goals are paramount if you want to achieve true success in life. This course gives you the Step by Step plan to * Set and reach your Goals and thus achieve Success in your Life. * Multiply your Productivity.
* Stay Focused and get Results.
* Visualize your Goals.
* Review and Reflect your Goals.
* Be more accountable towards your Goals.
* Develop Winning Habits.
* Handle Obstacles during the process of reaching your Goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy IBS Relief with EFT - Tapping Therapy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/easy-ibs-relief-with-eft-tapping-therapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/easy-ibs-relief-with-eft-tapping-therapy/</guid>
      <description>If you have been suffering from IBS this is the course to help you beat that feeling of helplessness with a easy to learn and apply technique that I will teach and guide you through each exercise so that you will be able to change how you think and feel and become a more relaxed person in all areas of your life. The technique I will be teaching you is called EFT (Emotional Freedom Technique) it is a gentle tapping technique where when you tap on certain points on the body while thinking about a problem you reduce or eliminate the bad feelings attached to that problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goal Settings Mastery - Win At The Game Of Life!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/goal-settings-mastery-win-at-the-game-of-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/goal-settings-mastery-win-at-the-game-of-life/</guid>
      <description>Goal Setting Skill Separates The WINNERS From The LOSERS! It&#39;s That Simple!
This Goal Setting Course is Designed To Transform Your Life! We Want You To Have The Power Skills Needed To Transform ANY Area Of Your Life!
Goal Setting Is Especially Important If You Are In Business ... It Is The Difference Between Success &amp;amp; Failure! Are YOU Trained In Goal Setting? Is Your STAFF?
QUESTION: &#34;How Can You Get Ahead In Life If You Are Not Good At Goal Setting?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Survive Purim with Sanity with Your ADHD Child</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-survive-purim-with-sanity-with-your-adhd-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-survive-purim-with-sanity-with-your-adhd-child/</guid>
      <description>The Jewish calendar is full of beautiful Festivals, full of meaning. If you have an ADHD child, the Festival of Purim can be a nightmare. When Purim is over, does your home feel like a hurricane has just passed, leaving destruction in it&#39;s wake? Does the excitement turn your ADHD child upside down? Does it take you weeks to get yourself, your ADHD child and your house back in some semblance of order?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peak Productivity Hacks – Triple Your Productivity</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/peak-productivity-hacks-triple-your-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/peak-productivity-hacks-triple-your-productivity/</guid>
      <description>In this Peak Productivity course you will learn how the pros teach people how to maximize productivity. Get more done with the same hours you have and create more time and freedom for things that matter most!
Do you sometimes spend hours or even the entire day at your work desk, but can’t seem to get much done? Do you wish to be more productive for your time? Here’s the GOOD NEWS … There is a simple FORMULA to put an end to procrastination and get more done in less time … And we will share it with you in this course!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation Skills: Give a Great Acceptance Speech</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/presentation-skills-give-a-great-acceptance-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 10:00:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/presentation-skills-give-a-great-acceptance-speech/</guid>
      <description>Presentation Skills for any occasion. Imagine giving an acceptance speech in front of the people you respect the most (or perhaps the whole world) and you are brief, funny, thoughtful and insightful. Wouldn&#39;t it be great if you could leave a fantastic impression on people during your brief acceptance speech? In this How to Give an Acceptance Speech - Presentation Skills course you will learn the following: *How to say thanks in a genuine and memorable way *How to avoid the most common blunders made by award winners *How to appear poised and relaxed *How to rehearse on video *How to master Presentation Skills</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Song Tantra - Songwriting from the Soul!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-song-tantra-songwriting-from-the-soul/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-song-tantra-songwriting-from-the-soul/</guid>
      <description>In this course I teach you a special vocal technique that opens the voice and creative flow! My technique connects you to the creative energy from your soul, so you can create beautiful music that will entrance audiences to you and your music. I have personally have studied singing and sung professionally for over 20 years, graduated cum la mentored with pro- songwriters who write for celebrities and learn their songwriting techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management Techniques 101: The Beginner&#39;s Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-techniques-101-the-beginners-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-techniques-101-the-beginners-guide/</guid>
      <description>Planning your day does not necessarily mean filling out all your available hours with tasks and ending up working all day. Working non-stop all day will end up burning you out and you will end up not finishing and getting behind your schedule instead
Finding the right moment for your different priorities you will find that you can accomplish more with less time.
The goal of this course is you are going to be more effective and efficiency by getting things done with less time so that you have time to do things you enjoy doing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hörbuchsprecher werden - Hörbuch Aufnahme,Marketingstrategie</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/h%C3%B6rbuchsprecher-werden-h%C3%B6rbuch-aufnahmemarketingstrategie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/h%C3%B6rbuchsprecher-werden-h%C3%B6rbuch-aufnahmemarketingstrategie/</guid>
      <description>Ein neuer, digitaler Berufszweig ist entstanden. Das #Hörbuch #Hörbücher sind in aller Ohren. Ob auf Streaming-Plattformen, für Fachbücher, Belletristik-Bestseller oder im Homeoffice-Lernbereich. Hast Du Dich auch schonmal gefragt, ob auch Du mit Deiner Stimme als Hörbuchsprecherin /Hörbuchsprecher Menschen begeistern kannst? Findest Du Synchronstimmen auf Netflix, in Hollywood-Filmen und Co. auch so sexy? Hast Du Dich einmal gefragt, wie und wieviel Geld man auf diese Art und Weise verdienen kann?
Wie sieht das Hörbuchsprecher-Dasein ist der Praxis aus?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Manipulation Works</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-manipulation-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-manipulation-works/</guid>
      <description>A MATTER OF MANIPULATION
Manipulation is, no doubt, dangerous in the world of today.
It&#39;s important to be able to identify it so that you can stop it in its tracks.
You can be manipulated:
At work, by your manager or coworkers;
In business relationships, by partners or suppliers;
In relationships or friendships, through emotion or even bullying;
By politicians, the media or others, with false numbers;
By any type of person that wants to drive you to a specific type of action;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview Essentials</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/interview-essentials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/interview-essentials/</guid>
      <description>This course provides insights and best practices to help enhance your skills to land an entry-level or mid-level job. Here are some of the topics covered in this course:
Interview skills: learn key skills you need to have to do well in an interview.
Job application: learn best practices to use when filling out job applications.
Resume: learn some quick tips to help you put together a professional resume.
Your internet presence: learn how to present yourself online to ensure you don’t scare off potential employers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cultivating Gratitude with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cultivating-gratitude-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:50:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cultivating-gratitude-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>Here&#39;s what you&#39;ll discover inside of this life-changing online course with MRS JOY:
Learn that gratitude is a state of being.
Learn how to use gratitude in your relationships to develop a deeper connection.
Learn how the power of positive emotions and gratitude can change your life.
Discover how practicing mindfulness and meditation can cultivate an attitude of gratitude.
Discover what unbalanced gratitude is and how you can counteract it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Timers Guide to Approach A Girl - Basic Do&#39;s &amp; Don&#39;ts</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/first-timers-guide-to-approach-a-girl-basic-dos-donts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:47:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/first-timers-guide-to-approach-a-girl-basic-dos-donts/</guid>
      <description>If you want to start conversations with girls in different environments, get their phone numbers or add them on Instagram/Facebook/Snapchat, and begin dating them, then this is the course for you.
This course focuses on the basic question every guy has to get things going for him with a girl; be it the start of a friendship or the first step to a blossoming relationship; in different scenarios from parties to your empty high school corridors; and the different types of girls, be it shy or the obnoxious kind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solve Problems by Rising above Problems For New Perspective</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/solve-problems-by-rising-above-problems-for-new-perspective/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/solve-problems-by-rising-above-problems-for-new-perspective/</guid>
      <description>Solve Problems by Rising above Problems for New Perspective
5 Star Review
GREAT little course on how to overcome your fears, anxiety, stress, problems by using your imagination with self-hypnosis and/or EFT tapping.
Ivon Timmermans
Learn how you can easily change your perspective of old experiences that have clouded how you see the world and people in it. Because not everyone has the same life experiences that hold them back, but it is those past experiences that have created who you are today because of your perspective of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Steps To Permanent Happiness</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/10-steps-to-permanent-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/10-steps-to-permanent-happiness/</guid>
      <description>This is a lifetime journey that we will take together. I will be your teacher, guide, psychologist, motivator and friend.
To be truly happy we need to learn and understand why we are unhappy, what is happiness and how we can achieve it. We have different types of happiness, but here we are going to be focused on permanent happiness.
For permanent happiness, we have to make changes in our minds and soul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NLP - Beginner Level - Personal Growth Mastery</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/nlp-beginner-level-personal-growth-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/nlp-beginner-level-personal-growth-mastery/</guid>
      <description>What is NLP?
NLP (Neuro Linguistic Programming) is &#39;the science &amp;amp; art of human excellence&#39;.
NLP is a simple, easy to learn, yet powerful methodology for studying what goes on inside you. How you think, feel &amp;amp; act in different situations in your life.
NLP provides you with the keys to change your thinking processes to effect lasting positive change in your life.
With NLP , you can change &#39;how&#39; you think about anything &amp;amp; transform your fears into strengths, overcome your limitations, change bad habits, get rid of phobias .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness for Parents with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mindfulness-for-parents-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mindfulness-for-parents-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>Mindfulness For Parents is designed to support you to discover:
-What is Mindfulness and how it can help you and your family
-The 3 Pillars of Mindfulness
-How to bring Mindfulness into your daily activities
-How to practice Mindfulness with your child – or kids, if you have more than one
- How to develop more concentration
- How to increase kindness, self-compassion and wellbeing to your life and in the lives of the ones you love and care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of Mindfulness</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentals-of-mindfulness/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:43:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentals-of-mindfulness/</guid>
      <description>We are so busy in our everyday lives that we rarely stop to think and be aware of our surroundings. However, this is harmful, as it prevents us from being more calm - both in terms of relaxing our body, but also quieting the internal chatter in our minds.
In this course, you are going to learn more about the fundamentals of mindfulness and its components. Elements such as presence, awareness, self-acceptance and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness for Executives</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mindfulness-for-executives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:43:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mindfulness-for-executives/</guid>
      <description>Do you wish you could be less stressed and more present?
We are so busy in our everyday lives that we rarely stop to think and be aware of our surroundings. However, this is harmful, as it prevents us from being more calm - both in terms of relaxing our body, but also quieting the internal chatter in our minds.
Especially as an executive, being present and aware is crucial, because it&#39;s reflected on the presentations you give, on how &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness for Busy People</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mindfulness-for-busy-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:43:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mindfulness-for-busy-people/</guid>
      <description>Do you wish you could be less stressed and more present?
We are so busy in our everyday lives that we rarely stop to think and be aware of our surroundings. However, this is harmful, as it prevents us from being more calm - both in terms of relaxing our body, but also quieting the internal chatter in our minds.
Especially as a busy person, that runs from one task to another, it&#39;s easy to never stop and relax, which can make you more stressed or anxious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flexible Laundry Systems for the Creative ADHD  Business Mum</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/flexible-laundry-systems-for-the-creative-adhd-business-mum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/flexible-laundry-systems-for-the-creative-adhd-business-mum/</guid>
      <description>WHO I AM AND WHY I AM EQUIPPED TO GUIDE YOU
I have ADHD. I am a mum of 5 successful ADHD children.
Throughout my life I have had my share of challenges and struggles related to ADHD. I have searched long and hard for the tools to unlock my ADHD. Searching for those answers has been one of the most difficult tasks of my life. I have found those answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to find first Job in certain fields/ Common tips</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-find-first-job-in-certain-fields/-common-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-find-first-job-in-certain-fields/-common-tips/</guid>
      <description>The goal of hiring managers is not just to hire people who need a job. It’s to hire people who believe in their organization, its mission and the work that’s involved in the job position. Every hiring manager knows: Hire people to do a job and they’ll work for your money. Hire people who believe in the work and they’ll work for their passion.
And this is not a case of “fake it until you make it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management And Goal Planning: The Productivity Combo</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-and-goal-planning-the-productivity-combo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/time-management-and-goal-planning-the-productivity-combo/</guid>
      <description>What about setting 48-Hour Productivity from a 24-hour day? So many things, so little time, right? Wrong!
Time management is all about working SMARTER, not harder!
Time management, focus and motivation are the basis for planning and achieving our goals and being more productive. Distraction turns seemingly busy days into wasted time, producing a negative impact on our productivity.
This course will show you the best time management and goal planning strategies to focus on what really matters, prioritizing those actions that lead to the achievement of our short and long term goals in order to fulfill your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resilience Masterclass: Build a Refugee Mindset for Survival</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/resilience-masterclass-build-a-refugee-mindset-for-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/resilience-masterclass-build-a-refugee-mindset-for-survival/</guid>
      <description>Resilience Masterclass: Build a Refuge Mindset for Survival to Thrival
The Resilience Mindset- Survival Tips for the Worst Time of Your Life - For Refugees &amp;amp; Those Who Want Survival Skills
Refugees are persons who are outside their country of origin for reasons of feared persecution, conflict, generalized violence, or other circumstances that have seriously disturbed public order and, as a result, require international protection. This is what I experience. I will help you to prepare and get ready mentally and physically to travel and be a successful refugee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Charisma Guide for Men:Increase Your Influence</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-charisma-guide-for-menincrease-your-influence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-charisma-guide-for-menincrease-your-influence/</guid>
      <description>It was 2005 and I was fed up with always being Mr. Nice Guy. It was then clear to me the nicer I was the more people would take advantage of me! So I decided to learn how to stop all this mess, to learn from my experience, from the behavior of bigger men than me, and to extensively research how to become more charismatic! So I opened my eyes, ears, and mind to everything around me in all areas of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total Confidence: The Pillars Of Unshakeable Confidence</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/total-confidence-the-pillars-of-unshakeable-confidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/total-confidence-the-pillars-of-unshakeable-confidence/</guid>
      <description>In This Online Video Self-Confidence Training Course You Will Learn Easy Ways To Build Your Confidence. Discover How Successful People Create Greater Confidence Fast! Self-Confidence Is The Master Skill To Success. Having These Self-Confidence Tools &amp;amp; Strategies Will Make Your Life So Much Easier, Dramatically Increase The Results You Get &amp;amp; Help You Achieve Your Goals In Less Time.
This Course Will Give You The Hidden Secrets Of Self-Confidence In The Following Areas: 1) Learn Secret Language Of Confident People 2) Learn The Steps To Building Unshakeable Confidence 3) Discover How To Bounce Back From Failure 4) Specific Tips &amp;amp; Practices For Unshakeable Confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principles Of Success – Growth Mindset</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/principles-of-success-growth-mindset/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 10:48:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/principles-of-success-growth-mindset/</guid>
      <description>In this online “Principles Of Success” training course you will learn how the pros teach people how to be Massively Successful and Develop a Growth Mindset. This Success course is based on scientific research &amp;amp; principles that are known to get results fast! Having these tools &amp;amp; strategies will make becoming successful so much easier, dramatically increase the results you get &amp;amp; help you achieve your goals in far less time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Put a Dead-Halt Stop to Self-Sabotage and Get Motivated</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/put-a-dead-halt-stop-to-self-sabotage-and-get-motivated/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 10:48:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/put-a-dead-halt-stop-to-self-sabotage-and-get-motivated/</guid>
      <description>Are you a lifelong student of personal development of transformation?
Do you need help with motivation, stress management, or productivity?
If you said &#34;yes&#34; to any of those, a MindMastery course is right for you.
Specifically, students who take our Put a Dead-Halt Stop to Self-Sabotage and Get Motivated course experience these roadblocks:
Self-sabotage
Procrastination and bad habits
A lack of motivation
And they report these benefits from the MindMastery experience:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Creative Way to Declutter and Organise with Your ADHD</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-creative-way-to-declutter-and-organise-with-your-adhd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-creative-way-to-declutter-and-organise-with-your-adhd/</guid>
      <description>Are you a woman with ADHD or ADHD tendencies? Are you a busy professional mum, struggling to balance your life and the life of your ADHD child? Only you know of the dark side lurking behind your front door. The clutter, the mess and general chaos. I know, because I have ADHD myself. I have struggled mightily for many years to find systems that work for my brain. I searched high and low.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>İş ve Özel Yaşamda Alışkanlıkları Yönetmenin Sırları</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/i%C5%9F-ve-%C3%B6zel-ya%C5%9Famda-al%C4%B1%C5%9Fkanl%C4%B1klar%C4%B1-y%C3%B6netmenin-s%C4%B1rlar%C4%B1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 22:23:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/i%C5%9F-ve-%C3%B6zel-ya%C5%9Famda-al%C4%B1%C5%9Fkanl%C4%B1klar%C4%B1-y%C3%B6netmenin-s%C4%B1rlar%C4%B1/</guid>
      <description>Alışkanlık, otomatikleşecek kadar çok tekrarlanmış davranıştır. Davranışlar duygulara, duygular ise kimliğinize bağlıdır. Altıncı his diye de ifade edebileceğimiz otomatik alışkanlıkları yaparken farketmeyiz bile. İçgüdülerimiz tarafından yönetildiğini düşündüğümüz bu alışkanlıklar aslında beynimizin ve vücudumuzun hiç düşünmediği alışkanlıklardır. İyi alışkanlıkları güçlendirerek, bunun duygu ve düşüncelerinize katkısını görebilirsiniz. Küçük değişimler ile büyük farklar yaratılabilir.
Alışkanlıkların nasıl oluştuğunu öğrenmek değiştirmek ve geliştirmek için önemlidir. 21 günde yapılan alışkanlık olur dense de konu bu kadar basite indirgenemez.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comunicazione: come gestirla in maniera efficace</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/comunicazione-come-gestirla-in-maniera-efficace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/comunicazione-come-gestirla-in-maniera-efficace/</guid>
      <description>In questo corso ti spiegherò nei minimi dettagli come poter superare le difficoltà del parlare in pubblico e rendere più incisivo il tuo modo di Comunicare. Esporrò tecniche precise e dettagliate, ti darò consigli teorici e pratici per far sì che tu possa padroneggiare nel migliore dei modi la Voce(intesa come Contenuto e Comunicazione Para-Verbale) ed il linguaggio del corpo (Comunicazione Non Verbale) spiegandoti l&#39;importanza del tenere viva l&#39;attenzione dall&#39;esordio alla conclusione di un discorso.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Over a Break up</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-get-over-a-break-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-get-over-a-break-up/</guid>
      <description>Breakups blow chunks. Whether it’s an amicable breakup or a horrible, crash-and-burn situation, you’ve invested a part of you into another person and must accept that a relationship that you once nurtured is dead and gone. Brain-mapping studies have shown that the same regions of the brain are activated when an addict is going through withdrawals as when someone is going through a breakup.
Whether the relationship lasted three weeks or three years, breakups can leave us feeling heartbroken, lost and even physically ill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Letter For Myself: Self-Affirmations with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/a-letter-for-myself-self-affirmations-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/a-letter-for-myself-self-affirmations-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>A Letter For Myself: 56 Days To Reprogram Your Subconscious Mind For A Healthy &amp;amp; Loving Relationship is developed to increase your love for yourself and for your partner or even for your future partner, if you don&#39;t have one yet.
“A Letter For Myself” is a self-development audio course from MRS JOY’s Academy, where you will find special narrations of MRS JOY, as you are talking with yourself. They help you to reprogram your subconscious mind and imprint the life you love to live.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern Job Interview Preparation, Tips &amp; Tricks Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/modern-job-interview-preparation-tips-tricks-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/modern-job-interview-preparation-tips-tricks-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Modern businesses are hiring for culture, not just skills. Having a spot-on resume and cover letter is necessary, but it’s only the one third of the battle. Who you are as a person is just as important to your next employer as what you can do for them.
Most of us have been taught a specific traditional method for job interviewing. Once we learn the traditional method, it can be hard to change our approach!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Common Job Interview Questions with Answer</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/most-common-job-interview-questions-with-answer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/most-common-job-interview-questions-with-answer/</guid>
      <description>(The course content has updated according to students&#39; interest on 16th August 2019)
‘Why did you leave your last job?’ ‘What are your weaknesses?’ ‘If you were a type of fruit, what would you be, and why?’
OK, so some interview questions are easier to answer than others. But whilst you can’t predict exactly what you’ll be asked, any question has the potential to make you stumble – unless, of course, you’ve prepared in advance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Become a Firefighter!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-become-a-firefighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:42:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-become-a-firefighter/</guid>
      <description>Learn how a career as a firefighter can provide you with financial stability, allowing you to give back to your community and make you excited to come to work. Firefighting is a rewarding career that offers great opportunity for growth and advancement, amazing medical benefits and a high level of job satisfaction. This course will teach you how to prepare for your new career full of thrills and excitement while helping your community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Confidence Building Course - Exude Confidence Now</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-confidence-building-course-exude-confidence-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-confidence-building-course-exude-confidence-now/</guid>
      <description>Complete Confidence Building Course - Exude Confidence NowBuild Your Confidence - Increase Self-Esteem - Radiate More Confidence - Become a Truly Confident Person - Communication
Imagine going through life filled with confidence. You are confident in your abilities, your talents, your communication skills, your appearance and in having an accurate sense of how others perceive you. and other people judge you as supremely confident (though not cocky or arrogant!)
Confidence is not something you are born with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beat Procrastination in Turbulent Covid Era</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/beat-procrastination-in-turbulent-covid-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 17:46:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/beat-procrastination-in-turbulent-covid-era/</guid>
      <description>Procrastination is one of the principle boundaries obstructing you from getting up, settling on the correct choices, and carrying on with the fantasy life you&#39;ve considered.
Ongoing investigations have shown that individuals regret more the things they haven&#39;t done than the things they have done. Furthermore, sensations of disappointment and blame coming about because of botched freedoms will in general remain with individuals any longer.
Some of the time every one of our chances appear to be on our fingertips, however we can&#39;t contact them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-Discipline: Build Habits &amp; Develop a Growth Mindset</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/self-discipline-build-habits-develop-a-growth-mindset/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:28:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/self-discipline-build-habits-develop-a-growth-mindset/</guid>
      <description>Join our students who have taken our time management, goal setting and focus mastery courses with great results!
This course will teach you why and how to develop self-discipline, increase your motivation and stop procrastinating, empowering you to build daily habits for long-term success.
Whether you are a student, employee or entrepreneur, you will need to get your job done and, possibly, do it in the best possible way.
In fact, we have all faced the frustration of a job we don&#39;t like or a task we find difficult to complete, or a passion we have to fight for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Freedom: From PAIN To POWER</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mental-freedom-from-pain-to-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mental-freedom-from-pain-to-power/</guid>
      <description>Isn&#39;t It Bizarre That You Were Never Trained In How To Control &amp;amp; Get The Best From Your Own Mind? That Is INSANE! Yet That Is The Hand Everybody Is Dealt! Inside This Course You Will Learn The Secrets Of Psychology That Will Give You The Mental &amp;amp; Emotional Control You Always Wanted!
You Are About To Discover:
1) Discover The Secret Of How To SOLVE Problems ... Rather Than Live With Them</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Career Coaching Course - Career Development</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-career-coaching-course-career-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-career-coaching-course-career-development/</guid>
      <description>Coaching is a $3 billion a year global business that&#39;s growing at rate of 7% annually. And one of the most important segments in this accelerating industry of career coaching where the median rate is $500 per hour. Tens of millions of people either want a new job, change their fields, or substantially improve their performance at their current occupation. We&#39;re going to give you the skills to help your clients reach success in both their personal and professional lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to be a good PR</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-be-a-good-pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-be-a-good-pr/</guid>
      <description>This course is presented by me: Alhassan Ahmed younes Ahmed a good PR in many teams. You will gain a lot of knowledge from my experience in this committee. You will learn how to pass any interview in this field, how to complete any form in registering in any team.
You will learn all of the information of this topic in student activities.
You will learn how to make deals from zero to hero, and I will help you with some important contact numbers of some people are very famous around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning to Religion to reduce STRESS</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/turning-to-religion-to-reduce-stress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/turning-to-religion-to-reduce-stress/</guid>
      <description>Notice: Please do NOT enrol on this course on impulse, thinking you might watch it later. Maybe show an interest on impulse, yes, but before you enrol, watch the Preview videos, read the Course Description and then make a decision. If you then enrol then please start the course as soon as possible. Watch the lectures, look at the workbooks and join in the discussions. Joining my courses is a serious business and I want you to get the most out of your study – but I also want you to enjoy the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fully Accredited Professional EFT Tapping Certification</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fully-accredited-professional-eft-tapping-certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fully-accredited-professional-eft-tapping-certification/</guid>
      <description>This IAOTH, UK accredited EFT Tapping certification is a masterclass that will enable you to help an endless number of people (including yourself).
This concise programme is designed, keeping in mind that you may not have any prior knowledge about Art Therapy, and you want to learn despite your busy schedule. So we have tried to avoid jargon as much as possible and simplified concepts and terminology for you. for EFT is found extremely useful for a wide range of conditions/situations e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stress Management - For Relief From Stress of Life &amp; Work</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/stress-management-for-relief-from-stress-of-life-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/stress-management-for-relief-from-stress-of-life-work/</guid>
      <description>Stress Management: Stress can weigh you down until you can hardly think straight! Beat it Today with this Comprehensive Stress Management Course filled with Cutting-Edge Tools &amp;amp; Strategies - Feel better TODAY! Created by Master Therapist &amp;amp; Multiple Award-Winning Educator Prof. Paul J. Cline Ed.D ... Get His 35+ years of Expertise in Helping others Beat Stress ... Condensed down into this Training.
Here Are Just A Few Of the Skills You Will Gain:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Repair - Auto Repair &amp; Tuning - Auto Technician Training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/car-repair-auto-repair-tuning-auto-technician-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/car-repair-auto-repair-tuning-auto-technician-training/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
One of the things that I find most interesting about automotive technology is how it advances and changes. It is also interesting that ideas from many years ago often return to favour. In this course I have therefore concentrated on core technologies, in other words how the technology works, rather than giving too many examples from specific vehicles. However, I have included some examples of Formula 1 technology, arguably the pinnacle of automotive engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Master Your Origin Challenge</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-master-your-origin-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-master-your-origin-challenge/</guid>
      <description>This course includes:
1 hours of on-demand video instruction
7 video sections
Over 30 downloadable exercises &amp;amp; resources
Downloadable book chapter
Full lifetime access
Access on mobile and TV
Certificate of completion
What you’ll learn:
Learn who and what you are and why.
Discover the “origin programming” done by your parents, etc. during your first 18 years of life.
Identify which of your traits and relationship characteristics come from your origin programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Stop Fear Spiritually</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-stop-fear-spiritually/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-stop-fear-spiritually/</guid>
      <description>Do you still allow fear to stop you from taking developmental steps?
If you have struggled to put that business idea that has been in your heart for many years&amp;nbsp;to work, then you&#39;re dwelling in the cage of fear.
&amp;nbsp;A wise man once said a child is born without fear except for the ones he&#39;s taught by society&amp;nbsp;as he grows up.
I want you to understand that everyone has the tendency to have fear but those who are great&amp;nbsp;achievers in our society have found a way to consistently kill it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview Success</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/interview-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/interview-success/</guid>
      <description>This course is for anyone wanting to do better at Job interviews and successfully get a Job offer in the career you want!
Created by practising Recruitment professionals with decades of experience in Business and Executive Recruitment from both Corporate leadership and Recruitment Agency backgrounds, we know what interviewers are looking for and what it takes to stand out - the competition is tougher than ever and we will help you shine!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Miraculous Faith</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-miraculous-faith/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-miraculous-faith/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling to overcome a problem or a challenge in your life, business, or marriage? Do you want simple-to-understand and easy-to-apply descriptions or explanations of the Christian faith that will help you solve those nagging problems in your life, business, or marriage?
If those questions apply to you, then this course, ‘The Miraculous Faith: Principles of Christian Faith Manifestation: How to make miracles through faith’ is just the right one for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PNL: Conversación transformacional &amp; Negociación efectiva</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pnl-conversaci%C3%B3n-transformacional-negociaci%C3%B3n-efectiva/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pnl-conversaci%C3%B3n-transformacional-negociaci%C3%B3n-efectiva/</guid>
      <description>Los seres humanos hemos concebido la idea de que existen variables que están fuera de la gestión individual, por tal motivo se ha exteriorizado la responsabilidad de aquellos pilares transformándonos en víctima de factores externos configurados en paradigmas (política, economía, ciencia y religión) encarnados en autoridades dueñas de conocimientos, reglas y mandamientos que han configurado las estructuras mentales por las cuales construimos nuestras experiencias y realidades.
Sin embargo, gracias a la era de la información y a consecuencia de la conectividad producida por el mismo fenómeno, estamos comenzando a cambiar la percepción del tiempo y el conocimiento desde un paradigma lineal e inamovible a otro holístico y constituidos por millares de posibilidades.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
