<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Development on </title>
    <link>/tags/personal-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal Development on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/personal-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automate your Job-Search with LoopCV in 2021</title>
      <link>/automate-your-job-search-with-loopcv-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/automate-your-job-search-with-loopcv-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the fifth course in Term 2 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Just imagine, how much time do you spend applying to jobs and all you get is a rejection letter after a week or a month&#39;s time?
Let&#39;s get this right as we elaborate on this problem faced by every job-seeker out there.
Do you actually spend a lot of time applying to a job, only to wait for weeks without any kind of positive feedback or response from recruiters and hiring managers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Confidence Building Course - Exude Confidence Now</title>
      <link>/complete-confidence-building-course-exude-confidence-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-confidence-building-course-exude-confidence-now/</guid>
      <description>Complete Confidence Building Course - Exude Confidence NowBuild Your Confidence - Increase Self-Esteem - Radiate More Confidence - Become a Truly Confident Person - Communication
Imagine going through life filled with confidence. You are confident in your abilities, your talents, your communication skills, your appearance and in having an accurate sense of how others perceive you. and other people judge you as supremely confident (though not cocky or arrogant!)
Confidence is not something you are born with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cultivating Gratitude with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>/cultivating-gratitude-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cultivating-gratitude-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>Here&#39;s what you&#39;ll discover inside of this life-changing online course with MRS JOY:

Learn that gratitude is a state of being.
Learn how to use gratitude in your relationships to develop a deeper connection.
Learn how the power of positive emotions and gratitude can change your life.
Discover how practicing mindfulness and meditation can cultivate an attitude of gratitude.
Discover what unbalanced gratitude is and how you can counteract it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effective Time Management Skills For A Productivity Boost</title>
      <link>/effective-time-management-skills-for-a-productivity-boost/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/effective-time-management-skills-for-a-productivity-boost/</guid>
      <description>This course approaches time management from 3 unique angles:
Time management in a single day
Time management in a week
Time management in your life to make sure that the tasks you work on are the right ones for your overall life direction, because if you are working on the wrong tasks, then all that time is mismanaged and wasted
Try this course and its unique approach which ends at you looking at the bigger picture of your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Become a Firefighter!</title>
      <link>/how-to-become-a-firefighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-become-a-firefighter/</guid>
      <description>Learn how a career as a firefighter can provide you with financial stability, allowing you to give back to your community and make you excited to come to work. Firefighting is a rewarding career that offers great opportunity for growth and advancement, amazing medical benefits and a high level of job satisfaction. This course will teach you how to prepare for your new career full of thrills and excitement while helping your community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness for Parents with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>/mindfulness-for-parents-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mindfulness-for-parents-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>Mindfulness For Parents is designed to support you to discover:

-What is Mindfulness and how it can help you and your family
-The 3 Pillars of Mindfulness
-How to bring Mindfulness into your daily activities
-How to practice Mindfulness with your child – or kids, if you have more than one
- How to develop more concentration
- How to increase kindness, self-compassion and wellbeing to your life and in the lives of the ones you love and care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nomad Lifestyle: LIVE YOUR DREAM &amp; Travel the World</title>
      <link>/digital-nomad-lifestyle-live-your-dream-travel-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/digital-nomad-lifestyle-live-your-dream-travel-the-world/</guid>
      <description>IS IT POSSIBLE TO LIVE YOUR DREAM LIFE WITHOUT WORKING SO HARD? DOES IT HAVE TO TAKE SO MUCH EFFORT, STRESS, AND ENERGY TO HAVE A LIFE THAT DEEPLY FULFILS YOU? HONOR AND TRUST YOUR PROCESS, AND SURRENDER TO THE MAGIC OF LIFE!!! BEING A DIGITAL NOMAD MEANS LIVING LIFE 100% ON YOUR OWN TERMS!!!
From leaving behind the corporate life of a consistent and often capped salary, saying goodbye to cubicles, a regular work commute and the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beat Procrastination in Turbulent Covid Era</title>
      <link>/beat-procrastination-in-turbulent-covid-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 17:46:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/beat-procrastination-in-turbulent-covid-era/</guid>
      <description>Procrastination is one of the principle boundaries obstructing you from getting up, settling on the correct choices, and carrying on with the fantasy life you&#39;ve considered.

Ongoing investigations have shown that individuals regret more the things they haven&#39;t done than the things they have done. Furthermore, sensations of disappointment and blame coming about because of botched freedoms will in general remain with individuals any longer.

Some of the time every one of our chances appear to be on our fingertips, however we can&#39;t contact them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management And Goal Planning: The Productivity Combo</title>
      <link>/time-management-and-goal-planning-the-productivity-combo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 17:46:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/time-management-and-goal-planning-the-productivity-combo/</guid>
      <description>What about setting 48-Hour Productivity from a 24-hour day? So many things, so little time, right? Wrong!
Time management is all about working SMARTER, not harder!
Time management, focus and motivation are the basis for planning and achieving our goals and being more productive. Distraction turns seemingly busy days into wasted time, producing a negative impact on our productivity.
This course will show you the best time management and goal planning strategies to focus on what really matters, prioritizing those actions that lead to the achievement of our short and long term goals in order to fulfill your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goal Setting For Success: Plan And Achieve Your Goals</title>
      <link>/goal-setting-for-success-plan-and-achieve-your-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:28:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/goal-setting-for-success-plan-and-achieve-your-goals/</guid>
      <description>Are you a student, struggling at setting and achieving your goals?
This goal setting course will quickly allow you to start setting personal and professional goals to boost your success.
If you are a studente you can start seeing a path to the success you hope for: you will be able to develop a goal setting mindset, find out what you want in life and create a concrete action plan to reach your targets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-Discipline: Build Habits &amp; Develop a Growth Mindset</title>
      <link>/self-discipline-build-habits-develop-a-growth-mindset/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:28:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/self-discipline-build-habits-develop-a-growth-mindset/</guid>
      <description>Join our students who have taken our time management, goal setting and focus mastery courses with great results!
This course will teach you why and how to develop self-discipline, increase your motivation and stop procrastinating, empowering you to build daily habits for long-term success.
Whether you are a student, employee or entrepreneur, you will need to get your job done and, possibly, do it in the best possible way.
In fact, we have all faced the frustration of a job we don&#39;t like or a task we find difficult to complete, or a passion we have to fight for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Educa ed Allena la tua Voce</title>
      <link>/educa-ed-allena-la-tua-voce/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:15:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/educa-ed-allena-la-tua-voce/</guid>
      <description>Hai problemi nel farti comprendere senza dover ripetere?
Ti senti insicuro dei tuoi mezzi di parola e voce? Parli col timore di non esser capito?
Quando comunichi hai problemi nel far comprendere pensieri ed emozioni?
Vorresti avere una migliore articolazione ?

Bene! Sei proprio nell&#39;aula virtuale giusta!
In questo corso troverai un approccio all&#39;utilizzo e allo sviluppo della voce del tuto differente da quello classico che muove le prime mosse da esercizi sulla vocalizzazione, sicuro fondamentali ma solo dopo aver acquisito piena conoscenza degli organi addetti alla fonazione.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser Focus Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/laser-focus-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/laser-focus-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>We live in an era of information overload. We are bombarded with media, technology, entertainment, and notifications every day. It seems there are hundreds of people and things competing for your attention at any given time.
There is no wonder why in the last few years, our attention spans have become shorter and our ability to focus has decreased.
Not being able to focus can have a negative effect on how successful we are at work and in our personal lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Freedom: From PAIN To POWER</title>
      <link>/mental-freedom-from-pain-to-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mental-freedom-from-pain-to-power/</guid>
      <description>Isn&#39;t It Bizarre That You Were Never Trained In How To Control &amp;amp; Get The Best From Your Own Mind? That Is INSANE! Yet That Is The Hand Everybody Is Dealt! Inside This Course You Will Learn The Secrets Of Psychology That Will Give You The Mental &amp;amp; Emotional Control You Always Wanted!
You Are About To Discover:
1) Discover The Secret Of How To SOLVE Problems ... Rather Than Live With Them</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Success Rituals: The Ultimate Path To Success</title>
      <link>/success-rituals-the-ultimate-path-to-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/success-rituals-the-ultimate-path-to-success/</guid>
      <description>In This Success Ritual Online Training Course You Will Learn How To Take Your LIFE &amp;amp; CAREER To The Next Level. This Course Covers ALL The Major Success Rituals You Need To Be Massively Successful … Giving You The Key Tools, Strategies &amp;amp; Techniques You Need Make Your Life &amp;amp; Career Take Off! Learn How To Realize Your FULL Potential!
Learning These Key Success Ritual Skills &amp;amp; Techniques Can Help You Be Massively Successful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/public-speaking-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 20:19:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/public-speaking-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>This course was designed to show even absolute beginners how to become more confident when speaking in public. It includes 5 preformatted lessons packed with easy to understand information.

Discover how to be more confident when speaking in public!
Do you know what one of the easiest ways to become a successful public speaker is? Well it is really easy and that is to study other successful speakers.
Why not learn from the best?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Career Coaching Course - Career Development</title>
      <link>/the-complete-career-coaching-course-career-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-career-coaching-course-career-development/</guid>
      <description>Coaching is a $3 billion a year global business that&#39;s growing at rate of 7% annually. And one of the most important segments in this accelerating industry of career coaching where the median rate is $500 per hour. Tens of millions of people either want a new job, change their fields, or substantially improve their performance at their current occupation. We&#39;re going to give you the skills to help your clients reach success in both their personal and professional lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to be a good PR</title>
      <link>/how-to-be-a-good-pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-be-a-good-pr/</guid>
      <description>This course is presented by me: Alhassan Ahmed younes Ahmed a good PR in many teams. You will gain a lot of knowledge from my experience in this committee. You will learn how to pass any interview in this field, how to complete any form in registering in any team.

You will learn all of the information of this topic in student activities.

You will learn how to make deals from zero to hero, and I will help you with some important contact numbers of some people are very famous around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning to Religion to reduce STRESS</title>
      <link>/turning-to-religion-to-reduce-stress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/turning-to-religion-to-reduce-stress/</guid>
      <description>Notice: Please do NOT enrol on this course on impulse, thinking you might watch it later. Maybe show an interest on impulse, yes, but before you enrol, watch the Preview videos, read the Course Description and then make a decision. If you then enrol then please start the course as soon as possible. Watch the lectures, look at the workbooks and join in the discussions. Joining my courses is a serious business and I want you to get the most out of your study – but I also want you to enjoy the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fully Accredited Professional EFT Tapping Certification</title>
      <link>/fully-accredited-professional-eft-tapping-certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fully-accredited-professional-eft-tapping-certification/</guid>
      <description>This IAOTH, UK accredited EFT Tapping certification is a masterclass that will enable you to help an endless number of people (including yourself).
This concise programme is designed, keeping in mind that you may not have any prior knowledge about Art Therapy, and you want to learn despite your busy schedule. So we have tried to avoid jargon as much as possible and simplified concepts and terminology for you. for EFT is found extremely useful for a wide range of conditions/situations e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stress Management - For Relief From Stress of Life &amp; Work</title>
      <link>/stress-management-for-relief-from-stress-of-life-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stress-management-for-relief-from-stress-of-life-work/</guid>
      <description>Stress Management: Stress can weigh you down until you can hardly think straight! Beat it Today with this Comprehensive Stress Management Course filled with Cutting-Edge Tools &amp;amp; Strategies - Feel better TODAY! Created by Master Therapist &amp;amp; Multiple Award-Winning Educator Prof. Paul J. Cline Ed.D ... Get His 35+ years of Expertise in Helping others Beat Stress ... Condensed down into this Training.
Here Are Just A Few Of the Skills You Will Gain:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness para desarrollar la inteligencia emocional</title>
      <link>/mindfulness-para-desarrollar-la-inteligencia-emocional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mindfulness-para-desarrollar-la-inteligencia-emocional/</guid>
      <description>Te enseño herramientas efectivas y sencillas de aplicar en tu rutina diaria, invirtiendo sólo entre 5 a 15 minutos al día tus emociones no serán más un obstáculo en la consecución de tus metas, tampoco volverás a sentir la culpa o vergüenza de tus impulsos y reacciones emocionales. 
Tu también puedes gozar de relaciones empáticas, satisfactorias y sin tantas fricciones. Poder solucionar de manera asertiva y consciente las diferencias con tus seres queridos, colegas, clientes y colaboradores es posible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Repair - Auto Repair &amp; Tuning - Auto Technician Training</title>
      <link>/car-repair-auto-repair-tuning-auto-technician-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/car-repair-auto-repair-tuning-auto-technician-training/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
One of the things that I find most interesting about automotive technology is how it advances and changes. It is also interesting that ideas from many years ago often return to favour. In this course I have therefore concentrated on core technologies, in other words how the technology works, rather than giving too many examples from specific vehicles. However, I have included some examples of Formula 1 technology, arguably the pinnacle of automotive engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Master Your Origin Challenge</title>
      <link>/how-to-master-your-origin-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-master-your-origin-challenge/</guid>
      <description>This course includes:
1 hours of on-demand video instruction
7 video sections
Over 30 downloadable exercises &amp;amp; resources
Downloadable book chapter
Full lifetime access
Access on mobile and TV
Certificate of completion

What you’ll learn:
Learn who and what you are and why.
Discover the “origin programming” done by your parents, etc. during your first 18 years of life.
Identify which of your traits and relationship characteristics come from your origin programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Stop Fear Spiritually</title>
      <link>/how-to-stop-fear-spiritually/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-stop-fear-spiritually/</guid>
      <description>Do you still allow fear to stop you from taking developmental steps?
If you have struggled to put that business idea that has been in your heart for many years&amp;nbsp;to work, then you&#39;re dwelling in the cage of fear.
&amp;nbsp;A wise man once said a child is born without fear except for the ones he&#39;s taught by society&amp;nbsp;as he grows up.
I want you to understand that everyone has the tendency to have fear but those who are great&amp;nbsp;achievers in our society have found a way to consistently kill it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview Success</title>
      <link>/interview-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/interview-success/</guid>
      <description>This course is for anyone wanting to do better at Job interviews and successfully get a Job offer in the career you want!
Created by practising Recruitment professionals with decades of experience in Business and Executive Recruitment from both Corporate leadership and Recruitment Agency backgrounds, we know what interviewers are looking for and what it takes to stand out - the competition is tougher than ever and we will help you shine!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Brain Training Course - Neuroplasticity -</title>
      <link>/the-complete-brain-training-course-neuroplasticity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-brain-training-course-neuroplasticity/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Brain Training Course - Neuroplasticity -
Brain Training for the Modern Smart Phone Era! You Can Train Your Brain to Think More Clearly and Creatively
Brain training is essential if you want do you live up to your full potential as a human being. Your brain is your most important organ, therefore it is essential that you train it for peak performance.
Like it or not, every single day your brain is being trained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Miraculous Faith</title>
      <link>/the-miraculous-faith/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-miraculous-faith/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling to overcome a problem or a challenge in your life, business, or marriage? Do you want simple-to-understand and easy-to-apply descriptions or explanations of the Christian faith that will help you solve those nagging problems in your life, business, or marriage?
If those questions apply to you, then this course, ‘The Miraculous Faith: Principles of Christian Faith Manifestation: How to make miracles through faith’ is just the right one for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PNL: Conversación transformacional &amp; Negociación efectiva</title>
      <link>/pnl-conversaci%C3%B3n-transformacional-negociaci%C3%B3n-efectiva/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pnl-conversaci%C3%B3n-transformacional-negociaci%C3%B3n-efectiva/</guid>
      <description>Los seres humanos hemos concebido la idea de que existen variables que están fuera de la gestión individual, por tal motivo se ha exteriorizado la responsabilidad de aquellos pilares transformándonos en víctima de factores externos configurados en paradigmas (política, economía, ciencia y religión) encarnados en autoridades dueñas de conocimientos, reglas y mandamientos que han configurado las estructuras mentales por las cuales construimos nuestras experiencias y realidades.
Sin embargo, gracias a la era de la información y a consecuencia de la conectividad producida por el mismo fenómeno, estamos comenzando a cambiar la percepción del tiempo y el conocimiento desde un paradigma lineal e inamovible a otro holístico y constituidos por millares de posibilidades.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
