<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Development on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/personal-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal Development on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/personal-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beating Anxiety: Learn The Hidden Secrets Of Beating Anxiety</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/beating-anxiety-learn-the-hidden-secrets-of-beating-anxiety/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/beating-anxiety-learn-the-hidden-secrets-of-beating-anxiety/</guid>
      <description>Don&#39;t LIVE With Anxiety ... Learn How To Beat It! 
Anxiety Has Horrible Plans For You ... Don&#39;t Go Along With It ... Gain The Tools To Fight Back &amp;amp; WIN!
This Course Give You The Hidden Skills Know Only To A Few ... Learn How To Beat Anxiety ... Don&#39;t Let Anxiety Beat You!
You Are About To Discover…
1) Discover How To Beat Back Anxiety &amp;amp; Worry .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beating Depression: The Hidden Secrets Of Beating Depression</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/beating-depression-the-hidden-secrets-of-beating-depression/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/beating-depression-the-hidden-secrets-of-beating-depression/</guid>
      <description>In This Online Course on Depression You Will Learn How You Can Transform Your LIFE By BEATING DEPRESSION! This Self-Help Course Covers ALL The Major Skills You Need To BEAT DEPRESSION, And Get Your LIFE Back! Depression Is HORRIBLE … And NOBODY Should Have To Live With It. Unfortunately … We Were NEVER Taught HOW To Beat Depression … NOW You WILL Have Those Skills With This One Simple Course!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motivation Mastery: Discover The Secrets Of Motivation</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/motivation-mastery-discover-the-secrets-of-motivation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/motivation-mastery-discover-the-secrets-of-motivation/</guid>
      <description>Motivation Is THE Key Life Skill .... Without it ... You Can&#39;t Get The Slightest Thing Done! How Do The MOST Motivated People Get So Motivated? ... FIND OUT!
Learn The Science Of Motivation ... In Ways That Make It Fast, Simple &amp;amp; Easy!
Get Ready To Discover …
1) What Motivation Is &amp;amp; How To Use It In Powerful Ways
2) Learn About “The Mind Games Of Motivation”
3) Discover How To Eliminate The Things That DE-Motivate You</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Communication-Introduce Yourself With Confidence</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/personal-communication-introduce-yourself-with-confidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/personal-communication-introduce-yourself-with-confidence/</guid>
      <description>Imagine that every time you introduce yourself, you know you are coming across as completely confident, comfortable and memorable. You will never again have to worry about what to say or how you come across.
 How to Introduce Yourself  In this &#34;How to Introduce Yourself&#34; course you will learn how to avoid the awkwardness and tediousness displayed when many people introduce themselves. You will be taught how to appear to be confident, comfortable and relaxed when standing to introduce yourself, and you will know how to say something interesting and memorable to the other people in the room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking for Women</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-for-women/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-for-women/</guid>
      <description>Public Speaking - Imagine that every time you speak, people are in awe of your confidence and actually remember your messages and key ideas. Wouldn&#39;t you love to be able to stand up and speak to any crown, anytime, and know that you are coming across your very best, and that people understand you and remember your messages?  In this Public Speaking for Women course you will learn the following:  *How to speak with confidence  *How to tell stories  *How to avoid the most common Public Speaking blunders that affect both men and women public speakers  *How to get your audience to understand you and remember your messages  This course is delivered primarily through spoken lecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Success Rituals: The Ultimate Path To Success</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/success-rituals-the-ultimate-path-to-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/success-rituals-the-ultimate-path-to-success/</guid>
      <description>In This Success Ritual Online Training Course You Will Learn How To Take Your LIFE &amp;amp; CAREER To The Next Level. This Course Covers ALL The Major Success Rituals You Need To Be Massively Successful … Giving You The Key Tools, Strategies &amp;amp; Techniques You Need Make Your Life &amp;amp; Career Take Off! Learn How To Realize Your FULL Potential!
Learning These Key Success Ritual Skills &amp;amp; Techniques Can Help You Be Massively Successful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Personal Development Course - 22 Courses in 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-personal-development-course-22-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-personal-development-course-22-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>*Update - A 50-Questions Master Quiz has been added! :)
If You Only Buy ONE Course This Year … It GOT To Be This One!
With over 54 hours of video content, 283 lectures, downloadable resources and bonuses - this is one of the most comprehensive personal development courses available! You&#39;ll also get access to:
Lifetime Access to course updates
Fast &amp;amp; Friendly Support in the Q&amp;amp;A section
Udemy Certificate of Completion Ready for Download</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automate your Job-Search with LoopCV in 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/automate-your-job-search-with-loopcv-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/automate-your-job-search-with-loopcv-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the fifth course in Term 2 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Just imagine, how much time do you spend applying to jobs and all you get is a rejection letter after a week or a month&#39;s time?
Let&#39;s get this right as we elaborate on this problem faced by every job-seeker out there.
Do you actually spend a lot of time applying to a job, only to wait for weeks without any kind of positive feedback or response from recruiters and hiring managers?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goal Setting For Success: Plan And Achieve Your Goals</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/goal-setting-for-success-plan-and-achieve-your-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/goal-setting-for-success-plan-and-achieve-your-goals/</guid>
      <description>Are you a student, struggling at setting and achieving your goals?
This goal setting course will quickly allow you to start setting personal and professional goals to boost your success.
If you are a studente you can start seeing a path to the success you hope for: you will be able to develop a goal setting mindset, find out what you want in life and create a concrete action plan to reach your targets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser Focus Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/laser-focus-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 13:24:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/laser-focus-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>We live in an era of information overload. We are bombarded with media, technology, entertainment, and notifications every day. It seems there are hundreds of people and things competing for your attention at any given time.
There is no wonder why in the last few years, our attention spans have become shorter and our ability to focus has decreased.
Not being able to focus can have a negative effect on how successful we are at work and in our personal lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond common sense: A scientific positive parenting course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/beyond-common-sense-a-scientific-positive-parenting-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/beyond-common-sense-a-scientific-positive-parenting-course/</guid>
      <description>Parenting is not easy and children (unfortunately) do not come with a manual. Although parenting advice can be found anywhere, it is often difficult to determine the quality of these parenting tips. This course aims to provide you with high-quality knowledge and skills on positive parenting, fully based on scientific findings.
Gain Science-Based Knowledge and Master Skills to be a Positive Light in Children’s Life
· Learn about Positive Parenting based on the Self-Determination Theory</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First impression hack - cheat based on scientific evidence!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/first-impression-hack-cheat-based-on-scientific-evidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/first-impression-hack-cheat-based-on-scientific-evidence/</guid>
      <description>You’ll never get a second chance to make a great first impression.Summary of the courseIn other words, when you meet someone for the first time, you need to be on top of your game from the very beginning. The key is to build rapport. Rapport is the lubricant for social communication. When rapport is established, communication barriers go down and you will have the opportunity to make a lasting connection. This practice is used actively by the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) to get interviewees to open up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking: A tactical approach</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-a-tactical-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-a-tactical-approach/</guid>
      <description>This course was born from frustration! Frustration that no one seems to be able to do what they’re teaching when it comes to speaking and communication. Everyone is either trying to teach you how to be a motivational speaker or some BS on overcoming your fears. In other words, it’s all self-help. But what does facing your fears and embracing your passion have to do with your regional sales report? Or a meeting with five people?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career Coaching Summary: TOP 5 Secrets of Effcient Sessions</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/career-coaching-summary-top-5-secrets-of-effcient-sessions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/career-coaching-summary-top-5-secrets-of-effcient-sessions/</guid>
      <description>Hello, everyone! Thanks for paying attention to this lection!
Our world today is one that celebrates being busy. Being busy is something that we strive for, despite the feeling of overwhelm - the feeling of having no time like you’re drowning. Surely, being busy is a sign of success?
Well, not necessarily. You can be busy, but be in a job that you hate. One that makes you dread each morning, or you’re sat at your desk each day, bored and unfulfilled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habitually Better: Building habits to be your best self!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/habitually-better-building-habits-to-be-your-best-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/habitually-better-building-habits-to-be-your-best-self/</guid>
      <description>Join the journey to become habitually better!
Pursuing long term goals does not have to be a long shot. It does not have to take an inordinate amount of will power either.
Join the journey to craft a focussed, effortless and satisfying path towards your future.

I have struggled with habit formation, and I empathize with you. Having seen how that powerful habits are and how some people face challenges in utilizing them, I believe that it should be made reachable to everyone and I would like to share this course as a humble guidance to those who are going through a similar journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Become a Facilitator: 7 Effective Skills Summary</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-become-a-facilitator-7-effective-skills-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-become-a-facilitator-7-effective-skills-summary/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever felt like the task of becoming a leader and leading people to success is impossible? Well, it is no secret that the task may seem quite daunting and out of the realms of our possibilities. Well, the beauty of life is that nothing is impossible and with courage and willpower one can overcome their greatest fears and lead people to greatness.
That is one of the main functions of a facilitator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of Memory Summary: 3 Ways of Memorising Like a Spy</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/secrets-of-memory-summary-3-ways-of-memorising-like-a-spy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/secrets-of-memory-summary-3-ways-of-memorising-like-a-spy/</guid>
      <description>Our brain is really stubborn at times. It doesn’t want to remember certain things, it doesn’t want to cope with the fact that you just have to remember certain information. Lucky us – this problem can be solved.
This course is about memory, about memorizing like a spy, so that’s exactly what we are going to do. We are going to learn how to memorize like a spy. Spies have to remember a lot, their life depends on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Success Mindset Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/success-mindset-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/success-mindset-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Most of people spent quite a bit of time thinking about what constitutes success, how they will achieve it, and how good they&#39;ll feel when they achieve their goals.
In this course you will learn 5 key steps that will help you reach your goals and accomplish what you’ve set out to do.
Learn how to nurture a mindset of success to become an unstoppable entrepreneur.

Success Mindset  Course For EVERY Level</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career Change: The 5 Key Skills To Change Your Career</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/career-change-the-5-key-skills-to-change-your-career/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/career-change-the-5-key-skills-to-change-your-career/</guid>
      <description>This is a step by step course on HOW TO CHANGE YOUR CAREER!

Welcome to this 2 hour course that will teach you the five key skills that high achievers use to change their careers!

My name is Paul and I&#39;ll be your instructor. :-) I&#39;m a Career Coach, Finance Director &amp;amp; ex PriceWaterhouseCoopers Consultant.

I guarantee that this course will help you change careers - or your money back, no questions asked!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motivation: You Can Become a Motivational Speaker</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/motivation-you-can-become-a-motivational-speaker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/motivation-you-can-become-a-motivational-speaker/</guid>
      <description>Motivation. Motivational Speaking: You Can Become a Motivational Speaker Imagine yourself speaking on the stage in front of hundreds or thousands of people. Your words are inspiring and motivating your audience to make changes and take positive actions. You can lead from the platform!
How to Be a Motivational Speaker - Motivation
In this &#34;How to be a Motivational Speaker&#34; Motivation course you will learn the fundamentals of how to structure a motivational speech and how to run a motivational speaking business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passions of the soul. Resurrection</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/passions-of-the-soul.-resurrection/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/passions-of-the-soul.-resurrection/</guid>
      <description>Passions make us suffer and can ruin our life.
Create a better understanding of human passions.
Intense feelings of passionate love affect the brain in the same way as drugs like cocaine.
How to transit from passionate love to compassionate?
Gain a deeper insight into chemistry, lust and obsession.
Why is chemistry not the same as compatibility?
Learn about neuroscience of chemistry, lust, love and hatred.
Self-love, self- esteem and self- compassion are the keys for psychological well- being and mental health.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn To Focus: Meditation &amp; Mindfulness For ADHD</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-to-focus-meditation-mindfulness-for-adhd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-to-focus-meditation-mindfulness-for-adhd/</guid>
      <description>ADD and ADHD can make it hard to focus &amp;amp; get things done. You have lots of mental energy (that&#39;s why you&#39;re so smart!) but you have a hard time directing it to one thing at a time. Many people go through their entire lives in this scatter-brained state, jumping from thing to thing, never fully concentrating on, or actually enjoying, anything. This can lead to major school &amp;amp; career problems (not paying attention in class, not paying attention at work, not caring about what you&#39;re working on, bouncing from job to job, career to career, etc), and problems becoming a successful adult.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win at Job Interviews for High Potential Candidates</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/win-at-job-interviews-for-high-potential-candidates/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/win-at-job-interviews-for-high-potential-candidates/</guid>
      <description>In many High Profile, Consultancy, Leadership and Strategic roles, employers are looking not only for High performers but also for candidates who are High Potentials to advance and significantly contribute to an organisation and potentially advance to Senior Executive Leadership roles based on their evidenced Behavioral and Competency skill set. If you want to get on a fast Management or a High Potential training track within top organisations you need to demonstrate how you excel in key areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking: Give a Great Retirement Speech!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-give-a-great-retirement-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-give-a-great-retirement-speech/</guid>
      <description>Public Speaking: you can go out with a bang by delivering a fantastic retirement speech. Imagine giving your retirement speech and every one of your colleagues feels as though you are personally speaking to them and thanking them in a meaningful way. Wouldn&#39;t it be nice to end your career on a high note by giving a retirement speech where you hit all the right notes?  In this How to Give a Retirement Speech Public Speaking course you will learn the following:  *How to give a great retirement speech  *How to plan stories for your speech  *How to practice your speech on video  *How to use the right amount of emotion and retain composure  This public speaking course is delivered primarily through spoken lecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Psychology for Stress and Leadership</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/advanced-psychology-for-stress-and-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/advanced-psychology-for-stress-and-leadership/</guid>
      <description>This isn&#39;t a managing program, it&#39;s psychology. It&#39;s about YOU. Your thoughts, blocks, obstacles, stressors, and how they affect you and the people you care for. Within every craft there is always a mental side of performance, and leadership is not different.
There are many ways stress can be viewed in our normal day-to-day struggle, but I’ll do my best to try not to treat it like a superficial topic, and while I wrote this with the intention of it being clear and practical, this is not a how-to guide or a tutorial on deep breathing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Win at Job Interviews for Recent Graduates</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/win-at-job-interviews-for-recent-graduates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/win-at-job-interviews-for-recent-graduates/</guid>
      <description>This course is for anyone wanting to do better at Job interviews and successfully get a Job offer in the career you want!
This course is not just about getting any job, its about getting the job that will set you firmly on your career path with your ideal brand name and chosen professional direction.
Ideal for Recent Graduates and people with relatively little professional working experience.
Fulfilling your career ambitions is a daily mission, and Winning at critical job interviews for that job you want is just the start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Couples Counseling | Learn to Live happy with Life Partner</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/couples-counseling-learn-to-live-happy-with-life-partner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/couples-counseling-learn-to-live-happy-with-life-partner/</guid>
      <description>Happy Couple Relationship is basic ambition of Life Partners, however this relationship is very sensitive and needs extra attention from Life Partners to make the relationship happy and smooth.
Couples who do not give proper attention for effective management of Marriage Relationship are likely to go into deep conflicts which may result into divorce.
This Couples Counseling course is designed for those Couples who have been facing difficulty in maintaining the healthy relationship with life partners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rational Thinking</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/rational-thinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/rational-thinking/</guid>
      <description>The way you think influences the way you feel and behave. Irrational thoughts will lead to emotional distress and behavioral problems. Rational thoughts will help you experience positive emotions or negative, yet adaptive emotions. We all experience both types of thoughts - rational and irrational. But few know how to identify and separate them, so often they rule our life. Learn how to identify your irrational thinking patterns and make them more rational, through rational emotive behavior therapy (REBT).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goal Setting Mastery</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/goal-setting-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/goal-setting-mastery/</guid>
      <description>Setting Goals are paramount if you want to achieve true success in life. This course gives you the Step by Step plan to * Set and reach your Goals and thus achieve Success in your Life. * Multiply your Productivity.
* Stay Focused and get Results.
* Visualize your Goals.
* Review and Reflect your Goals.
* Be more accountable towards your Goals.
* Develop Winning Habits.
* Handle Obstacles during the process of reaching your Goals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy IBS Relief with EFT - Tapping Therapy</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/easy-ibs-relief-with-eft-tapping-therapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/easy-ibs-relief-with-eft-tapping-therapy/</guid>
      <description>If you have been suffering from IBS this is the course to help you beat that feeling of helplessness with a easy to learn and apply technique that I will teach and guide you through each exercise so that you will be able to change how you think and feel and become a more relaxed person in all areas of your life. The technique I will be teaching you is called EFT (Emotional Freedom Technique) it is a gentle tapping technique where when you tap on certain points on the body while thinking about a problem you reduce or eliminate the bad feelings attached to that problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innovation &amp; Personality</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/innovation-personality/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/innovation-personality/</guid>
      <description>Learn more how to identify, evaluate and motivate innovative people to boost innovation in your organization.
Discover how to boost your own individual innovativeness.
Explore the innovator’s persona. 
It might be challenging to identify whether a person is an innovator or not. However, several personality traits are closely related to the innovative personality.
Innovative people usually express a strong desire for autonomy, are imaginative, curious, energetic, and confident. They are open to new experiences having flexible mindset and propensity to successfully generate ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goal Settings Mastery - Win At The Game Of Life!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/goal-settings-mastery-win-at-the-game-of-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/goal-settings-mastery-win-at-the-game-of-life/</guid>
      <description>Goal Setting Skill Separates The WINNERS From The LOSERS! It&#39;s That Simple!
This Goal Setting Course is Designed To Transform Your Life! We Want You To Have The Power Skills Needed To Transform ANY Area Of Your Life!
Goal Setting Is Especially Important If You Are In Business ... It Is The Difference Between Success &amp;amp; Failure! Are YOU Trained In Goal Setting? Is Your STAFF?
QUESTION: &#34;How Can You Get Ahead In Life If You Are Not Good At Goal Setting?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Survive Purim with Sanity with Your ADHD Child</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-survive-purim-with-sanity-with-your-adhd-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-survive-purim-with-sanity-with-your-adhd-child/</guid>
      <description>The Jewish calendar is full of beautiful Festivals, full of meaning. If you have an ADHD child, the Festival of Purim can be a nightmare. When Purim is over, does your home feel like a hurricane has just passed, leaving destruction in it&#39;s wake? Does the excitement turn your ADHD child upside down? Does it take you weeks to get yourself, your ADHD child and your house back in some semblance of order?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peak Productivity Hacks – Triple Your Productivity</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/peak-productivity-hacks-triple-your-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/peak-productivity-hacks-triple-your-productivity/</guid>
      <description>In this Peak Productivity course you will learn how the pros teach people how to maximize productivity. Get more done with the same hours you have and create more time and freedom for things that matter most!
Do you sometimes spend hours or even the entire day at your work desk, but can’t seem to get much done? Do you wish to be more productive for your time? Here’s the GOOD NEWS … There is a simple FORMULA to put an end to procrastination and get more done in less time … And we will share it with you in this course!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation Skills: Give a Great Acceptance Speech</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/presentation-skills-give-a-great-acceptance-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 10:00:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/presentation-skills-give-a-great-acceptance-speech/</guid>
      <description>Presentation Skills for any occasion. Imagine giving an acceptance speech in front of the people you respect the most (or perhaps the whole world) and you are brief, funny, thoughtful and insightful. Wouldn&#39;t it be great if you could leave a fantastic impression on people during your brief acceptance speech?  In this How to Give an Acceptance Speech - Presentation Skills course you will learn the following:  *How to say thanks in a genuine and memorable way  *How to avoid the most common blunders made by award winners  *How to appear poised and relaxed  *How to rehearse on video *How to master Presentation Skills</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ADHD Mums! Focus Your Morning &amp; Evenings For Your ADHD Child</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/adhd-mums-focus-your-morning-evenings-for-your-adhd-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/adhd-mums-focus-your-morning-evenings-for-your-adhd-child/</guid>
      <description>If you are a mum of an ADHD child, you must have realised by now that the traditional parenting methods don&#39;t work at best, or backfire at worst.
If you have an ADHD child, normal, regular household rules are almost impossible to create and maintain. Your success at parenting your ADHD child will largely depend on the severity of your ADHD child&#39;s symptoms, whether they have a comorbid condition, and most importantly how well you are managing your ADHD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EFT Your Dentist</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/eft-your-dentist/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/eft-your-dentist/</guid>
      <description>It is estimated that nearly seventy five percent of adults in the United States experience some amount of fear with regarding going to the dentist. Of that percentage, about five to ten percent of those people have a strong enough fear to be considered sufferers of a dental phobia. If you are one of those people you are in the right place.
I am going to take you through a complementary and alternative method known as Emotional Freedom Techniques or EFT/tapping for short.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Song Tantra - Songwriting from the Soul!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-song-tantra-songwriting-from-the-soul/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-song-tantra-songwriting-from-the-soul/</guid>
      <description>In this course I teach you a special vocal technique that opens the voice and creative flow! My technique connects you to the creative energy from your soul, so you can create beautiful music that will entrance audiences to you and your music. 
I have personally have studied singing and sung professionally for over 20 years, graduated cum la mentored with pro- songwriters who write for celebrities and learn their songwriting techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management Techniques 101: The Beginner&#39;s Guide</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/time-management-techniques-101-the-beginners-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/time-management-techniques-101-the-beginners-guide/</guid>
      <description>Planning your day does not necessarily mean filling out all your available hours with tasks and ending up working all day. Working non-stop all day will end up burning you out and you will end up not finishing and getting behind your schedule instead
Finding the right moment for your different priorities you will find that you can accomplish more with less time.
The goal of this course is you are going to be more effective and efficiency by getting things done with less time so that you have time to do things you enjoy doing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/time-management-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 11:41:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/time-management-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>No matter what business or industry you’re involved in, learning how to effectively manage your time is one of the most important skills that will set you on the path towards ongoing success.
This course will help you get more done in less time by levelling up your productivity score quickly and easily.
The strategies contained in this guide are designed to help you learn to value your time, make informed decisions about the kind of work you’re focused on and ultimately, beat the clock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Manipulation Works</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-manipulation-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-manipulation-works/</guid>
      <description>A MATTER OF MANIPULATION
Manipulation is, no doubt, dangerous in the world of today.
It&#39;s important to be able to identify it so that you can stop it in its tracks.
You can be manipulated:
At work, by your manager or coworkers;
In business relationships, by partners or suppliers;
In relationships or friendships, through emotion or even bullying;
By politicians, the media or others, with false numbers;
By any type of person that wants to drive you to a specific type of action;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hörbuchsprecher werden - Hörbuch Aufnahme,Marketingstrategie</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/h%C3%B6rbuchsprecher-werden-h%C3%B6rbuch-aufnahmemarketingstrategie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/h%C3%B6rbuchsprecher-werden-h%C3%B6rbuch-aufnahmemarketingstrategie/</guid>
      <description>Ein neuer, digitaler Berufszweig ist entstanden. Das #Hörbuch #Hörbücher sind in aller Ohren. Ob auf Streaming-Plattformen, für Fachbücher, Belletristik-Bestseller oder im Homeoffice-Lernbereich. Hast Du Dich auch schonmal gefragt, ob auch Du mit Deiner Stimme als Hörbuchsprecherin /Hörbuchsprecher Menschen begeistern kannst? Findest Du Synchronstimmen auf Netflix, in Hollywood-Filmen und Co. auch so sexy? Hast Du Dich einmal gefragt, wie und wieviel Geld man auf diese Art und Weise verdienen kann?
Wie sieht das Hörbuchsprecher-Dasein ist der Praxis aus?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview Essentials</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/interview-essentials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/interview-essentials/</guid>
      <description>This course provides insights and best practices to help enhance your skills to land an entry-level or mid-level job. Here are some of the topics covered in this course:
Interview skills: learn key skills you need to have to do well in an interview.
Job application: learn best practices to use when filling out job applications.
Resume: learn some quick tips to help you put together a professional resume.
Your internet presence: learn how to present yourself online to ensure you don’t scare off potential employers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cultivating Gratitude with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cultivating-gratitude-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:50:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cultivating-gratitude-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>Here&#39;s what you&#39;ll discover inside of this life-changing online course with MRS JOY:

Learn that gratitude is a state of being.
Learn how to use gratitude in your relationships to develop a deeper connection.
Learn how the power of positive emotions and gratitude can change your life.
Discover how practicing mindfulness and meditation can cultivate an attitude of gratitude.
Discover what unbalanced gratitude is and how you can counteract it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neuroplasticity: Teach Your Brain  To Work 3 Times Faster</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/neuroplasticity-teach-your-brain-to-work-3-times-faster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:50:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/neuroplasticity-teach-your-brain-to-work-3-times-faster/</guid>
      <description>If you have never imagined what living life on autopilot is, this may be because you are going all autopilot and not realizing it. Being conscious about our lives is the least we can do to actually live the better life.
So, what does neuroplasticity have to do with it? Pretty easy. Neuroplasticity helps our brain to get out of the ‘comfort zone’, of sorts. It helps us learn new things, thus expanding our brain broad and wide for everything new the world can offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nomad Lifestyle: LIVE YOUR DREAM &amp; Travel the World</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-nomad-lifestyle-live-your-dream-travel-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:47:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-nomad-lifestyle-live-your-dream-travel-the-world/</guid>
      <description>IS IT POSSIBLE TO LIVE YOUR DREAM LIFE WITHOUT WORKING SO HARD? DOES IT HAVE TO TAKE SO MUCH EFFORT, STRESS, AND ENERGY TO HAVE A LIFE THAT DEEPLY FULFILS YOU? HONOR AND TRUST YOUR PROCESS, AND SURRENDER TO THE MAGIC OF LIFE!!! BEING A DIGITAL NOMAD MEANS LIVING LIFE 100% ON YOUR OWN TERMS!!!
From leaving behind the corporate life of a consistent and often capped salary, saying goodbye to cubicles, a regular work commute and the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Timers Guide to Approach A Girl - Basic Do&#39;s &amp; Don&#39;ts</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/first-timers-guide-to-approach-a-girl-basic-dos-donts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:47:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/first-timers-guide-to-approach-a-girl-basic-dos-donts/</guid>
      <description>If you want to start conversations with girls in different environments, get their phone numbers or add them on Instagram/Facebook/Snapchat, and begin dating them, then this is the course for you.
This course focuses on the basic question every guy has to get things going for him with a girl; be it the start of a friendship or the first step to a blossoming relationship; in different scenarios from parties to your empty high school corridors; and the different types of girls, be it shy or the obnoxious kind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>This course was designed to show even absolute beginners how to become more confident when speaking in public. It includes 5 preformatted lessons packed with easy to understand information.

Discover how to be more confident when speaking in public!
Do you know what one of the easiest ways to become a successful public speaker is? Well it is really easy and that is to study other successful speakers.
Why not learn from the best?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solve Problems by Rising above Problems For New Perspective</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/solve-problems-by-rising-above-problems-for-new-perspective/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/solve-problems-by-rising-above-problems-for-new-perspective/</guid>
      <description>Solve Problems by Rising above Problems for New Perspective
5 Star Review
GREAT little course on how to overcome your fears, anxiety, stress, problems by using your imagination with self-hypnosis and/or EFT tapping.
Ivon Timmermans
Learn how you can easily change your perspective of old experiences that have clouded how you see the world and people in it. Because not everyone has the same life experiences that hold them back, but it is those past experiences that have created who you are today because of your perspective of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Steps To Permanent Happiness</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/10-steps-to-permanent-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/10-steps-to-permanent-happiness/</guid>
      <description>This is a lifetime journey that we will take together. I will be your teacher, guide, psychologist, motivator and friend.
To be truly happy we need to learn and understand why we are unhappy, what is happiness and how we can achieve it. We have different types of happiness, but here we are going to be focused on permanent happiness.
For permanent happiness, we have to make changes in our minds and soul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NLP - Beginner Level - Personal Growth Mastery</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/nlp-beginner-level-personal-growth-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/nlp-beginner-level-personal-growth-mastery/</guid>
      <description>What is NLP?
NLP (Neuro Linguistic Programming) is &#39;the science &amp;amp; art of human excellence&#39;.
NLP is a simple, easy to learn, yet powerful methodology for studying what goes on inside you. How you think, feel &amp;amp; act in different situations in your life.
NLP provides you with the keys to change your thinking processes to effect lasting positive change in your life.
With NLP , you can change &#39;how&#39; you think about anything &amp;amp; transform your fears into strengths, overcome your limitations, change bad habits, get rid of phobias .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness for Parents with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/mindfulness-for-parents-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/mindfulness-for-parents-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>Mindfulness For Parents is designed to support you to discover:

-What is Mindfulness and how it can help you and your family
-The 3 Pillars of Mindfulness
-How to bring Mindfulness into your daily activities
-How to practice Mindfulness with your child – or kids, if you have more than one
- How to develop more concentration
- How to increase kindness, self-compassion and wellbeing to your life and in the lives of the ones you love and care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of Mindfulness</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-mindfulness/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:43:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-mindfulness/</guid>
      <description>We are so busy in our everyday lives that we rarely stop to think and be aware of our surroundings. However, this is harmful, as it prevents us from being more calm - both in terms of relaxing our body, but also quieting the internal chatter in our minds.
In this course, you are going to learn more about the fundamentals of mindfulness and its components. Elements such as presence, awareness, self-acceptance and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness for Executives</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/mindfulness-for-executives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:43:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/mindfulness-for-executives/</guid>
      <description>Do you wish you could be less stressed and more present?
We are so busy in our everyday lives that we rarely stop to think and be aware of our surroundings. However, this is harmful, as it prevents us from being more calm - both in terms of relaxing our body, but also quieting the internal chatter in our minds.
Especially as an executive, being present and aware is crucial, because it&#39;s reflected on the presentations you give, on how &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness for Busy People</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/mindfulness-for-busy-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:43:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/mindfulness-for-busy-people/</guid>
      <description>Do you wish you could be less stressed and more present?
We are so busy in our everyday lives that we rarely stop to think and be aware of our surroundings. However, this is harmful, as it prevents us from being more calm - both in terms of relaxing our body, but also quieting the internal chatter in our minds.
Especially as a busy person, that runs from one task to another, it&#39;s easy to never stop and relax, which can make you more stressed or anxious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Australian Citizenship Test  The Dream</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-australian-citizenship-test-the-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-australian-citizenship-test-the-dream/</guid>
      <description>Welcome ! 
 get Ready for Certificate of Australian Citizenship CAC
Get ready to say &#34;I am Australian.&#34;
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily

2021 Australian Citizenship Test
Congratulations on choosing to become an Australian citizen. It takes courage, endeavor and commitmentto live in a new country and participate fully as a citizen. We value your contribution to our peaceful anddemocratic society. Australian citizenship is an important step in your migration story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flexible Laundry Systems for the Creative ADHD  Business Mum</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/flexible-laundry-systems-for-the-creative-adhd-business-mum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/flexible-laundry-systems-for-the-creative-adhd-business-mum/</guid>
      <description>WHO I AM AND WHY I AM EQUIPPED TO GUIDE YOU
I have ADHD. I am a mum of 5 successful ADHD children.
Throughout my life I have had my share of challenges and struggles related to ADHD. I have searched long and hard for the tools to unlock my ADHD. Searching for those answers has been one of the most difficult tasks of my life. I have found those answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to find first Job in certain fields/ Common tips</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-find-first-job-in-certain-fields/-common-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-find-first-job-in-certain-fields/-common-tips/</guid>
      <description>The goal of hiring managers is not just to hire people who need a job. It’s to hire people who believe in their organization, its mission and the work that’s involved in the job position. Every hiring manager knows: Hire people to do a job and they’ll work for your money. Hire people who believe in the work and they’ll work for their passion.

And this is not a case of “fake it until you make it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Management And Goal Planning: The Productivity Combo</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/time-management-and-goal-planning-the-productivity-combo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/time-management-and-goal-planning-the-productivity-combo/</guid>
      <description>What about setting 48-Hour Productivity from a 24-hour day? So many things, so little time, right? Wrong!
Time management is all about working SMARTER, not harder!
Time management, focus and motivation are the basis for planning and achieving our goals and being more productive. Distraction turns seemingly busy days into wasted time, producing a negative impact on our productivity.
This course will show you the best time management and goal planning strategies to focus on what really matters, prioritizing those actions that lead to the achievement of our short and long term goals in order to fulfill your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resilience Masterclass: Build a Refugee Mindset for Survival</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/resilience-masterclass-build-a-refugee-mindset-for-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/resilience-masterclass-build-a-refugee-mindset-for-survival/</guid>
      <description>Resilience Masterclass: Build a Refuge Mindset for Survival to Thrival
The Resilience Mindset- Survival Tips for the Worst Time of Your Life - For Refugees &amp;amp; Those Who Want Survival Skills
Refugees are persons who are outside their country of origin for reasons of feared persecution, conflict, generalized violence, or other circumstances that have seriously disturbed public order and, as a result, require international protection. This is what I experience. I will help you to prepare and get ready mentally and physically to travel and be a successful refugee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Charisma Guide for Men:Increase Your Influence</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-ultimate-charisma-guide-for-menincrease-your-influence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-ultimate-charisma-guide-for-menincrease-your-influence/</guid>
      <description>It was 2005 and I was fed up with always being Mr. Nice Guy. It was then clear to me the nicer I was the more people would take advantage of me! So I decided to learn how to stop all this mess, to learn from my experience, from the behavior of bigger men than me, and to extensively research how to become more charismatic! So I opened my eyes, ears, and mind to everything around me in all areas of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total Confidence: The Pillars Of Unshakeable Confidence</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/total-confidence-the-pillars-of-unshakeable-confidence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/total-confidence-the-pillars-of-unshakeable-confidence/</guid>
      <description>In This Online Video Self-Confidence Training Course You Will Learn Easy Ways To Build Your Confidence. Discover How Successful People Create Greater Confidence Fast! Self-Confidence Is The Master Skill To Success. Having These Self-Confidence Tools &amp;amp; Strategies Will Make Your Life So Much Easier, Dramatically Increase The Results You Get &amp;amp; Help You Achieve Your Goals In Less Time.
This Course Will Give You The Hidden Secrets Of Self-Confidence In The Following Areas: 1) Learn Secret Language Of Confident People 2) Learn The Steps To Building Unshakeable Confidence 3) Discover How To Bounce Back From Failure 4) Specific Tips &amp;amp; Practices For Unshakeable Confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principles Of Success – Growth Mindset</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/principles-of-success-growth-mindset/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 10:48:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/principles-of-success-growth-mindset/</guid>
      <description>In this online “Principles Of Success” training course you will learn how the pros teach people how to be Massively Successful and Develop a Growth Mindset. This Success course is based on scientific research &amp;amp; principles that are known to get results fast! Having these tools &amp;amp; strategies will make becoming successful so much easier, dramatically increase the results you get &amp;amp; help you achieve your goals in far less time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Put a Dead-Halt Stop to Self-Sabotage and Get Motivated</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/put-a-dead-halt-stop-to-self-sabotage-and-get-motivated/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 10:48:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/put-a-dead-halt-stop-to-self-sabotage-and-get-motivated/</guid>
      <description>Are you a lifelong student of personal development of transformation?
Do you need help with motivation, stress management, or productivity?
If you said &#34;yes&#34; to any of those, a MindMastery course is right for you.
Specifically, students who take our Put a Dead-Halt Stop to Self-Sabotage and Get Motivated course experience these roadblocks:
Self-sabotage
Procrastination and bad habits
A lack of motivation
And they report these benefits from the MindMastery experience:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Creative Way to Declutter and Organise with Your ADHD</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-creative-way-to-declutter-and-organise-with-your-adhd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-creative-way-to-declutter-and-organise-with-your-adhd/</guid>
      <description>Are you a woman with ADHD or ADHD tendencies? Are you a busy professional mum, struggling to balance your life and the life of your ADHD child? Only you know of the dark side lurking behind your front door. The clutter, the mess and general chaos. I know, because I have ADHD myself. I have struggled mightily for many years to find systems that work for my brain. I searched high and low.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>İş ve Özel Yaşamda Alışkanlıkları Yönetmenin Sırları</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/i%C5%9F-ve-%C3%B6zel-ya%C5%9Famda-al%C4%B1%C5%9Fkanl%C4%B1klar%C4%B1-y%C3%B6netmenin-s%C4%B1rlar%C4%B1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 22:23:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/i%C5%9F-ve-%C3%B6zel-ya%C5%9Famda-al%C4%B1%C5%9Fkanl%C4%B1klar%C4%B1-y%C3%B6netmenin-s%C4%B1rlar%C4%B1/</guid>
      <description>Alışkanlık, otomatikleşecek kadar çok tekrarlanmış davranıştır. Davranışlar duygulara, duygular ise kimliğinize bağlıdır. Altıncı his diye de ifade edebileceğimiz otomatik alışkanlıkları yaparken farketmeyiz bile. İçgüdülerimiz tarafından yönetildiğini düşündüğümüz bu alışkanlıklar aslında beynimizin ve vücudumuzun hiç düşünmediği alışkanlıklardır. İyi alışkanlıkları güçlendirerek, bunun duygu ve düşüncelerinize katkısını görebilirsiniz. Küçük değişimler ile büyük farklar yaratılabilir.
Alışkanlıkların nasıl oluştuğunu öğrenmek değiştirmek ve geliştirmek için önemlidir. 21 günde yapılan alışkanlık olur dense de konu bu kadar basite indirgenemez.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reinvent Your Life: Master Life Transformation Techniques</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/reinvent-your-life-master-life-transformation-techniques/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 20:22:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/reinvent-your-life-master-life-transformation-techniques/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you will learn the Life Transformation Techniques for personal Development, Personal Transformation, and Finding Your Life Purpose. In just 10-minutes a day, The Personal Life Transformation Masterclass will help revolutionize your life by improving your mindset, goals, and personal and professional productivity. You&#39;ll unlock the potential concentration, confidence, and optimism you need to start moving forward again and again. Once you&#39;ve mastered mentioned areas completely, you&#39;ll feel unstoppable and have total belief in your ability to achieve incredible results with ease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comunicazione: come gestirla in maniera efficace</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/comunicazione-come-gestirla-in-maniera-efficace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/comunicazione-come-gestirla-in-maniera-efficace/</guid>
      <description>In questo corso ti spiegherò nei minimi dettagli come poter superare le difficoltà del parlare in pubblico e rendere più incisivo il tuo modo di Comunicare.  Esporrò tecniche precise e dettagliate, ti darò consigli teorici e pratici per far sì che tu possa padroneggiare nel migliore dei modi la Voce(intesa come Contenuto e Comunicazione Para-Verbale) ed il linguaggio del corpo (Comunicazione Non Verbale) spiegandoti l&#39;importanza del tenere viva l&#39;attenzione dall&#39;esordio alla conclusione di un discorso.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art of stress free Productivity -Plan &amp; Execute Effectively</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/art-of-stress-free-productivity-plan-execute-effectively/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/art-of-stress-free-productivity-plan-execute-effectively/</guid>
      <description>Objectives: Research shows that a large number of professionals fail to execute their action plan successfully. The problem often isn’t with planning but with executing the planning. It is very important to take a well-structured approach to implement and execute what is planned.
The Art of Being Productive: Planning &amp;amp; Effective Execution is an online course, that will help professionals to overcome their most challenging execution obstacles on a working day and execute their tasks effectively to achieve better results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Over a Break up</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-get-over-a-break-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-get-over-a-break-up/</guid>
      <description>Breakups blow chunks. Whether it’s an amicable breakup or a horrible, crash-and-burn situation, you’ve invested a part of you into another person and must accept that a relationship that you once nurtured is dead and gone. Brain-mapping studies have shown that the same regions of the brain are activated when an addict is going through withdrawals as when someone is going through a breakup.
Whether the relationship lasted three weeks or three years, breakups can leave us feeling heartbroken, lost and even physically ill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Letter For Myself: Self-Affirmations with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/a-letter-for-myself-self-affirmations-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/a-letter-for-myself-self-affirmations-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>A Letter For Myself: 56 Days To Reprogram Your Subconscious Mind For A Healthy &amp;amp; Loving Relationship is developed to increase your love for yourself and for your partner or even for your future partner, if you don&#39;t have one yet.

“A Letter For Myself” is a self-development audio course from MRS JOY’s Academy, where you will find special narrations of MRS JOY, as you are talking with yourself. They help you to reprogram your subconscious mind and imprint the life you love to live.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern Job Interview Preparation, Tips &amp; Tricks Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/modern-job-interview-preparation-tips-tricks-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/modern-job-interview-preparation-tips-tricks-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Modern businesses are hiring for culture, not just skills. Having a spot-on resume and cover letter is necessary, but it’s only the one third of the battle. Who you are as a person is just as important to your next employer as what you can do for them.
Most of us have been taught a specific traditional method for job interviewing. Once we learn the traditional method, it can be hard to change our approach!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Common Job Interview Questions with Answer</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/most-common-job-interview-questions-with-answer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/most-common-job-interview-questions-with-answer/</guid>
      <description>(The course content has updated according to students&#39; interest on 16th August 2019)
‘Why did you leave your last job?’ ‘What are your weaknesses?’ ‘If you were a type of fruit, what would you be, and why?’
OK, so some interview questions are easier to answer than others. But whilst you can’t predict exactly what you’ll be asked, any question has the potential to make you stumble – unless, of course, you’ve prepared in advance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Become a Firefighter!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-become-a-firefighter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:42:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-become-a-firefighter/</guid>
      <description>Learn how a career as a firefighter can provide you with financial stability, allowing you to give back to your community and make you excited to come to work. Firefighting is a rewarding career that offers great opportunity for growth and advancement, amazing medical benefits and a high level of job satisfaction. This course will teach you how to prepare for your new career full of thrills and excitement while helping your community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intelligence quotient IQ Test Questions and Answers</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/intelligence-quotient-iq-test-questions-and-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 20:12:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/intelligence-quotient-iq-test-questions-and-answers/</guid>
      <description>TEST YOUR INTELLGENCE 
Intelligence quotient IQ Test Questions and Answers
2021 Measure students, employees, humans, scientists and child&#39;s intelligence, PSYCHOMETRIC and Personality

An intelligence quotient (IQ) is a total score derived from a set of standardized tests or subtests designed to assess human intelligence. The abbreviation &#34;IQ&#34; was coined by the psychologist William Stern for the German term Intelligenzquotient, his term for a scoring method for intelligence tests at University of Breslau he advocated in a 1912 book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effective Time Management Skills For A Productivity Boost</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/effective-time-management-skills-for-a-productivity-boost/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 11:42:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/effective-time-management-skills-for-a-productivity-boost/</guid>
      <description>This course approaches time management from 3 unique angles:
Time management in a single day
Time management in a week
Time management in your life to make sure that the tasks you work on are the right ones for your overall life direction, because if you are working on the wrong tasks, then all that time is mismanaged and wasted
Try this course and its unique approach which ends at you looking at the bigger picture of your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Confidence Building Course - Exude Confidence Now</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-confidence-building-course-exude-confidence-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-confidence-building-course-exude-confidence-now/</guid>
      <description>Complete Confidence Building Course - Exude Confidence NowBuild Your Confidence - Increase Self-Esteem - Radiate More Confidence - Become a Truly Confident Person - Communication
Imagine going through life filled with confidence. You are confident in your abilities, your talents, your communication skills, your appearance and in having an accurate sense of how others perceive you. and other people judge you as supremely confident (though not cocky or arrogant!)
Confidence is not something you are born with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beat Procrastination in Turbulent Covid Era</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/beat-procrastination-in-turbulent-covid-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 17:46:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/beat-procrastination-in-turbulent-covid-era/</guid>
      <description>Procrastination is one of the principle boundaries obstructing you from getting up, settling on the correct choices, and carrying on with the fantasy life you&#39;ve considered.

Ongoing investigations have shown that individuals regret more the things they haven&#39;t done than the things they have done. Furthermore, sensations of disappointment and blame coming about because of botched freedoms will in general remain with individuals any longer.

Some of the time every one of our chances appear to be on our fingertips, however we can&#39;t contact them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-Discipline: Build Habits &amp; Develop a Growth Mindset</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/self-discipline-build-habits-develop-a-growth-mindset/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:28:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/self-discipline-build-habits-develop-a-growth-mindset/</guid>
      <description>Join our students who have taken our time management, goal setting and focus mastery courses with great results!
This course will teach you why and how to develop self-discipline, increase your motivation and stop procrastinating, empowering you to build daily habits for long-term success.
Whether you are a student, employee or entrepreneur, you will need to get your job done and, possibly, do it in the best possible way.
In fact, we have all faced the frustration of a job we don&#39;t like or a task we find difficult to complete, or a passion we have to fight for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Educa ed Allena la tua Voce</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/educa-ed-allena-la-tua-voce/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:15:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/educa-ed-allena-la-tua-voce/</guid>
      <description>Hai problemi nel farti comprendere senza dover ripetere?
Ti senti insicuro dei tuoi mezzi di parola e voce? Parli col timore di non esser capito?
Quando comunichi hai problemi nel far comprendere pensieri ed emozioni?
Vorresti avere una migliore articolazione ?

Bene! Sei proprio nell&#39;aula virtuale giusta!
In questo corso troverai un approccio all&#39;utilizzo e allo sviluppo della voce del tuto differente da quello classico che muove le prime mosse da esercizi sulla vocalizzazione, sicuro fondamentali ma solo dopo aver acquisito piena conoscenza degli organi addetti alla fonazione.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Freedom: From PAIN To POWER</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/mental-freedom-from-pain-to-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/mental-freedom-from-pain-to-power/</guid>
      <description>Isn&#39;t It Bizarre That You Were Never Trained In How To Control &amp;amp; Get The Best From Your Own Mind? That Is INSANE! Yet That Is The Hand Everybody Is Dealt! Inside This Course You Will Learn The Secrets Of Psychology That Will Give You The Mental &amp;amp; Emotional Control You Always Wanted!
You Are About To Discover:
1) Discover The Secret Of How To SOLVE Problems ... Rather Than Live With Them</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Career Coaching Course - Career Development</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-career-coaching-course-career-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-career-coaching-course-career-development/</guid>
      <description>Coaching is a $3 billion a year global business that&#39;s growing at rate of 7% annually. And one of the most important segments in this accelerating industry of career coaching where the median rate is $500 per hour. Tens of millions of people either want a new job, change their fields, or substantially improve their performance at their current occupation. We&#39;re going to give you the skills to help your clients reach success in both their personal and professional lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to be a good PR</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-be-a-good-pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-be-a-good-pr/</guid>
      <description>This course is presented by me: Alhassan Ahmed younes Ahmed a good PR in many teams. You will gain a lot of knowledge from my experience in this committee. You will learn how to pass any interview in this field, how to complete any form in registering in any team.

You will learn all of the information of this topic in student activities.

You will learn how to make deals from zero to hero, and I will help you with some important contact numbers of some people are very famous around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning to Religion to reduce STRESS</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/turning-to-religion-to-reduce-stress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/turning-to-religion-to-reduce-stress/</guid>
      <description>Notice: Please do NOT enrol on this course on impulse, thinking you might watch it later. Maybe show an interest on impulse, yes, but before you enrol, watch the Preview videos, read the Course Description and then make a decision. If you then enrol then please start the course as soon as possible. Watch the lectures, look at the workbooks and join in the discussions. Joining my courses is a serious business and I want you to get the most out of your study – but I also want you to enjoy the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fully Accredited Professional EFT Tapping Certification</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fully-accredited-professional-eft-tapping-certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fully-accredited-professional-eft-tapping-certification/</guid>
      <description>This IAOTH, UK accredited EFT Tapping certification is a masterclass that will enable you to help an endless number of people (including yourself).
This concise programme is designed, keeping in mind that you may not have any prior knowledge about Art Therapy, and you want to learn despite your busy schedule. So we have tried to avoid jargon as much as possible and simplified concepts and terminology for you. for EFT is found extremely useful for a wide range of conditions/situations e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stress Management - For Relief From Stress of Life &amp; Work</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/stress-management-for-relief-from-stress-of-life-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/stress-management-for-relief-from-stress-of-life-work/</guid>
      <description>Stress Management: Stress can weigh you down until you can hardly think straight! Beat it Today with this Comprehensive Stress Management Course filled with Cutting-Edge Tools &amp;amp; Strategies - Feel better TODAY! Created by Master Therapist &amp;amp; Multiple Award-Winning Educator Prof. Paul J. Cline Ed.D ... Get His 35+ years of Expertise in Helping others Beat Stress ... Condensed down into this Training.
Here Are Just A Few Of the Skills You Will Gain:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness para desarrollar la inteligencia emocional</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/mindfulness-para-desarrollar-la-inteligencia-emocional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/mindfulness-para-desarrollar-la-inteligencia-emocional/</guid>
      <description>Te enseño herramientas efectivas y sencillas de aplicar en tu rutina diaria, invirtiendo sólo entre 5 a 15 minutos al día tus emociones no serán más un obstáculo en la consecución de tus metas, tampoco volverás a sentir la culpa o vergüenza de tus impulsos y reacciones emocionales. 
Tu también puedes gozar de relaciones empáticas, satisfactorias y sin tantas fricciones. Poder solucionar de manera asertiva y consciente las diferencias con tus seres queridos, colegas, clientes y colaboradores es posible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Repair - Auto Repair &amp; Tuning - Auto Technician Training</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/car-repair-auto-repair-tuning-auto-technician-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/car-repair-auto-repair-tuning-auto-technician-training/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
One of the things that I find most interesting about automotive technology is how it advances and changes. It is also interesting that ideas from many years ago often return to favour. In this course I have therefore concentrated on core technologies, in other words how the technology works, rather than giving too many examples from specific vehicles. However, I have included some examples of Formula 1 technology, arguably the pinnacle of automotive engineering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Master Your Origin Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-master-your-origin-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-master-your-origin-challenge/</guid>
      <description>This course includes:
1 hours of on-demand video instruction
7 video sections
Over 30 downloadable exercises &amp;amp; resources
Downloadable book chapter
Full lifetime access
Access on mobile and TV
Certificate of completion

What you’ll learn:
Learn who and what you are and why.
Discover the “origin programming” done by your parents, etc. during your first 18 years of life.
Identify which of your traits and relationship characteristics come from your origin programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Stop Fear Spiritually</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-stop-fear-spiritually/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-stop-fear-spiritually/</guid>
      <description>Do you still allow fear to stop you from taking developmental steps?
If you have struggled to put that business idea that has been in your heart for many years&amp;nbsp;to work, then you&#39;re dwelling in the cage of fear.
&amp;nbsp;A wise man once said a child is born without fear except for the ones he&#39;s taught by society&amp;nbsp;as he grows up.
I want you to understand that everyone has the tendency to have fear but those who are great&amp;nbsp;achievers in our society have found a way to consistently kill it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview Success</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/interview-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/interview-success/</guid>
      <description>This course is for anyone wanting to do better at Job interviews and successfully get a Job offer in the career you want!
Created by practising Recruitment professionals with decades of experience in Business and Executive Recruitment from both Corporate leadership and Recruitment Agency backgrounds, we know what interviewers are looking for and what it takes to stand out - the competition is tougher than ever and we will help you shine!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Brain Training Course - Neuroplasticity -</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-brain-training-course-neuroplasticity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-brain-training-course-neuroplasticity/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Brain Training Course - Neuroplasticity -
Brain Training for the Modern Smart Phone Era! You Can Train Your Brain to Think More Clearly and Creatively
Brain training is essential if you want do you live up to your full potential as a human being. Your brain is your most important organ, therefore it is essential that you train it for peak performance.
Like it or not, every single day your brain is being trained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Miraculous Faith</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-miraculous-faith/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-miraculous-faith/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling to overcome a problem or a challenge in your life, business, or marriage? Do you want simple-to-understand and easy-to-apply descriptions or explanations of the Christian faith that will help you solve those nagging problems in your life, business, or marriage?
If those questions apply to you, then this course, ‘The Miraculous Faith: Principles of Christian Faith Manifestation: How to make miracles through faith’ is just the right one for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PNL: Conversación transformacional &amp; Negociación efectiva</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pnl-conversaci%C3%B3n-transformacional-negociaci%C3%B3n-efectiva/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pnl-conversaci%C3%B3n-transformacional-negociaci%C3%B3n-efectiva/</guid>
      <description>Los seres humanos hemos concebido la idea de que existen variables que están fuera de la gestión individual, por tal motivo se ha exteriorizado la responsabilidad de aquellos pilares transformándonos en víctima de factores externos configurados en paradigmas (política, economía, ciencia y religión) encarnados en autoridades dueñas de conocimientos, reglas y mandamientos que han configurado las estructuras mentales por las cuales construimos nuestras experiencias y realidades.
Sin embargo, gracias a la era de la información y a consecuencia de la conectividad producida por el mismo fenómeno, estamos comenzando a cambiar la percepción del tiempo y el conocimiento desde un paradigma lineal e inamovible a otro holístico y constituidos por millares de posibilidades.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
