<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yoga on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/yoga/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Yoga on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/yoga/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Yoga, Pranayam and Meditation for Women</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/yoga-pranayam-and-meditation-for-women/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/yoga-pranayam-and-meditation-for-women/</guid>
      <description>Every one is a fitness freak these days. Generally women are a little more conscious, as beauty is directly proportional to health. A technique called &#39;Yoga&#39; which has the oldest history of knowledge which dates back to 15000 years old as per some Indian scholarly articles has truly tested the test of time as a proven technique to sustain health of the body and the mind and often even called as a health panacea for the soul too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yoga Sutras of Patañjali: Ashtanga Yoga, Asanas, Pranayama</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/yoga-sutras-of-pata%C3%B1jali-ashtanga-yoga-asanas-pranayama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 21:07:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/yoga-sutras-of-pata%C3%B1jali-ashtanga-yoga-asanas-pranayama/</guid>
      <description>The Yoga Sūtras of Patañjali are 196 Indian sutras (aphorisms). The Yoga Sutras were compiled prior to 400 CE by Sage Patanjali, taking materials about yoga from older traditions. The Yoga Sūtras of Patañjali was the most translated ancient Indian text in the medieval era, having been translated into about forty Indian languages and two non-Indian languages: Old Javanese and Arabic. The text fell into obscurity for nearly 700 years from the 12th to 19th century, and began to regain popularity in late 19th century due to the efforts of Swami Vivekananda, the Theosophical Society and others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
