<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IT &amp; Software on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/it-software/</link>
    <description>Recent content in IT &amp; Software on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 01:39:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/it-software/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Kanban: Kanban for Software Development Teams</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/agile-kanban-kanban-for-software-development-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 01:39:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/agile-kanban-kanban-for-software-development-teams/</guid>
      <description>Kanban is not a software development lifecycle methodology or an approach to project management.
It requires that some process is already in place so that Kanban can be applied to
incrementally change the underlying process.
—David Anderson, Kanban
Kanban is a popular framework used to implement agile and DevOps software development. It requires real-time communication of capacity and full transparency of work. Work items are represented visually on a kanban board, allowing team members to see the state of every piece of work at any time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Command Line Terminal Basic for Beginners (In Hindi)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/linux-command-line-terminal-basic-for-beginners-in-hindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 01:39:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/linux-command-line-terminal-basic-for-beginners-in-hindi/</guid>
      <description>Become an effective Linux user and advance your Career. Learning the Linux Command Line will take you FAR!

Learn to appreciate the power of the Linux command line.

Understand the structure of the Linux File System.

Learn how to navigate your Linux File System using few simple commands!

Learn how to create, modify, and process files.

This course is aimed at IT professionals or people who wish to become familiar with Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Power Platform Fundamentals (PL-900)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-power-platform-fundamentals-pl-900/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 01:39:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-power-platform-fundamentals-pl-900/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to take the Microsoft PL-900 Analyzing and Visualizing Data with Microsoft Power BI exam?

This practice test course contains 3 complete timed tests, of over 52-questions each, properly balanced based on the exam domains just like you will get in the official exam. That&#39;s over 189 questions to see how prepared you are for the real test. In addition, after taking the exam you can review your answers compared against the correct answers including comprehensive explanations of each question, links to documentation and articles, the correct and incorrect answer options</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PL-900: Microsoft Power Platform Fundamentals Practical Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pl-900-microsoft-power-platform-fundamentals-practical-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 01:39:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pl-900-microsoft-power-platform-fundamentals-practical-test/</guid>
      <description>PL-900: Microsoft Power Platform Fundamentals- Practice Exams

Set yourself apart with the first and only official professional certification program for PL-900: Microsoft Power Platform Fundamentals1.
ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator is for the engineers and developper to validate their PL-900: Microsoft Power Platform Fundamentals 

Practice tests are designed by experts to simulate the real exam scenario. The questions are based on the exam syllabus outlined by official documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Administración de Windows desde la Consola</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/administraci%C3%B3n-de-windows-desde-la-consola/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/administraci%C3%B3n-de-windows-desde-la-consola/</guid>
      <description>Curso 100% práctico, ya que incluso dentro de la teoría que se comparte mediante documentos, se explican con prácticas. Trata de mejorar las habilidades Administrativas usando sólo la consola del sistema de Windows, en este caso, CMD. Este curso te promete implementaciones desde un nivel básico hasta avanzado. Un curso al que le he dedicado más de 5 años estudiarlo y condensado en este material.
 Ratings: 4.55/5
Enrollments: 65043</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner (CLF-C01) Practise Exams</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-clf-c01-practise-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-clf-c01-practise-exams/</guid>
      <description>AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner (CLF-C01) Practise Tests is there to aid and prepare you for the AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner (CLF-C01) exam.
The test comprises out of selected questions and topics covered in the exam so you can pass your exam successfully.
With the AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner credential, organizations can identify and develop employees with critical knowledge about implementing cloud initiatives. Achieving the certification validates cloud fluency and the foundation of Amazon Web Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft AZ-104: Azure Administrator Exam Prep Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-az-104-azure-administrator-exam-prep-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-az-104-azure-administrator-exam-prep-test/</guid>
      <description>Get Yourself Certified and earn a Cloud Skill.
Three separate Timed Test of 55 questions each. All real questions close to the exam live questions. Use this question set to test your knowledge before taking the AZ-104 exam. Microsoft Azure is the fastest growing cloud platform. Getting yourself certified in cloud can help you to improve your resume for possibilities of landing into a Job. AZ-104 examination will have around 40 to 60 questions, which you have to appear in 120 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft AZ-104: Microsoft Azure Fundamentals Prep Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-az-104-microsoft-azure-fundamentals-prep-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-az-104-microsoft-azure-fundamentals-prep-test/</guid>
      <description>All answers are justified with a very detailed explanation.

Set yourself apart with the first and only official professional certification program for Microsoft AZ-104: Microsoft Azure Fundamentals Prep Test
ServiceNow - Certified System Administrator is for the engineers and developper to validate their Microsoft AZ-104: Microsoft Azure Fundamentals Prep Test

Practice tests are designed by experts to simulate the real exam scenario. The questions are based on the exam syllabus outlined by official documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOGAF 9 Practice Exams 2022 [Combined Level 1 and 2]</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/togaf-9-practice-exams-2022-combined-level-1-and-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/togaf-9-practice-exams-2022-combined-level-1-and-2/</guid>
      <description>Welcome!
Are you ready to take the TOGAF 9 exam?
Exam Summary
This is a combined TOGAF 9 Part 1 and Part 2 examination for candidates who want to achieve Level 2 certification directly.
Exam Name: TOGAF 9 Combined Part 1 and Part 2
Exam Number:
OG0-093 - English
OG0-098 - Simplified Chinese
Qualification upon passing: TOGAF 9 Certified
Delivered at: Authorized Examination Provider Test Centers
Prerequisites: None
Supervised: Yes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>¡Curso Profesional Excel 2021– Para Empresas!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/curso-profesional-excel-2021-para-empresas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/curso-profesional-excel-2021-para-empresas/</guid>
      <description>El curso te proporciona los cimientos que todo Profesional Excel debe poseer. Obtendrás un vasto conocimiento lleno de recursos y estarás capacitado para hacer frente a cualquier tarea en Excel de una manera eficaz y productiva.
Al terminar el curso, habrás dominado Excel y nada te será desconocido para empezar a trabajar como todo un Profesional.
El curso Incluye:
⭐ Más de 8 Horas de Contenido Exclusivo
⭐ Tareas Prácticas Al Final de Cada Capitulo (Desafíos)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OBS Studio - Ultimate Livestreaming Guide to OBS Studio</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/obs-studio-ultimate-livestreaming-guide-to-obs-studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/obs-studio-ultimate-livestreaming-guide-to-obs-studio/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to OBS Studio - Ultimate Livestreaming Guide to OBS Studio!
Nick Nyxson here, your instructor.
In this course, you will learn how to start using Open Broadcaster Software (OBS Studio) for Livestreaming on Twitch, YouTube, Mixer, and other platforms, even if you have no idea where to start.
In this course You Will Learn:
Which version of OBS Studio (Open Broadcaster Software) You need to use;
How to download OBS Studio;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>مهارات معالجة الكلمات باستخدام مايكروسوفت وورد 2016</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/%D9%85%D9%87%D8%A7%D8%B1%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D9%85%D8%B9%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AC%D8%A9-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%83%D9%84%D9%85%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D8%A8%D8%A7%D8%B3%D8%AA%D8%AE%D8%AF%D8%A7%D9%85-%D9%85%D8%A7%D9%8A%D9%83%D8%B1%D9%88%D8%B3%D9%88%D9%81%D8%AA-%D9%88%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%AF-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/%D9%85%D9%87%D8%A7%D8%B1%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D9%85%D8%B9%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AC%D8%A9-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%83%D9%84%D9%85%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D8%A8%D8%A7%D8%B3%D8%AA%D8%AE%D8%AF%D8%A7%D9%85-%D9%85%D8%A7%D9%8A%D9%83%D8%B1%D9%88%D8%B3%D9%88%D9%81%D8%AA-%D9%88%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%AF-2016/</guid>
      <description>يهدف هذا البرنامج إلى إكساب المشاركين المهارات الأساسية في استخدام برنامج معالجة الكلمات &#34;مايكروسوفت وورد&#34;، في إنشاء المستندات وتنسيق النصوص وإخراج المستندات بشكل جذاب ومنظم، من خلال التعرف على عمليات التحرير في المستند (تحديد، نسخ، قص، لصق) وكذلك عمليات التنسيق في المستند (تنسيق الخط، تنسيق الفقرة، تنسيق التعداد) والالوان والحدود للخطوط والنصوص المستخدمة في المستند، كذلك تصميم الجداول وتنسيقها، وإدراج الرسوم والصور والأشكال الذكية والهياكل التنظيمية إلى غير ذلك من أدوات الرسم والأشكال الأخرى، فضلاً عن مراجعة المستند والترجمة ومعرفة عدد الكلمات والفقرات في المستند وأدوات المراجعة الأخرى، وبنهاية التدريب سيتمكن المشاركون من:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon EKS Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/amazon-eks-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/amazon-eks-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to do use Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service but don&#39;t know where to start?	Would you like to make amazing Kubernetes applications in AWS Cloud or on-premise and bring your ideas to life?	Then Amazon EKS Ultimate Course is for you!	Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.	Amazon EKS is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe XD 2021 Basics</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/adobe-xd-2021-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/adobe-xd-2021-basics/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Design but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Designs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe XD 2021 Basics is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Design is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building designs like an expert with Adobe XD 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Redshift Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/amazon-redshift-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/amazon-redshift-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to do use Amazon Redshift but don&#39;t know where to start?	Would you like to access data lakes and bring your data to life?	Then Amazon Redshift Ultimate Course is for you!	Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Amazon Redshift is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. We&#39;ll Cover everything you need to know about Amazon Redshift from scratch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git with Visual Studio Code</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/git-with-visual-studio-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/git-with-visual-studio-code/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to get stared quickly to use Git, right inside your favorite IDE, Visual Studio Code?
Then you are at the right place!
Welcome to my Git with Visual Studio Code course, where you will learn everything you need in order to keep track of your awesome projects!
Here you will learn only what you need, no extra content, because time is precious!
 Ratings: 4.45/5
Enrollments: 27680</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Visual Studio Code</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/mastering-visual-studio-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/mastering-visual-studio-code/</guid>
      <description>In just 3 years, Visual Studio Code became the number 1 tool any programmer should use. Even if you need a simple code editor, or a complex IDE, with rich features like refactoring, linting or debugger, VSCode is the tool you need. Why use one tool for your HTML and CSS, one for your back-end development and another one for course control, when you can have everything you need in one single, fast and beautiful program: Visual Studio Code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMP® Practice Test: Project Management Professional 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pmp-practice-test-project-management-professional-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pmp-practice-test-project-management-professional-2021/</guid>
      <description>The PMP® certification is the most widely and globally recognized project management certification in 2021. It validates your experience and knowledge of Project Management. Unfortunately PMP® Exam content outline has changed in 2021, Hence old mock test preparations can not completely prepare you to take the challenge. This course can align your preparation to the new expectation of PMI from its students. Each practice test covers a deep understanding to carry out project management responsibilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Linux on  VirtualBox quick setup</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ubuntu-linux-on-virtualbox-quick-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ubuntu-linux-on-virtualbox-quick-setup/</guid>
      <description>Running Linux on a virtual machine has many advantages: easy and secure setup, complete control over the machine, easy backUp and folder sharing.
Do you want to quickly start using Linux Ubuntu?
In this course you will learn how to easily set it up on a virtual machine using VirtualBox.
You will be able to fix the errors that might come along and set up a complete coding environment.  Ratings: 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Key DAX functions in POWER BI</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/understanding-key-dax-functions-in-power-bi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/understanding-key-dax-functions-in-power-bi/</guid>
      <description>Course covers different functions that are used in day to day reporting development and is helpful to understand the core concepts of these DAX functions. The videos are precise to topic and no additional information is covered other than the topic itself. ** This is not recommended for you , if you are already good at DAX and understand the core DAX functionality , as this course is designed for who wanted to explore the KEY DAX functions and just getting to learn DAX.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exam C_SM100_7208 SAP Certified  Solution manager (7.2 SPS8)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/exam-c_sm100_7208-sap-certified-solution-manager-7.2-sps8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 13:13:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/exam-c_sm100_7208-sap-certified-solution-manager-7.2-sps8/</guid>
      <description>Description
The &#34;SAP Certified Technology Associate - SAP Solution Manager, Mandatory and Managed System Configuration (7.2 SPS8)&#34; certification exam validates that the candidate knows mandatory and managed system configuration of the SAP Solution Manager, including infrastructure. The exam also validates that the candidate can describe the various activities, functions and features that belong to the area of operations of the SAP Solution Manager solution.
Topic Areas
Please see below the list of topics that may be covered within this certification and the courses that cover them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT &amp; Desktop Computer Support - Real World Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/it-desktop-computer-support-real-world-troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 13:13:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/it-desktop-computer-support-real-world-troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description>Over this course we&#39;ll be covering some real world issues that can often appear when troubleshooting computer systems. Some of the topics covered are as follows:

* An overview of physical and logical troubleshooting, explaining the differences between the two and how these issues can be identified
* Troubleshooting steps to take in the case of a suspected hard disk failure
* How to identify and troubleshoot memory issues, such as insufficient and/or faulty RAM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Practice Exams</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-practice-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-practice-exams/</guid>
      <description>Pass your AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner exam on the first attempt and become AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner. All questions and answers in these practice exams have been carefully curated and updated to be fit for 2021 AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner exam. Every question has a detailed explanation of why an option is correct and why the other options are wrong.

The scenarios covered in this practice tests and the breadth and complexity of the questions here are indicative of what you see in the real exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSM1™ Practice Tests Professional Scrum Master certification</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/psm1-practice-tests-professional-scrum-master-certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/psm1-practice-tests-professional-scrum-master-certification/</guid>
      <description>The Professional Scrum Master certification or PSM1™ is most widely accepted and globally recognized Scrum certification. This certification is provided by Scrum org and to pass the exam the candidate need to be aligned with the latest changes in the Scrum Guide. The best way to validate the knowledge is to take practice Exams.
Exam Details:
Total 80 Questions
Exam time 60 Min.
Pass at 85%
Exam price 150$
This course provides 160 practice test questions, which will help you get ready to pass the PSM1™ exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering The Complete Agile Scrum Master Workshop</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/mastering-the-complete-agile-scrum-master-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/mastering-the-complete-agile-scrum-master-workshop/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE FOR 2020 &amp;amp; 2021 with Tanmay&#39;s latest knowledge on Agile Scrum Master Certification!
This course is about learning the latest Agile Scrum Methodology for the Software Development field. In this course, you will learn all other Agile methodologies along with detailed information on Scrum.
This course helps the students in understanding the fundamental principles that form the foundation of Agile. The course also explores the Scrum framework in deep detail and also blends an overview of the key practices for Agile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Services for Solutions Architect Associate [2021]</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-services-for-solutions-architect-associate-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-services-for-solutions-architect-associate-2021/</guid>
      <description>***UPDATE: New Content ALERT!!! Around 50+ video content added to the course!***

AWS is a public cloud and a pioneer in the cloud computing domain. Aws provides every kind of service model like IAAS, PAAS, and SAAS. In this course, I will discuss various cloud services provided by Amazon Web Services (AWS).
Here we will elaborate on the features of AWS services, their use cases, how to create those services, how to configure them, and how to integrate various services together to present a holistic cloud solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSD Professional Scrum Developer certification Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/psd-professional-scrum-developer-certification-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/psd-professional-scrum-developer-certification-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>Acknowledgment: Scrum (.) org is a protected Brand. These practice exams are neither endorsed by nor affiliated with Scrum (.) org. Although all practice tests mock real tests, they are unofficial.
---
Are you looking to take a Scrum Certification Exam like PSD™ but you still feel a bit insecure or you are curious about how the questions look like? Do you want to be sure that is aligned with the latest Scrum Guide 2020?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMI-ACP®: Agile Certified Project Management 200 Questions</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pmi-acp-agile-certified-project-management-200-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 13:24:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pmi-acp-agile-certified-project-management-200-questions/</guid>
      <description>The PMI-ACP® certification is the most widely and globally recognized Agile project management certification. It validates your experience and knowledge of Agile Project Management. The domains of PMI-ACP® exam are as following, Exam Domains: 
Agile Framework (16%)
Value Driven Delivery (20%)
Stakeholder Engagement (17%)
Boosting Team Performance (16%)
Adaptive Planning (12%)
Problem Detection and Resolution (10%)
Continuous Improvement (9%)
This course provides 200 practice test questions, which will help you get ready to pass the PMI-ACP® exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PRINCE2-Practitioner Exam-LATEST Questions OCT 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/prince2-practitioner-exam-latest-questions-oct-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 13:24:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/prince2-practitioner-exam-latest-questions-oct-2021/</guid>
      <description>PRINCE2 stands for Projects IN Controlled Environments (Not the easiest acronym) and is a specific certification for Project Management. PRINCE2 is most often seen in Commonwealth countries like the UK and an expensive certification to train for if you use the in-house materials provided by most PRINCE2 vendors (Literally thousands of dollars!). So we recommend picking up some online practice exams instead, they’re free, written by experts, and can save you several thousand!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Operating System: A complete Linux guide for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/linux-operating-system-a-complete-linux-guide-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/linux-operating-system-a-complete-linux-guide-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>This is a brand new Linux Administration course launched in August 2021.
Linux is the number 1 operating system in the Corporate world. Industry&#39;s most powerful computers are Linux based. Linux is a popular open-source operating system that’s easy to use and highly secure.

Every time you use Google or Facebook or any other major Internet site, you are communicating with servers running Linux. Most DVRs, airplane, and automobile entertainment systems, and recent TVs run on Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Azure AI Fundamentals AI-900 Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-azure-ai-fundamentals-ai-900-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-azure-ai-fundamentals-ai-900-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Azure, is a cloud computing service created by Microsoft for building, testing, deploying, and managing applications and services through Microsoft-managed data centers. It provides software as a service (SaaS), platform as a service (PaaS) and infrastructure as a service (IaaS) and supports many different programming languages, tools, and frameworks, including both Microsoft-specific and third-party software and systems. Azure is the largest commercial cloud vendor by revenue, although that designation stems in part from the company&#39;s &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical Cisco Networking Labs in Cisco Packet Tracer</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/practical-cisco-networking-labs-in-cisco-packet-tracer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/practical-cisco-networking-labs-in-cisco-packet-tracer/</guid>
      <description>This course&#39;s goal is to teach you some of the most important computer networking concepts, but also provide practical, real-life scenario labs &amp;amp; guide you through configuring those successfully. Some of the labs come from CCNA, but they&#39;re mostly original topologies I created for my Computer Networking students. They were very successful so I decided to post them on Udemy as well. Hope you will find them useful and feel free to send ideas on additional labs I might add!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tout connaître sur PowerPoint</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tout-conna%C3%AEtre-sur-powerpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/tout-conna%C3%AEtre-sur-powerpoint/</guid>
      <description>Avec 4 projets d&#39;applications, plus de 47 vidéos, 10 questionnaires ce cours est incontestablement le plus complet pour tout apprendre sur PowerPoint ! Vous apprendrez toutes les fonctionnalités de PowerPoint, des techniques pour être plus productif et surtout les bases du design de présentations pour captiver votre auditoire !
Le ton pédagogique est de mise, chaque notion est étudiée trois fois sous différentes formes (vidéos théoriques, projet simple et projet complexe), des adresses de contact sont disponibles pour les moindres questions sans oublier les questionnaires qui vous permettront de valider vos compétences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner CLF-C01 : Exam and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-clf-c01-exam-and-beyond/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-clf-c01-exam-and-beyond/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to get started in AWS and also get certified?
We created this course to cover everything you should learn to qualify for the AWS Cloud Practitioner Certification Exam. I structured this course in 14 sections. The first section gives you some preliminary information about the course and what you should do before you start the course. The second section of this course is your getting started for cloud computing and the AWS Cloud platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/devops-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/devops-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>DevOps is not only a set of processes and tools but is more rightly represented by the culture of enhanced communication and collaboration between IT operation guys and Developers. DevOps culture is guided by principles of DevOps such as Automation, infrastructure as code, practices such as continuous integration, continuous delivery, and implemented by a large set of DevOps tools. In this course, DevOps concepts are explained in easy to understand language along with hands-on examples on basic tools of DevOps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Google Colaboratory with Python</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-google-colaboratory-with-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-google-colaboratory-with-python/</guid>
      <description>Google Colaboratory is a Google cloud-based service that replicates Jupyter Notebook in the cloud. You don’t have to install anything on your system to use it. In most respects, you use Colaboratory as you would a desktop installation of Jupyter Notebook. Google Colaboratory is primarily for those readers who use something other than a standard desktop setup to work.
You&#39;ll learn about the all features of Google Colaboratory.
The course is for you if you&#39;re a newcomer to Data Science and Python programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lua&#39;s Core Syntax (Programming Language)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/luas-core-syntax-programming-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/luas-core-syntax-programming-language/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you&#39;ll learn about Lua&#39;s Core Syntax.
In each lecture, I&#39;ll discuss a few lines of code explaining a concept. Over in the lecture resources, you&#39;ll be linked to the code, which you can fork, run, &amp;amp; alter to complete some easy exercises.
I&#39;m using an online IDE called replit. This means that you can start coding right away and learn easily, even on your tablet or smartphone. Don’t waste time setting up your environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Crash Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-crash-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-crash-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Whether you want to:
Build the skills you need to get your first Python programming job
Move to a more senior software developer position
Get started with Machine Learning, Data Science, Django or other hot areas that Python specialises in
Learn Python to be able to create your own Python apps quickly.
Will I be able to learn Python and find a job after completing this course?
I have heard of quite a few success stories where students have rigorously followed the course and have found a job afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Beginner Guide to Streamlabs OBS (OBS)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ultimate-beginner-guide-to-streamlabs-obs-obs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ultimate-beginner-guide-to-streamlabs-obs-obs/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Ultimate Beginner Guide to Streamlabs OBS (OBS)!
Nick Nyxson here, Your Instructor for this course.
In this course, you will learn how to start using Streamlabs OBS which is live streaming software made by Streamlabs and is a modified version of Open Broadcaster Software (OBS).
In this course You Will Learn:
What is SLOBS (Streamlabs OBS);
How Streamlabs OBS is any different from OBS Studio;
Streamlabs OBS Settings Walkthrough;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CheckPoint-NGFW Security : Basic Introduction</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/checkpoint-ngfw-security-basic-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/checkpoint-ngfw-security-basic-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Learn all the Concepts about the Features of CheckPoint - Next Generation Firewall, Learn how to evaluate or Review a Firewall. Why are Firewalls needed and how its&#39; features justify the Deployment in modern Day networks in spite of ACLs on Router, Packet filters &amp;amp; Proxy based Firewalls. You will learn all the additional features they provide on top of other traditional Networking and legacy security solutions. Learn about Stateful Inspection and how it is Used in Firewall to provide security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CompTIA A&#43; Core2 220-1002 Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/comptia-a-core2-220-1002-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/comptia-a-core2-220-1002-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>CompTIA A+ Core2 220-1002 Practice Test
500 Questions with Accurate Answers

CompTIA A+ certified professionals are proven problem solvers. They support today’s core technologies from security to cloud to data management and more. CompTIA A+ is the industry standard for launching IT careers into today’s digital world.
- The only credential with performance-based items to prove pros can think on their feet to perform critical IT support tasks in the moment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SolarWinds ARM / Access Monitoring / Prevent Data Breaches</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/solarwinds-arm-/-access-monitoring-/-prevent-data-breaches/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/solarwinds-arm-/-access-monitoring-/-prevent-data-breaches/</guid>
      <description>SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (ARM) is designed to assist IT and security administrators in quickly and easily provisioning, deprovisioning, managing, and auditing user access rights to systems, data, and files, so they can help protect their organizations from the potential risks of data loss and breaches. By analyzing user authorizations and access permissions, you get visualization of who has access to what, and when they accessed it. With just a few clicks, customized reports can be generated to help demonstrate compliance with many regulatory requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SolarWinds DPA Monitor/Tuning Performance Databases Software</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/solarwinds-dpa-monitor/tuning-performance-databases-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/solarwinds-dpa-monitor/tuning-performance-databases-software/</guid>
      <description>SolarWinds Database Performance Analyzer (DPA) pinpoints performance issues while providing expert advice with tuning advisors. Anomaly detection powered by machine learning allows DBAs to proactively optimize databases before small issues become big problems.

FEATURES • Find your worst-performing applications, SQL, and tables in seconds • Hybrid monitoring for virtualized, physical, and cloud-based database instances • Uncover root causes from CPU and I/O down to the SQL statement • Visualize all wait times from resources to blocking, to host and VM resources, and more • Anomaly detection powered by machine learning gets better over time • Detailed blocking and deadlock analysis expose your SQL blocking hierarchy • Integrated VMware ESXi visualization with the optional VM Option • Ability to search for and filter individual SQL query statements</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C_MDG_1909 | SAP Master Data Governance Certification Exam</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/c_mdg_1909-sap-master-data-governance-certification-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/c_mdg_1909-sap-master-data-governance-certification-exam/</guid>
      <description>The SAP Certified Application Associate - SAP Master Data Governance certification exam validates that the candidate possesses the fundamental and core knowledge required of the application consultant profile. This certification proves that the candidate has an overall understanding and in‐depth technical skills to participate as a member of a project team in a mentored role. This certification exam is recommended as an entry level qualification.
MDG Overview and Architecture | 12%</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CompTIA A&#43; Core1 220-1001 Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/comptia-a-core1-220-1001-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/comptia-a-core1-220-1001-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>CompTIA A+ Core1 220-1001 Practice Test
500 Questions with Accurate Answers

CompTIA A+ certified professionals are proven problem solvers. They support today’s core technologies from security to cloud to data management and more. CompTIA A+ is the industry standard for launching IT careers into today’s digital world.
- The only credential with performance-based items to prove pros can think on their feet to perform critical IT support tasks in the moment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CompTIA Cloud &#43; CV0-003 Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/comptia-cloud-cv0-003-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/comptia-cloud-cv0-003-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>CompTIA Cloud+ shows you have the expertise needed for data center jobs.

200 questions with accurate answers

CompTIA Cloud+ is a global certification that validates the skills needed to deploy and automate secure cloud environments that support the high availability of business systems and data.
CompTIA Cloud+ is the only performance-based IT certification that views cloud-based infrastructure services in the context of broader IT systems operations regardless of the platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science Real World Projects in Python</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/data-science-real-world-projects-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/data-science-real-world-projects-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to land a top-paying job in Data Science?
Or are you a seasoned AI practitioner who want to take your career to the next level?
Or are you an aspiring data scientist who wants to get Hands-on Data Science and Artificial Intelligence?

If the answer is yes to any of these questions, then this course is for you!
Data Science is one of the hottest tech fields to be in right now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Troubleshooting with Palo Alto Firewalls</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-troubleshooting-with-palo-alto-firewalls/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-troubleshooting-with-palo-alto-firewalls/</guid>
      <description>*** The only Palo Alto Networks Firewall course on Udemy 100% Troubleshooting oriented .***
When things turn wrong, the Admin guide or Google search will have their limits very quickly! Troubleshooting takes time, a logical methodology and sharp skills: This training will give you the tools to find most problem root causes and help you to become quick at solving them on Palo Alto Networks firewalls.

WHAT OTHER STUDENTS SAY</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSM1 Exam Simulation</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/psm1-exam-simulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/psm1-exam-simulation/</guid>
      <description>Each simulation exam contains 80 practice PSM1 exam questions. A total of 160 practice exam questions are provided in this course. The passing score for the PSM1 exam is pretty high, 85%. That means you can only miss no more than 12 questions in a total of 80 exam questions. So, I encourage you to try to score above 90% on both simulation exams before taking the real PSM 1 exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSPO1™ Practice Tests Scrum Product Owner certification-160Q</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pspo1-practice-tests-scrum-product-owner-certification-160q/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pspo1-practice-tests-scrum-product-owner-certification-160q/</guid>
      <description>The Professional Scrum Product Owner certification or PSPO1™ is most widely accepted and globally recognized Product Owner Certification. This certification is provided by Scrum org and to pass the exam the candidate need to be aligned with the latest changes in the Scrum Guide. The best way to validate the knowledge is to take practice Exams.
Exam Details:
Total 80 Questions
Exam time 60 Min.
Pass at 85%
Exam price 150$</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Data Hadoop and Spark with Scala</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/big-data-hadoop-and-spark-with-scala/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/big-data-hadoop-and-spark-with-scala/</guid>
      <description>This course will make you ready to switch career on big data hadoop and spark.
After this watching this, you will understand about Hadoop, HDFS, YARN, Map reduce, python, pig, hive, oozie, sqoop, flume, HBase, No SQL, Spark, Spark sql, Spark Streaming.

This is the one stop course. so dont worry and just get started. You will get all possible support from my side. For any queries, feel free to message me here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft MB-300 Exam : Practice Test 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-mb-300-exam-practice-test-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-mb-300-exam-practice-test-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Microsoft MB-300: Dynamics 365 Core Finance and Operations Exam ? Don’t be stressed, Take our Microsoft MB-300 Exam Based Latest Practice Test and prepare yourself for the Exam.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
What you will get in These Practice Test ? 
It Contains Sample Questions which are likely to be asked in the Real Exam.
These Practice Tests are Prepared According to the Latest Exam Format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Security ( SC-900 ) Exam : Practice Test 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-security-sc-900-exam-practice-test-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-security-sc-900-exam-practice-test-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Microsoft SC-900 Exam? Don’t be stressed, Take our Microsoft SC-900 Exam Based Practice Test and prepare yourself for the Exam.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
What you will get in These Practice Test ? 
It contains sample questions which are likely to be asked in the Real Exam.
These Questions help you with Self-Study and Self-Assessment.
These Practice Test helps you check your Knowledge.
These practice tests are prepared according to the Latest Exam Format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python PCEP: Pass Certified Entry-Level Python Programmer</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-pcep-pass-certified-entry-level-python-programmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-pcep-pass-certified-entry-level-python-programmer/</guid>
      <description>The Python PCEP exam is conducted by the &#34;python institute&#34;. This Python PCEP certification Course(Video-based course) will guide you to pass the Python PCEPexam on 1st attempt and once you practice all the examples in this course, you will easily pass the exam with at least 90% marks. There are more than 250 examples in this course that will serve you like Python PCEP Practice Tests. There are multiple PCEP quizzes to test your Knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question For CERTIFIED ETHICAL HACKER (CEH) EXAM</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-for-certified-ethical-hacker-ceh-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-for-certified-ethical-hacker-ceh-exam/</guid>
      <description>Dear Students,
Are you preparing for CEH Exam ? Don’t be stressed, Take our Practice Test for CERTIFIED ETHICAL HACKER EXAM. Here we Discuss the Practical Questions on the Different topics of Ethical Hacking Such as MALWARE, DENIAL OF SERVICE, SYSTEM HACKING, FOOTPRINTING, EVASION and WI-FI and Bluetooth Hacking.
Certified Ethical Hacker EXAM is not so difficult. If you have basic knowledge about Different programming languages, servers and Computer networking it will be easy for you and I hope these Practice test will help you for Success in CEH Exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental Question on Application of Ethical Hacking</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-application-of-ethical-hacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamental-question-on-application-of-ethical-hacking/</guid>
      <description>Dear Students,
Are you preparing for Job Exam and Interview in Ethical Hacking)?
Don’t be stressed, Take our Ethical Hacking Based Practice Test and prepare yourself for the Interview. Here we Discuss the Practical Questions on the Ethical Hacking.
Here we are going to build your confidence by Providing Practice Test on Ethical Hacking based questions. There will be a series of practice Tests where you can test your Knowledge in the field of Ethical Hacking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS And Javascript Crash Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/css-and-javascript-crash-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/css-and-javascript-crash-course/</guid>
      <description>CSS And Javascript Crash Course
1) Learn CSS Crash Course
This course shows you how to create CSS classes from a beginner&#39;s level. It starts off with basic HTML declarations, properties, values, and how to include a CSS style sheet with your HTML code. For those of you who are new to CSS and HTML, we show you step-by-step how to create a CSS file and include it in your HTML code, even if you use a cloud server for your hosting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qt 6 Core Advanced with C&#43;&#43;</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/qt-6-core-advanced-with-c-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/qt-6-core-advanced-with-c-/</guid>
      <description>This is not a beginners course! 
This is an advanced Qt 6 course using C++ to create high performance applications on Windows, Mac and Linux. This course also includes advanced topics such as threading, networking, libraries, plugins, databases, unit testing, and application deployment.

This is a followup to the Udemy Qt 5 Core for beginners and intermediate courses and picks up where they both left off. It is highly recommended to take those courses before attempting this one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qt 6 Core Beginners with C&#43;&#43;</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/qt-6-core-beginners-with-c-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/qt-6-core-beginners-with-c-/</guid>
      <description>Learn cross platform programming with Qt and C++, write once, build anywhere – Qt runs on virtually anything. You probably have applications built with Qt running on your computer, smart phone, television, and other electronics.
No experience necessary, this is a beginners course that will teach you the foundations of both Qt 6 and C++. This course is meant as a direct replacement for an introduction to C++ class. This course starts off with simple topics such as &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Splunk Core Power User Practice Tests Certification 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/splunk-core-power-user-practice-tests-certification-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/splunk-core-power-user-practice-tests-certification-2021/</guid>
      <description>Splunk Core Certified Power User exam is the final step towards completion of the Splunk Core Certified Power User certification. This next-level certification exam evaluates a candidate’s knowledge and skills of field aliases and calculated fields, creating tags and event types, using macros, creating workflow actions and data models, and normalizing data with the CIM. This certification demonstrates an individual&#39;s foundational competence of Splunk’s core software.
Splunk Core Certified Power User has a basic understanding of SPL searching and reporting commands and can create knowledge objects, use field aliases and calculated fields and normalize data with the Common Information Model in either the Splunk Enterprise or Splunk Cloud platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe photoshop practice Tests Certification 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/adobe-photoshop-practice-tests-certification-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/adobe-photoshop-practice-tests-certification-2021/</guid>
      <description>The Adobe certificate is one of the most sought-after computer certificates around the world. Acquiring the Adobe certificate can serve as a stepping stone to obtaining an IT position in medium or large companies. Universally renowned IT companies prefer to employ candidates with professional certification, according to a survey. In addition, obtaining the Adobe Photoshop （TS: Adobe Photoshop CS ACE Exam） certificate will earn you a much higher salary. Using the latest version of the Adobe Photoshop Certificate Exam Reference Book （TS: Adobe Photoshop CS ACE Exam provided by this course you will be able to do this without difficulty!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CompTIA IT Fundamentals ITF&#43; FC0-U61 Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/comptia-it-fundamentals-itf-fc0-u61-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/comptia-it-fundamentals-itf-fc0-u61-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>CompTIA IT Fundamentals (ITF+) is an introduction to basic IT knowledge and skills.

200 questions with accurate answers

Why is it different?
CompTIA ITF+ helps professionals to decide if a career in IT is right for them or to develop a broader understanding of IT.
ITF+ is the only pre-career certification that helps students or career changers determine if they have a competency for information technology and if it is the right career path for them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISTQB : Advanced Test Analyst &amp; Advanced Test Manager certif</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/istqb-advanced-test-analyst-advanced-test-manager-certif/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/istqb-advanced-test-analyst-advanced-test-manager-certif/</guid>
      <description>This course provides test engineers with advanced skills in test analysis, design, and execution. This hands-on course provides test engineers with the ability to define and carry out the tasks required to put the test strategy into action. The course will teach attendees how to analyze the system, taking into account the user’s quality expectations. They will learn how to evaluate system requirements as part of formal and informal reviews, using their understanding of the business domain to determine requirement validity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Foundation System Administrator Certification 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/linux-foundation-system-administrator-certification-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/linux-foundation-system-administrator-certification-2021/</guid>
      <description>The Linux job market continues to grow and expand, and this course will help prepare you for one of the industry standard Linux administration certifications. This course has been designed to match the areas, skills, knowledge and skills detailed by the Linux Foundation.

Linux Foundation Certifications help you quickly identify the best candidates during the recruiting process. Performance-based exams, developed by experts and flexible in distribution are challenging by design, so you can rest assured that a Linux Foundation approved candidate has the skills your organization is looking for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pegasystems Exam: Certified Senior System Architect (CSSA)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pegasystems-exam-certified-senior-system-architect-cssa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pegasystems-exam-certified-senior-system-architect-cssa/</guid>
      <description>The Pega Certified System Architect (PCSA) Version certification is for developers and technical staff members who want to learn how to develop Pega applications. This certification is the first level in the System Architect certification path and provides a baseline measurement on your knowledge of Pega applications. The PCSA Version 8 exam includes scenario questions, multiple choice questions and drag/drop items. If multiple answers are required, the text states how many responses are needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TE0-123 Proven Physical Design Implementation Teradata Exam</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/te0-123-proven-physical-design-implementation-teradata-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/te0-123-proven-physical-design-implementation-teradata-exam/</guid>
      <description>106 UNIQUE practice questions for TE0-123 Proven Physical Design Implementation Teradata Exam
Practice tests are created by Subject Matter Experts and the questions always stay current with the actual exam.
100% verified answers and explanations to each question.
After taking the practice test you can atleast get 80% on the main exam.
Official Exam Details:
Exam Name : TE0-123 Proven Physical Design Implementation Teradata Exam
Total Questions : 106
Type of Questions : Multiple choice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified Ethical Hacker CEH v11 Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/certified-ethical-hacker-ceh-v11-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/certified-ethical-hacker-ceh-v11-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>Certified Ethical Hacker CEH v 11 Practice Test
More than 500 questions with accurate answers

Certified Ethical Hacker CEH v11 will teach you the latest commercial-grade hacking tools, techniques, and methodologies used by hackers and information security professionals to lawfully hack an organization.

What is an Ethical Hacker?
To beat a hacker, you need to think like one!
Ethical Hacking is often referred to as the process of penetrating one’s own computer/s or computers to which one has official permission to do so as to determine if vulnerabilities exist and to undertake preventive, corrective, and protective countermeasures before an actual compromise to the system takes place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Forensics: Analyzing Data Streams in NTFS</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cyber-forensics-analyzing-data-streams-in-ntfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cyber-forensics-analyzing-data-streams-in-ntfs/</guid>
      <description>The course will help students to learn about the basics of Microsoft Windows File System (NTFS), the Master File Table (MFT) and how data is stored in data streams, both primary and alternate. Students will also get to differentiate between resident and non-resident data and learn how to hide data in the ADS. It would also enable students to analyze the data inside and outside of the MFT and to locate the specific cluster/sector on the hard disk where this data is actually stored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Web- The complete Introduction to the hidden web</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/deep-web-the-complete-introduction-to-the-hidden-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/deep-web-the-complete-introduction-to-the-hidden-web/</guid>
      <description>Have you heard many times about the deep/dark web but you never knew what it is. Or you you have an Idea of what is it but you never visited this part of the web. Then this course for you. You will learn all the basics of the deep/dark and how to access this part of the web. At the end of the course, you will be able to use the TOR browser as your default browser and surf on all the parts of the Web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accelerated Learning Techniques for Success in IT Industry</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/accelerated-learning-techniques-for-success-in-it-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/accelerated-learning-techniques-for-success-in-it-industry/</guid>
      <description>&#34;My expectations were low having been disappointed by other &#34;how to learn&#34; courses. Really wanted practical &#34;meat&#34; on learning how to become a better programmer. WOW this course has blown me away. If you&#39;re looking for specific guidance for IT learning especially where hands-on practice is essential – this is it.&#34;, Rick Sline
&#34;Really interesting concepts and to the point. I thought, &#34;what could I really learn in less than 2 hours?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MS-740 : Troubleshooting Microsoft Teams -Practice Test 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ms-740-troubleshooting-microsoft-teams-practice-test-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ms-740-troubleshooting-microsoft-teams-practice-test-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Microsoft MS-740 Exam ? Don’t be stressed, Take our Microsoft MS-740 Exam Based Practice Test and prepare yourself for the Exam. This Ultimate Exam Training Course for the Microsoft MS-740 is packed with comprehensive questions &amp;amp; answers. If you want to clear the Microsoft MS-740 Exam confidently, This Practice Tests helps you to do that.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
What you will get in These Practice Test ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ST0-085 Symantec Security Information Manager Technical Exam</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/st0-085-symantec-security-information-manager-technical-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/st0-085-symantec-security-information-manager-technical-exam/</guid>
      <description>Sample Questions:
What two search templates are the predefined information administrator?
Host activity	internal activity	IDS activity	Firewall activity	port activity

At the request of historical data on the event, can you request available to other users of the system?
Keep your queries published.	Keep it in public templates	Permit for granting to read applications to the domain.	Check the saved query shared option	None

What is the function of Symantec Security Information Manager provides a centralized list of nodes and devices on the network, which are subject to the correlation of security events?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4A0-101 Nokia Interior Routing Protocols and High Exam</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/4a0-101-nokia-interior-routing-protocols-and-high-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/4a0-101-nokia-interior-routing-protocols-and-high-exam/</guid>
      <description>Sample Questions:
Q) What is another term to describe the default route for a client?
A. Black hole
B. Default gateway
C. Gateway path
D. Proxy ARP

Q) Which of the following is not one of the MT topologies defined for IS-IS?
A.IPv4 In-Band Management
B. IPv6 Routing
C. IPv4 Multicast Routing
D. IPv6 Multicast Routing
E. All of the above are MT topologies defined for IS-IS.

Q) Which of the following commands can be used to display the number of SPF computations that have been performed on a router?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build and Deploy Dialogflow Chatbot Waitress Lilis</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/build-and-deploy-dialogflow-chatbot-waitress-lilis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/build-and-deploy-dialogflow-chatbot-waitress-lilis/</guid>
      <description>This course provides a step-by-step guild to create a chatbot waitress Lilis who works at a coffee shop using Dialogflow.
You will learn how to design the architecture of a chatbot
the 7 Minimum-Viable-Product Features of a chatbot waiter
modify Default Welcome and Fallback Intents for chatbot&#39;s purpose
code fulfillment and webhook with javascript to handle intents for taking customer orders
code fulfillment webhook for product availability check
code follow-up intents to handle user responses: yes, no, or change</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Python With NumPy For Data Science &amp; Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/master-python-with-numpy-for-data-science-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/master-python-with-numpy-for-data-science-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>Hi, welcome to the &#39;NumPy For Data Science &amp;amp; Machine Learning&#39; course. This forms the basis for everything else. The central object in Numpy is the Numpy array, on which you can do various operations. We know that the matrix and arrays play an important role in numerical computation and data analysis. Pandas and other ML or AI tools need tabular or array-like data to work efficiently, so using NumPy in Pandas and ML packages can reduce the time and improve the performance of the data computation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Programming Full Course for Beginners 2021 ( Hindi )</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-programming-full-course-for-beginners-2021-hindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-programming-full-course-for-beginners-2021-hindi/</guid>
      <description>Full Course OF Python With HD Practical Video. 
Self Placed Videos.

Python3 We will Learn In This Course.

VS Code IDE We will Use For Python Coding.

Udemy Verified Course Completion Certificate.

Lifetime Access of all the Course Content.

All the Videos Explanation in Hindi .

Guaranteed Instructor Support.

This Course Fully Beginners Course

After Complete This Course You Will Become Master In Python</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Architecture: 8 Crucial Software Architecture KPIs!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/software-architecture-8-crucial-software-architecture-kpis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/software-architecture-8-crucial-software-architecture-kpis/</guid>
      <description>Are your systems build for change? Are you measuring technical debt?Are you suffering from low developer productivity?Did you know that secure software follows software quality? If you can not answer these questions, this course is made for you! Within one hour you will understand the most important software quality concepts essential for software architects. This knowledge is essential for software quality assurance.
Can you explain this without showing code?Yes. The software quality concepts are technology independent and are explained by making use of analogies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Containerize Springboot CRUD App with Docker &amp; DockerCompose</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/containerize-springboot-crud-app-with-docker-dockercompose/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 10:00:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/containerize-springboot-crud-app-with-docker-dockercompose/</guid>
      <description>Learn everything about Docker &amp;amp; run your Springboot apps &amp;amp; Database inside containers using Docker &amp;amp; Docker Compose
Following are the topics that you will learn in this course:
What is the need to run applications inside the container
What is Docker
What is Image
What is Container
What is Docker hub
What is Dockerfile
Benefits of using Docker and running applications inside a container
How to create your own Dockerfile</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin blockchain - Under the hood for beginners.</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/bitcoin-blockchain-under-the-hood-for-beginners./</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/bitcoin-blockchain-under-the-hood-for-beginners./</guid>
      <description>In this course you will learn how bitcoin blockchain works internally and technical concepts which people generally don&#39;t know.
Topics you will learn are :
Bitcoin Introduction
Addresses - Private key and public address
How to generate addresses.
Who are miners?
Proof of work
What makes blockchain so secure.
Ways to buy and sell bitcoin.
Merits and demerits of using online exchanges
Other Applications of blockchain.
Analysis of latest block of bitcoin blockchain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft AZ-120 Exam : Practice Tests 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-az-120-exam-practice-tests-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-az-120-exam-practice-tests-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Microsoft AZ-120 Exam ? Don’t be stressed, Take our Microsoft AZ-120 Exam Based Practice Test and prepare yourself for the Exam. This Ultimate Exam Training Course for the Planning and Administering Microsoft Azure for SAP Workloads Expert Certification is packed with comprehensive questions &amp;amp; answers. If you want to clear the Microsoft AZ-120 Exam confidently, This Practice Tests helps you to do that.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL Injection Attacks: The 2021 Guide</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sql-injection-attacks-the-2021-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sql-injection-attacks-the-2021-guide/</guid>
      <description>About the course:
Welcome to this course on SQL injection attacks! In this course, we explore one of the biggest risks facing web applications today. We start out by creating a safe and legal environment for us to perform attacks in. Then, we cover the core concepts of SQL and injections. After that, we learn SQL injection techniques with the help of cheat sheets and references. At that point, we start to gather information about our target in order to find weaknesses and potential vulnerabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Python 3 Programming for the Absolute Beginner</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/starting-python-3-programming-for-the-absolute-beginner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/starting-python-3-programming-for-the-absolute-beginner/</guid>
      <description>Python is the fastest programming language out there!It is popular among developers, hobbyists, data scientists and is the language of choice of the big tech companies.
For beginners that want to learn Python in a structured way, it can be confusing to find a great resource that teaches you Python step-by-step from the ground up covering fundamentals to give you a strong foundation to grow from.
Searching for good material online often takes hours and hours and this course is meant to make it easy for you, save time and get you proficient in Python as quickly as possible in a hands-on way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MD-101: Managing Modern Desktops Exam -&gt; Practice Test 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/md-101-managing-modern-desktops-exam-practice-test-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/md-101-managing-modern-desktops-exam-practice-test-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Microsoft MD-101 Exam? Don’t be stressed, Take our Microsoft MD-101: Managing Modern Desktops Exam Based Practice Test and prepare yourself for the Exam.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
What you will get in These Practice Test ? 
It Contains Sample Questions which are likely to be asked in the Real Exam.
These Questions Help you with Self-Study and Self-Assessment.
These Practice Test Helps you check your Knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Splunk In 1 Hour</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-splunk-in-1-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 09:38:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-splunk-in-1-hour/</guid>
      <description>Course Description:
This course is designed to teach the power of Splunk in 1 hour. This will teach you how to search and navigate in Splunk, use fields, get statistics from your data, create reports, dashboards, and alerts.
Following are the topics that will be covered inside the lecture Course Topics:
1) Introduction to Splunk&#39;s interface
2) Instaling Splunk
3) Getting Data Into Splunk
4) Using fields in searches
5) Writing Splunk Search Commands using Search Processing Language (SPL)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-140 : Azure Virtual Desktop Exam --&gt; Practice Test 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/az-140-azure-virtual-desktop-exam-practice-test-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:35:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/az-140-azure-virtual-desktop-exam-practice-test-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Microsoft AZ-140 Exam? Don’t be stressed, Take our Microsoft Azure Virtual Desktop Exam Based Practice Test and prepare yourself for the Exam.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
What you will get in These Practice Test ? 
It Contains Sample Questions which are likely to be asked in the Real Exam.
These Questions help you with Self-Study and Self-Assessment.
These Practice Test helps you check your Knowledge.
These Practice Tests are Prepared According to the Latest Exam Format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate Exam - Mock Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-exam-mock-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-exam-mock-test/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate Exam? 
Don’t be stressed, Take our AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate Exam Based Practice Test and prepare yourself for the Exam. Here you will get AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate Exam based Multiple Choice Question for your Next.
What you will get in These Practice Test ? 
It contains sample questions which are likely to be asked in the Real Exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified Kubernetes Administrator (CKA) Exam: Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/certified-kubernetes-administrator-cka-exam-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/certified-kubernetes-administrator-cka-exam-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Certified Kubernetes Administrator Exam? Don’t be stressed, Take our Certified Kubernetes Administrator Exam Based Practice Test and prepare yourself for the Exam.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
What you will get in These Practice Test ? 
It contains sample questions which are likely to be asked in the Real Exam.
These Questions help you with Self-Study and Self-Assessment.
These Mock Test helps you check your Knowledge.
These practice tests are prepared according to the Latest Exam Format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Online (QBO) Bookkeeping With Bank Feeds 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-online-qbo-bookkeeping-with-bank-feeds-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-online-qbo-bookkeeping-with-bank-feeds-2021/</guid>
      <description>This course is a project based course that will dive into bank feeds in detail using a step by step process. We will start by setting up a free 30 day trial QuickBooks Online QBO file for the practice problem. Intuit, the owner of QuickBooks Online QBO, often offers a free 30 day trial period, a great tool for practice. The course will demonstrate how to link QuickBooks Online QBO to the bank to receive bank data directly from the bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veeam Exam: V9_VEEAM  Engineer (VMCE9) Certification 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/veeam-exam-v9_veeam-engineer-vmce9-certification-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/veeam-exam-v9_veeam-engineer-vmce9-certification-2021/</guid>
      <description>Veeam Certified Engineer (VMCE) Certification: Overview and Benefits
The immense possibilities in the field of virtualization involve professionals having consistent awareness and skills. VMCE certification is designed to promote Veeam professionals differentiate themselves from other IT experts through their performance and by reducing company costs.

VMCE certification is a new program launched by Veeam in 2014 certifying your experience and skills to present a wide array of tasks with Veeam solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-304 : Microsoft Azure Architect Design Practice Test 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/az-304-microsoft-azure-architect-design-practice-test-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 11:17:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/az-304-microsoft-azure-architect-design-practice-test-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Microsoft AZ-304 Exam ? Don’t be stressed, Take our Microsoft AZ-304 Exam Based Practice Test and prepare yourself for the Exam. This Ultimate Exam Training Course for the Microsoft Azure Architect Design Exam is packed with comprehensive questions &amp;amp; answers. If you want to clear the Microsoft Azure Architect Design Exam confidently, This Practice Tests helps you to do that.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
What you will get in These Practice Test ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FC0-GR1 CompTIA Strata Green IT Certified Practice Exam</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fc0-gr1-comptia-strata-green-it-certified-practice-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 11:17:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fc0-gr1-comptia-strata-green-it-certified-practice-exam/</guid>
      <description>Sample Questions:
A bank runs 50 workstations and would like to decrease its electricity costs, while not sacrificing functionality. All of the workstations are high-end performance units that are intended to be used for CAD-like applications. Analysts benefit from the added performance, but tellers and associates could use more minimalist systems. Which of the following methods would decrease the banks electricity and hardware costs?
Swap all teller and associate machines with servers	Swap all teller and associate machines with thin clients	Swap all teller and associate machines with low-profile high-end workstations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMI-100 Certified Associate Project Management Practice Exam</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pmi-100-certified-associate-project-management-practice-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 11:17:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pmi-100-certified-associate-project-management-practice-exam/</guid>
      <description>281 UNIQUE practice questions for PMI-100 Certified Associate Project Management Practice Exam
Practice tests are created by Subject Matter Experts and the questions always stay current with the actual exam.
100% verified answers and explanations to each question.
After taking the practice test you can atleast get 80% on the main exam.
Official Exam Details:
Exam Name : PMI-100 Certified Associate Project Management Practice Exam
Total Questions : 281
Type of Questions : Multiple choice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware VCAD510 Certified Associate Data Center Practice Exam</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/vmware-vcad510-certified-associate-data-center-practice-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 11:17:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/vmware-vcad510-certified-associate-data-center-practice-exam/</guid>
      <description>Sample Questions:
Do you have a physical server, which should be replaced by a fan? It does not have maintenance windows available for a few days, but do not want to risk a second failure, it caused the server to lock. What feature does allow you to move all virtual machines to another host without downtime for virtual machines?
VSPhere replication (VR),	Fault tolerance (FT)	VSPhere data protection	Vmois	None</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI-900 : Microsoft Azure AI Fundamentals Exam-&gt;Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ai-900-microsoft-azure-ai-fundamentals-exam-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:50:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ai-900-microsoft-azure-ai-fundamentals-exam-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Microsoft AI-900 Exam ? Don’t be stressed, Take our Microsoft AI-900 Exam Based Practice Test and prepare yourself for the Exam.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
What you will get in These Practice Test ? 
It Contains Sample Questions which are likely to be asked in the Real Exam.
These Practice Tests are Prepared According to the Latest Exam Format.
These Questions Help you with Self-Study and Self-Assessment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-220 : Microsoft Azure IoT Developer Exam -&gt; Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/az-220-microsoft-azure-iot-developer-exam-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:50:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/az-220-microsoft-azure-iot-developer-exam-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Microsoft AZ-220 Exam ? Don’t be stressed, Take our Microsoft AZ-220 Exam Based Practice Test and prepare yourself for the Exam.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
What you will get in These Practice Test ? 
It Contains Sample Questions which are likely to be asked in the Real Exam.
These Practice Tests are Prepared According to the Latest Exam Format.
These Questions Help you with Self-Study and Self-Assessment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python For Absolute Beginners : Learn Python From Scratch</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-for-absolute-beginners-learn-python-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:47:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-for-absolute-beginners-learn-python-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>There is no doubt that Python is the most popular programming language at the moment. Python is used in Machine Learning, Data Science, Web Development and almost all the areas of Software Development. If you want to learn Python and don&#39;t know how to start, then this course is for you. This course is designed for complete beginners.
 Ratings: 4.14/5
Enrollments: 25206
Coupon Code: 45B5C0549D3571620CD9
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of Network Security</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-network-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-network-security/</guid>
      <description>Dear Learners
Are you Preparing for Interview in IT Industry? Don’t be stressed, take our Network Security Course and prepare yourself for your Interview
We know that Network Security is the basic Requirement of IT Company, so it is necessary for every students on IT Industry that he learn the Basic Concept of Network Security. In this Course You Will Learn the fundamentals of Network Security and take the first leap to the world of IT Industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux for Network Engineers: Practical Linux with GNS3</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/linux-for-network-engineers-practical-linux-with-gns3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/linux-for-network-engineers-practical-linux-with-gns3/</guid>
      <description>It is important for you as a network engineer to learn Linux!
Why? There are many reasons including:
1) A lot of network operating systems are based on Linux, or have a Linux shell you can access, or use Linux type commands. I&#39;ll show you an example using Cisco, Arista and Cumulus Linux.
2) Network Automation tools such as Ansible don&#39;t run the command node on Windows. You are probably going to use Linux with tools such as Ansible, Netmkio, NAPALM and other network automation tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python And Flask Framework Complete Course For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-and-flask-framework-complete-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-and-flask-framework-complete-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Learn Python From Scratch
 I’ve created thorough, extensive, but easy to follow content which you’ll easily understand and absorb.
 The course starts with the basics, including Python fundamentals, programming, and user interaction.

The curriculum is going to be very hands-on as we walk you from start to finish becoming a professional Python developer. We will start from the very beginning by teaching you Python basics and programming fundamentals, and then going into advanced topics and different career fields in Python so you can get real-life practice and be ready for the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teramind Employee Monitoring &amp; Data Loss Prevention</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/teramind-employee-monitoring-data-loss-prevention/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/teramind-employee-monitoring-data-loss-prevention/</guid>
      <description>Teramind offers employee monitoring, insider threat detection, and data loss prevention (DLP) solutions. Teramind UAM monitors user activities on applications, websites, file systems, network, email, social media and more. Behavioral rules can be created to automatically warn, block, notify, lockout or take other actions when an anomaly is detected. Its session recording feature allows investigation of incidents with video and optional audio recordings of users&#39; desktop.
Teramind DLP comes with all the features available in Teramind UAM plus: automated data discovery and classification with built-in support for many sensitive data types for personal information, health and financial information (PII/PHI/PFI).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-900 - Microsoft Azure Fundamentals --&gt; Practice Test 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/az-900-microsoft-azure-fundamentals-practice-test-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/az-900-microsoft-azure-fundamentals-practice-test-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for AZ-900 Azure Fundamentals Exam? 
Don’t be stressed, Take our AZ-900 Azure Fundamentals Exam Based Practice Test and prepare yourself for the Exam. Here you will get AZ-900 Azure Fundamentals based Multiple Choice Question for your Next Exam.
What you will get in These Practice Test ? 
It contains sample questions which are likely to be asked in the Real Exam.
These Questions help you with Self-Study and Self-Assessment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digishock 1.0: Experience World-Changing Technologies</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digishock-1.0-experience-world-changing-technologies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digishock-1.0-experience-world-changing-technologies/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the exhaustive course series &#34;MBA in Programming and Trending Technologies&#34;. The first course in this series kickstarts with &#34;Digishock 1.0&#34;. Ready to know what it is all about? Let&#39;s dive right in. &#34;Digishock 1.0&#34; is the ultimate technology course in 2021 to make you a technology expert today. This is the first beginner&#39;s part course of getting involved with Machine Learning and the unique technologies associated with the field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Forensics - Complete Digital Forensics Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-forensics-complete-digital-forensics-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-forensics-complete-digital-forensics-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
Most comprehensive Digital Forensics Course, You will learn Depth understanding of how computers work and how to do digital forensics.
Upgrading every week 2021 Course Computer Forensics
Digital Forensics is defined as the process of preservation, identification, extraction, and documentation of computer evidence which can be used by the court of law. It is a science of finding evidence from digital media like a computer, mobile phone, server, or network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker - Almost Complete Guide with Hands-On for 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/docker-almost-complete-guide-with-hands-on-for-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/docker-almost-complete-guide-with-hands-on-for-2021/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to take your DevOps skills and career to the next level, take this course now!
You will go from zero to Docker hero in couple of hours.
Why choosing this course?
This course is very hands on, Himanshu has put lots effort to provide you with not only the theory but also real-life examples of developing Docker applications that you can try out on your own laptop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helm 3 - Package Manager For Kubernetes for 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/helm-3-package-manager-for-kubernetes-for-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/helm-3-package-manager-for-kubernetes-for-2021/</guid>
      <description>What you&#39;ll learn
Working with Helm Charts and Releases
Helm Architecture and concepts
Create custom Helm Charts and Deploy applications to Kubernetes using Helm
Working with Stable and Custom Helm Charts
Create Automated Kubernetes Deployments with Helm
Helm package manager installation and configuration
Working with Chartmuseum Repository
Expert Secrets from Industry - master troubleshooting tricks that you won’t find anywhere else
Description
You will learn all the required topics as given below for HELM - The Package Manager for Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes: CKA/CKAD, Production Grade Course for 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/kubernetes-cka/ckad-production-grade-course-for-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/kubernetes-cka/ckad-production-grade-course-for-2021/</guid>
      <description>In this Course you are going to learn most of the things which everyone is looking for. This course will help you in understading production environment and i have capture most of the things in the course which you going to face in the Interview and while working in production. Like what are the options we can use to create a cluster, Like Kubeadm, KOPS, Rancher, K3s, EKS . Have almost covered from the Installation to deploying the applications and securing them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Programming Masterclass™:Java Socket, TCP/IP, Server</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/network-programming-masterclassjava-socket-tcp/ip-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/network-programming-masterclassjava-socket-tcp/ip-server/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
The world is becoming interconnected on an unprecedented scale with more services being provided on the Internet. Applications ranging from business transactions to embedded applications, such as those found in refrigerators, are connecting to the Internet. With isolated applications no longer being the norm, it is becoming increasingly important for applications to be network enabled. The goal of this course is to provide the student with the necessary skills to develop Java applications that connect and work with other applications and services across a network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncle Rat&#39;s XXE Handbook</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/uncle-rats-xxe-handbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/uncle-rats-xxe-handbook/</guid>
      <description>Who am i?
An experienced instructor with over 10 000 happy students on udemy, i spend my time making complex topic reacheable for anyone wanting to learn and understand them. As a dad of a toddler, i know what it means to have to simplify things but even before all this i was already emerged in the world of training IT profiles in software test automation and performance testing, having gotten my neoload expert certification in Paris so i could teach that software in a 3 day course that would prepare staff for neoload certification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ 900 Practice Test Microsoft Azure Fundamentals Exam 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/az-900-practice-test-microsoft-azure-fundamentals-exam-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:43:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/az-900-practice-test-microsoft-azure-fundamentals-exam-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you are preparing for Microsoft AZ900 or Microsoft Azure Fundamentals certification exam in 2021 and looking for best resources then this practice tests is for you. Practice tests plays a key role in passing IT certification in first attempt and AZ-900 is no exception. If you want to pass this in-demand cloud certification then these 6 topic-wise practice tests are must have. While there are many Azure Fundamentals or AZ-900 practice test you can find here in Udemy and other online platforms there is not many which help you with individual topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angular Material Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/angular-material-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/angular-material-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to do use Angular Material but don&#39;t know where to start? Would you like to learn components and bring Angular Material Code to Life? Then Angular Material Ultimate Course is for you! Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course. Angular Material is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. We&#39;ll Cover everything you need to know about Angular Material from scratch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAS Certified Associate SAS Programming Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sas-certified-associate-sas-programming-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sas-certified-associate-sas-programming-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>97% Pass in First Attempt Easily

SAS Certified Associate: Programming Fundamentals Using SAS 9.4. The SAS 9.4 Programming Fundamentals exam will test the candidate&#39;s ability to apply the knowledge necessary to write basic SAS programs to access, explore, prepare, manipulate and analyze data. The exam is based upon foundational knowledge covered in the SAS Programming 1. Essentials and SAS Programming 2. Data Manipulation Techniques courses. This is an entry-level exam designed for the novice programmer who does not have much practical experience programming in SAS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supply Chain Professional Practical tests ... Be Certified</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/supply-chain-professional-practical-tests-...-be-certified/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/supply-chain-professional-practical-tests-...-be-certified/</guid>
      <description>Supply Chain Professional Practical tests ... Be Certified 
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily
A supply chain is the network of all the individuals, organizations, resources, activities and technology involved in the creation and sale of a product. A supply chain encompasses everything from the delivery of source materials from the supplier to the manufacturer through to its eventual delivery to the end user.
The Top-level of this model has five different processes which are also known as components of Supply Chain Management – Plan, Source, Make, Deliver and Return.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time Series Analysis Real World Projects in Python</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/time-series-analysis-real-world-projects-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/time-series-analysis-real-world-projects-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to land a top-paying job in Data Science , AI &amp;amp; Time Series Analysis &amp;amp; Forecasting?
Or are you a seasoned AI practitioner who want to take your career to the next level?
Or are you an aspiring data scientist who wants to get Hands-on Data Science and Time Series Analysis?

If the answer is yes to any of these questions, then this course is for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Certified Associate Cloud Engineer Practice Exam</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/google-certified-associate-cloud-engineer-practice-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 22:18:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/google-certified-associate-cloud-engineer-practice-exam/</guid>
      <description>The Associate Cloud Engineer or as it’s also known, the Associate Cloud Engineer, like all tests, there is a bit of freedom on Google&#39;s part to exam an array of subjects. That means knowing the majority of Associate Cloud Engineer content is required because they test randomly on the many subjects available. Be aware too that experience requirements often exist because they have observed the average person and what is required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MS-500 : Microsoft 365 Security Admin Exam --&gt; Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ms-500-microsoft-365-security-admin-exam-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ms-500-microsoft-365-security-admin-exam-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Microsoft MS-500 Exam? Don’t be stressed, Take our Microsoft 365 Security Admin Exam Based Practice Test and prepare yourself for the Exam.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
What you will get in These Practice Test ? 
It Contains Sample Questions which are likely to be asked in the Real Exam.
These Questions help you with Self-Study and Self-Assessment.
These Practice Test helps you check your Knowledge.
These Practice Tests are Prepared According to the Latest Exam Format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MS-600 : Microsoft 365 Core Services --&gt; Practice Test 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ms-600-microsoft-365-core-services-practice-test-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ms-600-microsoft-365-core-services-practice-test-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Microsoft MS-600 Exam? Don’t be stressed, Take our Microsoft 365 Core Services Exam Based Practice Test and prepare yourself for the Exam.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
What you will get in These Practice Test ? 
It Contains Sample Questions which are likely to be asked in the Real Exam.
These Questions help you with Self-Study and Self-Assessment.
These Practice Test helps you check your Knowledge.
These Practice Tests are Prepared According to the Latest Exam Format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Complete Course For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-complete-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-complete-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Learn Python From Beginner To Advanced Level By Demonstrations
The course is created thorough, extensive, but easy to follow content which you’ll easily understand and absorb.
 The course starts with the basics, including Python fundamentals, programming, and user interaction.

The curriculum is going to be very hands-on as we walk you from start to finish to become a professional Python developer. We will start from the very beginning by teaching you Python basics and programming fundamentals, and then going into advanced topics and different career fields in Python so you can get real-life practice and be ready for the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blue Prism Certified Developer Exam --&gt; Practice Test 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/blue-prism-certified-developer-exam-practice-test-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 12:19:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/blue-prism-certified-developer-exam-practice-test-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Blue Prism Certified Developer Exam ? 
Don’t be stressed, Take our Unique &amp;amp; Latest Mock Test and prepare yourself for the Exam. Here you will get Latest Multiple Choice Question for your Next Exam.
What you will get in These Mock Test ? 
It contains sample questions which are likely to be asked in the Exam.
These MCQ questions help you with self-study and self-assessment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel Pivot-Tabellen für Einsteiger</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/excel-pivot-tabellen-f%C3%BCr-einsteiger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 12:19:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/excel-pivot-tabellen-f%C3%BCr-einsteiger/</guid>
      <description>ALLGEMEIN
Bei Excel-Auswertungen ist es nicht selten, dass große Datenmengen analysiert werden müssen. Nicht jeder kennt alle erforderlichen Excel-Formeln und hat die Zeit, die Daten aufwendig professionell aufzubereiten.
Hier kann eine Pivot-Tabelle weiterhelfen
In diesem Kurs lernen Sie die wichtigsten Grundlagen, um Pivot-Tabellen und -Diagramme zu erstellen.

INHALT
Pivot-Erstellung
Aufbau der Pivot-Tabelle
Berechnungen
Diagramme
Daten ändern und aktualisieren
Abweichungen
mehrere Tabellen konsolidieren

Hinweis: Die Übungen wurden mit Excel 2016 erstellt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PCAP Certification-Certified Associate in Python -&gt;Mock Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pcap-certification-certified-associate-in-python-mock-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 12:19:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pcap-certification-certified-associate-in-python-mock-test/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Interview in Python? 
Don’t be stressed, Take our Python Based Mock Test and prepare yourself for the Interview. Here you will get Python based Multiple Choice Question for your Next Interview.
What you will get in These Mock Test ? 
It contains sample questions which are likely to be asked in the Interview and Exam.
These Python based MCQ questions help you with self-study and self-assessment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master in Agile Scrum : Complete Training &amp; Best Practices</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/master-in-agile-scrum-complete-training-best-practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:52:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/master-in-agile-scrum-complete-training-best-practices/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you will Understand The Agile Mindset &amp;amp; Scrum Framework. This course will help you to Prepare for Scrum Master Certification. You will get all the required Guidance About Agile Scrum Implementation in your organization. It has covered All Topics From Basic to Advance. Every Concept is Explained With an Example.
This course is divided into 8 sections. Each section has covered unique elements about Agile and Scrum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create AI Voice Assistant (JARVIS) With Python</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/create-ai-voice-assistant-jarvis-with-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/create-ai-voice-assistant-jarvis-with-python/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you will learn how you can make one Artificial Intelligence Assistant (JARVIS) using Python Programming Language.
This course you will Teach how you can create a basic Artificial Intelligence VOICE Assistant and add basic features to it like sending emails, playing songs, searching on Google etc.
It is a Beginner level course and more following courses will be coming up soon.
No specific skills are required, just passion to learn something new.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Processing Real-World Projects in Python</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/natural-language-processing-real-world-projects-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/natural-language-processing-real-world-projects-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to land a top-paying job in Data Science , AI &amp;amp; Natural Language Processing?
Or are you a seasoned AI practitioner who want to take your career to the next level?
Or are you an aspiring data scientist who wants to get Hands-on Data Science and Artificial Intelligence?

If the answer is yes to any of these questions, then this course is for you!
Data Science is one of the hottest tech fields to be in right now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python And Flask  Demonstrations Practice Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-and-flask-demonstrations-practice-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-and-flask-demonstrations-practice-course/</guid>
      <description>Learn Python By Demonstrations
The course is created thorough, extensive, but easy to follow content which you’ll easily understand and absorb.
 The course starts with the basics, including Python fundamentals, programming, and user interaction.

The curriculum is going to be very hands-on as we walk you from start to finish becoming a professional Python developer. We will start from the very beginning by teaching you Python basics and programming fundamentals, and then going into advanced topics and different career fields in Python so you can get real-life practice and be ready for the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Crash Course for Beginners - 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/linux-crash-course-for-beginners-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 16:04:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/linux-crash-course-for-beginners-2021/</guid>
      <description>This course is for someone who needs basic training in Linux, someone who is already in IT and wants to add a new skill. It is specifically designed for those who have been really busy with their work and don&#39;t have enough time. Now you don&#39;t have to stay awake at night or sneak out of your lunch break. You will learn so many Linux commands in just 2 days. Sounds unreal?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Citrix 1Y0-371 Designing, Deploying and Managing Citrix Exam</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/citrix-1y0-371-designing-deploying-and-managing-citrix-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 10:29:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/citrix-1y0-371-designing-deploying-and-managing-citrix-exam/</guid>
      <description>Sample Questions:
What are the advantages of the two options established by programming policies always?
Improvement of the e-mail experience.	Reduces the number of authentication requests.	Increase responsibility pushes politics.	Improves the level of security.	
What configuration engineer should integrate Citrix XenMobile with the XenApp / XenDesktop client that users can access their internal and external locations environment from the network?
Add the XENMOBILE server to the list of protected ticketing agencies (STAS) or in the StoreFront website-based interface.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TE0-125 Teradata 12 Solutions Development Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/te0-125-teradata-12-solutions-development-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 10:29:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/te0-125-teradata-12-solutions-development-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>Sample Questions:
Given the following explanation text: &#34;6) We do all the amplifiers, we obtained a step ... if one or more rows inserted in spool 3, and then we go to step 4.&#34; What does this text explain?
This selection of insertion.	This is a recursive consultation.	Correlated Subquery.	It is a multi-declaration contract.	None

The application combines the character data of a non-redirection database. Requirements for download include the following data types: Date and time requirements for digital date / time / time test applications include the types of characters to download to avoid the rejection line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pentesting and Securing Web Applications (Ethical Hacking)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pentesting-and-securing-web-applications-ethical-hacking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pentesting-and-securing-web-applications-ethical-hacking/</guid>
      <description>Computer security is one of the biggest job gaps in history, with a shortage of 3.5 million skilled workers needing to tackle a problem estimated to be worth $6 trillion. This is one of the biggest opportunities in history.
When I was at university I did a lot of security courses and to be honest I was pretty frustrated at how they were taught. The concepts and their importance captured my imagination but I knew it could be taught in a better way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Beginner&#39;s guide to Cyber Security</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-beginners-guide-to-cyber-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 12:05:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-beginners-guide-to-cyber-security/</guid>
      <description>Why should you enroll? Since we&#39;ve been working in this field for over 15 years, we wanted to share part of what we&#39;ve learned in all these years with people that are completely new to Cyber Security, or people that would like to understand the 2021 basics in this field. You will find the general information mixed with real-life scenarios and real tips &amp;amp; tricks on how to protect from different threats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MCIA-Mulesoft Certified Integration Architect-Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/mcia-mulesoft-certified-integration-architect-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 12:05:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/mcia-mulesoft-certified-integration-architect-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>These practice tests will test your knowledge on Mule internals. This will help you to architect mule applications confidently. You will be able to clear &#34;Anypoint Platform Architecture - Integration Solutions&#34; exam. Some exam questions which i gathered will be discussed so that u will get confidence to clear exam. Completing this course will boost your confidence on working with mule and helps to progress in your career.
This course is for you if</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft MD-100 : Modern Desktop Exam -&gt; Practice Test 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-md-100-modern-desktop-exam-practice-test-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 23:49:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-md-100-modern-desktop-exam-practice-test-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Microsoft MD-100 Exam? Don’t be stressed, Take our Microsoft 365 Certified - Modern Desktop Administrator Associate Exam Based Practice Test and prepare yourself for the Exam.
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
What you will get in These Practice Test ? 
It Contains Sample Questions which are likely to be asked in the Real Exam.
These Questions Help you with Self-Study and Self-Assessment.
These Practice Test Helps you check your Knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latest DP-900 Azure Data Fundamentals Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/latest-dp-900-azure-data-fundamentals-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/latest-dp-900-azure-data-fundamentals-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Azure Data Fundamentals can be used to prepare for other Azure role-based certifications like Azure Database Administrator Associate or Azure Data Engineer Associate, but it’s not a prerequisite for any of them.
Course questions incudes questions from this categories:
Describe core data concepts (15-20%)
Describe how to work with relational data on Azure (25-30%)
Describe how to work with non-relational data on Azure (25-30%)
Describe an analytics workload on Azure (25-30%)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>أسرع دورة لتعلم مايكروسوفت ورد من البداية (Word 2019)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/%D8%A3%D8%B3%D8%B1%D8%B9-%D8%AF%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%A9-%D9%84%D8%AA%D8%B9%D9%84%D9%85-%D9%85%D8%A7%D9%8A%D9%83%D8%B1%D9%88%D8%B3%D9%88%D9%81%D8%AA-%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%AF-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A8%D8%AF%D8%A7%D9%8A%D8%A9-word-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/%D8%A3%D8%B3%D8%B1%D8%B9-%D8%AF%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%A9-%D9%84%D8%AA%D8%B9%D9%84%D9%85-%D9%85%D8%A7%D9%8A%D9%83%D8%B1%D9%88%D8%B3%D9%88%D9%81%D8%AA-%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%AF-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A8%D8%AF%D8%A7%D9%8A%D8%A9-word-2019/</guid>
      <description>تعلم مايكروسوفت ورد من البداية حتي الاحتراف (Word 2019)
هو كورس مناسب للجميع من المستوي المبتدئ وحتي المستوي المتوسط ، حيث أن الشرح يبدأ معك خطوة بخطوة من الصفر ويضعك علي بداية طريق الإحتراف. الكورس مخصص لكل شخص يحب أن يتعلم أو يرغب بتطوير مهاراته في برنامج مايكروسوفت ورد. ويهدف إلي مساعدة جميع المتعاملين مع تكنولوجيا المعلومات نحو سهولة استخدام و بداية احتراف برنامج مايكروسوفت ورد.
في هذه الدورة سوف تتعلم أساسيات مايكروسوفت ورد ثم ستتعرف على الأدوات الرئيسية التي يجب استخدامها لإنشاء ملفات ورد ، ثم ستتعرف علي أبسط طرق تنسيق المستندات الخاصة بك ، ثم ستتعرف علي طرق إضافة الصور والجداول وغيرها من العناصر ، ثم ضبط حجم الصفحة و أبعادها ، و أخيرا الإعدادات المختلفة لطباعة المستنات.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>تعلم برمجة تطبيقات الموبايل للمبتدئين</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/%D8%AA%D8%B9%D9%84%D9%85-%D8%A8%D8%B1%D9%85%D8%AC%D8%A9-%D8%AA%D8%B7%D8%A8%D9%8A%D9%82%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D9%88%D8%A8%D8%A7%D9%8A%D9%84-%D9%84%D9%84%D9%85%D8%A8%D8%AA%D8%AF%D8%A6%D9%8A%D9%86/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/%D8%AA%D8%B9%D9%84%D9%85-%D8%A8%D8%B1%D9%85%D8%AC%D8%A9-%D8%AA%D8%B7%D8%A8%D9%8A%D9%82%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%85%D9%88%D8%A8%D8%A7%D9%8A%D9%84-%D9%84%D9%84%D9%85%D8%A8%D8%AA%D8%AF%D8%A6%D9%8A%D9%86/</guid>
      <description>تطبقات الموبايل هي نوع من أنواع البرمجيات التي يتم تشغيلها على الموبايل أو التابلت أو الساعات الرقمية و التي تعد من أحدث أنواع البرمجياتو هناك نوعان من أنواع أنظمة التشغيل الخاصة بالموبايل (الاندرويد و الاي أو اس).
في هذه الدورة التدريبية سوف نتعلم كيفية تطوير برامج للموبايل بطريقة سهلة و مبسرة و لا تحتاج إلى أي خبرة سابقة بالبرمجة سوف نستخدم برنامج MIT App Inventor في تطوير برامج الموبايل و الذي تم تصميمه من جامعة MIT و شركة Google العالمية.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI-900/AZ-900Microsoft Azure Practice Test Updated April2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ai-900/az-900microsoft-azure-practice-test-updated-april2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 10:31:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ai-900/az-900microsoft-azure-practice-test-updated-april2021/</guid>
      <description>This AI900 is an opportunity to demonstrate knowledge of common ML and AI workloads and how to implement them on Azure.
This exam (AI900) is intended for candidates with both technical and non-technical backgrounds. Data science and software engineering experience are not required; however, some general programming knowledge or experience would be beneficial.
Azure AI Fundamentals can be used to prepare for other Azure role-based certifications like Azure Data Scientist Associate or Azure AI Engineer Associate,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS Crash Course For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/css-crash-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 10:31:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/css-crash-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Learn CSS Crash Course
Ever wonder how the latest website designs are made? Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) are the main coding files used to layout a website and its design. CSS 3 is the latest in styling standards, and it brings several new properties and declarations you can use to make your website design more easily created. CSS is currently the only standard in website design that plugs directly into your HTML, even the latest HTML 5 standards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Bootcamp 2021 Build 15 working Applications and Games</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-bootcamp-2021-build-15-working-applications-and-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-bootcamp-2021-build-15-working-applications-and-games/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of getting videos and lectures on just python basics and syntaxes or just strucked in college studies and hello world program. so I guess you have to give a try to this course this course is designed after analysing what a student need to study python. After analysing what they required and what they want in a course, how they can easily start any course but didn&#39;t able to finish it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create own Artificial Neural Network in Python</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/create-own-artificial-neural-network-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/create-own-artificial-neural-network-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Artificial neural networks (ANNs), also known as neural networks (NNs), are computer systems that are modelled after the biological neural networks that make up animal brains.
In this course ,we will learn to create our own neural networks with python.
Details are:
Introduction to artificial neural network
Python basics
Let&#39;s understand algorithm
Implement ANN in python
Wrapping up

Introduction to artificial neural network: Artificial neural networks simulates the functioning of human brain .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linkerd - Service mesh for Kubernetes - 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/linkerd-service-mesh-for-kubernetes-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/linkerd-service-mesh-for-kubernetes-2021/</guid>
      <description>A different kind of service mesh
Ultra light, ultra simple, ultra powerful. Linkerd adds security, observability, and reliability to Kubernetes, without the complexity. CNCF-hosted and 100% open source.

Instant platform health metrics
Instantly track success rates, latencies, and request volumes for every meshed workload, without changes or config.
Simpler than any other mesh
Minimalist, Kubernetes-native design. No hidden magic, as little YAML and as few CRDs as possible.
Zero-config mutual TLS</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Server 2012 R2 - Hands-on Training Part I</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-server-2012-r2-hands-on-training-part-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-server-2012-r2-hands-on-training-part-i/</guid>
      <description>About this course: 
This is Part I of a two-part series for learning Windows Server 2012 r2. Part I is for those needing to become familiar with Server 2012, virtualization, and configuring a Microsoft network from the ground up. In this first part, students will learn how to install and configure Server 2012 r2 just as they would as network administrators or networking consultants.
Part one of the course trains the student on installing, configuring, and managing the most common roles and features found on a Microsoft network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Server 2012 R2 - Intermediate Hands-on Training</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-server-2012-r2-intermediate-hands-on-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-server-2012-r2-intermediate-hands-on-training/</guid>
      <description>Please do not enroll in this course until you have completed the first building of your virtual lab environment. If you cannot create a virtual install of Server 2012, r2 using a Hypervisor, you will not partake in the lab exercises. 
This course picks up where Windows Server 2012r2 - Hands-on Training Part I leaves off. In part I of the course, we looked at installing and configuring a Windows Server 2012 r2 domain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Analytics Real-World Projects in Python</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/data-analytics-real-world-projects-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 13:08:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/data-analytics-real-world-projects-in-python/</guid>
      <description>This is the first course that gives hands-on Data Analysis Projects using Python..


Can you start right now?
A frequently asked question of Python Beginners is: &#34;Do I need to become an expert in Python coding before I can start working on Data Analysis Projects?&#34;
The clear answer is: &#34;No!
You just require some Python Basics like data types, simple operations/operators, lists and numpy arrays that you can learn from my Free Python course &#39;Basics Of Python&#39;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C# Full Course in 5 Hours [in Arabic]</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/c#-full-course-in-5-hours-in-arabic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:16:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/c#-full-course-in-5-hours-in-arabic/</guid>
      <description>*هذا الكورس لكل من يريد البدء بلغة سي شارب الجميلة من الصفر و*
-ستتعلم الكثير من الأشياء في هذا الكورس بالتفصيل الذي يجعلك تفهم حتى ولو نسبة قليلة ,المهم أن تجرب وتحلل العديد من المشاكل في ابرمجة -ستتعلم في الكورس المبادئ من تحت الصفر حتى , ستصل الى نقطة يمكنك اختيار المجال الذي يريجك فأنت تعرف كل ما تريد معرفته بعد انهاء الكورس لتتخصص وتبدع في مجال معين .
ستتعلم الأساسيات بالتفصيل</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>480 Questions: Scrum Master Certification &amp; 2 Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/480-questions-scrum-master-certification-2-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 20:12:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/480-questions-scrum-master-certification-2-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>480 Questions for Scrum Master Certification &amp;amp; 2 Practice Tests
This has 480 questions with answers and explanations, that prepare you to answer questions in professional scrum master certification assessments of leading organizations.
Please note:: This has same questions from our course &#34;Practice Tests - Scrum Master Certification Assessments 2021&#34;, but in video format.
  · In Video Format
 · Prepared keeping Scrum org Professional Master® I (PSM®) certification assessment in mind</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ETHICAL HACKING IN TAMIL</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ethical-hacking-in-tamil/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ethical-hacking-in-tamil/</guid>
      <description>In This Course You Will be Taught many Hacking Demonstration Like Android Hacking,Instagram Hacking, Wifi Hacking and Cybersecurity Related Challenges like CTF etc.


Know The Some Basics

What is Ethical Hacking?

Ethical Hacking sometimes called as Penetration Testing is an act of intruding/penetrating into system or networks to find out threats, vulnerabilities in those systems which a malicious attacker may find and exploit causing loss of data, financial loss or other major damages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Ethical Hacking Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ultimate-ethical-hacking-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ultimate-ethical-hacking-course/</guid>
      <description>What is ethical hacking?
Ethical hacking involves an authorized attempt to gain unauthorized access to a computer system, application, or data. Carrying out an ethical hack involves duplicating strategies and actions of malicious attackers. This practice helps to identify security vulnerabilities which can then be resolved before a malicious attacker has the opportunity to exploit them.
Also known as “white hats,” ethical hackers are security experts that perform these assessments. The proactive work they do helps to improve an organization’s security posture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MS Word for Novice to Expert : 2021 Updated</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ms-word-for-novice-to-expert-2021-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ms-word-for-novice-to-expert-2021-updated/</guid>
      <description>An ultimate course for novice who want to learn basic MS Word. This course will help you to have clear concept of using MS Word. After complete this course using of MS Word will be very easy and friendly to you. This course focused from beginner level to advance level and its covered up with almost every major part of MS Word for using in personal and business uses.  Ratings: 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python And Flask Framework Complete Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-and-flask-framework-complete-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-and-flask-framework-complete-course/</guid>
      <description>This course is a depth introduction to fundamental python programming concepts.
Learn Python From Beginner To Advanced Level
 I’ve created thorough, extensive, but easy to follow content which you’ll easily understand and absorb.
 The course starts with the basics, including Python fundamentals, programming, and user interaction.

The curriculum is going to be very hands-on as we walk you from start to finish becoming a professional Python developer. We will start from the very beginning by teaching you Python basics and programming fundamentals, and then going into advanced topics and different career fields in Python so you can get real-life practice and be ready for the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Engineering, Debugging and Malware Analysis - 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/reverse-engineering-debugging-and-malware-analysis-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/reverse-engineering-debugging-and-malware-analysis-2021/</guid>
      <description>*Printable online certificate available upon completion of course*
Breaking something down and putting it back together is a process that helps people understand how things were made.
 A person would be able to redo and reproduce an origami by unfolding it first. Knowing how cars work requires understanding each major and minor mechanical part and their purposes. The complex nature of the human anatomy requires people to understand each and every part of the body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practice Python by Solving 250&#43; Python Problems</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/practice-python-by-solving-250-python-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 17:46:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/practice-python-by-solving-250-python-problems/</guid>
      <description>Why would you take this course?
Practice and boost your Python 3 skills with 250+ coding exercises.
I am answering all your questions, usually in less than 24 hours.
No slides, no boring theory, no rambling, no chitchat. Just coding exercises.
There is NO REQUIREMENT of any cross-platform. You just need a desktop/laptop and start your practice on Udemy inbuilt IDE without any software!!! 
What&#39;s this course all about?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1Y0-200 Citrix XenDesktop 7 Solutions General Practice Exam</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/1y0-200-citrix-xendesktop-7-solutions-general-practice-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:15:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/1y0-200-citrix-xendesktop-7-solutions-general-practice-exam/</guid>
      <description>125 UNIQUE practice questions for 1Y0-200 Citrix XenDesktop 7 Solutions General Practice Exam
Practice tests are created by Subject Matter Experts and the questions always stay current with the actual exam.
100% verified answers and explanations to each question.
After taking the practice test you can atleast get 80% on the main exam.
Official Exam Details:
Exam Name : 1Y0-200 Citrix XenDesktop 7 Solutions General Practice Exam
Total Questions : 125</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Forensics for Pentesters - Hands-on Learning</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-forensics-for-pentesters-hands-on-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-forensics-for-pentesters-hands-on-learning/</guid>
      <description>Digital forensics is becoming very important in Cyber Security to detect and backtrack Black Hat Criminals. It is essential to remove Hackers’ malicious backdoors/malware and trace them back to avoid possible future incidents. Digital forensics is becoming very important in Cyber Security to detect and backtrack Black Hat Criminals. Digital forensics is essential to remove Hackers’ malicious backdoors/malware and trace them back to avoid possible future incidents.
This course acts as a digital forensics’ primer for pentesters and cybersecurity professionals wanting to expand their knowledge and add additional tools and skills to their resumes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS Complete Course For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/css-complete-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 20:19:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/css-complete-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Learn CSS Complete Course
CSS Course with basics and advanced concepts of CSS
Ever wonder how the latest website designs are made? Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) are the main coding files used to layout a website and its design. CSS 3 is the latest in styling standards, and it brings several new properties and declarations you can use to make your website design more easily created. CSS is currently the only standard in website design that plugs directly into your HTML, even the latest HTML 5 standards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethical Hacking - Hands-On Training - Part I</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ethical-hacking-hands-on-training-part-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 20:19:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ethical-hacking-hands-on-training-part-i/</guid>
      <description>Course Overview
This course provides learners with a basic level of competency using a hands-on approach to gaining practical experience as a penetration tester or an ethical hacker (white, grey, or black). This course provides a fundamental look at offensive security concepts and techniques using a virtual install of Kali Linux and three different target victims, Windows XP, Windows 7, Server 2008, and Linux (Metesploitable2). This course provides a 100% hands-on approach to learning to be an ethical hacker or a pentester.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermediate Ethical Hacking Hands-on Training</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/intermediate-ethical-hacking-hands-on-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 20:19:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/intermediate-ethical-hacking-hands-on-training/</guid>
      <description>Alert -
Intermediate Ethical Hacking Hands-on Training is a continuation of Ethical Hacking - Hands-on Training Part I. Before taking this course, students should have completed an introduction to an ethical hacking or pentesting course. Students should have completed Ethical Hacking - Hands-on Training Part I for best results before signing up for the intermediate course. 
Intermediate Ethical Hacking Hands-on Training picks up where Part I leaves off. In Part I, students was taught the fundamentals of pentesting while being introduced to some basic skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI (Artificial Intelligence) for CXOs &amp; Senior Managers</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ai-artificial-intelligence-for-cxos-senior-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ai-artificial-intelligence-for-cxos-senior-managers/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;This course covers concepts &amp;amp; case studies for executives and senior managers to better understand AI. This course doesn&#39;t cover programming aspects of AI&amp;gt;
Demystifying Artificial Intelligence including ML, DL, NLP, Industry 4.0, IoT &amp;amp; RPA with Caselets for CxOs and Senior Managers.
AI, AI, AI Everywhere! If you don’t do something about AI, you will be left behind or disrupted into extinction – this is a message that executives, Managers, Team Leaders and CXOs often hear, especially in the last year or so from consultants, vendors, industry experts or the IT organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-304: Microsoft Azure Architect Design -  Prep Exam Tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/az-304-microsoft-azure-architect-design-prep-exam-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/az-304-microsoft-azure-architect-design-prep-exam-tests/</guid>
      <description>I help you to have the best performance when taking the AZ-304 exam, with updated practical Tests that are not designed to simulate the exam scenario. The questions are based on the examination program described in the official documentation. The questions that appear in each practical test are recent. You will gain more confidence in exam preparation and evaluate them against the exam content.
Benefits:
4 complete mock exams (updated questions)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-400 Microsoft Azure DevOps Solutions : Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/az-400-microsoft-azure-devops-solutions-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/az-400-microsoft-azure-devops-solutions-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>The main highlight of the AZ-400 practice tests is the coverage of all recently added AZ-400 exam topics.
The AZ-400 exam, also called Designing and Implementing Microsoft DevOps Solutions, focuses primarily on testing candidates&#39; skills for Azure DevOps functions.
 The exam primarily evaluates candidates&#39; experience in the subject to work with people, technologies and processes to provide constant business value.
The high demand for DevOps is being driven by the wave of digital transformation with requirements for faster delivery of software solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become A Certified Python Programmer: Python Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/become-a-certified-python-programmer-python-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/become-a-certified-python-programmer-python-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>What is Python?
Python is an interpreted, object-oriented, high-level programming language with dynamic semantics. ... Python&#39;s simple, easy to learn syntax emphasizes readability and therefore reduces the cost of program maintenance. Python supports modules and packages, which encourages program modularity and code reuse. It was created by Guido van Rossum, and released in 1991.

Why Python?
Python works on different platforms (Windows, Mac, Linux, Raspberry Pi, etc).
Python has a simple syntax similar to the English language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Foundation</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/devops-foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/devops-foundation/</guid>
      <description>If you are new to DevOps, this course will give you the basic information about DevOps, including key concepts and the terminologies. This course covers the DevOps Full Stack: People and Culture, Processes and Practices, Technology and Automation. People and Culture:
You will be able to summarize the cultural, structural, and technological barriers that IT faces, when attempting to deliver services at the right quality, speed, and cost, and why challenges are faced when implementing DevOps in today’s organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Complete Course For Python Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-complete-course-for-python-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-complete-course-for-python-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Learn Python From Beginner To Advanced Level
 I’ve created thorough, extensive, but easy to follow content which you’ll easily understand and absorb.
 The course starts with the basics, including Python fundamentals, programming, and user interaction.

The curriculum is going to be very hands-on as we walk you from start to finish becoming a professional Python developer. We will start from the very beginning by teaching you Python basics and programming fundamentals, and then going into advanced topics and different career fields in Python so you can get real-life practice and be ready for the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP C_FSUTIL_60 Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sap-c_fsutil_60-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sap-c_fsutil_60-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>New challenges are part of life and I know that you will overcome them if you really find the right way.
We created the SAP C_FSUTIL_60 test practice, for you to have good results and pass your official exam.
You will have lifetime access to practice tests and future updates without worrying about new fees.
C_FSUTIL_60 - SAP Certified Associate - Utilities with SAP ERP 6.0
SAP Certified Associate Utilities with SAP ERP 6.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI-900 Azure AI Fundamentals Real Only Practice Set</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ai-900-azure-ai-fundamentals-real-only-practice-set/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ai-900-azure-ai-fundamentals-real-only-practice-set/</guid>
      <description>With help of these AI-900 Practice Tests, you will be able to develop confidence inside you and these practice tests will help you to develop an understanding of all the concepts of AI-900 to pass the AI-900 exam. If you are willing to instantly get AI-900 certified this practice test is for you. I am not including extra questions in these practice tests to save your time. This test contains only real exam questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PL-600 : MS Power Platform Solution Architect Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pl-600-ms-power-platform-solution-architect-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pl-600-ms-power-platform-solution-architect-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Exam PL-600 Microsoft Power Platform Solution Architect: Tests
Exam PL-600 candidate for the Power Platform Solution Architect Expert certification, you work with stakeholders and focus on solutions that affect your organization’s broad business and technical needs. A solution architect has functional and technical knowledge of the Power Platform, Dynamics 365 customer engagement apps, related Microsoft cloud solutions, and other third-party technologies. Microsoft Power Platform solution architects lead successful implementations and focus on how solutions address the broader business and technical needs of organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI-102 Microsoft Azure AI Engineer Associate Exam Tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ai-102-microsoft-azure-ai-engineer-associate-exam-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ai-102-microsoft-azure-ai-engineer-associate-exam-tests/</guid>
      <description>With help of these AI-102 Practice Tests, you will be able to develop confidence inside you and these practice tests will help you to develop an understanding of all the concepts of AI-102 to pass the AI-102 exam. If you are willing to instantly get AI-102 certified this practice test is for you. I am not including extra questions in these practice tests to save your time. This test contains only real exam questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-204 PracticeTest Developing Solutions for Microsoft Azure</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/az-204-practicetest-developing-solutions-for-microsoft-azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/az-204-practicetest-developing-solutions-for-microsoft-azure/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Azure Developer Associate exam is tougher than compared to Azure Fundamentals. The exam will test your Azure knowledge on all the topics. It&#39;s highly recommended to take a practice test before taking the official exam.
These Azure Developer Associate training practice papers are developed by the industry experts &amp;amp; are followed by multiple students. This set involves all the latest topics covered under AZ-204.
What do we offer in our Developing solution Microsoft Azure training test?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DP-900 - Azure Data Fundamental - Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/dp-900-azure-data-fundamental-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/dp-900-azure-data-fundamental-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>With the help of these DP-900 Practice Tests, you will be able to develop confidence inside you and these practice tests will help you develop an understanding of all the concepts of DP-900 to pass the AI-900 exam. If you are willing to instantly get DP-900 certified this practice test is for you. I am not including extra questions in these practice tests to save your time. This test contains only real exam questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM Big Data Engineer Certification 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ibm-big-data-engineer-certification-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ibm-big-data-engineer-certification-2021/</guid>
      <description>This certification is intended for IBM Big Data Engineers. The Big Data Engineer works directly with the Data Architect and hands-on Developers to convert the architect&#39;s Big Data vision and blueprint into a Big Data reality. The Data Engineer possesses a deep level of technical knowledge and experience across a wide array of products and technologies. A Data Engineer understands how to apply technologies to solve big data problems, and has the ability to build large-scale data processing systems for the enterprise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP C_THR12_65 Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sap-c_thr12_65-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sap-c_thr12_65-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Preparing from the beginning of life we prepare ourselves for the challenges of taking the first step or speaking the first words.
In the current world, that is, in the present, it remains the same or you prepare for the exam or you may fail to waste time and money.
Practice tests offer mock questions where you can answer your questions if you are really prepared for the official exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate Exam SAA-C02</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-exam-saa-c02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-exam-saa-c02/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate Exam SAA-C02
The AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate (SAA-C02) examination is intended for individuals who perform in a solutions architect role. This exam validates an examinee’s ability to effectively demonstrate knowledge of how to architect and deploy secure and robust applications on AWS technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-104 Microsoft Azure Administrator Practice Exam july 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/az-104-microsoft-azure-administrator-practice-exam-july-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/az-104-microsoft-azure-administrator-practice-exam-july-2021/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; FULLY UPDATED to the latest AZ-104 Microsoft Azure Administrator exam version july 2021
There are a lot of courses out there that are claiming that their courses are fully updated, but they&#39;re actually not! Our practice tests contain the latest additions on the new AZ-104 topics, the exam received an update in july 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-104 Microsoft Azure Administrator Practice Exams JUN21</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/az-104-microsoft-azure-administrator-practice-exams-jun21/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/az-104-microsoft-azure-administrator-practice-exams-jun21/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; UPDATED to the latest AZ-104 Microsoft Azure Administrator exam JUN 2021
Microsoft&#39;s AZ-104 Microsoft Azure Administrator exam is one of the way to prove that you have a deep and thorough understanding &amp;amp; experience in Microsoft Azure. As you may aware, employers always look for latest certifications in the resume while filing up vacancies. Getting the Azure Administrator Associate certification is the ultimate proof of your expertise in Azure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-900 Microsoft Azure Fundamentals Exam - july 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/az-900-microsoft-azure-fundamentals-exam-july-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/az-900-microsoft-azure-fundamentals-exam-july-2021/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;AZ-900 Microsoft Azure Fundamentals Exam - july 2021
Microsoft Azure Fundamentals is the first certification exam for Azure cloud. Through the completion of our three practice exams, you will gain all knowledge needed to successfully achieve your Azure qualification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AZ-900 Microsoft Azure Fundamentals Practice Exams JUN2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/az-900-microsoft-azure-fundamentals-practice-exams-jun2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/az-900-microsoft-azure-fundamentals-practice-exams-jun2021/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; AZ-900 Microsoft Azure Fundamentals Practice Exams
The AZ-900 Microsoft Azure Fundamentals exam is intended for beginners who work with cloud-based solutions and services. Candidates should be able to demonstrate a fundamental knowledge of cloud concepts, Azure services, workloads, security, privacy, pricing, support, as well as networking, storage, compute, application support, and application development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CLF-C01  AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/clf-c01-aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/clf-c01-aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Get ready to validate your skills with the latest and most up-to-date practice exam from the AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner and become a Certified Professional now!
AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam (CLF-C01)
The AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner examination is intended for individuals who have the knowledge and skills necessary to effectively demonstrate an overall understanding of the AWS Cloud, independent of specific technical roles addressed by other AWS Certifications. The exam can be taken at a testing center or from the comfort and convenience of a home or office location as an online proctored exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PDE-GooglE Cloud Professional Data Engineer Practice tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pde-google-cloud-professional-data-engineer-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pde-google-cloud-professional-data-engineer-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Description
This Google certified professional data engineer practice test 2021 is a sum of modules covering design systems that ingest large volume data, effective storage of data, efficient processing and analysis of data. The test series also includes questions that revolve arounds the utilization of tools for visualization, reporting and machine learning.
Post the practice test the applicants will have a sound knowledge of how to build, tune and monitor a high performance data system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP C_TSCM52_67 Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sap-c_tscm52_67-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sap-c_tscm52_67-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>Improve your score with hours of practice tests is the right way to test your knowledge with lifetime access to study anywhere.
Understanding the exam topics is one of the advantages of preparing for the official exam.
Find out more about the exam: C_TSCM52_67 - SAP Certified Application Associate - Acquisition with SAP ERP 6.0 EhP7
The SAP C_TSCM52_67 certification exam verifies that the candidate has adequate knowledge in the Purchasing area to meet the requirements of the consultant profile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP HANA C_HANATEC_12 Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sap-hana-c_hanatec_12-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sap-hana-c_hanatec_12-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>In today&#39;s world, people need a source of study to prepare for life&#39;s new challenges.
Welcome to the practice tests for the exam: SAP C_HANATEC_12.
Our goal is to test your knowledge with questions and answers with the latest exam references, giving you the chance to pass the first attempt.
You have lifelong access to practice tests, meaning you can study from anywhere without hurrying to win this challenge.
Brief Details</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Coach Fundamentos basado en Certtificacion CertiProf</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/agile-coach-fundamentos-basado-en-certtificacion-certiprof/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/agile-coach-fundamentos-basado-en-certtificacion-certiprof/</guid>
      <description>Este curso muestra aspectos básicos del rol de un Agile Coach.
Basado en el currículo académico desarrollado por CertiProf. No es una vision completa del impacto de un Agile Coach, pero si brinda todos los fundamentos requeridos para iniciar una carrera que considero nunca termina.
Ser un Agile Coach es un desafío y responsabilidad que debe mantener abierta la formación constante. Tener un mindset de aprendizaje constante.
Los portales de trabajo de todos los países muestran cifras de la necesidad de este rol, sus responsabilidades y sus ingresos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete CompTIA Network&#43; (N10-007) Video Training Series</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-comptia-network-n10-007-video-training-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-comptia-network-n10-007-video-training-series/</guid>
      <description>** Get Ready to Crush Your CompTIA Network+ (N10-007) Exam **
Embark on (or continue) your IT certification journey with CompTIA’s Network+ certification. The Network+ certification acts as a “sampler platter” of networking, where you get to “taste test” a wide variety of technologies, like cloud, wireless, software defined networking, route/switch, security, troubleshooting, network management, and so many others.
Guiding you through each step of your journey is award-winning instructor and double CCIE (Cisco Certified Internetworking Expert) Kevin Wallace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Introduction to Cybersecurity 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-introduction-to-cybersecurity-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-introduction-to-cybersecurity-2021/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Complete Introduction to Cybersecurity 2021. In this course, you will learn the fundamentals of I.T. while learning the working components of cybersecurity. No prior knowledge or skill is required. If you are a cybersecurity student, aspiring security professional, security enthusiast or someone intrigued to learn more about the industry, this course will provide a springboard for you to learn the basics. As a current cybersecurity student, I know exactly what type of questions, doubts, and thoughts you are experiencing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CompTIA Cloud&#43; CV0-002 Bootcamp Get Certified!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/comptia-cloud-cv0-002-bootcamp-get-certified/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/comptia-cloud-cv0-002-bootcamp-get-certified/</guid>
      <description>Course comes with a 900+ page study guide with exam tips! Updated June 2020
This course is taught by a current CompTIA&amp;nbsp;SME&amp;nbsp;and CompTIA&amp;nbsp;Cloud Plus Train the Trainer.&amp;nbsp; 
This course is meant to provide you the baseline knowledge to pass the course and is meant for professionals that have IT&amp;nbsp;experience.&amp;nbsp; Get Certified promptly and efficiently.

The CompTIA Cloud+ certification is an internationally recognized validation of the knowledge required of IT practitioners working in cloud computing environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps - Introducción y Fundamentos no técnicos</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/devops-introducci%C3%B3n-y-fundamentos-no-t%C3%A9cnicos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/devops-introducci%C3%B3n-y-fundamentos-no-t%C3%A9cnicos/</guid>
      <description>DevOps Fundamentos 
*** BONUS *** Preparación Examen para DevOps Essentials Certification
Este curso le brindara conocimiento general y fundamental de lo que es DevOps y lo que no es DevOps.
No es un curso de uso de herramientas de software.&amp;nbsp;
No es un curso de implementación de entrega continua.
Este curso forma parte de la serie que he creado de &#34;alcanza la certificación&#34;. Este curso te brindara la posibilidad de entender la importancia de DevOps, un poco de mapeo con Scrum y otras técnicas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethical Hacking for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ethical-hacking-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ethical-hacking-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>This course is for anyone interested in becoming an ethical hacker, no matter your current skill level. The curriculum is designed for absolute beginners interested in a career as a security professional, beginning with the absolute basics of penetration testing, and progressing to advanced topics and techniques. Get started today in your Ethical Hacking career.
The goal of ethical hacking is to find security vulnerabilities in an organization’s digital systems and networks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ethical Hacking: Introduction to Exploits</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ethical-hacking-introduction-to-exploits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ethical-hacking-introduction-to-exploits/</guid>
      <description>In a corner of the internet where there are no rules, there is a group of people who do not play by the rules. These are the hackers and crackers who cross lines and get away with it.
It&#39;s been around for a long time. There are entire generations of hackers that merely know how to utilize exploits; So what is an exploit?
In the security software industry, an exploit is a piece of software, a chunk of data, or a sequence of commands that takes advantage of a bug or vulnerability in order to cause unintended or unanticipated behavior to occur on computer software, hardware, or something electronic (usually computerized).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Face Recognition Web App with Machine Learning in Flask</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/face-recognition-web-app-with-machine-learning-in-flask/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/face-recognition-web-app-with-machine-learning-in-flask/</guid>
      <description>Face Recognition Web Project using Machine Learning in Flask Python
Face recognition is one of the most widely used in my application. If at all you want to develop and deploy the application on the web only knowledge of machine learning or deep learning is not enough. You also need to know the creation of pipeline architecture and call it from the client-side, HTTP request, and many more. While doing so you might face many challenges while developing the app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FPGA UART communication protocol series Vol1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fpga-uart-communication-protocol-series-vol1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fpga-uart-communication-protocol-series-vol1/</guid>
      <description>This Course was made by a professional electronic engineer specializes in FPGA !
This course is the first one on a series of courses about communication protocols.
In this course you will learn everything you need to know about UART
No prior communications protocol knowledge is needed - I will teach everything about serial communication and how to sample it, and about the issues we might have inside FPGA when trying to sample a signal from the outside world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacking Ético: Fundamentos de Rede e Ataques de Camada</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/hacking-%C3%A9tico-fundamentos-de-rede-e-ataques-de-camada/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/hacking-%C3%A9tico-fundamentos-de-rede-e-ataques-de-camada/</guid>
      <description>Hola,
Bem-vindos ao curso de segurança cibernética “Segurança Cibernética: Fundamentos de Rede &amp;amp; Ataques de Camada de Rede“.
Para se tornar um Hacker Ético e aprender a hackear, o curso Fundamentos de Rede &amp;amp; Ataques de Camada de Rede é o começo perfeito para você. Este é um meio divertido porque a gente pode realmente olhar para os dados que vão nas redes como: como farejar a rede e coletar informações da rede.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Android Hacking For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-android-hacking-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-android-hacking-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>We will use msfvenom for creating a payload and save it as an apk file. After generating the payload, we need to setup a listener to Metasploit framework. Once the target downloads and installs the malicious apk then, an attacker can easily get back a meterpreter session on Metasploit. An attacker needs to do some social engineering to install apk on the victim’s mobile device.
in this course we gonna learn different kind of lauching attacks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mathematics &amp; Statistics for Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/mathematics-statistics-for-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/mathematics-statistics-for-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;This course doesn&#39;t cover programming related to AI but helps you to build a strong foundation in math &amp;amp; statistics needed for AI&amp;gt;
The trainer of this course is an AI expert and he has observed that many students and young professionals make the mistake of learning machine learning without understanding the core concepts in maths and statistics. This course will help to address that gap in a big way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Java Game Development Course for 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-java-game-development-course-for-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-java-game-development-course-for-2021/</guid>
      <description>Learn JAVA by developing fun games from scratch.&amp;nbsp; This course is for everyone who has desire to learn JAVA. The game complexity increases with every section and you will be able to rise your knowledge throughout the course. You will develop amazing games and you will see how JAVA works moving things on screen and objects interaction. You will also create and import pictures used in the games and get familiar with creating randomly movable enemies, animating the game characters and playing music while playing the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VIVADO Xilinx FPGA -Learn From The Beginning (&#43;PCIe project)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/vivado-xilinx-fpga-learn-from-the-beginning-pcie-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/vivado-xilinx-fpga-learn-from-the-beginning-pcie-project/</guid>
      <description>In this course you will learn how to use VIVADO tool to develop Xilinx FPGAs.
As it&#39;s easy for you to understand, working as an FPGA developer is the most profitable job in the Hardware development industry. And by now, it is a profession with great demand in every big company: Apple, Microsoft, Intel, Amazon, Google and many others!
If you want to work as an FPGA developer or just to know how to design an FPGA this is the course for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Command Line (cmd) &amp; Batch Script Management</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/windows-command-line-cmd-batch-script-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/windows-command-line-cmd-batch-script-management/</guid>
      <description>One of the many tools that administrators use on a daily basis is the Windows Command Line / Prompt. Over this course, you&#39;ll learn the following skills, which are often used in the real world:

* How to create, rename, move and delete files and directories.
* The different types of file systems and how to navigate between directories
*&amp;nbsp;Setting the date and time on your PC using the date, time and tzutil commands</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wireshark: Packet Analysis and Ethical Hacking: Core Skills</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/wireshark-packet-analysis-and-ethical-hacking-core-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/wireshark-packet-analysis-and-ethical-hacking-core-skills/</guid>
      <description>Learn Wireshark practically. Wireshark pcapng files provided so you can practice while you learn! There is so much to learn in this course:
- Capture Telnet, FTP, TFTP, HTTP passwords. - Replay VoIP conversations. - Capture routing protocol (OSPF) authentication passwords.
- Troubleshoot network issues.
- Free software.
- Free downloadable pcapng files.
- Answer quiz questions.
The course is very practical. You can practice while you learn!
Learn how to analyze and interpret network protocols and leverage Wireshark for what it was originally intended: Deep Packet Inspection and network analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner 500 Practice Exam Questions</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-500-practice-exam-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-500-practice-exam-questions/</guid>
      <description>Want to test your exam readiness for the Amazon AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner AND feel confident to pass your AWS exam first time? Then these ultimate AWS Cloud Practitioner exam questions are for you! These 6 practice tests reflect the difficulty of the Amazon Web Services exam questions and are the most similar to the real AWS exam experience available on Udemy as demonstrated by the fantastic student reviews from over 500,000 students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Developer Associate Exam Training 2021 [NEW]</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-developer-associate-exam-training-2021-new/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-developer-associate-exam-training-2021-new/</guid>
      <description>This popular AWS Developer Associate Training for the AWS Certified Developer Associate certification exam (DVA-C01) is packed with over 28 hours of comprehensive video lessons, hands-on labs, full-length practice exam simulation, quizzes and exam-crams. With our mixture of in-depth theory, architectural diagrams and hands-on training, you&#39;ll learn how to architect and build applications on Amazon Web Services, fully preparing you for the AWS Developer Certification exam. With this complete Udemy AWS Developer training course, you have everything you need to comfortably pass the AWS Developer Certification exam at the first attempt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate - 2021 [SAA-C02]</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-2021-saa-c02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-2021-saa-c02/</guid>
      <description>This Ultimate Exam Training for the AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate is packed with comprehensive video lessons, guided hands-on labs, a full-length practice exam, 3 hours exam-cram lectures and 90&amp;nbsp;Quiz questions! If you are looking to confidently pass your AWS Solutions Architect certification exam first time AND learn how to build the best solution architecture on Amazon Web Services - then this AWS Certification course is for you!
This AWS Training covers 70% of what you need to know for the AWS Certified SysOps Administrator Associate and AWS Certified Developer Associate Exams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate: Complete Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-complete-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-complete-course/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the AWS Certified Solutions Architect Complete Course!
Where you’re going to learn how to get started with AWS as a solutions architect so you can pass the exam and officially get certified.
I want to congratulate you for making the decision to get certified as a solutions architect.
In this practical, hands-on course our main objective is to give you education not just to understand the ins and outs of AWS, but also to learn exactly how you can apply what you learn to real world scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Solutions Architect Professional SAP-C01 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-solutions-architect-professional-sap-c01-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-solutions-architect-professional-sap-c01-2021/</guid>
      <description>This is the year to pass your AWS&amp;nbsp;Certified Solutions Architect Professional exam!&amp;nbsp;Get access to the most comprehensive and well-delivered course for this exam anywhere on the Internet. This AWS&amp;nbsp;Solutions Architect professional certification course will have you sailing through the AWS&amp;nbsp;exam with confidence. Delivered using visual animations, architectural diagrams, and hands-on exercises this course will have you covered - whatever your preferred learning style.
This course is for you if you:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python And Django Framework For Beginners Complete Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-and-django-framework-for-beginners-complete-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-and-django-framework-for-beginners-complete-course/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Learn Python From Scratch
 I’ve created thorough, extensive, but easy to follow content which you’ll easily understand and absorb.
 The course starts with the basics, including Python fundamentals, programming, and user interaction.

The curriculum is going to be very hands-on as we walk you from start to finish becoming a professional Python developer. We will start from the very beginning by teaching you Python basics and programming fundamentals, and then going into advanced topics and different career fields in Python so you can get real-life practice and be ready for the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Python Modules to Create AI Projects For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/some-python-modules-to-create-ai-projects-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/some-python-modules-to-create-ai-projects-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>In this course, we are going to cover some python modules which help us to make AI projects like J.A.R.V.I.S, Face recognition, Face detection, etc. In my next course i will show you how to create J.A.R.V.I.S .python is high level interpreted&amp;nbsp; language, in this project we are going to use python 3.6 Ratings: 3.29/5
Enrollments: 52297
Coupon Code: LETS_DO_IT
Current Price: FREE
Enroll NOW: Enroll now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner - Complete NEW Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-complete-new-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 12:19:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-cloud-practitioner-complete-new-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>100%&amp;nbsp;UPDATED in&amp;nbsp;MAY&amp;nbsp;2021:&amp;nbsp;This AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner training course has just been completely updated with 100% new content for May 2021! The course is packed with comprehensive video lessons, hands-on labs, practice exam questions, quizzes and exam-crams! If you are new to Amazon Web Services / Cloud Computing and looking to confidently pass your AWS Cloud Practitioner Certification Exam first time - then this value-packed AWS&amp;nbsp;training course is for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate Practice Exams</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-practice-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-practice-exams/</guid>
      <description>Want to test your exam readiness for the Amazon AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate AND feel confident to pass your AWS certification exam first time? Then these ultimate AWS Solutions Architect Associate practice exams are for you! These 6 practice tests reflect the difficulty of the Amazon Web Services exam questions and are the most similar to the real AWS exam experience available on Udemy as demonstrated by the fantastic student reviews from over 500,000 students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Certified SysOps Administrator Associate Practice Exams</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-sysops-administrator-associate-practice-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aws-certified-sysops-administrator-associate-practice-exams/</guid>
      <description>Want to maximize your chances of passing your AWS Certified SysOps Administrator Associate exam first time?&amp;nbsp;Then these brand-new AWS SysOps Administrator Associate practice exams are for you! These 3 sets of AWS&amp;nbsp;practice tests (with 65 practice questions each) reflect the difficulty of the Amazon Web Services exam questions and are the most similar to the real AWS certification exam experience available on Udemy. With this AWS Certification Training course, you&#39;ll know when you are ready to take your AWS Certified SysOps certification exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cursillo Excel Básico</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cursillo-excel-b%C3%A1sico/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cursillo-excel-b%C3%A1sico/</guid>
      <description>Curso de Bolsillo Excel que lo puedes llevar a todo lado. Tocaremos los temas más fundamentales pero a la vez indispensables cuando usamos Excel. Diseñado para todos aquellos que están empezando con esta poderosa herramienta. - Primero lo primero: En el primero video te cuento cuáles son los puntos a tratar. Luego, pasaremos al contenido principal del curso.&amp;nbsp; - Abordaremos Atajos y Truquitos para ya a empezar a sentir qué tan fácil resulta trabajar con la interfaz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring VirBELA 3D University Campus (2021 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/exploring-virbela-3d-university-campus-2021-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/exploring-virbela-3d-university-campus-2021-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the eighth course in Term 3 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Did you know?&amp;nbsp;Virtual worlds are simulated environments accessed by multiple users through an online interface or software. Virtual worlds integrate two things which can be intrinsic to human nature; social connectivity and creativeness.
Human beings are a social species that require verbal exchange to thrive and we are constantly seeking opportunities for interaction, expression and validation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>