<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Language Learning on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/language-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Language Learning on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 01:41:17 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/language-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Arabic Language Course: Learn to Read Arabic, Write &amp; Listen</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-language-course-learn-to-read-arabic-write-listen/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 01:41:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-language-course-learn-to-read-arabic-write-listen/</guid>
      <description>New Update: We added Arabic Audiobook + MP3 Files + Translation in English.
New Update: We added new Section to Learn Writing in Arabic.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 السلام عليكم

In this Course, you will learn to Read, Write &amp;amp; Listen to Arabic through Short Stories &amp;amp; Audiobooks.

This Course is divided into 9 Sections:
In the First Section: you will learn How to Write &amp;amp; Pronounce Arabic Alphabet, and we will take some words for each letter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Arabic Reading</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/basic-arabic-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/basic-arabic-reading/</guid>
      <description>Learning Arabic is challenging in many ways. This course focuses on building the skill to read any Arabic word, by both learning the alphabet, including learning the name, sound, and shapes of each letter. In addition, the diacritics that guide the pronunciation of words are also explained. Finally, major prefixes and suffixes are also introduced. After you complete this course, you will be able to recognize the letters of any word and sound it out, which is the first step to read Arabic script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Polish Course: Learn Polish for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-polish-course-learn-polish-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-polish-course-learn-polish-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to learn Polish? As the second most-spoken Slavic language with over 55 million native speakers, there are many benefits to learning this familiar, yet exotic language.
In this course, we’re going to take you through the first steps of your Polish journey, from absolute beginner to an intermediate level. Our lessons will cover everything, from teaching you how to read and write the Polish alphabet, to conjugating verbs and declining nouns, to forming sentences and describing yourself, the world around you and actions that take place within it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arabic language through Drama | learn and entertain</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-language-through-drama-learn-and-entertain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-language-through-drama-learn-and-entertain/</guid>
      <description>In this course you will learn Arabic by Fun, watching Arabic series. The method will I apply in my videos are new and creative. So I have made new methods to teach you Arabic, hopefully this method will help a lot students to learn Arabic easily.
And at the end if you got any questions, don&#39;t hesitate ask me directly. I will be happy to answer all of your questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Portuguese Course: Portuguese for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-portuguese-course-portuguese-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-portuguese-course-portuguese-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our ultimate Portuguese beginner course that will teach you Portuguese faster than you thought possible! If you’ve ever dreamed of travelling to Portugal and holding your own in real-life situations, being independent and able to communicate with the locals, our beginner series is the perfect place for you to continue your Portuguese journey! There’s always more to learn, and we’ve prepared yet another course to enrich your vocabulary, advance your grammar and help you express more and more complex thoughts, all in Portuguese!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master the English Irregular Verbs Once and For All</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/master-the-english-irregular-verbs-once-and-for-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/master-the-english-irregular-verbs-once-and-for-all/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&#39;m Carlos. I&#39;m a Trilingual Udemy Instructor, and I can&#39;t wait to help you improve your fluency, and other skills in speaking English.
I have created this shorter version for you to get a taste of another of my courses. This will help you see the quality of the course and our teaching style. Expect more information in the near future. 
When I designed this course, I put myself where you are now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sıfırdan Konuşturan İngilizce Kursu (20&#43; Saat)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/s%C4%B1f%C4%B1rdan-konu%C5%9Fturan-ingilizce-kursu-20-saat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/s%C4%B1f%C4%B1rdan-konu%C5%9Fturan-ingilizce-kursu-20-saat/</guid>
      <description>• Bir dil en iyi doğal haliyle öğrenilir, yani çocukların öğrendiği gibi, kelimeleri sık sık duyarak.

• Hem Türkçe hem Kürtçe konuşan arkadaşınızın neden İngilizce öğrenemediğini hiç düşündünüz mü?

• İngilizce zor diye mi?

• En zor dil hangisi?

• Size göre Çince mi?

• Peki 2 milyar insan Çinceyi nasıl konuşuyor?

• Peki okuma yazma bilmeyen anne babanın bile çocuğuna konuşma dilini öğretirken, üniversitede öğretmenlik okumuş birinin neden dil öğretemediğini?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to read Arabic for beginners | Basics &amp; principles</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-read-arabic-for-beginners-basics-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-read-arabic-for-beginners-basics-principles/</guid>
      <description>Arabic is widely taught in schools and universities and is used to varying degrees in workplaces, government and the media. Arabic, in its standard form, is the official language of 26 states, as well as the liturgical language of the religion of Islam, since the Quran and Hadith were written in Arabic.
In this course, you will learn how to read Arabic. by taking lessons gradually and easily, after finishing this course you will start practice reading by yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English grammar tenses &amp; structures, the ultimate course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/english-grammar-tenses-structures-the-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 11:17:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/english-grammar-tenses-structures-the-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>The course provides you with a variety of grammar rules that enable you to read, write and form perfect English sentences. The course forms a great combination of grammar rules with examples. It takes you step by step from understanding the rule into applying examples that enhance your English language skills. We add weekly quizzes with model answers.
 Ratings: 4.39/5
Enrollments: 174726
Coupon Code: SEPTEMBER26
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOEFL reading practice tests Questions and Answers</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/toefl-reading-practice-tests-questions-and-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/toefl-reading-practice-tests-questions-and-answers/</guid>
      <description>TOEFL reading practice tests Questions and Answers
2022 reading tests for TOEFL Test of English as a Foreign Language

Test of English as a Foreign Language TOEFL is a standardized test to measure the English language ability of non-native speakers wishing to enroll in English-speaking universities. The test is accepted by more than 11,000 universities and other institutions in over 150 countries. TOEFL is one of the two major English-language tests in the world, the other being the IELTS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deutsch - Klare Kommunikation  A2-C1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/deutsch-klare-kommunikation-a2-c1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/deutsch-klare-kommunikation-a2-c1/</guid>
      <description>Wie kann ich klar kommunizieren, das was mir wichtig ist?
Wie können Konflikte so angesprochen werden, dass mein Gegenüber bereit ist zu kooperieren?
Lernen Sie zu formulieren was Sie möchten, anstatt nur zu sagen was sie stört.
Kann ich mich so ausdrücken, dass das was ich bin, unzweideutig mitgeteilt wird?
Neben dem Erwerb von psychosozialen Kompetenzen für den Beruf und Alltag werden im Kurshilfreiche Kommunikationsstrukturen, sowie ein differenziertes psychologisches Vokabular erlernt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Language Practice Test</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/english-language-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/english-language-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>Preparing for Competitive Exams like IELTS or TOEFL and looking for more practice questions on English Grammar?
You have come to the right practice assessment course! 
Test your knowledge with this practice test created by experts who have years of experience in the field. Suitable for beginners who want to improve their understanding of written English or to improve their knowledge with explanations and timed tests.

Most questions and multiple choice and fill in the blank type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Egyptian Arabic through Cartoon movie</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-egyptian-arabic-through-cartoon-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-egyptian-arabic-through-cartoon-movie/</guid>
      <description>This is actually a new idea in teaching a foreign language , Hello everyone. I&#39;m Mr,Bakoor. I have been teaching Arabic for several years. so I have enough experience in teaching Arabic, in this course I come up with a new idea a new strategy to Egyptian Arabic this idea is you will get fun while learning Egyptian dialect. this idea will make memorization easier to, you will find it enjoyable and easy to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be an expert in English Grammar</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/be-an-expert-in-english-grammar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:52:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/be-an-expert-in-english-grammar/</guid>
      <description>The course has 14 sections. They display the different grammar rules in a funny way that depends on the animated cartoons. These 14 sections have 96 lectures. These 96 lectures have 2 hours of video content. This course takes you from level 1 to be a professional in the English grammar.  Ratings: 4.30/5
Enrollments: 72280
Coupon Code: SEPTEMBER16
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TESOL and TPRS Course (For Language Teachers)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tesol-and-tprs-course-for-language-teachers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:52:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/tesol-and-tprs-course-for-language-teachers/</guid>
      <description>Although uneducated parents can teach a languge to their children, how can educated teachers not teach a foreign language? In this course, you will learn how to teach a languge with a contemporary method but ancient.

In ancient times, people used to travel by horses or camels but then they invented cars and began to go everywhere with them. Today, we use planes. There is no doubt that cars are faster than horses, but planes are the fastest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Pronunciation Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/english-pronunciation-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/english-pronunciation-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Hi! My name is Professor G and I&#39;m an English teacher with more than 10 years of teaching experience. I previously studied French and Spanish at university, and I&#39;ve taught English in a number of countries around the world, including Brazil (Campinas), France (Paris) and Spain (Malaga). I understand the problems that language learners experience, especially when it comes to speaking the language. When I first moved to France, I had studied French for 5 years, but had very little speaking practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English language basics for beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/english-language-basics-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 12:13:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/english-language-basics-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>We make it easy for you to learn how to speak and write English fluently as a beginner learner. These English lessons will show you how to say and use almost anything in daily English conversation. Get started now with our speaking, vocabulary and grammar exercises that come with model answers. In this course, you will learn important topics and lessons in English, such as, Alphabet, numbers, saying hello, signs and symbols, telling the time, asking and answering questions about name, age, weather, classroom things, classroom instructions, days of the week, months of the year, seasons of the year, basic colors, simple shapes and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arabic: Learn Arabic Language| Online Arabic Language Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-learn-arabic-language-online-arabic-language-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 20:51:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-learn-arabic-language-online-arabic-language-course/</guid>
      <description>Marhaba (Hello and welcome)!
My name is Nezha, and welcome to Arabic 4 U!   ▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬▬
After taking this online Arabic language course, you will start to:
 Speak Arabic with Arabic speakers from around the world

 Understand Formal Arabic called Modern Standard Arabic MSA or Fusha
 Arabic speakers learn Modern Standard Arabic in school. It is used in Arabic books, Arabic news, Arabic documentaries, Arabic road signs, and Arabic formal speeches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Miller Analogies Test (MAT) TOP Practical Questions</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-miller-analogies-test-mat-top-practical-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-miller-analogies-test-mat-top-practical-questions/</guid>
      <description>Hello !
Most Common Miller Analogies Test (MAT) professional Questions with your hand
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily
The Miller Analogies Test (MAT) is a standardized test used both for graduate school admissions in the United States and entrance to high I.Q. societies. Created and still published by Harcourt Assessment (now a division of Pearson Education), the MAT consists of 120 questions in 60 minutes (formerly 100 questions in 50 minutes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Computer Basics Guide for Beginners: 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-computer-basics-guide-for-beginners-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-computer-basics-guide-for-beginners-2021/</guid>
      <description>The Computer Defined, Data versus Information, Classification of Computers based on how data is handled (Analog Computers, Digital Computers Hybrid Computers)
Computers for Individual Users or Personal Computers (Desktop Computers,Workstations, Laptops, Notebooks, Tablets, Handheld PCs, Smartphones)
Computers for Organizations (Network Server, Mainframes, Minicomputers, Supercomputers)
Parts of Computer System (Hardware , Software, User and Data)
Information Processing Cycle (Input, Processing, Output, Storage)
Computer Hardware Categorized ( Processing Devices, Memory Devices, Input and Output Devices, Storage Devices, Bus Interconnection)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American English Pronunciation for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/american-english-pronunciation-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/american-english-pronunciation-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling with your English pronunciation? 
Do you have a strong accent when speaking English?

Do native speakers always ask you to repeat yourself?

Do you want to begin speaking with an American accent confidently?

Do you what tips and help with speaking with an American accent? 
I welcome you to this - “American English Pronunciation Training - course where I will patiently guide you through the basic techniques you need to pronounce English sounds correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arabic complete beginner course through (Byna Yadek)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-complete-beginner-course-through-byna-yadek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/arabic-complete-beginner-course-through-byna-yadek/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I&#39;m Mr.Bakoor. I have been teaching Arabic for a while. I got students form All over the world. My respect for all of them. My students liked the way I teach because It&#39;s easy, it goes step by step, they easily understand and also show improvement,&amp;nbsp; I feel so happy when I my student telling me that they are really improving in Arabic, I hope to make Arabic teaching easier for everyone who think Learning Arabic is hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete French Course: Learn French for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-french-course-learn-french-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-french-course-learn-french-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to learn French? Dubbed the “language of love”, French is used by over 235 million speakers daily in over 54 countries. But why should you pick French out of all the languages you could be learning?
To start, France isn’t just one of the most beautiful countries in central Europe, but a global powerhouse with significant presence in the automobile, aircraft and chemical manufacturing, the electronic, machinery, metallurgy industries, as well as tourism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Tamil Course: Learn Tamil for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-tamil-course-learn-tamil-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-tamil-course-learn-tamil-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to learn Tamil? As one of the oldest classical languages in the world, Tamil is spoken by over 70 million people. But why should you pick Tamil out of all the languages you could be learning?
To start, Tamil is the official language of Tamil Nadu, India’s fourth largest state, which has seen significant economic growth and foreign investment over the last decade. The state is a leading figure in several industries, such as automobile and auto-components, engineering, pharmaceuticals and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japanese for French speakers : katakana</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/japanese-for-french-speakers-katakana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/japanese-for-french-speakers-katakana/</guid>
      <description>C&#39;est un cours complet pour apprendre tous les katakana, l&#39;alphabet de base japonais qui est utilisé pour écrire certaines catégories de mots tels que les mots étrangers ou les onomatopées. Grâce à des photos, des illustrations animées, une bande-son et des sous-titres en français, vous apprendrez facilement à lire le tableau entier des 46 katakana, à les prononcer parfaitement et à les écrire dans le bon ordre. Vous ne serez pas ennuyés, car à la fin de chaque section vous pourrez vérifier vos progrès avec des quiz amusants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 150 Most Important Irregular Verbs in English. Volume 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-150-most-important-irregular-verbs-in-english.-volume-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-150-most-important-irregular-verbs-in-english.-volume-1/</guid>
      <description>Support available in: English 
Spanish 
French

I can&#39;t wait to share with you this exciting English course based on Irregular Verbs. 
Do you feel unsure about the right conjugation when you try use irregular verbs in every day conversation?
Are you frustrated of having to memorize unending word lists? 
Then this course is for you. 
It is not a secret that Irregular Verbs are hard to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>