<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Language Learning on </title>
    <link>/tags/language-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Language Learning on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/language-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Computer Basics Guide for Beginners: 2021</title>
      <link>/the-complete-computer-basics-guide-for-beginners-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-computer-basics-guide-for-beginners-2021/</guid>
      <description>The Computer Defined, Data versus Information, Classification of Computers based on how data is handled (Analog Computers, Digital Computers Hybrid Computers)
Computers for Individual Users or Personal Computers (Desktop Computers,Workstations, Laptops, Notebooks, Tablets, Handheld PCs, Smartphones)
Computers for Organizations (Network Server, Mainframes, Minicomputers, Supercomputers)
Parts of Computer System (Hardware , Software, User and Data)
Information Processing Cycle (Input, Processing, Output, Storage)
Computer Hardware Categorized ( Processing Devices, Memory Devices, Input and Output Devices, Storage Devices, Bus Interconnection)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American English Pronunciation for Beginners</title>
      <link>/american-english-pronunciation-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/american-english-pronunciation-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling with your English pronunciation? 
Do you have a strong accent when speaking English?

Do native speakers always ask you to repeat yourself?

Do you want to begin speaking with an American accent confidently?

Do you what tips and help with speaking with an American accent? 
I welcome you to this - “American English Pronunciation Training - course where I will patiently guide you through the basic techniques you need to pronounce English sounds correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arabic complete beginner course through (Byna Yadek)</title>
      <link>/arabic-complete-beginner-course-through-byna-yadek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/arabic-complete-beginner-course-through-byna-yadek/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I&#39;m Mr.Bakoor. I have been teaching Arabic for a while. I got students form All over the world. My respect for all of them. My students liked the way I teach because It&#39;s easy, it goes step by step, they easily understand and also show improvement,&amp;nbsp; I feel so happy when I my student telling me that they are really improving in Arabic, I hope to make Arabic teaching easier for everyone who think Learning Arabic is hard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete French Course: Learn French for Beginners</title>
      <link>/complete-french-course-learn-french-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-french-course-learn-french-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to learn French? Dubbed the “language of love”, French is used by over 235 million speakers daily in over 54 countries. But why should you pick French out of all the languages you could be learning?
To start, France isn’t just one of the most beautiful countries in central Europe, but a global powerhouse with significant presence in the automobile, aircraft and chemical manufacturing, the electronic, machinery, metallurgy industries, as well as tourism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Tamil Course: Learn Tamil for Beginners</title>
      <link>/complete-tamil-course-learn-tamil-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-tamil-course-learn-tamil-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to learn Tamil? As one of the oldest classical languages in the world, Tamil is spoken by over 70 million people. But why should you pick Tamil out of all the languages you could be learning?
To start, Tamil is the official language of Tamil Nadu, India’s fourth largest state, which has seen significant economic growth and foreign investment over the last decade. The state is a leading figure in several industries, such as automobile and auto-components, engineering, pharmaceuticals and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japanese for French speakers : katakana</title>
      <link>/japanese-for-french-speakers-katakana/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/japanese-for-french-speakers-katakana/</guid>
      <description>C&#39;est un cours complet pour apprendre tous les katakana, l&#39;alphabet de base japonais qui est utilisé pour écrire certaines catégories de mots tels que les mots étrangers ou les onomatopées. Grâce à des photos, des illustrations animées, une bande-son et des sous-titres en français, vous apprendrez facilement à lire le tableau entier des 46 katakana, à les prononcer parfaitement et à les écrire dans le bon ordre. Vous ne serez pas ennuyés, car à la fin de chaque section vous pourrez vérifier vos progrès avec des quiz amusants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 150 Most Important Irregular Verbs in English. Volume 1</title>
      <link>/the-150-most-important-irregular-verbs-in-english.-volume-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-150-most-important-irregular-verbs-in-english.-volume-1/</guid>
      <description>Support available in: English 
Spanish 
French

I can&#39;t wait to share with you this exciting English course based on Irregular Verbs. 
Do you feel unsure about the right conjugation when you try use irregular verbs in every day conversation?
Are you frustrated of having to memorize unending word lists? 
Then this course is for you. 
It is not a secret that Irregular Verbs are hard to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
