<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fashion Design on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/fashion-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fashion Design on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:43 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/fashion-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Easy Patternmaking Kit: Learn How To Draft Trousers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/easy-patternmaking-kit-learn-how-to-draft-trousers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/easy-patternmaking-kit-learn-how-to-draft-trousers/</guid>
      <description>The Easy Patternmaking Kit - Trouser Drafting Course teaches you how to construct a beautiful pair of trousers.
In this course, you learn to draft a pattern for a pair of trousers along wit belt and zipper attachments, using fitting measurements, and quality techniques. We begin with organizing your pattern paper with accurate measurements laid out properly. You will then learn to calculate the circumference measurements, the darts, and allowances for a quality fit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patternmaking For Beginners: Draft An Offshoulder Dress</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/patternmaking-for-beginners-draft-an-offshoulder-dress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/patternmaking-for-beginners-draft-an-offshoulder-dress/</guid>
      <description>The Easy Sewing Kit - Learn To Draft An Offshoulder Dress Course teaches you how to construct a beautiful dress in the offshoulder style.
In this course, you learn to draft a pattern for an offshoulder dress and sleeve, using fitting measurements, and quality techniques. We begin with organizing your pattern paper with accurate measurements laid out properly. You will then learn to calculate the armhole, the waist darts, and allowances.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
