<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Real Estate on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/real-estate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Real Estate on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/real-estate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Real Estate Investment &amp; Finance</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/real-estate-investment-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/real-estate-investment-finance/</guid>
      <description>This course will provide many useful tools for real estate investors and home buyers.
Real estate investing in a complex topic for many reasons. Real estate is a large investment, often requiring a significant part of an and individual’s asset portfolio. Real estate investing often requires financing which increases the complexity. The reason for purchasing real estate varies greatly form person to person, some looking for a long-term home, others looking primarily for an investment, most wanting some mixture of both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Realtor Podcast Marketing For Real Estate Agents Success</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/realtor-podcast-marketing-for-real-estate-agents-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/realtor-podcast-marketing-for-real-estate-agents-success/</guid>
      <description>In the super-competitive real estate market, Realtors need every advantage they can get.
Don&#39;t you hate it when a potential client that you spoke with months ago, buys or sells their home... and uses another agent?
Imagine, for a minute, that you had the undivided attention of your ideal prospect. And not only that, you were talking in their ear on a weekly basis. Maybe, they aren&#39;t ready to sell their home or buy a new one this week, but what about next week, next month, next year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Networking for Real Estate Investors For Profits &amp; Funds</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/networking-for-real-estate-investors-for-profits-funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/networking-for-real-estate-investors-for-profits-funds/</guid>
      <description>Jay Conner shares how to Network for success as a real estate investor. At this live event, Jay, and his coaches, teach you powerful strategies for getting in front of your ideal prospect and have them breaking down the doors to fund your deals.
Funding deals are a major problem for real estate investors.
Banks often stop funding your deal with little notice. Hard money can be expensive. Private money is faster, less expensive, and easier to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Estate Investing: Foreclosures, Flipping Houses Profits</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/real-estate-investing-foreclosures-flipping-houses-profits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/real-estate-investing-foreclosures-flipping-houses-profits/</guid>
      <description>With 15 years experience investing in homes in his small (Pop. 9,768) town of Morehead City, North Carolina, Jay Conner has perfected systems which anyone with persistence, determination and willingness to work can do.
Real estate investing is one of the tried and proven paths to wealth. Ninety percent of millionaires used real estate as at least one of their paths to making their fortune. For the average investor, real estate offers the best way to develop significant wealth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foreclosure Success for Real Estate Investors by Jay Conner</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/foreclosure-success-for-real-estate-investors-by-jay-conner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/foreclosure-success-for-real-estate-investors-by-jay-conner/</guid>
      <description>Foreclosure is a legal process in which a lender attempts to recover the balance of a loan from a borrower who has stopped making payments to the lender by forcing the sale of the asset used as the collateral for the loan.
It creates a unique opportunity for real estate investors to acquire properties for a steep discount, while helping the owners get out of a tough situation. In this fast paced course based on Jay&#39;s live presentations to a small group of dedicated real estate investors, you will discover:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Ads Copywriting &amp; Facebook Ads for Real Estate 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/facebook-ads-copywriting-facebook-ads-for-real-estate-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:57:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/facebook-ads-copywriting-facebook-ads-for-real-estate-2022/</guid>
      <description>This Facebook Ads Copywriting Course &amp;amp; Facebook Ads for Real Estate Course is Completely Updated for 2022. Facebook Ads Course is filled with Assignments &amp;amp; Interactive Quizzes Making Learning Fun!
My course will level up your Facebook Ads Copywriting, Facebook Pixel &amp;amp; Business Manager Correct Setup ready for iOS 14.5+, Real Estate Facebook Ads &amp;amp; Facebook Marketing knowledge even if you’ve never used Facebook to conduct Real Estate business before. Master Real Estate Facebook Marketing, Drive Traffic To Your Website, &amp;amp; Create Engagement For Your Properties using my successful, tested and proven Facebook Marketing and Facebook Ads techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Estate Underwriting Training- Full Loan Review Process</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/real-estate-underwriting-training-full-loan-review-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/real-estate-underwriting-training-full-loan-review-process/</guid>
      <description>This course is designed to help you land your first job as a mortgage credit analyst and beginning a rewarding career in the mortgage industry. The willingness to learn and having an open mind alongside education is key for growth in this industry. Real estate analyst and underwriting is the process of reviewing a loan application to determine the amount of risk involved. The Analyst will look at the borrower&#39;s financial standing and the value of the property at hand to review the potential of the deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to Co-Living</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/intro-to-co-living/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 17:02:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/intro-to-co-living/</guid>
      <description>REAL ESTATE IS THE #1 way to guaranteed CASH FLOW and the absolute only way you make money while you sleep each and every week. This course teaches you how to maximize your cash flow from a current home, a rental property or a newly acquired property. Turn your extra room in your home into cash or turn your rental property into a cash cow by increasing your rent at least 2 times by converting a single-family home into Co-Living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentos de la Inversión Inmobiliaria</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentos-de-la-inversi%C3%B3n-inmobiliaria/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundamentos-de-la-inversi%C3%B3n-inmobiliaria/</guid>
      <description>Fundamentos de la Inversión Inmobiliaria
Conviértete en un Especialista en la Inversión Inmobiliaria de Alta Rentabilidad
Instructores: Arquitecto Álvaro García y Arquitecta Lucía Fernández Actualizado: Marzo de 2022 Estudiantes: +3.000
Descripción del Curso:
La formación te permitirá convertirte en un experto en la materia, y todo ello desde una formación principalmente práctica. A través de variadas actividades y proyectos completos podrás adquirir los conocimientos suficientes para ejercer profesionalmente de forma solvente.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cambio de Uso de Local a Vivienda</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cambio-de-uso-de-local-a-vivienda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 18:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cambio-de-uso-de-local-a-vivienda/</guid>
      <description>Cambio de Uso de Local a Vivienda
Conviértete en un Experto en Cambio de Uso de Local a Vivienda
Instructores: Arquitecto Álvaro García y Arquitecta Lucía Fernández Actualizado: Enero de 2022 Estudiantes: +3.000
Calificación: ⭐⭐⭐⭐⭐
Descripción del Curso:
La formación te permitirá convertirte en un experto en la materia, y todo ello desde una formación principalmente práctica. A través de variadas actividades y proyectos completos podrás adquirir los conocimientos suficientes para ejercer profesionalmente de forma solvente.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Streams of Realtor Income - Real Estate Investing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/multiple-streams-of-realtor-income-real-estate-investing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 12:27:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/multiple-streams-of-realtor-income-real-estate-investing/</guid>
      <description>As a Realtor, you have a unique position in your market. However, most realtors miss out on many profitable opportunities because their training has focused on one thing: Selling a house.
Instead, realtors should focus on helping people find affordable housing. By opening up their minds, new lucrative streams of income open up.
Louis &#39;Lou&#39; Brown has been buying, selling and holding property for over 30 years. Lou is the nations leading real estate trainer, author, speaker and investor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Self Storage Businesses for Maximum Profit</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/analyzing-self-storage-businesses-for-maximum-profit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 21:12:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/analyzing-self-storage-businesses-for-maximum-profit/</guid>
      <description>Self-storage units are one of the best real estate investing niche. No one pays attention to them as an investment, which means the competition is a fraction of that of commercial, single or multi-family units.
Fernando Angelucci has been investing in Self Storage for years with highly profitable results.
How do you uncover the best self-storage businesses to buy?
In this fast-paced, enthralling course, Fernando walks you through a real-life example analyzing a self-storage business while explaining in simple terms how he evaluates the properties he buys.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
