<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Real Estate on </title>
    <link>/tags/real-estate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Real Estate on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:42:45 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/real-estate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GET on TOP of Real Estate Business with Facebook Ads in 2021</title>
      <link>/get-on-top-of-real-estate-business-with-facebook-ads-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:42:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/get-on-top-of-real-estate-business-with-facebook-ads-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>My course will level up your Real Estate Facebook Ads &amp;amp; Facebook Marketing knowledge even if you’ve never used Facebook to conduct Real Estate business before. MASTER REAL ESTATE FACEBOOK MARKETING, DRIVE TRAFFIC TO YOUR WEBSITE, &amp;amp; SELL YOUR PROPERTIES using my successful, tested and proven Facebook Marketing and Facebook Ads techniques! Get POWERFUL Blueprints and walkthroughs for your Real Estate Facebook Ads Strategy that you can start to follow IMMEDIATELY!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foreclosure Success for Real Estate Investors by Jay Conner</title>
      <link>/foreclosure-success-for-real-estate-investors-by-jay-conner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/foreclosure-success-for-real-estate-investors-by-jay-conner/</guid>
      <description>Foreclosure is a legal process in which a lender attempts to recover the balance of a loan from a borrower who has stopped making payments to the lender by forcing the sale of the asset used as the collateral for the loan.
It creates a unique opportunity for real estate investors to acquire properties for a steep discount, while helping the owners get out of a tough situation. In this fast paced course based on Jay&#39;s live presentations to a small group of dedicated real estate investors, you will discover:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
