<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Real Estate on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/real-estate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Real Estate on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/real-estate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Real Estate Investment &amp; Finance</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/real-estate-investment-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/real-estate-investment-finance/</guid>
      <description>This course will provide many useful tools for real estate investors and home buyers.
Real estate investing in a complex topic for many reasons. Real estate is a large investment, often requiring a significant part of an and individual’s asset portfolio. Real estate investing often requires financing which increases the complexity. The reason for purchasing real estate varies greatly form person to person, some looking for a long-term home, others looking primarily for an investment, most wanting some mixture of both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GET on TOP of Real Estate Business with Facebook Ads in 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/get-on-top-of-real-estate-business-with-facebook-ads-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/get-on-top-of-real-estate-business-with-facebook-ads-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>My course will level up your Real Estate Facebook Ads &amp;amp; Facebook Marketing knowledge even if you’ve never used Facebook to conduct Real Estate business before. MASTER REAL ESTATE FACEBOOK MARKETING, DRIVE TRAFFIC TO YOUR WEBSITE, &amp;amp; SELL YOUR PROPERTIES using my successful, tested and proven Facebook Marketing and Facebook Ads techniques! Get POWERFUL Blueprints and walkthroughs for your Real Estate Facebook Ads Strategy that you can start to follow IMMEDIATELY!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Networking for Real Estate Investors For Profits &amp; Funds</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/networking-for-real-estate-investors-for-profits-funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/networking-for-real-estate-investors-for-profits-funds/</guid>
      <description>Jay Conner shares how to Network for success as a real estate investor. At this live event, Jay, and his coaches, teach you powerful strategies for getting in front of your ideal prospect and have them breaking down the doors to fund your deals.
Funding deals are a major problem for real estate investors.
Banks often stop funding your deal with little notice. Hard money can be expensive. Private money is faster, less expensive, and easier to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foreclosure Success for Real Estate Investors by Jay Conner</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/foreclosure-success-for-real-estate-investors-by-jay-conner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 22:18:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/foreclosure-success-for-real-estate-investors-by-jay-conner/</guid>
      <description>Foreclosure is a legal process in which a lender attempts to recover the balance of a loan from a borrower who has stopped making payments to the lender by forcing the sale of the asset used as the collateral for the loan.
It creates a unique opportunity for real estate investors to acquire properties for a steep discount, while helping the owners get out of a tough situation. In this fast paced course based on Jay&#39;s live presentations to a small group of dedicated real estate investors, you will discover:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Estate Investing: Foreclosures, Flipping Houses Profits</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/real-estate-investing-foreclosures-flipping-houses-profits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 12:19:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/real-estate-investing-foreclosures-flipping-houses-profits/</guid>
      <description>With 15 years experience investing in homes in his small (Pop. 9,768) town of Morehead City, North Carolina, Jay Conner has perfected systems which anyone with persistence, determination and willingness to work can do.
Real estate investing is one of the tried and proven paths to wealth. Ninety percent of millionaires used real estate as at least one of their paths to making their fortune. For the average investor, real estate offers the best way to develop significant wealth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
