<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Financial Modeling &amp; Analysis on </title>
    <link>/tags/financial-modeling-analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Financial Modeling &amp; Analysis on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/financial-modeling-analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Standard Costing And Variance Analysis Full Course</title>
      <link>/standard-costing-and-variance-analysis-full-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/standard-costing-and-variance-analysis-full-course/</guid>
      <description>Administrative and cost management tools
The course will introduce subject management topics to be covered throughout the course, comparing management accounting and accounting so that we are in the right frame of mind as we move forward.
The study will explain and analyze general costs and cost variance analyzes, providing an overview of the cost analysis concepts that we will go into in detail in later sections.
We will explain the analysis of sales differences, discuss when they can be used and how to calculate sales variations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Reporting Automation with Google Sheets</title>
      <link>/master-reporting-automation-with-google-sheets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/master-reporting-automation-with-google-sheets/</guid>
      <description>Learn to solve any business modeling task you might ever experience!
Have you ever felt that you&#39;re regularly repeating some tasks in Google Sheets or Excel?
Have you ever thought about the time you would save if you would automate those tasks?

All the work you&#39;re doing in a repetitive manner in Google Sheets or Excel could be automated.&amp;nbsp;It requires no coding skills, add-ons, or special tools - all you need to know is how to execute advanced formula combinations that will do all the automation for you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
