<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design Tools on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/design-tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Design Tools on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 11:41:03 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/design-tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Creative Cloud 2021 Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/adobe-creative-cloud-2021-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 11:41:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/adobe-creative-cloud-2021-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Adobe Creative Cloud but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Designs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Creative Cloud 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Adobe Creative Cloud is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start working with Adobe Creative Cloud like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro CC Video Editing Course Beginners To Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-video-editing-course-beginners-to-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 10:06:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-video-editing-course-beginners-to-pro/</guid>
      <description>Hi There,
My name is Stephen Koel Soren and I am a graphics and web expert. If you are absolute beginner or if you never open Adobe Premiere pro cc before than this is a perfect class for you. This is a beginner level class so so together me you we will learn Adobe Premiere pro from basic to advance.
The Main Topics you will learn:
· Set your workspace. How to efficiently import and organize your media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Editing with Avid Media Composer First for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/video-editing-with-avid-media-composer-first-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 10:06:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/video-editing-with-avid-media-composer-first-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Requirements
A licensed copy of Avid Media Composer First ( Free to download )
Description
Avid Media Composer is widely used video production software in Film and TV industry. This training class provides the critical fundamentals of video editing with Avid Media Composer for beginners.

In this course we have covered the basics of editing with Avid where you get a detailed look at the workings of the interface and learn how to do Basic Edits and apply Transitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Basics Of Adobe After Effects CC 2021 for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-basics-of-adobe-after-effects-cc-2021-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-basics-of-adobe-after-effects-cc-2021-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the “Adobe After Effects 2021 - The Beginner&#39;s Basics” course.
Adobe After Effects is a digital visual effects, motion graphics, and compositing application developed by Adobe Systems and used in the post-production process of film making, video games, and television production.
Motion Graphics and Visual Effects are becoming increasingly valuable and important in any video created. Learning how to create these animations using Adobe After Effects has become essential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Affinity Publisher Guide - Affinity Publisher for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/affinity-publisher-guide-affinity-publisher-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/affinity-publisher-guide-affinity-publisher-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Affinity Publisher Guide - Affinity Publisher for Beginners!
The only course you will need to start with Affinity Publisher, one of the best publishing software in the industry.
Affinity Publisher is an easy-to-use desktop publishing software that helps you create beautiful layouts with custom graphics and images in minutes. It&#39;s the perfect choice for a graphic designer who wants to take on a more creative role, or for someone who has always wanted to create their own book, magazine, or brochure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Procreate: Getting Started With Procreate on the iPad (2021)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/procreate-getting-started-with-procreate-on-the-ipad-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/procreate-getting-started-with-procreate-on-the-ipad-2021/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to use Procreate 5X on the iPad with the Apple Pencil for digital art, illustration, drawing and painting.
The iPad (Pro, Air 3, Mini 5, iPad 7) with Procreate 5X  can be turned into a mini art studio, a powerful digital drawing tool that you can take with you anywhere. Procreate is one of the best digital art apps in the world of digital art.
I believe in the Learning by Doing principle.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
