<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design Tools on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/design-tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Design Tools on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/design-tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence Presentation Creation (2022 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-presentation-creation-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-presentation-creation-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>Creating presentation decks can get hectic and time-consuming! Believe it or not! Just imagine, what if an Artificial Intelligence (AI) tool does it for you? Welcome to this course that teaches you AI tech tools to achieve this sole purpose.
A must-to-take course for each one of us to enrol in 2022 that is ideal for students, educators, marketers, and of course - graphic designers.
Ready to create instant powerful presentation decks in just minutes?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creative Infographics in PowerPoint</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/creative-infographics-in-powerpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/creative-infographics-in-powerpoint/</guid>
      <description>You certainly know that boring PowerPoint presentation can kill a brilliant idea?
Is there a way to make it better, way better? Sure, and I&#39;ll tell you how! A tip: use data to make your presentation more convincing. Don&#39;t use standard Microsoft PowerPoint charts and graphs to visualize the data. They are boring! Instead, do something different, unexpected! A creative infographic! In this course you&#39;ll learn:
what informational graphic is and why people use it (very quick insight);</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Basics Of Adobe After Effects CC 2022 for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-basics-of-adobe-after-effects-cc-2022-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-basics-of-adobe-after-effects-cc-2022-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the “Adobe After Effects 2022 - The Beginner&#39;s Basics” course.
Adobe After Effects is a digital visual effects, motion graphics, and compositing application developed by Adobe Systems and used in the post-production process of film making, video games, and television production.
Motion Graphics and Visual Effects are becoming increasingly valuable and important in any video created. Learning how to create these animations using Adobe After Effects has become essential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Editing with Avid Media Composer First for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-editing-with-avid-media-composer-first-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/video-editing-with-avid-media-composer-first-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Requirements
A licensed copy of Avid Media Composer First ( Free to download )
Description
Avid Media Composer is widely used video production software in Film and TV industry. This training class provides the critical fundamentals of video editing with Avid Media Composer for beginners.
In this course we have covered the basics of editing with Avid where you get a detailed look at the workings of the interface and learn how to do Basic Edits and apply Transitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creo Parametric Training_In Hindi</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/creo-parametric-training_in-hindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/creo-parametric-training_in-hindi/</guid>
      <description>Creo is a 3D CAD modelling software, which is useful for engineering students and Professionals, in this course you will learn how to make a realistic 3D CAD model using CREO Parametric and learn how to model engine parts. The following modules are included in this course.
1. Sketcher
2. Part modelling - Solid
3. part modelling - Surface
4. Part modelling - Sheet metal
5. Assembly design
6. Detailing and drafting</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Creative Cloud 2022 Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-creative-cloud-2022-ultimate-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-creative-cloud-2022-ultimate-guide/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Adobe Creative Cloud but don’t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Designs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Creative Cloud 2022 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Adobe Creative Cloud is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I’ll take you through everything you need to know to start working with Adobe Creative Cloud like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Creative Cloud 2022 Projects</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-creative-cloud-2022-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-creative-cloud-2022-projects/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Adobe Creative Cloud but don’t know where to start? Would you like to make amazing Designs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Creative Cloud 2022 Projects is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Adobe Creative Cloud is an in-demand skill in 2022.
The course begins with the basics.
I’ll take you through everything you need to know to start working with Adobe Creative Cloud like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop 2022 Photo Editing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-2022-photo-editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-2022-photo-editing/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Design but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Photos and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Photoshop 2022 Photo Editing is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Photo Editing is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start Editing Photos like an expert with Adobe Photoshop 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro CC Video Editing Course Beginners To Pro</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-video-editing-course-beginners-to-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-video-editing-course-beginners-to-pro/</guid>
      <description>Hi There,
My name is Stephen Koel Soren and I am a graphics and web expert. If you are absolute beginner or if you never open Adobe Premiere pro cc before than this is a perfect class for you. This is a beginner level class so so together me you we will learn Adobe Premiere pro from basic to advance.
The Main Topics you will learn:
· Set your workspace. How to efficiently import and organize your media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Sketching S01: Create Amazing Designs with Procreate</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/design-sketching-s01-create-amazing-designs-with-procreate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/design-sketching-s01-create-amazing-designs-with-procreate/</guid>
      <description>Christmas Sale! 3 hours of extensive course for just 19 USD!! Turn your iPad into the most powerful design tool on earth with Procreate and Apple Pencil!
Design Sketching: Create Amazing Designs with Procreate This is a learn anywhere video course, where you will be able to use all of Procreates features to ideate and sketch effectively on your iPad or iPad Pro. I’ve covered all the core knowledge and practical theory you need to know in order to utilize Procreate to a professional level to create super cool design sketches on your iPad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Audition 2022 Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-audition-2022-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-audition-2022-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Edit Audio but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Videos and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Audition 2022 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Audio Editing is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start Editing Audio like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autocad | Sıfırdan Uzmanlığa 30&#43; Saat Sektörel Eğitim Seti</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/autocad-s%C4%B1f%C4%B1rdan-uzmanl%C4%B1%C4%9Fa-30-saat-sekt%C3%B6rel-e%C4%9Fitim-seti/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/autocad-s%C4%B1f%C4%B1rdan-uzmanl%C4%B1%C4%9Fa-30-saat-sekt%C3%B6rel-e%C4%9Fitim-seti/</guid>
      <description>Autocad eğitimini kalıp tasarım mühendislerinden öğrenmeye hazır mısınız? Tüm tasarım ve imalat tecrübelerimizi sizinle paylaşacağımız Autocad eğitiminde göreceğiniz ileri seviye çizim teknikleri ile piyasada rahatlıkla fark yaratabileceksiniz! Eğitmenler olarak uzun yıllar çalıştığımız plastik enjeksiyon ve sac metal kalıp tasarımlarında edindiğimiz bilgi birikimlerimizi şimdi sizinle paylaşmaya hazırız! Bu eğitimimizde Autocad programının önemli olan tüm özelliklerine sıfırdan başlayarak, ileri seviyeye kadar değineceğiz. Eğitimimiz gelen istekler doğrultusunda her zaman güncel tutulmaya da çalışılacaktır. Aynı zamanda da tüm sorularınızı eğitimi izlerken anında sorabilirsiniz ve 24 saat içerisinde sorularınıza yanıt almış olacaksınız!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whiteboard Video Creation with VideoScribe (2022 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/whiteboard-video-creation-with-videoscribe-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/whiteboard-video-creation-with-videoscribe-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Whiteboard Video Creation with VideoScribe (2022 Edition)&#34;.
In a typical product training session - imagine you&#39;ve made a presentation which you believe, may engage or wow the audience. However, it doesn&#39;t work out at the end of the day. It simply doesn&#39;t. The audience just walks out bleary-eyed, shell-shocked, and bored after a long line of presenters has in-fact bombarded them with PowerPoint slide presentations. This would include your 30 slider presentation on the latest and greatest products, features, functions, or benefits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clone yourself in a video using ScreenFlow 9 in 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/clone-yourself-in-a-video-using-screenflow-9-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 16:26:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/clone-yourself-in-a-video-using-screenflow-9-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Clone yourself in a video using ScreenFlow 9 in 2022&#34;.
&#34;Ever wondered how to multiply yourself in the videos you create? Well, now is the right time to start learning that craft&#34;.
This mind-blowing course titled &#34;Clone Yourself in a Video using ScreenFlow 9 in 2022&#34; created by Digital Marketing Legend &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34; and Mastermind &#34;Saranya Srinidhi&#34; will teach you the simplest method to execute this trick using ScreenFlow 9 on Mac.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comic Creation for Entrepreneurs (2022 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/comic-creation-for-entrepreneurs-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 22:09:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/comic-creation-for-entrepreneurs-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience the course &#34;Comic Creation for Entrepreneurs (2022 Edition)&#34;.
Nowadays online marketing has become increasingly important to all businesses worldwide. Digital comics have become a market having a high ROI. The comic industry has come a long way and it has the potential to enter the minds of customers to help provoke decision-making. Most startup companies and SME&#39;s (Small Medium Enterprises) aren&#39;t even aware of this astonishing fact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop 2022 Projects</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-2022-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-2022-projects/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Design but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Designs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Adobe Photoshop 2022 Projects is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Design is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building designs like an expert with Adobe Photoshop 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Course in CATIA</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-course-in-catia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-course-in-catia/</guid>
      <description>CATIA V5, developed by Dassault Systemes, France, is a completely re-engineered, next-generation family of CAD/CAM/CAE software solutions for Product Lifecycle Management. CATIA V5 delivers innovative technologies for maximum productivity and creativity through its exceptionally easy-to-use and state-of-the-art user interface, from inception to the final product. CATIA V5 reduces the learning curve, as it allows the flexibility of using feature-based and parametric designs. CATIA V5 serves the design tasks by providing different workbenches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Thumbnail Blaster: Create 3D Video Thumbnails (2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-thumbnail-blaster-create-3d-video-thumbnails-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-thumbnail-blaster-create-3d-video-thumbnails-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;YouTube Thumbnail Blaster&#34; course.
So, want to create breathtaking and clickable video thumbnails for your YouTube videos, but not knowing how?
You&#39;ve come to the right place, my passionate learner. Look no further than this course.
Welcome, my name is Srinidhi Ranganathan. My fans fondly call me &#34;Digital Marketing Legend&#34;. Teaming up with Saranya, I have now put this training course &#34;YouTube Thumbnail Blaster: Create 3D Video Thumbnails&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Affinity Publisher Guide - Affinity Publisher for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/affinity-publisher-guide-affinity-publisher-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2022 21:32:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/affinity-publisher-guide-affinity-publisher-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Affinity Publisher Guide - Affinity Publisher for Beginners!
The only course you will need to start with Affinity Publisher, one of the best publishing software in the industry.
Affinity Publisher is an easy-to-use desktop publishing software that helps you create beautiful layouts with custom graphics and images in minutes. It&#39;s the perfect choice for a graphic designer who wants to take on a more creative role, or for someone who has always wanted to create their own book, magazine, or brochure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Lightroom Classic Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-lightroom-classic-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:30:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-lightroom-classic-basics/</guid>
      <description>SO, YOU’RE LOOKING FOR A COURSE THAT WILL TEACH YOU BASIC LIGHTROOM CLASSIC QUICKLY &amp;amp; IN A FUN MANNER?
I’ve got just the course for you!
Welcome, my name is Josh Werner with Learn Tech Plus and I’ve put this course together to help people just like you quickly master Basic Lightroom Classic...Whether you’re a beginner or experienced with existing Adobe Applications!
If your goal is to become a user of Basic Lightroom Classic, then this course is perfect for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catia V5 Composites Design Eğitimi! | Kompozit Tasarımı!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/catia-v5-composites-design-e%C4%9Fitimi-kompozit-tasar%C4%B1m%C4%B1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/catia-v5-composites-design-e%C4%9Fitimi-kompozit-tasar%C4%B1m%C4%B1/</guid>
      <description>CATIA, bir Fransız Havacılık Şirketi tarafından tasarlanan ileri seviye bir CAD (Computer Aided Design), yani Bilgisayar Destekli Tasarım Programıdır. İçerisinde bir çok sektöre hitap eden modüllerin bulunması, CATIA programının birinci tercih edilme sebebidir. Programın bu kadar çok modüle sahip olmasından da en çok ülkemizde Otomotiv, Havacılık ve Savunma Sanayi gibi sektörlerde kullanılmaktadır. Aynı zamanda da ülkemizde CATIA programının en çok kullanılan versiyonu da CATIA V5 versiyonudur. Bu eğitim de CATIA V5 R21 sürümü ile hazırlanmıştır.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kalıp Tasarım Mühendislerinden Solidworks Eğitimi!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kal%C4%B1p-tasar%C4%B1m-m%C3%BChendislerinden-solidworks-e%C4%9Fitimi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kal%C4%B1p-tasar%C4%B1m-m%C3%BChendislerinden-solidworks-e%C4%9Fitimi/</guid>
      <description>Solidworks eğitimini Kalıp Tasarım Mühendislerinden öğrenmeye hazır mısınız? Tüm tasarım ve imalat tecrübelerimizi sizinle paylaşacağımız Solidworks eğitiminde göreceğiniz ileri seviye 3D modelleme teknikleri ile piyasada rahatlıkla fark yaratabileceksiniz! Eğitmenler olarak uzun yıllar çalıştığımız plastik enjeksiyon ve sac metal kalıp tasarımlarında edindiğimiz bilgi birikimlerimizi şimdi sizinle paylaşmaya hazırız! Bu eğitimimizde Solidworks programının önemli olan tüm modüllerine sıfırdan başlayarak, ileri seviyeye kadar değineceğiz. Eğitimimiz gelen istekler doğrultusunda her zaman güncel tutulmaya da çalışılacaktır.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NX ile EDM Tezgahları için Bakır Elektrot Tasarımı Eğitimi!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/nx-ile-edm-tezgahlar%C4%B1-i%C3%A7in-bak%C4%B1r-elektrot-tasar%C4%B1m%C4%B1-e%C4%9Fitimi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/nx-ile-edm-tezgahlar%C4%B1-i%C3%A7in-bak%C4%B1r-elektrot-tasar%C4%B1m%C4%B1-e%C4%9Fitimi/</guid>
      <description>Elektroerozyon (EDM), iş parçasına istenilen şekli vermek için elektrik boşalmasından faydalanılan üretim yöntemidir. Elektrik iletkeni malzemelere uygulananır. Metal aşındırma işlemi takım görevini yapan bir elektrot ile iş parçası arasında meydana gelen kıvılcımların yardımıyla gerçekleştirilir. Kıvılcımlar, ergime ve buharlaşma yoluyla çok küçük malzeme parçacıkları kaldırarak parça yüzeyini erozyona tabi tutar ve parça üzerinde ufak çukurlar oluşturur. EDM sırasında elektrot ile iş parçası arasındaki mesafe 0,0125 mm ile 0,05 mm arasındadır. Bu mesafe takım ve iş parçası arasında elektrik arkı oluşması için yeterlidir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Photoshop Quick Start for Absolute Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-quick-start-for-absolute-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 21:05:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-photoshop-quick-start-for-absolute-beginners/</guid>
      <description>If you want to learn the basics of photoshop but do not have a great deal of time, this course is for you!
Adobe Photoshop used to be this really complex and even cryptic piece of software that only a few people knew how to really get in there and work. I have been using Photoshop off and on for about 20 years and not just for digital art. My name is rich Grayson.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>»PHOTOSHOP | realiza 100 DISEÑOS en un minuto «</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/photoshop-realiza-100-dise%C3%B1os-en-un-minuto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/photoshop-realiza-100-dise%C3%B1os-en-un-minuto/</guid>
      <description>Desde hace tiempo estas usando Photoshop ya sea como fotógrafo, diseñador o community manager, sin embargo, a pesar de que manejas muy bien el programa en tu área de interés, tu flujo de trabajo es sumamente lento, durando horas en procesos que te consumen todo el tiempo.
En este curso avanzado de Photoshop te desvelo todos mis secretos para que al igual que yo puedas tener un flujo de trabajo acelerado, gracias a los procesos automatizados de Photoshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Procreate: Getting Started With Procreate on the iPad (2021)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/procreate-getting-started-with-procreate-on-the-ipad-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/procreate-getting-started-with-procreate-on-the-ipad-2021/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to use Procreate 5X on the iPad with the Apple Pencil for digital art, illustration, drawing and painting.
The iPad (Pro, Air 3, Mini 5, iPad 7) with Procreate 5X can be turned into a mini art studio, a powerful digital drawing tool that you can take with you anywhere. Procreate is one of the best digital art apps in the world of digital art.
I believe in the Learning by Doing principle.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
