<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Transformation on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/personal-transformation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal Transformation on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/personal-transformation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Innovation &amp; Personality</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/innovation-personality/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/innovation-personality/</guid>
      <description>Learn more how to identify, evaluate and motivate innovative people to boost innovation in your organization.
Discover how to boost your own individual innovativeness.
Explore the innovator’s persona. 
It might be challenging to identify whether a person is an innovator or not. However, several personality traits are closely related to the innovative personality.
Innovative people usually express a strong desire for autonomy, are imaginative, curious, energetic, and confident. They are open to new experiences having flexible mindset and propensity to successfully generate ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nomad Lifestyle: LIVE YOUR DREAM &amp; Travel the World</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-nomad-lifestyle-live-your-dream-travel-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:47:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-nomad-lifestyle-live-your-dream-travel-the-world/</guid>
      <description>IS IT POSSIBLE TO LIVE YOUR DREAM LIFE WITHOUT WORKING SO HARD? DOES IT HAVE TO TAKE SO MUCH EFFORT, STRESS, AND ENERGY TO HAVE A LIFE THAT DEEPLY FULFILS YOU? HONOR AND TRUST YOUR PROCESS, AND SURRENDER TO THE MAGIC OF LIFE!!! BEING A DIGITAL NOMAD MEANS LIVING LIFE 100% ON YOUR OWN TERMS!!!
From leaving behind the corporate life of a consistent and often capped salary, saying goodbye to cubicles, a regular work commute and the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Habitually Better: Building habits to be your best self!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/habitually-better-building-habits-to-be-your-best-self/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/habitually-better-building-habits-to-be-your-best-self/</guid>
      <description>Join the journey to become habitually better!
Pursuing long term goals does not have to be a long shot. It does not have to take an inordinate amount of will power either.
Join the journey to craft a focussed, effortless and satisfying path towards your future.

I have struggled with habit formation, and I empathize with you. Having seen how that powerful habits are and how some people face challenges in utilizing them, I believe that it should be made reachable to everyone and I would like to share this course as a humble guidance to those who are going through a similar journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Personal Development Course - 22 Courses in 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-personal-development-course-22-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-personal-development-course-22-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>*Update - A 50-Questions Master Quiz has been added! :)
If You Only Buy ONE Course This Year … It GOT To Be This One!
With over 54 hours of video content, 283 lectures, downloadable resources and bonuses - this is one of the most comprehensive personal development courses available! You&#39;ll also get access to:
Lifetime Access to course updates
Fast &amp;amp; Friendly Support in the Q&amp;amp;A section
Udemy Certificate of Completion Ready for Download</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reinvent Your Life: Master Life Transformation Techniques</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/reinvent-your-life-master-life-transformation-techniques/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 20:22:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/reinvent-your-life-master-life-transformation-techniques/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you will learn the Life Transformation Techniques for personal Development, Personal Transformation, and Finding Your Life Purpose. In just 10-minutes a day, The Personal Life Transformation Masterclass will help revolutionize your life by improving your mindset, goals, and personal and professional productivity. You&#39;ll unlock the potential concentration, confidence, and optimism you need to start moving forward again and again. Once you&#39;ve mastered mentioned areas completely, you&#39;ll feel unstoppable and have total belief in your ability to achieve incredible results with ease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beat Procrastination in Turbulent Covid Era</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/beat-procrastination-in-turbulent-covid-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 17:46:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/beat-procrastination-in-turbulent-covid-era/</guid>
      <description>Procrastination is one of the principle boundaries obstructing you from getting up, settling on the correct choices, and carrying on with the fantasy life you&#39;ve considered.

Ongoing investigations have shown that individuals regret more the things they haven&#39;t done than the things they have done. Furthermore, sensations of disappointment and blame coming about because of botched freedoms will in general remain with individuals any longer.

Some of the time every one of our chances appear to be on our fingertips, however we can&#39;t contact them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goal Setting For Success: Plan And Achieve Your Goals</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/goal-setting-for-success-plan-and-achieve-your-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:28:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/goal-setting-for-success-plan-and-achieve-your-goals/</guid>
      <description>Are you a student, struggling at setting and achieving your goals?
This goal setting course will quickly allow you to start setting personal and professional goals to boost your success.
If you are a studente you can start seeing a path to the success you hope for: you will be able to develop a goal setting mindset, find out what you want in life and create a concrete action plan to reach your targets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-Discipline: Build Habits &amp; Develop a Growth Mindset</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/self-discipline-build-habits-develop-a-growth-mindset/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:28:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/self-discipline-build-habits-develop-a-growth-mindset/</guid>
      <description>Join our students who have taken our time management, goal setting and focus mastery courses with great results!
This course will teach you why and how to develop self-discipline, increase your motivation and stop procrastinating, empowering you to build daily habits for long-term success.
Whether you are a student, employee or entrepreneur, you will need to get your job done and, possibly, do it in the best possible way.
In fact, we have all faced the frustration of a job we don&#39;t like or a task we find difficult to complete, or a passion we have to fight for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Educa ed Allena la tua Voce</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/educa-ed-allena-la-tua-voce/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:15:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/educa-ed-allena-la-tua-voce/</guid>
      <description>Hai problemi nel farti comprendere senza dover ripetere?
Ti senti insicuro dei tuoi mezzi di parola e voce? Parli col timore di non esser capito?
Quando comunichi hai problemi nel far comprendere pensieri ed emozioni?
Vorresti avere una migliore articolazione ?

Bene! Sei proprio nell&#39;aula virtuale giusta!
In questo corso troverai un approccio all&#39;utilizzo e allo sviluppo della voce del tuto differente da quello classico che muove le prime mosse da esercizi sulla vocalizzazione, sicuro fondamentali ma solo dopo aver acquisito piena conoscenza degli organi addetti alla fonazione.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fully Accredited Professional EFT Tapping Certification</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fully-accredited-professional-eft-tapping-certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fully-accredited-professional-eft-tapping-certification/</guid>
      <description>This IAOTH, UK accredited EFT Tapping certification is a masterclass that will enable you to help an endless number of people (including yourself).
This concise programme is designed, keeping in mind that you may not have any prior knowledge about Art Therapy, and you want to learn despite your busy schedule. So we have tried to avoid jargon as much as possible and simplified concepts and terminology for you. for EFT is found extremely useful for a wide range of conditions/situations e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness para desarrollar la inteligencia emocional</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/mindfulness-para-desarrollar-la-inteligencia-emocional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/mindfulness-para-desarrollar-la-inteligencia-emocional/</guid>
      <description>Te enseño herramientas efectivas y sencillas de aplicar en tu rutina diaria, invirtiendo sólo entre 5 a 15 minutos al día tus emociones no serán más un obstáculo en la consecución de tus metas, tampoco volverás a sentir la culpa o vergüenza de tus impulsos y reacciones emocionales. 
Tu también puedes gozar de relaciones empáticas, satisfactorias y sin tantas fricciones. Poder solucionar de manera asertiva y consciente las diferencias con tus seres queridos, colegas, clientes y colaboradores es posible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Brain Training Course - Neuroplasticity -</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-brain-training-course-neuroplasticity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-brain-training-course-neuroplasticity/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Brain Training Course - Neuroplasticity -
Brain Training for the Modern Smart Phone Era! You Can Train Your Brain to Think More Clearly and Creatively
Brain training is essential if you want do you live up to your full potential as a human being. Your brain is your most important organ, therefore it is essential that you train it for peak performance.
Like it or not, every single day your brain is being trained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PNL: Conversación transformacional &amp; Negociación efectiva</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pnl-conversaci%C3%B3n-transformacional-negociaci%C3%B3n-efectiva/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pnl-conversaci%C3%B3n-transformacional-negociaci%C3%B3n-efectiva/</guid>
      <description>Los seres humanos hemos concebido la idea de que existen variables que están fuera de la gestión individual, por tal motivo se ha exteriorizado la responsabilidad de aquellos pilares transformándonos en víctima de factores externos configurados en paradigmas (política, economía, ciencia y religión) encarnados en autoridades dueñas de conocimientos, reglas y mandamientos que han configurado las estructuras mentales por las cuales construimos nuestras experiencias y realidades.
Sin embargo, gracias a la era de la información y a consecuencia de la conectividad producida por el mismo fenómeno, estamos comenzando a cambiar la percepción del tiempo y el conocimiento desde un paradigma lineal e inamovible a otro holístico y constituidos por millares de posibilidades.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
