<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Transformation on </title>
    <link>/tags/personal-transformation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal Transformation on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/personal-transformation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beat Procrastination in Turbulent Covid Era</title>
      <link>/beat-procrastination-in-turbulent-covid-era/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/beat-procrastination-in-turbulent-covid-era/</guid>
      <description>Procrastination is one of the principle boundaries obstructing you from getting up, settling on the correct choices, and carrying on with the fantasy life you&#39;ve considered.

Ongoing investigations have shown that individuals regret more the things they haven&#39;t done than the things they have done. Furthermore, sensations of disappointment and blame coming about because of botched freedoms will in general remain with individuals any longer.

Some of the time every one of our chances appear to be on our fingertips, however we can&#39;t contact them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fully Accredited Professional EFT Tapping Certification</title>
      <link>/fully-accredited-professional-eft-tapping-certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fully-accredited-professional-eft-tapping-certification/</guid>
      <description>This IAOTH, UK accredited EFT Tapping certification is a masterclass that will enable you to help an endless number of people (including yourself).
This concise programme is designed, keeping in mind that you may not have any prior knowledge about Art Therapy, and you want to learn despite your busy schedule. So we have tried to avoid jargon as much as possible and simplified concepts and terminology for you. for EFT is found extremely useful for a wide range of conditions/situations e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness para desarrollar la inteligencia emocional</title>
      <link>/mindfulness-para-desarrollar-la-inteligencia-emocional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mindfulness-para-desarrollar-la-inteligencia-emocional/</guid>
      <description>Te enseño herramientas efectivas y sencillas de aplicar en tu rutina diaria, invirtiendo sólo entre 5 a 15 minutos al día tus emociones no serán más un obstáculo en la consecución de tus metas, tampoco volverás a sentir la culpa o vergüenza de tus impulsos y reacciones emocionales. 
Tu también puedes gozar de relaciones empáticas, satisfactorias y sin tantas fricciones. Poder solucionar de manera asertiva y consciente las diferencias con tus seres queridos, colegas, clientes y colaboradores es posible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Nomad Lifestyle: LIVE YOUR DREAM &amp; Travel the World</title>
      <link>/digital-nomad-lifestyle-live-your-dream-travel-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/digital-nomad-lifestyle-live-your-dream-travel-the-world/</guid>
      <description>IS IT POSSIBLE TO LIVE YOUR DREAM LIFE WITHOUT WORKING SO HARD? DOES IT HAVE TO TAKE SO MUCH EFFORT, STRESS, AND ENERGY TO HAVE A LIFE THAT DEEPLY FULFILS YOU? HONOR AND TRUST YOUR PROCESS, AND SURRENDER TO THE MAGIC OF LIFE!!! BEING A DIGITAL NOMAD MEANS LIVING LIFE 100% ON YOUR OWN TERMS!!!
From leaving behind the corporate life of a consistent and often capped salary, saying goodbye to cubicles, a regular work commute and the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Brain Training Course - Neuroplasticity -</title>
      <link>/the-complete-brain-training-course-neuroplasticity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-brain-training-course-neuroplasticity/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Brain Training Course - Neuroplasticity -
Brain Training for the Modern Smart Phone Era! You Can Train Your Brain to Think More Clearly and Creatively
Brain training is essential if you want do you live up to your full potential as a human being. Your brain is your most important organ, therefore it is essential that you train it for peak performance.
Like it or not, every single day your brain is being trained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PNL: Conversación transformacional &amp; Negociación efectiva</title>
      <link>/pnl-conversaci%C3%B3n-transformacional-negociaci%C3%B3n-efectiva/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pnl-conversaci%C3%B3n-transformacional-negociaci%C3%B3n-efectiva/</guid>
      <description>Los seres humanos hemos concebido la idea de que existen variables que están fuera de la gestión individual, por tal motivo se ha exteriorizado la responsabilidad de aquellos pilares transformándonos en víctima de factores externos configurados en paradigmas (política, economía, ciencia y religión) encarnados en autoridades dueñas de conocimientos, reglas y mandamientos que han configurado las estructuras mentales por las cuales construimos nuestras experiencias y realidades.
Sin embargo, gracias a la era de la información y a consecuencia de la conectividad producida por el mismo fenómeno, estamos comenzando a cambiar la percepción del tiempo y el conocimiento desde un paradigma lineal e inamovible a otro holístico y constituidos por millares de posibilidades.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
