<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Game Development on </title>
    <link>/tags/game-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Game Development on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/game-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Game Development with PyGame  | Real World Games</title>
      <link>/game-development-with-pygame-real-world-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/game-development-with-pygame-real-world-games/</guid>
      <description>Learn PyGame by developing fun games from scratch. This course is for everyone who has desire to learn Python and PyGame. The game complexity increases with every section and you will be able to rise your knowledge throughout the course. You will develop amazing games and you will see how PyGame works moving things on screen and objects interaction. You will also create and import pictures used in the games and get familiar with creating randomly movable enemies, animating the game characters and playing music and sounds while playing the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unity 3D Make A Complete Racing Game</title>
      <link>/unity-3d-make-a-complete-racing-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 11:42:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/unity-3d-make-a-complete-racing-game/</guid>
      <description>Learn Unity Game engine and C# by making a complete racing game. What can be more fun way of learning programming by making your own racing game? In this course we will start from scratch and at the end we will have a complete racing game developed. We will develop AI which will compete with players. You will learn how to make a virtual currency system in your game to buy and unlock cars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Python By building Games in Python</title>
      <link>/learn-python-by-building-games-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 20:19:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-python-by-building-games-in-python/</guid>
      <description>Python Programming course, full Guide for Python Programmers &amp;amp; Python Coders in a simple and easy way with Python Examples, Python quizzes, Resources &amp;amp; 5 Python Games Projects in Python Games, Python OOP, to master Python 3 from zero to hero in this course.
What you will learn in this course ?
Learn Python by doing 5 Python Games Projects.
In this course you will learn how to Install Python 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Unity Shaders from Scratch</title>
      <link>/learn-unity-shaders-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-unity-shaders-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>In this course we&#39;re going to look at Unity ShaderLab and the HLSL shading language to create amazing shaders. Maybe you are
a developer struggling to bring to life a particular game feature because it needs a custom shader.
a developer who always wanted to create custom shaders but was too scared to start. a developer wanting to add some custom post-processing effects to your 3d renders.
Unity ShaderLab is how you create custom shaders.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
