<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dance on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/dance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dance on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/dance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to use breakdancing moves in dance fitness</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-use-breakdancing-moves-in-dance-fitness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-use-breakdancing-moves-in-dance-fitness/</guid>
      <description>What is breakdance?
Breakdancing is a style of street dancing that incorporates coordination, acrobatic and intricate body movements, style, and aesthetics. It evolved from the hip hop movement during the early 1970s and is the most widely known of all hip hop dance styles. Interested in learning how to breakdance? This popular, energetic form of dancing includes everything from spinning on your hands or head to using stylized footwork. Not only does breakdancing involve moves that are more complex and acrobatic than many other forms of dance, but it also has its own unique culture, lingo, and history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sıfırdan Shuffle,HipHop,Popping,DanceHall ve House Dansı</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/s%C4%B1f%C4%B1rdan-shufflehiphoppoppingdancehall-ve-house-dans%C4%B1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 12:00:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/s%C4%B1f%C4%B1rdan-shufflehiphoppoppingdancehall-ve-house-dans%C4%B1/</guid>
      <description>Dans etmek istiyorsun ancak kursa gitmekten mi çekiniyorsun yada vaktin mi yok ?
12 Yıllık dans tecrübeme dayanarak sizler için her seviyeye uygun basit ve eğlenceli eğitim seti hazırladım.
Bu kursu diğer kurslardan ayıran en büyük özelliği daha önce dans eğitimi almamış kişilere özel olarak hazırlanması Yani sıfırdan başlayıp adım adım kendimizi geliştireceğiz.
Ne Tür Danslar Sizleri bekliyor ;
Türkiyenin bir çok yerinde araştırmalar yaptın ama bir sonuca varmadın Biliyorum Hazır ol !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K-POP Dance Hits 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/k-pop-dance-hits-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 06:56:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/k-pop-dance-hits-2021/</guid>
      <description>Shoutout to all the KPOP fans out there! JNA is a Korean dancer who has participated and featured in many KPOP idols music videos and dance broadcasts. She is famously known for her work as a BLACKPINK stage dancer! You will be learning choreography to the hottest 2021 K-POP hits from JNA who has long experience working in the K-POP industry. She will be teaching you not only the choreography, but also tips and dance moves helpful for mastering idol group dances overall.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
