<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing Analytics &amp; Automation on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/marketing-analytics-automation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing Analytics &amp; Automation on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/marketing-analytics-automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Analytics: Customer Value and Promotion Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/marketing-analytics-customer-value-and-promotion-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/marketing-analytics-customer-value-and-promotion-strategy/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re looking for a complete course that will teach you how to calculate customer value to drive business decisions involving product pricing, acquisition cost, marketing cost, and many other parts of the business., right?
You&#39;ve found the right course Customer Valuation for Entrepreneurs and Marketers! This course teaches you everything you need to know about different methods to find customer lifetime value and how to find it in Excel using advanced excel tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics, GA4, GTM. How to improve your marketing?</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/google-analytics-ga4-gtm.-how-to-improve-your-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/google-analytics-ga4-gtm.-how-to-improve-your-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Description
Web analytics is the pulse of digital marketing. Everything is measured, and everything is measurable. With Google Analytics and a call tracking system, you can clearly understand who your client is, how to improve your site, and which traffic sources are the most beneficial for your business.
What will you learn in this course?
After completing this course, you will learn how to work with and get the most out of your web analytics data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
