<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Science on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Science on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Archaische Astronomie 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/archaische-astronomie-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/archaische-astronomie-1/</guid>
      <description>Kennst du dich am Nachthimmel aus?

In diesem einführenden Kurs zur Archaischen Astronomie beschäftigen wir uns mit den sichtbaren Planeten und deren zyklischen Wiederkehr am Sternenhimmel.
Du weißt sicher über den Mondzyklus Bescheid. Unser Zeitbegriff &#34;Monat&#34; stammt vom synodischen Mondzyklus. Es gibt aber noch weitere 5 sichtbare Planeten, deren Zyklus du mit freiem Auge beobachten kannst: Merkur, Venus, Mars, Jupiter und Saturn. Deren Bewegung lässt sich über den Lauf eines oder mehrere Jahre ohne Hilfsmittel und mit freiem Auge beobachten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Manipulation Works in Research</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-manipulation-works-in-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-manipulation-works-in-research/</guid>
      <description>DON&#39;T MANIPULATE RESEARCH - RESEARCH MANIPULATION
Manipulation is dangerous, regardless of where it occurs in life.
In this course, we are going to explore specifically how it occurs in scientific research.
Both researchers and other stakeholders can use a myriad methods to twist facts, change emotions in people, reduce the perceived effort of supporting someone, and other means.
This is the only course you will find that focuses on manipulation specifically for research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drug Design and Molecular Docking by using computation Tools</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/drug-design-and-molecular-docking-by-using-computation-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/drug-design-and-molecular-docking-by-using-computation-tools/</guid>
      <description>In the filed molecular orientation modeling, Molecular Docking the perfect binding of two molecules, like prediction of ligand binding on the active size of the protein. On the basic knowledge of computer you learn ligand based Computer Aided Drug design (CADD) approach involves the analysis of ligands known to interact with a target of interest. One such course is particularly designed to maintain knowledge at the beginner level of computer Drug Discovery applications for science students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn DNA Primer Design for Polymerase Chain Reaction</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-dna-primer-design-for-polymerase-chain-reaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-dna-primer-design-for-polymerase-chain-reaction/</guid>
      <description>In this Bioinformatics course you will be find out how to DNA Primer Design for polymerase chain reaction. Primer BLAST performs only a specificity check when a target template and both primers are provided. Design primers for single- or multi-insert cloning or for your site-directed mutagenesis experiment (insertion, deletion, replacement) with our primer design tool. Primer3 is a computer program that suggests PCR primers for a variety of applications, for example to create STSs (sequence tagged sites) for radiation hybrid mapping, or to amplify sequences for single nucleotide polymor- phism discovery</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Foundations of Biology: An Introduction</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-foundations-of-biology-an-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-foundations-of-biology-an-introduction/</guid>
      <description>This course will teach you the foundations and basics of biology and go further in-depth on various interesting concepts.
Topics Covered In Course
Characteristics of Life
Properties of Water
Atoms and Elements
Bonds
Cells
Lipid Bilayers and Osmosis
Macromolecules
Content Overview
Suitable for all levels, this is an in-depth learning course with lectures and quizzes. You do not need any prior experience to understand the material in this course. This course will walk you through your adventure into Biology and the Characteristics of Life by providing engaging video&#39;s on various topics and quizzes to test your knowledge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AP Physics 1 - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ap-physics-1-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ap-physics-1-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Master AP Physics 1 and get the score you want in this clear, concise, and in-depth course! This course will teach you everything, from kinematics to energy to momentum, and consists of lectures and practice problems for each unit. This is the first part of the entire AP Physics 1 course, covering the first portion of the curriculum units. Each unit has specific videos with hand-picked problems to supplement the lectures, making the overall learning process easy, efficient, and effective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angiosperm :  Flowering Plant</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/angiosperm-flowering-plant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/angiosperm-flowering-plant/</guid>
      <description>The flowering plants, also known as Angiospermae, meaning hidden seeds in Greek, are the most diverse group of land plants with 64 orders, 416 families, approximately 13,000 known genera and 300,000 known species. Like gymnosperms, angiosperms, which are also known by Magnoliophyta, are seed-producing plants.
The angiosperms dominate Earth’s surface and vegetation in more environments, particularly terrestrial habitats, than any other group of plants. As a result, angiosperms are the most important ultimate source of food for birds and mammals, including humans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning &amp; Data Science A-Z: Hands-on Python 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/machine-learning-data-science-a-z-hands-on-python-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/machine-learning-data-science-a-z-hands-on-python-2021/</guid>
      <description>Are you interested in data science and machine learning, but you don&#39;t have any background, and you find the concepts confusing?
Are you interested in programming in Python, but you always afraid of coding?
I think this course is for you!
Even if you are familiar with machine learning, this course can help you to review all the techniques and understand the concept behind each term.
This course is completely categorized, and we don&#39;t start from the middle!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introductory Biology: Complete course of Biology</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introductory-biology-complete-course-of-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introductory-biology-complete-course-of-biology/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt; This course is designed to meet the requirement of the students to understand the Complete Introduction of Biology.

&amp;gt;This course presents many of the topics Found in O and A level biology.

&amp;gt;The topics are presented through PowerPoints presentation.Each body system is presented separately and there are quizzes at the end of each section.

&amp;gt;In this Course , Students will learn the introduction of Biology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete General Chemistry 20&#43; hours of lectures &amp; examples</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-general-chemistry-20-hours-of-lectures-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-general-chemistry-20-hours-of-lectures-examples/</guid>
      <description>Description:
General Chemistry is a basic course for a broad range of students from different fields of science and engineering. This course is designed to help you get a firm grasp over the most important topics in chemistry that you need to know in order to do great in your exams and classes. By the end of the course you’ll learn the principals and important concepts regarding matter, atoms, solutions, phases, chemical reactions, equilibrium, kinetics, acids and bases and so much more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>