<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Science on </title>
    <link>/tags/science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Science on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Angiosperm :  Flowering Plant</title>
      <link>/angiosperm-flowering-plant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/angiosperm-flowering-plant/</guid>
      <description>The flowering plants, also known as Angiospermae, meaning hidden seeds in Greek, are the most diverse group of land plants with 64 orders, 416 families, approximately 13,000 known genera and 300,000 known species. Like gymnosperms, angiosperms, which are also known by Magnoliophyta, are seed-producing plants.
The angiosperms dominate Earth’s surface and vegetation in more environments, particularly terrestrial habitats, than any other group of plants. As a result, angiosperms are the most important ultimate source of food for birds and mammals, including humans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning &amp; Data Science A-Z: Hands-on Python 2021</title>
      <link>/machine-learning-data-science-a-z-hands-on-python-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/machine-learning-data-science-a-z-hands-on-python-2021/</guid>
      <description>Are you interested in data science and machine learning, but you don&#39;t have any background, and you find the concepts confusing?
Are you interested in programming in Python, but you always afraid of coding?
I think this course is for you!
Even if you are familiar with machine learning, this course can help you to review all the techniques and understand the concept behind each term.
This course is completely categorized, and we don&#39;t start from the middle!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introductory Biology: Complete course of Biology</title>
      <link>/introductory-biology-complete-course-of-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/introductory-biology-complete-course-of-biology/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt; This course is designed to meet the requirement of the students to understand the Complete Introduction of Biology.

&amp;gt;This course presents many of the topics Found in O and A level biology.

&amp;gt;The topics are presented through PowerPoints presentation.Each body system is presented separately and there are quizzes at the end of each section.

&amp;gt;In this Course , Students will learn the introduction of Biology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete General Chemistry 20&#43; hours of lectures &amp; examples</title>
      <link>/complete-general-chemistry-20-hours-of-lectures-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-general-chemistry-20-hours-of-lectures-examples/</guid>
      <description>Description:
General Chemistry is a basic course for a broad range of students from different fields of science and engineering. This course is designed to help you get a firm grasp over the most important topics in chemistry that you need to know in order to do great in your exams and classes. By the end of the course you’ll learn the principals and important concepts regarding matter, atoms, solutions, phases, chemical reactions, equilibrium, kinetics, acids and bases and so much more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
