<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Science on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/science/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Science on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Carbon Offsets and Climate Change Mitigation</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/carbon-offsets-and-climate-change-mitigation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/carbon-offsets-and-climate-change-mitigation/</guid>
      <description>Carbon offsets have been a popular climate change mitigation option for individuals and companies alike, but they have also been very contentious. This course provides you with an in-depth understanding of what kind of commodity carbon offsets are, how they have evolved, the biggest challenges offsets have encountered when it comes to delivering climate change mitigation, and where offset markets might be headed next. It answers several key questions: What defines a carbon offset?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>general mycology a brief review</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/general-mycology-a-brief-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/general-mycology-a-brief-review/</guid>
      <description>Topics In this course you find
introduction
history of science development
Morphology of fungi
Growth of fungi
Metabolism of fungi Genetics f fungi
Diseases caused by fungi Allergies Mycosis Mycotoxin
Laboratory diagnosis of fungi
Antifungal Drugs used in treatment fungal diseases
HISTORY OF THE SCIENCE GIVE AN IDEA OF ITS DEVELOPEMENT STAGES
The term &#34;mycology&#34; is derived from Greek word &#34;mykes&#34; meaning mushroom. Therefore mycology is the study of fungi The ability of fungi to invade plant and animal tissue was observed in early 19th century but the first documented animal infection by any fungus was made by Augastino Bassi , who in 1835 studied the muscardine disease of silkworm proved that the infection was caused by a fungus Beauveria bassiana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generative Adversarial Networks in Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/generative-adversarial-networks-in-artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/generative-adversarial-networks-in-artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>AI is an enabler in transforming diverse realms by exploiting deep learning architectures.
The course aims to expose students to cutting-edge algorithms, techniques, and codes related to AI and particularly the Generative Adversarial Networks used for data creation in deep learning routines. This course encompasses multidimensional implementations of the themes listed below; 1. Deep Learning: A subset of Hybrid Artificial Intelligence
2. Big Data is Fueling Applied AI.
3. How to model a problem in AI using datasets in Python (Keras &amp;amp; TensorFlow Libraries).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Physics Class 12 Practical Tests and Answers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/school-physics-class-12-practical-tests-and-answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/school-physics-class-12-practical-tests-and-answers/</guid>
      <description>School Physics Class 12 Practical Tests and Answers
Physics Lovers Save your Time and Effort ….. Physics Class 12 Practical Tests and Answers [Part 2 of 2] Special thanks to Ibn-ElHaytham, Isaac Newton, Albert Einstein, and other Giants who provides us &#34;Physics&#34;
Physics is the natural science that studies matter, its fundamental constituents, its motion and behavior through space and time, and the related entities of energy and force. Physics is one of the most fundamental scientific disciplines, and its main goal is to understand how the universe behaves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clinical Research in Pharmaceutical Industry Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/clinical-research-in-pharmaceutical-industry-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/clinical-research-in-pharmaceutical-industry-course/</guid>
      <description>A career in clinical research promises productive jobs in the country and abroad. At present, India is the most preferred hub for clinical trials among all the Asian countries.
If you are looking for a Career in clinical research in India, then keep reading the description below:
What is Clinical Research :
The health sector is an important sector in the economy. It not only provides health care facilities but also generates great academic and career choices for aspirants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete IPQC Tests for Pharmaceutical Tablet Dosage Form</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-ipqc-tests-for-pharmaceutical-tablet-dosage-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-ipqc-tests-for-pharmaceutical-tablet-dosage-form/</guid>
      <description>The development of a drug product is a lengthy process involving drug discovery, laboratory testing, animal studies, clinical trials and regulatory registration. To further enhance the effectiveness and safety of the drug product after approval, many regulatory agencies such as the United States Food and Drug Administration (FDA) also require that the drug product be tested for its identity, strength, quality, purity and stability before it can be released for use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eCTD &amp; CTD Preparation &amp; Submission Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ectd-ctd-preparation-submission-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ectd-ctd-preparation-submission-course/</guid>
      <description>The eCTD specification has been developed to facilitate the Global electronic Submission, Review and Lifecycle management of medicinal product dossiers for regulatory applications. *Complete the course as per your free time as life time access is available.
If you are paying more than 5k INR or $70 for private institute/academy then you are in loss. Please compare the course description and amount you are paying for such course.
It broadens the scope of the CTD to include information on variations, renewals and amendments, so that it is no longer a static document but is updatable throughout the life of the product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pharmaceutical Clinical Bioequivalence Study (BA/BE)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pharmaceutical-clinical-bioequivalence-study-ba/be/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pharmaceutical-clinical-bioequivalence-study-ba/be/</guid>
      <description>Bioequivalence studies are very important for the development of a pharmaceutical preparation in the pharmaceutical industry. Their rationale is the monitoring of pharmacokinetic and pharmacodynamic parameters after the administration of tested drugs.
Note: If you are paying more than 5k INR or $15 for private institute/academy then you are in loss. Please compare the course description and amount you are paying for such course.
Bioavailability &amp;amp; Bioequivalence
Bioavailability (BA) is defined as the rate and extent to which the unchanged active substance is absorbed and becomes available in the systemic circulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climatology - Meteorology of Climate</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/climatology-meteorology-of-climate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/climatology-meteorology-of-climate/</guid>
      <description>Climatology and Meteorology is a field of study on climate, to study the climate, we know how we can predict the weather and forecasting, If we can grasp the laws of climate we can benefit the economy and society. The resident that do laundry every day is inseparable from climate condition, as well the same as farmer, the construction worker, the seafarer, the fisherman, the miner, the traveler, the journalist, also the aviation flight that pilot the plane are closely relate to the climate condition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basics of CRISPR/Cas9 Technology</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basics-of-crispr/cas9-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 17:15:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/basics-of-crispr/cas9-technology/</guid>
      <description>CRISPR/Cas9 is a gene-editing tool that can manipulate gene expression in plants, humans, and animals. CRISPR, or Clustered Regularly Interspaced Short Palindromic Repeats, are short sections of bacterial DNA containing repetitive base sequences. CRISPR plays a crucial role in the immune response of bacteria against foreign DNA. When a bacterium detects viral DNA, it produces two strands of short RNA called guide RNA, which then go on to form a complex with an endonuclease enzyme called Cas9 (CRISPR-associated protein 9).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carbon Neutrality Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/carbon-neutrality-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 17:13:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/carbon-neutrality-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Carbon Neutrality Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn important knowledge about carbon neutrality and how you can contribute to a better.
I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge from carbon neutral basic to best practices in contributing to a carbon neutral future.
I will teach you the basic concepts of the different greenhouse gasses as well as the different energy options that we have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Virology</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-virology/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 14:59:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-virology/</guid>
      <description>You will learn about basics of Virology, history of virology, shape and structure, classification of virus, types of viruses, how are viruses beneficial, virus isolation, cultivation methods, DNA virus, RNA virus, reverse transcribing virus.
There is a glossary section in section 4 which will help you out further.
Being my third course, I have tried to make it simple.
Ratings: 4.44/5
Enrollments: 160
Coupon Code: 1B34121831F412F695ED
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archaische Astronomie 1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/archaische-astronomie-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/archaische-astronomie-1/</guid>
      <description>Kennst du dich am Nachthimmel aus?
In diesem einführenden Kurs zur Archaischen Astronomie beschäftigen wir uns mit den sichtbaren Planeten und deren zyklischen Wiederkehr am Sternenhimmel.
Du weißt sicher über den Mondzyklus Bescheid. Unser Zeitbegriff &#34;Monat&#34; stammt vom synodischen Mondzyklus. Es gibt aber noch weitere 5 sichtbare Planeten, deren Zyklus du mit freiem Auge beobachten kannst: Merkur, Venus, Mars, Jupiter und Saturn. Deren Bewegung lässt sich über den Lauf eines oder mehrere Jahre ohne Hilfsmittel und mit freiem Auge beobachten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Manipulation Works in Research</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-manipulation-works-in-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-manipulation-works-in-research/</guid>
      <description>DON&#39;T MANIPULATE RESEARCH - RESEARCH MANIPULATION
Manipulation is dangerous, regardless of where it occurs in life.
In this course, we are going to explore specifically how it occurs in scientific research.
Both researchers and other stakeholders can use a myriad methods to twist facts, change emotions in people, reduce the perceived effort of supporting someone, and other means.
This is the only course you will find that focuses on manipulation specifically for research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drug Design and Molecular Docking by using computation Tools</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/drug-design-and-molecular-docking-by-using-computation-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/drug-design-and-molecular-docking-by-using-computation-tools/</guid>
      <description>In the filed molecular orientation modeling, Molecular Docking the perfect binding of two molecules, like prediction of ligand binding on the active size of the protein. On the basic knowledge of computer you learn ligand based Computer Aided Drug design (CADD) approach involves the analysis of ligands known to interact with a target of interest. One such course is particularly designed to maintain knowledge at the beginner level of computer Drug Discovery applications for science students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn DNA Primer Design for Polymerase Chain Reaction</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-dna-primer-design-for-polymerase-chain-reaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-dna-primer-design-for-polymerase-chain-reaction/</guid>
      <description>In this Bioinformatics course you will be find out how to DNA Primer Design for polymerase chain reaction. Primer BLAST performs only a specificity check when a target template and both primers are provided. Design primers for single- or multi-insert cloning or for your site-directed mutagenesis experiment (insertion, deletion, replacement) with our primer design tool. Primer3 is a computer program that suggests PCR primers for a variety of applications, for example to create STSs (sequence tagged sites) for radiation hybrid mapping, or to amplify sequences for single nucleotide polymor- phism discovery</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Foundations of Biology: An Introduction</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-foundations-of-biology-an-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-foundations-of-biology-an-introduction/</guid>
      <description>This course will teach you the foundations and basics of biology and go further in-depth on various interesting concepts.
Topics Covered In Course
Characteristics of Life
Properties of Water
Atoms and Elements
Bonds
Cells
Lipid Bilayers and Osmosis
Macromolecules
Content Overview
Suitable for all levels, this is an in-depth learning course with lectures and quizzes. You do not need any prior experience to understand the material in this course. This course will walk you through your adventure into Biology and the Characteristics of Life by providing engaging video&#39;s on various topics and quizzes to test your knowledge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AP Physics 1 - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ap-physics-1-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ap-physics-1-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Master AP Physics 1 and get the score you want in this clear, concise, and in-depth course! This course will teach you everything, from kinematics to energy to momentum, and consists of lectures and practice problems for each unit. This is the first part of the entire AP Physics 1 course, covering the first portion of the curriculum units. Each unit has specific videos with hand-picked problems to supplement the lectures, making the overall learning process easy, efficient, and effective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angiosperm :  Flowering Plant</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/angiosperm-flowering-plant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/angiosperm-flowering-plant/</guid>
      <description>The flowering plants, also known as Angiospermae, meaning hidden seeds in Greek, are the most diverse group of land plants with 64 orders, 416 families, approximately 13,000 known genera and 300,000 known species. Like gymnosperms, angiosperms, which are also known by Magnoliophyta, are seed-producing plants.
The angiosperms dominate Earth’s surface and vegetation in more environments, particularly terrestrial habitats, than any other group of plants. As a result, angiosperms are the most important ultimate source of food for birds and mammals, including humans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning &amp; Data Science A-Z: Hands-on Python 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/machine-learning-data-science-a-z-hands-on-python-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/machine-learning-data-science-a-z-hands-on-python-2021/</guid>
      <description>Are you interested in data science and machine learning, but you don&#39;t have any background, and you find the concepts confusing?
Are you interested in programming in Python, but you always afraid of coding?
I think this course is for you!
Even if you are familiar with machine learning, this course can help you to review all the techniques and understand the concept behind each term.
This course is completely categorized, and we don&#39;t start from the middle!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introductory Biology: Complete course of Biology</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introductory-biology-complete-course-of-biology/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introductory-biology-complete-course-of-biology/</guid>
      <description>&amp;gt; This course is designed to meet the requirement of the students to understand the Complete Introduction of Biology.
&amp;gt;This course presents many of the topics Found in O and A level biology.
&amp;gt;The topics are presented through PowerPoints presentation.Each body system is presented separately and there are quizzes at the end of each section.
&amp;gt;In this Course , Students will learn the introduction of Biology.
&amp;gt;Understand the Division and Branches of Biology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete General Chemistry 20&#43; hours of lectures &amp; examples</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-general-chemistry-20-hours-of-lectures-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-general-chemistry-20-hours-of-lectures-examples/</guid>
      <description>Description:
General Chemistry is a basic course for a broad range of students from different fields of science and engineering. This course is designed to help you get a firm grasp over the most important topics in chemistry that you need to know in order to do great in your exams and classes. By the end of the course you’ll learn the principals and important concepts regarding matter, atoms, solutions, phases, chemical reactions, equilibrium, kinetics, acids and bases and so much more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
