<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business Law on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/business-law/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business Law on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/business-law/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Understanding HIPAA Compliance</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/understanding-hipaa-compliance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/understanding-hipaa-compliance/</guid>
      <description>This course gives you a basic understanding of the US regulation, Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 or HIPPA as it is commonly known. The training provides a broader view of the legal and governing background of HIPAA along with the various rules and standards associated with it. In recent years, with the increase in the number of health data breaches, HIPAA has gained a lot of prominence in the healthcare arena.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Income Tax-Business Use of Home Deduction</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/income-tax-business-use-of-home-deduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/income-tax-business-use-of-home-deduction/</guid>
      <description>Business use of your home deduction including practical examples with actual tax forms that allow colleagues to see the concepts in practice and fully comprehend the law and how best to apply it in different situations, circumstances, and scenarios.
The course will discuss qualifications for the business use of the home deduction providing examples where applicable.
We will show how to figure, or calculate, the business use of the home deduction using actual expenses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contract Negotiation: A Beginner&#39;s Guide to Drafting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/contract-negotiation-a-beginners-guide-to-drafting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 19:59:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/contract-negotiation-a-beginners-guide-to-drafting/</guid>
      <description>If you have an immediate negotiation and you want to learn the principles of contract negotiation very quickly, this course is for you. Because it is only 40 minutes, but the tips of more than 10 hours of training class will be practically taught to you.
Although contract negotiations haven&#39;t altered much since the invention of email, new technologies are making them faster, smarter, and less hazardous. While it may seem self-evident, many people fail to consider the importance of preparing for contract discussions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
