<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Influence on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/influence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Influence on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/influence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking for Women</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-for-women/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-for-women/</guid>
      <description>Public Speaking - Imagine that every time you speak, people are in awe of your confidence and actually remember your messages and key ideas. Wouldn&#39;t you love to be able to stand up and speak to any crown, anytime, and know that you are coming across your very best, and that people understand you and remember your messages?  In this Public Speaking for Women course you will learn the following:  *How to speak with confidence  *How to tell stories  *How to avoid the most common Public Speaking blunders that affect both men and women public speakers  *How to get your audience to understand you and remember your messages  This course is delivered primarily through spoken lecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Manipulation Works</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-manipulation-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-manipulation-works/</guid>
      <description>A MATTER OF MANIPULATION
Manipulation is, no doubt, dangerous in the world of today.
It&#39;s important to be able to identify it so that you can stop it in its tracks.
You can be manipulated:
At work, by your manager or coworkers;
In business relationships, by partners or suppliers;
In relationships or friendships, through emotion or even bullying;
By politicians, the media or others, with false numbers;
By any type of person that wants to drive you to a specific type of action;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/public-speaking-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>This course was designed to show even absolute beginners how to become more confident when speaking in public. It includes 5 preformatted lessons packed with easy to understand information.

Discover how to be more confident when speaking in public!
Do you know what one of the easiest ways to become a successful public speaker is? Well it is really easy and that is to study other successful speakers.
Why not learn from the best?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NLP - Beginner Level - Personal Growth Mastery</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/nlp-beginner-level-personal-growth-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/nlp-beginner-level-personal-growth-mastery/</guid>
      <description>What is NLP?
NLP (Neuro Linguistic Programming) is &#39;the science &amp;amp; art of human excellence&#39;.
NLP is a simple, easy to learn, yet powerful methodology for studying what goes on inside you. How you think, feel &amp;amp; act in different situations in your life.
NLP provides you with the keys to change your thinking processes to effect lasting positive change in your life.
With NLP , you can change &#39;how&#39; you think about anything &amp;amp; transform your fears into strengths, overcome your limitations, change bad habits, get rid of phobias .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Charisma Guide for Men:Increase Your Influence</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-ultimate-charisma-guide-for-menincrease-your-influence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-ultimate-charisma-guide-for-menincrease-your-influence/</guid>
      <description>It was 2005 and I was fed up with always being Mr. Nice Guy. It was then clear to me the nicer I was the more people would take advantage of me! So I decided to learn how to stop all this mess, to learn from my experience, from the behavior of bigger men than me, and to extensively research how to become more charismatic! So I opened my eyes, ears, and mind to everything around me in all areas of life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>