<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Food &amp; Beverage on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/food-beverage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food &amp; Beverage on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/food-beverage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>No Oil Cooking Recipes - Eat Healthy! Live Strong!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/no-oil-cooking-recipes-eat-healthy-live-strong/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/no-oil-cooking-recipes-eat-healthy-live-strong/</guid>
      <description>**Course Updated - June 2022**
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; COURSE REGULARLY UPDATED: NEW TIPS, MORE LESSONS &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; CERTIFIED COACH, SPEAKER AND TRAINER &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; OVER 180,000 STUDENTS IN TOTAL &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
Life is all about compromises, right?
Well, if you think you can ignore your bad eating habits just because you exercise regularly, think again. Unfortunately, spending an hour of rigorous exercise in the gym for a greasy double cheeseburger or relying on a good metabolism to take the place of healthy eating habits completely misses the point of living a healthy lifestyle…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Pie Baking Course: Bake a Pie for Every Season</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-pie-baking-course-bake-a-pie-for-every-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 20:40:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-pie-baking-course-bake-a-pie-for-every-season/</guid>
      <description>We decided to bring you &#34;The Ultimate Pie Baking Course: Bake a Pie for Every Season&#34; because we once fell in love with baking pies, and felt that mixing some flavors together was so magical and beautiful, so we had to share this course with you so you can also enjoy preparing and baking pies yourself, at your home, using very simple tools and ingredients.
You can enjoy the pies we have for you, with your loved ones on any season and occasion around the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obsession - with healthy eating</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/obsession-with-healthy-eating/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 13:13:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/obsession-with-healthy-eating/</guid>
      <description>Notice: Please do NOT enrol on this course on impulse, thinking you might watch it later. Maybe show an interest on impulse, yes, but before you enrol, watch the Preview videos, read the Course Description and then make a decision. If you then enrol then please start the course as soon as possible. Watch the lectures, look at the workbooks and join in the discussions. Joining my courses is a serious business and I want you to get the most out of your study – but I also want you to enjoy the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Sourdough Bread Baking - Levels 1, 2, 3 and 4!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-sourdough-bread-baking-levels-1-2-3-and-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-sourdough-bread-baking-levels-1-2-3-and-4/</guid>
      <description>**New Courses just added as of 2/19/21** Learn how Wheat Germ can improve the flavor of your Sourdough Bread. The new updates in the Sourdough Bread Baking demonstrate more advanced techniques and recipes. Make sure to check them out today!
Complete Sourdough Bread Baking Course – Bake Your Own Homemade Bread Today – Bread Baking Sourdough at Home – San Francisco Sourdough Bread Baking
Imagine waking up in the morning with the fresh smell of sourdough bread baking that you cooked out of your own oven.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
