<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>No-Code Development on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/no-code-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in No-Code Development on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/no-code-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Augelab Studio No-Code Görüntü İşleme ve Yapay Zeka Eğitimi</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/augelab-studio-no-code-g%C3%B6r%C3%BCnt%C3%BC-i%C5%9Fleme-ve-yapay-zeka-e%C4%9Fitimi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/augelab-studio-no-code-g%C3%B6r%C3%BCnt%C3%BC-i%C5%9Fleme-ve-yapay-zeka-e%C4%9Fitimi/</guid>
      <description>AugeLab Studio, görüntü işleme ve yapay zeka ile esnek çözümler geliştirmek için tasarlanmış bir no-code platformdur. Görüntü işleme (Image processing) ve yapay zeka (artificial intelligence) işlevleriyle üretim süreçlerinizi kontrol ederek verimliliğinizi arttırmanıza yardımcı olur. AugeLab Studio karmaşık Library (kütüphane) ve kodlama görevleri ile uğraşırken kodlama bilgisine ihtiyaç duymadan sürükle bırak programlama mantığı ile problemlerinize odaklanabilir ve sistemlerinizi kolayca geliştirebilirsiniz.
AugeLab Studio ile kendi fonksiyon bloklarınızı oluşturabilir, oluşturduğunuz algoritmaları Python, Pyside, OpenCv, Tensorflow, YOLO gibi popüler yazılım dilleri ve kütüphaneleriyle kolayca entegre edebilirsiniz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel Tips and trick : Learn MS Excel by making 7 Projects</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-tips-and-trick-learn-ms-excel-by-making-7-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-tips-and-trick-learn-ms-excel-by-making-7-projects/</guid>
      <description>Learning how to properly work with Microsoft can be very complicated espescially if you never worked with this applicaiton before. This is why, this course have been created, to help you learn how to work with Microsoft Excel and what are all the mazing things that you can do with this application. If you:
- Need to learn the basics of Microsoft Excel for work
- Always wanted to create various projects with this application</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Guide to Use WordPress Gutenberg Editor (2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-guide-to-use-wordpress-gutenberg-editor-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-guide-to-use-wordpress-gutenberg-editor-2022/</guid>
      <description>Today, every company wants amazing, out-of-box website design for their company. The ideal requirement of good websites are as follows: Website Speed
Good Interface
Easy to handle and use
Responsive
Lightweight
And the list is never-ending. And these all features can be included on the website through Gutenberg. WordPress Gutenberg already has a number of features. So, you don&#39;t install third-party plugins for additional functionality. Fewer plugins will always ensure a faster loading speed of the website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Practice Tests &amp; Interview Questions (Basic/Adv)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/wordpress-practice-tests-interview-questions-basic/adv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:13:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/wordpress-practice-tests-interview-questions-basic/adv/</guid>
      <description>WordPress is the perfect tool for creating a fully customized website for any purpose. Whether you want to create a blog, a personal portfolio, a corporate business site, a forum, a classified website, an eCommerce site, or a business website to sell your products and services, you can do it with WordPress.
WordPress is by far the most popular, open-source CMS system. WordPress itself powers 40% of all websites of the World.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress Create Your Own Website 2022!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/wordpress-create-your-own-website-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/wordpress-create-your-own-website-2022/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re here because you want to create your own WordPress websites, right?
You don&#39;t Need Coding Ath All no Javascript no html no css no Php
This WordPress for Beginners course is the perfect place to start. This complete WordPress course is designed for beginners like you who have never built a WordPress website (or any website for that matter).
WordPress is the perfect tool for creating a fully customized website for any purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress Elementor Course: Develop Site Without Coding</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/wordpress-elementor-course-develop-site-without-coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/wordpress-elementor-course-develop-site-without-coding/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone, if you are looking to learn develop responsive website without coding knowledge than you can enroll this class. Now, this course is simple and easily understandable. In this course I will talk straight to the point, So we will cover more in less time. In this course, I will show you step by step how to create a website using Elementor. Elementor is a page builder plugin that replaces the basic WordPress editor with a live frontend editor, so you can create complex layouts visually and design your website live without having to switch between the editor and the preview mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-Fast Web Design using Carrd (2022 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultra-fast-web-design-using-carrd-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultra-fast-web-design-using-carrd-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience the course &#34;Ultra-Fast Web Design using Carrd (2022 Edition)&#34;.
Web design is important because it impacts how your brand is viewed by your target niche audience. You can either get them to stay on your page and learn about your company or leave your page and turn to a rival with the impact you make on them. Great web design allows you to keep your leads on your website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super-Fast Web Design using Weebly (2022 Grand Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/super-fast-web-design-using-weebly-2022-grand-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/super-fast-web-design-using-weebly-2022-grand-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Super-Fast Web Design using Weebly (2022 Grand Edition)&#34;.
It&#39;s easier to build a stellar web design than you would ever imagine. It does take a strategy though. The strategy lies in using the right software platforms and tools and that&#39;s where the Weebly Website Builder comes in handy.
Weebly is one of the biggest website builders with over 50m websites created. In comparison to many of its rivals, Weebly has always been more interested in enhancing the technology of its product than in running costly ad campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build an Amazon Affiliate E-Commerce Store from Scratch</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/build-an-amazon-affiliate-e-commerce-store-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 13:36:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/build-an-amazon-affiliate-e-commerce-store-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for tuning into our latest course. This time, we’ve teamed up with Developer, and pro affiliate marketer, Hemlata Singh, to show you how to build a complete Amazon Affiliate E-Commerce Store from scratch. By taking this course not only will you be able to build a complete e-commerce site, but you’ll also learn how to populate it with thousands of top rated Amazon products. You’ll earn a generous commission on each sale, through the Amazon Associate Affiliate program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Elementor &amp; WordPress, for Startups &amp; Freelancers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-elementor-wordpress-for-startups-freelancers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-elementor-wordpress-for-startups-freelancers/</guid>
      <description>Create an amazing website with WordPress and the world’s best page builder, Elementor (and NO CODE)! This is a practice-based course on the free version of Elementor, which is a drag &amp;amp; drop page builder built on WordPress!
We’re going to go through everything regarding designing &amp;amp; building a WordPress &amp;amp; Elementor website:
Buying a domain and protecting yourself from spam on the internet
Getting the best hosting on the market with a heavy discount</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make an eCommerce Website with WordPress For Beginner</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-make-an-ecommerce-website-with-wordpress-for-beginner/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-make-an-ecommerce-website-with-wordpress-for-beginner/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to This course, it&#39;s a really useful course for those people who wants to build a brand new eCommerce website with WordPress and woo-commerce plugin for their existing physical store. If you are a complete beginner and still worried about to create and manage an eCommerce website then you are at the right place because in this course you are going to learn how to build an eCommerce website without knowing any types of programming or coding knowledge by using simple most popular WordPress Elementor drag and drop page builder and with most popular free theme Astra.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
