<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Operating Systems &amp; Servers on </title>
    <link>/tags/operating-systems-servers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Operating Systems &amp; Servers on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/operating-systems-servers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Server 2012 R2 - Hands-on Training Part I</title>
      <link>/microsoft-server-2012-r2-hands-on-training-part-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/microsoft-server-2012-r2-hands-on-training-part-i/</guid>
      <description>About this course: 
This is Part I of a two-part series for learning Windows Server 2012 r2. Part I is for those needing to become familiar with Server 2012, virtualization, and configuring a Microsoft network from the ground up. In this first part, students will learn how to install and configure Server 2012 r2 just as they would as network administrators or networking consultants.
Part one of the course trains the student on installing, configuring, and managing the most common roles and features found on a Microsoft network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Server 2012 R2 - Intermediate Hands-on Training</title>
      <link>/microsoft-server-2012-r2-intermediate-hands-on-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/microsoft-server-2012-r2-intermediate-hands-on-training/</guid>
      <description>Please do not enroll in this course until you have completed the first building of your virtual lab environment. If you cannot create a virtual install of Server 2012, r2 using a Hypervisor, you will not partake in the lab exercises. 
This course picks up where Windows Server 2012r2 - Hands-on Training Part I leaves off. In part I of the course, we looked at installing and configuring a Windows Server 2012 r2 domain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Command Line Terminal Basic for Beginners (In Hindi)</title>
      <link>/linux-command-line-terminal-basic-for-beginners-in-hindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/linux-command-line-terminal-basic-for-beginners-in-hindi/</guid>
      <description>Become an effective Linux user and advance your Career. Learning the Linux Command Line will take you FAR!


Learn to appreciate the power of the Linux command line.

Understand the structure of the Linux File System.

Learn how to navigate your Linux File System using few simple commands!

Learn how to create, modify, and process files.

यह पाठ्यक्रम आईटी पेशेवरों या ऐसे लोगों के लिए लक्षित है जो लिनक्स से परिचित होना चाहते हैं। और यह दर्शकों को वह जानकारी देने के लिए है जो उन्हें कमांड-लाइन के साथ आरंभ करने के लिए जानना आवश्यक है और इसकी मदद से Linux manage कैसे करें।</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Command Line (cmd) &amp; Batch Script Management</title>
      <link>/windows-command-line-cmd-batch-script-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/windows-command-line-cmd-batch-script-management/</guid>
      <description>One of the many tools that administrators use on a daily basis is the Windows Command Line / Prompt. Over this course, you&#39;ll learn the following skills, which are often used in the real world:

* How to create, rename, move and delete files and directories.
* The different types of file systems and how to navigate between directories
*&amp;nbsp;Setting the date and time on your PC using the date, time and tzutil commands</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
