<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Operating Systems &amp; Servers on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/operating-systems-servers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Operating Systems &amp; Servers on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 01:42:26 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/operating-systems-servers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Command Line Terminal Basic for Beginners (In Hindi)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/linux-command-line-terminal-basic-for-beginners-in-hindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 01:42:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/linux-command-line-terminal-basic-for-beginners-in-hindi/</guid>
      <description>Become an effective Linux user and advance your Career. Learning the Linux Command Line will take you FAR!

Learn to appreciate the power of the Linux command line.

Understand the structure of the Linux File System.

Learn how to navigate your Linux File System using few simple commands!

Learn how to create, modify, and process files.

This course is aimed at IT professionals or people who wish to become familiar with Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Administración de Windows desde la Consola</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/administraci%C3%B3n-de-windows-desde-la-consola/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 00:53:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/administraci%C3%B3n-de-windows-desde-la-consola/</guid>
      <description>Curso 100% práctico, ya que incluso dentro de la teoría que se comparte mediante documentos, se explican con prácticas. Trata de mejorar las habilidades Administrativas usando sólo la consola del sistema de Windows, en este caso, CMD. Este curso te promete implementaciones desde un nivel básico hasta avanzado. Un curso al que le he dedicado más de 5 años estudiarlo y condensado en este material.
 Ratings: 4.55/5
Enrollments: 65043</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Linux on  VirtualBox quick setup</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ubuntu-linux-on-virtualbox-quick-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 23:13:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ubuntu-linux-on-virtualbox-quick-setup/</guid>
      <description>Running Linux on a virtual machine has many advantages: easy and secure setup, complete control over the machine, easy backUp and folder sharing.
Do you want to quickly start using Linux Ubuntu?
In this course you will learn how to easily set it up on a virtual machine using VirtualBox.
You will be able to fix the errors that might come along and set up a complete coding environment.  Ratings: 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT &amp; Desktop Computer Support - Real World Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/it-desktop-computer-support-real-world-troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 13:13:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/it-desktop-computer-support-real-world-troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description>Over this course we&#39;ll be covering some real world issues that can often appear when troubleshooting computer systems. Some of the topics covered are as follows:

* An overview of physical and logical troubleshooting, explaining the differences between the two and how these issues can be identified
* Troubleshooting steps to take in the case of a suspected hard disk failure
* How to identify and troubleshoot memory issues, such as insufficient and/or faulty RAM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Operating System: A complete Linux guide for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/linux-operating-system-a-complete-linux-guide-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/linux-operating-system-a-complete-linux-guide-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>This is a brand new Linux Administration course launched in August 2021.
Linux is the number 1 operating system in the Corporate world. Industry&#39;s most powerful computers are Linux based. Linux is a popular open-source operating system that’s easy to use and highly secure.

Every time you use Google or Facebook or any other major Internet site, you are communicating with servers running Linux. Most DVRs, airplane, and automobile entertainment systems, and recent TVs run on Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Google Colaboratory with Python</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-google-colaboratory-with-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-google-colaboratory-with-python/</guid>
      <description>Google Colaboratory is a Google cloud-based service that replicates Jupyter Notebook in the cloud. You don’t have to install anything on your system to use it. In most respects, you use Colaboratory as you would a desktop installation of Jupyter Notebook. Google Colaboratory is primarily for those readers who use something other than a standard desktop setup to work.
You&#39;ll learn about the all features of Google Colaboratory.
The course is for you if you&#39;re a newcomer to Data Science and Python programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Forensics: Analyzing Data Streams in NTFS</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cyber-forensics-analyzing-data-streams-in-ntfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cyber-forensics-analyzing-data-streams-in-ntfs/</guid>
      <description>The course will help students to learn about the basics of Microsoft Windows File System (NTFS), the Master File Table (MFT) and how data is stored in data streams, both primary and alternate. Students will also get to differentiate between resident and non-resident data and learn how to hide data in the ADS. It would also enable students to analyze the data inside and outside of the MFT and to locate the specific cluster/sector on the hard disk where this data is actually stored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux for Network Engineers: Practical Linux with GNS3</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/linux-for-network-engineers-practical-linux-with-gns3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/linux-for-network-engineers-practical-linux-with-gns3/</guid>
      <description>It is important for you as a network engineer to learn Linux!
Why? There are many reasons including:
1) A lot of network operating systems are based on Linux, or have a Linux shell you can access, or use Linux type commands. I&#39;ll show you an example using Cisco, Arista and Cumulus Linux.
2) Network Automation tools such as Ansible don&#39;t run the command node on Windows. You are probably going to use Linux with tools such as Ansible, Netmkio, NAPALM and other network automation tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel Pivot-Tabellen für Einsteiger</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/excel-pivot-tabellen-f%C3%BCr-einsteiger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 12:19:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/excel-pivot-tabellen-f%C3%BCr-einsteiger/</guid>
      <description>ALLGEMEIN
Bei Excel-Auswertungen ist es nicht selten, dass große Datenmengen analysiert werden müssen. Nicht jeder kennt alle erforderlichen Excel-Formeln und hat die Zeit, die Daten aufwendig professionell aufzubereiten.
Hier kann eine Pivot-Tabelle weiterhelfen
In diesem Kurs lernen Sie die wichtigsten Grundlagen, um Pivot-Tabellen und -Diagramme zu erstellen.

INHALT
Pivot-Erstellung
Aufbau der Pivot-Tabelle
Berechnungen
Diagramme
Daten ändern und aktualisieren
Abweichungen
mehrere Tabellen konsolidieren

Hinweis: Die Übungen wurden mit Excel 2016 erstellt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Crash Course for Beginners - 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/linux-crash-course-for-beginners-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 16:04:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/linux-crash-course-for-beginners-2021/</guid>
      <description>This course is for someone who needs basic training in Linux, someone who is already in IT and wants to add a new skill. It is specifically designed for those who have been really busy with their work and don&#39;t have enough time. Now you don&#39;t have to stay awake at night or sneak out of your lunch break. You will learn so many Linux commands in just 2 days. Sounds unreal?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Server 2012 R2 - Hands-on Training Part I</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-server-2012-r2-hands-on-training-part-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-server-2012-r2-hands-on-training-part-i/</guid>
      <description>About this course: 
This is Part I of a two-part series for learning Windows Server 2012 r2. Part I is for those needing to become familiar with Server 2012, virtualization, and configuring a Microsoft network from the ground up. In this first part, students will learn how to install and configure Server 2012 r2 just as they would as network administrators or networking consultants.
Part one of the course trains the student on installing, configuring, and managing the most common roles and features found on a Microsoft network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Server 2012 R2 - Intermediate Hands-on Training</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-server-2012-r2-intermediate-hands-on-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-server-2012-r2-intermediate-hands-on-training/</guid>
      <description>Please do not enroll in this course until you have completed the first building of your virtual lab environment. If you cannot create a virtual install of Server 2012, r2 using a Hypervisor, you will not partake in the lab exercises. 
This course picks up where Windows Server 2012r2 - Hands-on Training Part I leaves off. In part I of the course, we looked at installing and configuring a Windows Server 2012 r2 domain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Command Line (cmd) &amp; Batch Script Management</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/windows-command-line-cmd-batch-script-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/windows-command-line-cmd-batch-script-management/</guid>
      <description>One of the many tools that administrators use on a daily basis is the Windows Command Line / Prompt. Over this course, you&#39;ll learn the following skills, which are often used in the real world:

* How to create, rename, move and delete files and directories.
* The different types of file systems and how to navigate between directories
*&amp;nbsp;Setting the date and time on your PC using the date, time and tzutil commands</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>