<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Operating Systems &amp; Servers on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/operating-systems-servers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Operating Systems &amp; Servers on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/operating-systems-servers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fedora Linux from Scratch</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fedora-linux-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fedora-linux-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>This course will teach you how to quickly and easily master the Linux Command Line using Fedora.
The entire course is built on practical approach, so you will learn only useful knowledge with lots of practical examples in a very short amount of time. Concepts taught are applicable to all Linux distributions.
After finishing this course you will be able to easily navigate your way around a Linux system and feel confident at the command line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Complete Masterclass of Virtualization from scratch</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/a-complete-masterclass-of-virtualization-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/a-complete-masterclass-of-virtualization-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>Description
In this course, you will get a detailed understanding of the components that make up a virtual environment to lay a strong foundation for mastering computer virtualization and is designed for beginners who have little or no knowledge of virtualization. You will grasp the concept of virtualization and how it is used in corporate environments.
You get lifelong access to this course only in Udemy!
This course comes with a 30-day money-back guarantee!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ACE the Linux Administrator Interview : Most Asked Q&amp;A</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ace-the-linux-administrator-interview-most-asked-qa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ace-the-linux-administrator-interview-most-asked-qa/</guid>
      <description>Linux is the number ONE operating system in the Corporate world. Linux is a popular open-source operating system that’s easy to use and highly secure.
This set of Linux MCQs focuses on various Linux commands and their command line options &amp;amp; parameters that check your basic/intermediate knowledge of Linux. This test contains the best basic and intermediate multiple-choice questions and answers. It will be useful for anyone learning Linux Basics, Essentials and/or Fundamentals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Command Line Terminal Basic for Beginners (In Hindi)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/linux-command-line-terminal-basic-for-beginners-in-hindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/linux-command-line-terminal-basic-for-beginners-in-hindi/</guid>
      <description>Student Feedback:
Aakash waghamare: I many course completed but this course is awesome . Main advantage of this course basic to advance level command . sir is awesome explain and practice for student. I LIKE IT
Rejwan Gazi: That&#39;s awsome! I dont know what to say in one line. I learn fron this course a lot. and thanks to udemy and jaikishan sir.
Manindra Tamang: salute to teaching level, I haven&#39;t bored at any time my will power is always high during the learning period.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Operating System: A complete Linux guide for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/linux-operating-system-a-complete-linux-guide-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/linux-operating-system-a-complete-linux-guide-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>This is a brand new Linux Administration course updated in November 2021.
Linux is the number 1 operating system in the Corporate world. Industry&#39;s most powerful computers are Linux-based. Linux is a popular open-source operating system that’s easy to use and highly secure.
Every time you use Google or Facebook or any other major Internet site, you are communicating with servers running Linux. Most DVRs, airplane, and automobile entertainment systems, and recent TVs run on Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operating System: Understanding the core</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/operating-system-understanding-the-core/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/operating-system-understanding-the-core/</guid>
      <description>This course is for complete beginners. In this course, we are going to look at the concepts of Operating System basics. This course is designed for a better understanding of basic concepts of Operating systems for people who do not have much idea about the operating systems.
In our daily lives, we interact with various smart devices like Smartphones, computers, ATMs, Car Music Systems. More and more devices are becoming digital by day and all these different devices have some or other sort of Operating system in them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Linux on  VirtualBox quick setup</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ubuntu-linux-on-virtualbox-quick-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 17:17:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ubuntu-linux-on-virtualbox-quick-setup/</guid>
      <description>Running Linux on a virtual machine has many advantages: easy and secure setup, complete control over the machine, easy backUp and folder sharing.
Do you want to quickly start using Linux Ubuntu?
In this course you will learn how to easily set it up on a virtual machine using VirtualBox.
You will be able to fix the errors that might come along and set up a complete coding environment. Ratings: 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Tmux</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/linux-tmux/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 20:10:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/linux-tmux/</guid>
      <description>tmux is a terminal multiplexer, it enables a number of terminals to be created, accessed, and controlled from a single terminal. tmux can be used to create &#34;virtual&#34; terminals, allowing applications like vim or irssi to be run in separate terminals within a single window or console. tmux can also be used to allow a single terminal multiple &#34;tabs&#34;, with all the terminals under the control of a single tmux &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desktop Support / Troubleshooting- Healthcare IT Technicians</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/desktop-support-/-troubleshooting-healthcare-it-technicians/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/desktop-support-/-troubleshooting-healthcare-it-technicians/</guid>
      <description>Over this course, we&#39;ll be covering some of the unique aspects of working as an IT Support Technician within a healthcare IT environment such as a hospital.
Topics covered include the following:
* Various types of hardware &amp;amp; software typically found in clinical environments
* Data protection with regards to GDPR and sensitive data
* How infection control procedures apply to IT Support Technicians
* Some tips on using Windows Compatibility Mode</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legacy IT - Technical Support &amp; Desktop Troubleshooting Tips</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/legacy-it-technical-support-desktop-troubleshooting-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/legacy-it-technical-support-desktop-troubleshooting-tips/</guid>
      <description>Over this course, we&#39;ll be covering legacy operating systems and the things you need to know when troubleshooting any issues. Course topics include the following:
* Hardware ports that you would find on older machines, such as PS/2, USB, Parallel, Serial &amp;amp; SCSI ports.
* Legacy file systems such as FAT16 and FAT32.
* Legacy boot configuration files and how they work
* Plug and play support for hardware devices</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading Computer Networks from Windows 7 to Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/upgrading-computer-networks-from-windows-7-to-windows-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:37:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/upgrading-computer-networks-from-windows-7-to-windows-10/</guid>
      <description>Over this course, you&#39;ll learn about the different stages involved in upgrading an organisation&#39;s computer network from Windows 7 to Windows 10, this includes considerations such as:
* Planning your upgrade project
* Identifying potential issues before proceeding with the upgrade
* Auditing your network environment
* Communicating with various departments within your organisation
* Ensuring that your IT helpdesk team are prepared to deal with additional incoming support requests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 System Administration &amp; Basic Computer Skills</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/windows-10-system-administration-basic-computer-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:37:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/windows-10-system-administration-basic-computer-skills/</guid>
      <description>This course covers Windows 10 Administration as well as some basic computer skills surrounding the Windows 10 operating system, as follows:
* Logging into your machine, switching users, and signing out
* Finding your way around File Explorer and pinning commonly used items to the Start Menu and Taskbar
* Setting a default printer, screen size and screen resolution
* Overview of Accessibility Options available within Windows 10
* CTRL+ALT+DEL menu options, including Task Manager and locking your machine</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Deployment Services (WDS) on Windows Server 2019</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/windows-deployment-services-wds-on-windows-server-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:37:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/windows-deployment-services-wds-on-windows-server-2019/</guid>
      <description>Over this course, we&#39;ll be covering how to install and configure Windows Deployment Services, otherwise known as WDS. Topics covered on this course are as follows:
* An overview of Windows Deployment Services and how it can benefit your organisation
* The difference between Active Directory Integrated and Standalone configuration modes
* Setting up and installing Windows Deployment Services
* A detailed overview of the WDS Console itself
* The DISM command and the various subcommands available within DISM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Command Line (cmd) &amp; Batch Script Management</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/windows-command-line-cmd-batch-script-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 13:34:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/windows-command-line-cmd-batch-script-management/</guid>
      <description>One of the many tools that administrators use on a daily basis is the Windows Command Line (cmd) / Prompt. Over this course, you&#39;ll learn the following skills, which are often used in the real world by computer technicians:
* How to create, rename, move and delete files and directories within the Windows operating system using the command line.
* The different types of file systems and how to navigate between directories using the cmd prompt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concepts of Operating Systems</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/concepts-of-operating-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 22:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/concepts-of-operating-systems/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my course on &#39;Concepts of Operating Systems&#39;
The objective of the course is to make the learners understand the core concepts of the Operating Systems and interpret the same. After completing this course, You&#39;ll be able to explain all the concepts that are dealt in this course. I suggest you to take notes and note down the important points wherever and whenever necessary. The contents that we&#39;ll be discussing in this course are:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Administración de Servidor Virtual Privado para WordPress</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/administraci%C3%B3n-de-servidor-virtual-privado-para-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 14:59:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/administraci%C3%B3n-de-servidor-virtual-privado-para-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>Tener un Servidor Virtual Privado (VPS) ya no es una opción solamente de algunos elegidos capaces de administrarlos. Y es que hoy día cada vez los sitios web demandan más recursos para que su carga sea lo suficientemente rápida. Tenemos clientes o usuarios que quieres que al navegar no tengan que esperar demasiado tiempo. La realidad es que no son pocos los que siguen prefiriendo un sitio web alojado en un hosting compartido en lugar de administrar su propio servidor y contar con una completa autonomía.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Administración de Windows desde la Consola</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/administraci%C3%B3n-de-windows-desde-la-consola/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 19:17:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/administraci%C3%B3n-de-windows-desde-la-consola/</guid>
      <description>Curso 100% práctico, ya que incluso dentro de la teoría que se comparte mediante documentos, se explican con prácticas. Trata de mejorar las habilidades Administrativas usando sólo la consola del sistema de Windows, en este caso, CMD. Este curso te promete implementaciones desde un nivel básico hasta avanzado. Un curso al que le he dedicado más de 5 años estudiarlo y condensado en este material.
Ratings: 4.52/5
Enrollments: 67795
Coupon Code: 4F163F1C4FDC7BB01883</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Windows Command Line || CMD || Begginer to Intermediate</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-windows-command-line-cmd-begginer-to-intermediate/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 13:01:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-windows-command-line-cmd-begginer-to-intermediate/</guid>
      <description>Understanding CMD
With the command shell, you can have direct interaction with the operating system. Think command prompt as an interpreter that accepts the commands or the User’s inputs and translate them into machine language. These commands are predefined and perform a specific task. These commands can be clubbed together as well to perform a series of task. Also, these commands need not be entered manually and can be written in a batch file to automate some of the manual tasks like taking a scheduled server backup, deleting junk files and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows PowerShell || Begginer to Intermediate</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/windows-powershell-begginer-to-intermediate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 21:07:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/windows-powershell-begginer-to-intermediate/</guid>
      <description>What is PowerShell?
PowerShell is a cross-platform task automation solution made up of a command-line shell, a scripting language, and a configuration management framework. PowerShell runs on Windows, Linux, and macOS.
PowerShell or Microsoft PowerShell is a task automation and configuration management program from Microsoft, consisting of a command-line shell and the associated scripting language
PowerShell is Microsoft&#39;s incredibly powerful command-line shell and scripting language that has transformed the role of Sys Admin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT &amp; Desktop Computer Support - Real World Troubleshooting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/it-desktop-computer-support-real-world-troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 13:13:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/it-desktop-computer-support-real-world-troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description>Over this course we&#39;ll be covering some real world issues that can often appear when troubleshooting computer systems. Some of the topics covered are as follows:
* An overview of physical and logical troubleshooting, explaining the differences between the two and how these issues can be identified
* Troubleshooting steps to take in the case of a suspected hard disk failure
* How to identify and troubleshoot memory issues, such as insufficient and/or faulty RAM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Google Colaboratory with Python</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-google-colaboratory-with-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-google-colaboratory-with-python/</guid>
      <description>Google Colaboratory is a Google cloud-based service that replicates Jupyter Notebook in the cloud. You don’t have to install anything on your system to use it. In most respects, you use Colaboratory as you would a desktop installation of Jupyter Notebook. Google Colaboratory is primarily for those readers who use something other than a standard desktop setup to work.
You&#39;ll learn about the all features of Google Colaboratory.
The course is for you if you&#39;re a newcomer to Data Science and Python programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Forensics: Analyzing Data Streams in NTFS</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cyber-forensics-analyzing-data-streams-in-ntfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cyber-forensics-analyzing-data-streams-in-ntfs/</guid>
      <description>The course will help students to learn about the basics of Microsoft Windows File System (NTFS), the Master File Table (MFT) and how data is stored in data streams, both primary and alternate. Students will also get to differentiate between resident and non-resident data and learn how to hide data in the ADS. It would also enable students to analyze the data inside and outside of the MFT and to locate the specific cluster/sector on the hard disk where this data is actually stored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux for Network Engineers: Practical Linux with GNS3</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/linux-for-network-engineers-practical-linux-with-gns3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/linux-for-network-engineers-practical-linux-with-gns3/</guid>
      <description>It is important for you as a network engineer to learn Linux!
Why? There are many reasons including:
1) A lot of network operating systems are based on Linux, or have a Linux shell you can access, or use Linux type commands. I&#39;ll show you an example using Cisco, Arista and Cumulus Linux.
2) Network Automation tools such as Ansible don&#39;t run the command node on Windows. You are probably going to use Linux with tools such as Ansible, Netmkio, NAPALM and other network automation tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel Pivot-Tabellen für Einsteiger</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-pivot-tabellen-f%C3%BCr-einsteiger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 12:19:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-pivot-tabellen-f%C3%BCr-einsteiger/</guid>
      <description>ALLGEMEIN
Bei Excel-Auswertungen ist es nicht selten, dass große Datenmengen analysiert werden müssen. Nicht jeder kennt alle erforderlichen Excel-Formeln und hat die Zeit, die Daten aufwendig professionell aufzubereiten.
Hier kann eine Pivot-Tabelle weiterhelfen
In diesem Kurs lernen Sie die wichtigsten Grundlagen, um Pivot-Tabellen und -Diagramme zu erstellen.
INHALT
Pivot-Erstellung
Aufbau der Pivot-Tabelle
Berechnungen
Diagramme
Daten ändern und aktualisieren
Abweichungen
mehrere Tabellen konsolidieren
Hinweis: Die Übungen wurden mit Excel 2016 erstellt. Diese können allerdings auch auf die vorigen Versionen angewendet werden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux Crash Course for Beginners - 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/linux-crash-course-for-beginners-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 16:04:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/linux-crash-course-for-beginners-2021/</guid>
      <description>This course is for someone who needs basic training in Linux, someone who is already in IT and wants to add a new skill. It is specifically designed for those who have been really busy with their work and don&#39;t have enough time. Now you don&#39;t have to stay awake at night or sneak out of your lunch break. You will learn so many Linux commands in just 2 days. Sounds unreal?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Server 2012 R2 - Hands-on Training Part I</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-server-2012-r2-hands-on-training-part-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-server-2012-r2-hands-on-training-part-i/</guid>
      <description>About this course: This is Part I of a two-part series for learning Windows Server 2012 r2. Part I is for those needing to become familiar with Server 2012, virtualization, and configuring a Microsoft network from the ground up. In this first part, students will learn how to install and configure Server 2012 r2 just as they would as network administrators or networking consultants.
Part one of the course trains the student on installing, configuring, and managing the most common roles and features found on a Microsoft network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Server 2012 R2 - Intermediate Hands-on Training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-server-2012-r2-intermediate-hands-on-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-server-2012-r2-intermediate-hands-on-training/</guid>
      <description>Please do not enroll in this course until you have completed the first building of your virtual lab environment. If you cannot create a virtual install of Server 2012, r2 using a Hypervisor, you will not partake in the lab exercises. This course picks up where Windows Server 2012r2 - Hands-on Training Part I leaves off. In part I of the course, we looked at installing and configuring a Windows Server 2012 r2 domain.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
