<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Photography Tools on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/photography-tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Photography Tools on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 20:22:08 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/photography-tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Lightroom Masterclass - Beginner to Expert</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/adobe-lightroom-masterclass-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 20:22:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/adobe-lightroom-masterclass-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Adobe Lightroom is a powerful, intuitive program used for enhancing, organizing, and editing your photos. Users can render enhancements on everything from smartphone photos to raw DSLR images. This course explores many of the exciting features this program offers. Take a look at just a brief summary of the course content below. Section 1: Introduction Students are provided with an overview of learning objectives and some of the key features that the course will explore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photo Colorization -  Colorize Old Photos Using a Free Tool</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/photo-colorization-colorize-old-photos-using-a-free-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 12:05:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/photo-colorization-colorize-old-photos-using-a-free-tool/</guid>
      <description>Want to give life to your old black &amp;amp; white photographs?

Then it&#39;s time for you to learn Photo Colorization!

In the span of one hour, you will learn a quick &amp;amp; simple method of coloring black &amp;amp; white images. Best of all, you will be using a free tool so you don&#39;t have to make any investment (other than your time of course). You just need to focus your time in quickly learning on how colorize old photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Lightroom For Beginners : Complete Photo/Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/adobe-lightroom-for-beginners-complete-photo/image-editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/adobe-lightroom-for-beginners-complete-photo/image-editing/</guid>
      <description>=== students&#39; reviews&#39; regarding this course ===
&#34;This course is great for Lightroom beginners. Although I do have some experience with Lightroom, I needed a course like this because of its simplicity and details covered. All the modules covered are important for any editing process. Would recommend this to every photographer out there starting out. Thank you for the course!&#34; -- Ansh Agrawal
&#34;It was informative and interactive&#34; -- Bamidele Joshua</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GIMP 2.10 für Anfänger - Grundkurs für jeden Einsteiger!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/gimp-2.10-f%C3%BCr-anf%C3%A4nger-grundkurs-f%C3%BCr-jeden-einsteiger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/gimp-2.10-f%C3%BCr-anf%C3%A4nger-grundkurs-f%C3%BCr-jeden-einsteiger/</guid>
      <description>Das GNU Image Manipulation Program (GIMP) ist eine kostenlose, Photoshop ähnliche Bildbearbeitungssoftware welche Windows, Max OS und Linux unterstützt.
Okay, aber warum nutzt es dann nicht jeder?
Selbst mit Zugriff auf viele GNU + Youtube-Tutorials ist das GIMP-Programm immer noch eine schwer zu erlernende Software.
Bis jetzt...
Mit meinem GIMP 2.10 für Anfänger - Grundkurs für jeden Einsteiger! lernt jeder, innerhalb von nur 3 Stunden, mit GIMP umzugehen und danach sein Projekt zu bearbeiten.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
