<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Other Marketing on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/other-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Other Marketing on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/other-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Market Research: Marketing Psychology &amp; Consumer Behavior</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/market-research-marketing-psychology-consumer-behavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/market-research-marketing-psychology-consumer-behavior/</guid>
      <description>If you have a business idea or an existing business that is researching new directions or strategies, you will learn to conduct market research using the following methods:
Interviews
Surveys
Focus groups
Measuring data and KPIs
Using industry reports
MARKETING PSYCHOLOGY
After going over standard industry research, you will also learn marketing psychology. These are common principles that marketers use to position their products and marketing messaging that align with how buyers make purchasing decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2022 - Part 11</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2022-part-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2022-part-11/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2022 - Part 11&#34;.
So, want to create more ebooks, reach more readers, and sell a ton of books, starting today?
Let&#39;s read and explore this interesting concept further.
In recent years, the book market has become even more and more saturated and has given rise to intense or fiery competition that will continue in 2022 and even the next year. eBook marketing can get very tricky and we need certain marketing tactics or new tricks to help in this regard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2022 - Part 7</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2022-part-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2022-part-7/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2022 - Part 7&#34;.
Business blogging is a marketing strategy that involves using blogs to increase your company&#39;s online visibility. A business blog, like social media, direct mail, and email marketing, is a marketing channel that aids in the growth of a company. Freelancers can increase their exposure and sign new clients by demonstrating their writing skills on large platforms with a large audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2022 - Part 9</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2022-part-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2022-part-9/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2022 - Part 9&#34;.
Authors typically use all their efforts, resources, and budgets to create an e-book and most of them aren&#39;t even aware of the one concept that is vital which will help them throughout the process of reaching an audience - whom they are writing for. The concept is called &#34;Marketing&#34;. We must know that just merely writing a great eBook alone won&#39;t ensure that you generate opt-ins, gain recognition, or capture sales unless you market them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Competitor Analysis Masterclass (Phenomenal Edition 2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/competitor-analysis-masterclass-phenomenal-edition-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/competitor-analysis-masterclass-phenomenal-edition-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Competitor Analysis Masterclass (Phenomenal Edition 2022)&#34;.
Do you know? Competitive analysis can make or break your marketing strategy in 2022.
There is intense competition in business everywhere nowadays. Identifying your target competitors and evaluating their strategies to determine their strengths and weaknesses relative to those of your own product or service is a must. This unforgettable course will provide a great framework to help marketers and newbies like you uncover the secrets of your competitors in an all-new fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New-Age Technologies For Fitness Trainers (2022 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/new-age-technologies-for-fitness-trainers-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/new-age-technologies-for-fitness-trainers-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>Technology is a flourishing sector today, with a plethora of intriguing and innovative products as well as new learning opportunities. Apps and wearable technology, as well as digital fitness platforms and equipment, are among the most popular fitness technologies today. Putting aside the excitement of new developments, the convenience that technology may provide is unrivalled. Long before the pandemic, the mix of fitness technology and digital fitness was altering our market; both areas were rising at a rapid pace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RoboAuthor: Content Writing Automation 2022 - Part 12</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2022-part-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/roboauthor-content-writing-automation-2022-part-12/</guid>
      <description>So, want to proofread effectively, or start a proofreading business and sell a ton of editing or writing services, right away?
Hop in.
Editing is not just the icing on the cake; it is a highly important part of the writing process. Get ready. Take the guesswork out of great writing with this course. See what you can accomplish with the power of these proofreading tools at your fingertips. Easily improve any text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Social Networking - Startups Meet (2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-future-of-social-networking-startups-meet-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-future-of-social-networking-startups-meet-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience the course &#34;The Future of Social Networking - Startups Meet (2022)&#34;.
&#34;We all know that Entrepreneurship is a steady race of life where you can experience the best and also the worst things together.&#34;
Despite constant challenges creeping up, entrepreneurship will be the centre stone of development in this ever-growing fast-paced world. The goal of Entrepreneurship is to drive innovation, create jobs, and improve the lives of people with products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copywriting: 3 Crucial Points For Your Text To Sell Itself</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/copywriting-3-crucial-points-for-your-text-to-sell-itself/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 22:09:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/copywriting-3-crucial-points-for-your-text-to-sell-itself/</guid>
      <description>We can’t go a day in our life without reading something on the internet: blogposts, articles, promotional texts, etc. Who writes them? Who makes us read all of that information? A copywriter. Just image the amount of power hidden inside copywriter’s brain. When someone needs something sold – they contact a copywriter, when someone needs something promoted – they contact a copywriter. Don’t underestimate that. If you want to learn how all the things forementioned here are done, come along and let’s talk about it in the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Render Classic Edition: Create Live Audio-Rooms (2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/space-render-classic-edition-create-live-audio-rooms-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/space-render-classic-edition-create-live-audio-rooms-2022/</guid>
      <description>Someone said that the Future of Social Media is &#34;All Talk&#34; and nothing more - back in the year 2016. He or she who thought about this true fact is absolutely right. Audio-based social media stepped up to the plate in response to a pandemic-induced demand for genuine connection while avoiding screen weariness this year. Experts say that while Android OS will help companies to grow, developing a creator community will be crucial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing Course for Fitness Professionals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-marketing-course-for-fitness-professionals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:30:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-marketing-course-for-fitness-professionals/</guid>
      <description>To succeed in the fitness industry or field, your company must stand out from the crowd and competition. That means developing and implementing a solid and proven digital marketing strategy that is powered by Artificial Intelligence (AI). Social media marketing allows you to showcase your skills and expertise while also allowing people to learn about your company. It&#39;s a great, low-cost way to get more customers. But manual implementation of the same takes a lot of time, effort and resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space Render 2.0: Transform your podcast into videos in 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/space-render-2.0-transform-your-podcast-into-videos-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:30:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/space-render-2.0-transform-your-podcast-into-videos-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the third course in Level 3 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Creative Arts, Design and Animation&#34;.
Marketers always desire to transform their podcast into videos. We also know that humans are naturally visual beings, after all.
Video adds visual ambiguity and the absence of audio&#39;s emotional depth. That&#39;s one of the reasons why the digital web is increasingly becoming the backbone of video.
In hopes of expanding their following, creators convert their work into a video for YouTube, like young actors flocking to Hollywood for more exposure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISTQB Acceptance Testing training with sample paper</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/istqb-acceptance-testing-training-with-sample-paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 13:47:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/istqb-acceptance-testing-training-with-sample-paper/</guid>
      <description>This course will help you to clear ISTQB Acceptance Testing EXAM,
First few video are provided for free, you can watch them to check the quality of the course.
we have maintained the same quality through the course. Chapters covered:
Introduction and Foundations
Acceptance Criteria, Acceptance Tests and Experience Based Practices
Business Process and Business Rules Modeling
Acceptance Testing for Non-Functional Requirements
Collaborative Acceptance Testing
Highlights of the course:
Each chapter is covered in a easy to understand language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction To SEO Based Content Writing (Hindi)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-seo-based-content-writing-hindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 13:19:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-seo-based-content-writing-hindi/</guid>
      <description>Feel Free To Enjoy This Course And Learn One Of The Best SEO Based Content Writing Course In Language “Hindi”. So, After Completing The Course, You Will Be Enable To Write Search Engine Based Contents. And With That, You Can Increase Good Valuable Content In Any Article. After Completing The Job You Can Do Freelance Or Create Your Own Blog To Earn Good Amount Of Dollars Every Month.
Ratings: 3.41/5</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentaciones de impacto, más allá del PowerPoint</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/presentaciones-de-impacto-m%C3%A1s-all%C3%A1-del-powerpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 10:34:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/presentaciones-de-impacto-m%C3%A1s-all%C3%A1-del-powerpoint/</guid>
      <description>Curso práctico en el descubrir recursos visuales y herramientas innovadoras para conseguir que la clásica presentación de PowerPoint de un giro de 180 grados. Si quieres diseñar presentaciones de impacto y distintas, es vital buscar recursos fuera de PowerPoint. Pero... ¿Dónde?
¿Cómo elegir fotografías? ¿Dónde? ¿Cómo diseño una paleta de colores armónica?¿Dónde encuentro iconos distintos?¿Cómo diseño gráficos originales? ¿Cómo diseño una tabla visualmente atractiva?
Estás son un ejemplo de preguntas que vamos a contestar en este curso: Presentaciones de impacto, más allá del PowerPoint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Become a Paid Influencer</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-become-a-paid-influencer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 13:12:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-become-a-paid-influencer/</guid>
      <description>Are you an influencer? Do you want to be paid by brands for your promotional services? In this course, you will learn how to sell your influencer marketing services to brands and agencies. Although we will focus only on sales on the Revenzer platform, you can apply these techniques to other platforms and contests.
You worked hard on your social media profile, you worked hard on creating good content, and how many hours did you invest in presenting yourself to brands?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inbound Marketing: Content Marketing, KPI &amp; Google Analytics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/inbound-marketing-content-marketing-kpi-google-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 09:38:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/inbound-marketing-content-marketing-kpi-google-analytics/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to use inbound marketing strategies to get the best leads and most engaged customers to your site or product.
Then monitor how those leads behave on your website using Google Analytics which is a data-driven approach where you identify and set the right KPIs (Key Performance Indicators) to monitor and work on improving. Once your KPIs are heading in the right direction, so will your business.
WHY IS INBOUND MARKETING GREAT?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
