<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Entrepreneurship on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/entrepreneurship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Entrepreneurship on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/entrepreneurship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>From Zoom No to Zoom Pro</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/from-zoom-no-to-zoom-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/from-zoom-no-to-zoom-pro/</guid>
      <description>Since 2020 we have used video conferences like never before and doing business on Zoom, Microsoft Teams, Google Meet or Skype has become the new standard and it is such a powerful and useful tool if used right. This course teaches you how to show up professionally on Zoom and how to handle the most common situations we come across on Zoom.
In this course, I walk you through step by step how to show up like the professional business owner you are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Passive Income 6 figures Drop Servicing Home Online Business</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/passive-income-6-figures-drop-servicing-home-online-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/passive-income-6-figures-drop-servicing-home-online-business/</guid>
      <description>Passive Income Drop Servicing Online Business Home Business
This passive income drop servicing online business or home business is the first course on Udemy that teaches you how to start to drop servicing online business or home business for passive income. This course will take you step by step from start to end to teach how to start a passive income drop servicing online business home business to make six figures per month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurship - Ft. Matthew Rolnick of Yaymaker, Groupon</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/entrepreneurship-ft.-matthew-rolnick-of-yaymaker-groupon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/entrepreneurship-ft.-matthew-rolnick-of-yaymaker-groupon/</guid>
      <description>Learn with Confidence:
This course has been featured in the following publications:
Mashable, New York Post, PCMag, The Hill, Neowin, Entrepreneur Magazine, Financial Post, PCWorld, Black Enterprise, AllHipHop Mag, Graham Media Group (KSAT, WJXT, ClickOrlando, Click2Houston).
Matthew Rolnick (Course Co-Author/Instructor) is a Forbes Contributor and the author of &#34;Find your YAY&#34;. Since release, his book has quickly climbed to the top spot on Amazon in several business and marketing categories. In this course you will learn:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Online 2021 &amp; 2020 Start to Finish</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-online-2021-2020-start-to-finish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-online-2021-2020-start-to-finish/</guid>
      <description>QuickBooks Online 2021 updates are being prepared. The current course community will have access to the updates as we create them.
We will update this course each year at no additional cost, so the course community has access to the latest look and feel of QuickBooks Online and can also look back to see the changes that have been made.
We have received a lot of positive feedback and suggestions for improvements that we will put into place as we update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audiobook Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/audiobook-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/audiobook-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>In today&#39;s age of virtual social interaction, the line between personal usage and sales is non-existent.
There are over two million self-published books released every year, and most of those books are sold predominantly online.
Once your book is narrated, perfected, and published, you have to get it out there to listeners.
Just like your digital and print versions, there are specific tactics you can use to generate traffic, reach new listeners, and maximize your profits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn 47 Different Ways to Make Money Online!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-47-different-ways-to-make-money-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-47-different-ways-to-make-money-online/</guid>
      <description>Imagine having the FREEDOM to make money just by using your smartphone or laptop.
That&#39;s what I&#39;ve been doing already for several years and now I have a privilege to help YOU too.
In this course, I&#39;ll show you +47 ways to make money online.
Learn just 1 strategy to make money and you&#39;ll earn your course price back. The rest will be pure profits for you!
Over the course of years, I&#39;ve helped 1,000&#39;s of ordinary people to start their &#39;Make Money Online&#39; journeys and you&#39;ll be the next one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Money From Home: 45 Work From Home Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/make-money-from-home-45-work-from-home-opportunities/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 10:23:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/make-money-from-home-45-work-from-home-opportunities/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to Make Money From Home?
Do you want to find a flexible Work From Home Job?
Then this is the PERFECT COURSE FOR YOU.
You&#39;re going to see over 45 make money from home opportunities.
I&#39;ve shown steps to make money for 100,000&#39;s people worldwide and every single month around 500,000 people watch my videos on my YouTube channel called &#34;Learn to Make Honest Money Online&#34;.
It will be my privilege to help YOU to make money online too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start A Successful Business: Best Questions</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/start-a-successful-business-best-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/start-a-successful-business-best-questions/</guid>
      <description>Do you have an idea for a business you really believe will work? Are you looking for simple, actionable information that will take you to the next level in your entrepreneurial journey? Do you want to convert your hobby into a business? Are you thinking about quitting the 9-5 grind and one day running your own successful business? If the answer to any of the above questions is yes, then I can confidently say you have come to the right place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Business – Work from Home</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/online-business-work-from-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/online-business-work-from-home/</guid>
      <description>This course gives learners the tools to create an online business, taking their current skills, and applying them to a structured business model.
There is a lot of useful information about building an online business, but much of the information is provided by professional marketers, making it difficult for many individuals to see how to apply their skills, their industry expertise, to an online business.
This course is not taught by a marketing professional.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authority Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/authority-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:50:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/authority-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you want to increase your sales and expand your outreach, you need to position yourself as an authority in your market.
Authority marketing is about positioning your business in a way that you become the logical choice when someone is making the decision who to turn to for help, advice, products or services.
Your goal is to become the go-to person in your niche, or at the very least, one of the first names that come to mind when someone thinks about who to turn to for help with specific topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local SEO &amp; Facebook ADS as PROJECT &amp; FUN: 10 Days CHALLENGE</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/local-seo-facebook-ads-as-project-fun-10-days-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:47:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/local-seo-facebook-ads-as-project-fun-10-days-challenge/</guid>
      <description>PLEASE, ACCEPT OUR 10 DAYS CHALLENGE AND LEARN LOCAL SEO, FACEBOOK ADS &amp;amp; CONTENT MARKETING!!! DIGITAL MARKETING SKILLS ARE NOT OPTIONAL ANYMORE AND YOU NEED TO KNOW WHAT TO DO IN ORDER TO AVOID WASTING PRECIOUS TIME, EFFORT, AND MONEY NOW IS THE TIME TO UPSKILL, GROW YOUR REACH, AND BUILD MOMENTUM. IF YOU TAKE TIME NOW TO PUT IN SOME EFFORT, YOU’LL ENJOY HUGE REWARDS LATER, AS THE WORLD MAKES THE SHIFT INTO A MOSTLY DIGITAL ECONOMY!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basics of Venture Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/basics-of-venture-capital/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/basics-of-venture-capital/</guid>
      <description>Venture capital is a type of financing that investors provide to startup companies and small businesses that are believed to have long-term growth potential.

As companies grow, they go through the different stages of venture capital. Additionally, firms or investors may focus specifically on certain stages—which impacts how they invest.

In a number of critical areas, including legal, tax and strategic matters, a VC firm can provide active support, which is all the more important at a key stage in the growth of a young company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kickstarter Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/kickstarter-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/kickstarter-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve ever wanted to create something new with a community of enthusiastic people cheering you on, you’ve come to the right place.
This course is based on everything we’ve learned from reviewing over 200,000 projects — each of them created by someone like you. We hope it’ll help you get started with shaping your own project, whether it’s to make a movie, an album, a game, a gadget, a play, a restaurant, or pretty much anything else that springs from the imagination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Money From Home: 12 EASY Options to Make Money Now</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/make-money-from-home-12-easy-options-to-make-money-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/make-money-from-home-12-easy-options-to-make-money-now/</guid>
      <description>If YOU have been looking for easy options to make money from home, this course is the right one for you.
I&#39;ll show you CLICK-BY-CLICK 12 easy ways to make money online.
This will also give YOU confidence that anyone can earn money from home.
Everything in this course is extremely simple and easy-to-follow.
If you are looking for more advanced strategies to make money online, I advise that you take my other Udemy courses where I&#39;ll show you more profitable strategies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming Biggest Challenges to Business Success Fast</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/overcoming-biggest-challenges-to-business-success-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/overcoming-biggest-challenges-to-business-success-fast/</guid>
      <description>Biggest challenges to success...
1) Comfort Zone - No sense of Urgency
 No BURNING Desire
2) Fear - of failure, success, unknown
 Paralysis Analysis
 No Action
3) Lack of Belief in oneself
 Constantly questioning
 Giving up
4) No Plan of Action - No Strategy
 No Consistency
 No Persistence
5) No Coach, guide, mentor
6) Not taking responsibility for your own life.
 Blaming others and other things</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create your online course now</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/create-your-online-course-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/create-your-online-course-now/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to Earn Money From Your Knowledge?
Then this is the course for you!
Key Benefits of Building An Online Course:
Having an Online Course to support your business is such a great idea at this time and age. We automate so many things in our business, so doing the same for the knowledge we share is essential to help your business grow and spend your time more intentionally and efficiently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digistore 24 Provisionen erhöhen mit Cross Device Tracking</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digistore-24-provisionen-erh%C3%B6hen-mit-cross-device-tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 16:04:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digistore-24-provisionen-erh%C3%B6hen-mit-cross-device-tracking/</guid>
      <description>Ich erinnere mich ungern an die Zeit, als ich kaum Affiliates bei Digistore24 hatte.
Damals habe ich verzweifelt versucht, endlich eine zuverlässige &#34;Affiliate-Armee&#34; aufzubauen, um dauerhaft mehr Umsatz zu machen.
Allerdings gab es ein Problem, denn Affiliates können sich nie 100%ig sicher sein, ob das Tracking funktioniert.
Das hat auch mich immer mehr frustriert, denn ich konnte ihnen keine klare Antwort geben.

Am schlimmsten wurde es, als ich tatsächlich nachgewiesen habe, dass das Standard-Tracking nicht richtig funktioniert und deswegen die Affiliates abspringen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Tech Startup 102 - Managing Human Resources</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-build-a-tech-startup-102-managing-human-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-build-a-tech-startup-102-managing-human-resources/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to build your own technology Startup? But you had no idea where to start? Maybe you are from a software engineering background and have no idea what to do next. No problem!
Course Content
The course is structured as follows:
Basics of Human Resource Management
Why it is important to build teams
How to hire people on a budget
Developing job descriptions, interviewing people How to on-board people and train them</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Pro Desktop 2021, 2020, 2019, &amp; 2018</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-pro-desktop-2021-2020-2019-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 08:36:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-pro-desktop-2021-2020-2019-2018/</guid>
      <description>This comprehensive course will provide an understanding of QuickBooks Pro Desktop 2021, 2020, 2019 &amp;amp; 2018 in a format beneficial to both beginners &amp;amp; advanced users.
We will start at the basics &amp;amp; go far beyond simple data entry, explaining how the software works in a clear step by step format.
We continually update this course, making it a community and recourse you can regularly return to and learn from. Current students will have access to the updates as they are created.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Money In Excel - Income Tax Sch. C &amp; Personal Financials</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/money-in-excel-income-tax-sch.-c-personal-financials/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/money-in-excel-income-tax-sch.-c-personal-financials/</guid>
      <description>Money in Excel is an Excel template provided by Microsoft that has bank connectivity similar to many accounting software applications such a QuickBooks, bank connectivity allowing for the download of financial data directly from the financial institutions.
Money in Excel can be used to construct a small business income statement which could be useful when preparing an income tax return Schedule C Profit or Loss From Business.
The Money in Excel template can also be used to complement accounting software such as QuickBooks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Marketing 0 to 1 Million Startup Entrepeneur Revenue</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/startup-marketing-0-to-1-million-startup-entrepeneur-revenue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:16:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/startup-marketing-0-to-1-million-startup-entrepeneur-revenue/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to grow your startup from the early to mid stages with an 11-year marketing veteran from a family of successful entrepreneurs. Learn the easiest marketing techniques get real results without a lot of budget. This course is for entrepreneurs and marketers selling business OR consumer products/services.
Some of the key learnings in this startup marketing course:
Growth hacking for entrepreneurs Customer acquisition marketing techniques for startups
Including real examples of successful campaigns I ran + other sample case studies</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Referral System - How To Create A Successful One!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/referral-system-how-to-create-a-successful-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:28:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/referral-system-how-to-create-a-successful-one/</guid>
      <description>This is a no-fluff actionable course on &#34;How To Create A Successful Referral System&#34;. I want to unpack for you the exact system that I&#39;ve used to grow, one of my current businesses. I&#39;m telling you now that it works. If you will take action and follow what you learn on this course if you would create the systems, the way that I will describe it for you in the next half an hour or so then you will be able to grow your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emprendimiento Productivo</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/emprendimiento-productivo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/emprendimiento-productivo/</guid>
      <description>En un principio, el ser humano entendió que por sí solo no podía obtener mejores recursos y bienes, por lo que decidió aliarse a otros, formando aldeas y comunidades, la antesala de lo que fue evolucionando en las sociedades primitivas y la consecuente división de las tareas, dando lugar a los roles definidos dentro de una sociedad. Miles de años de evolución hacen que el mundo moderno estos emprendimientos sean compañías o empresas que pueden alcanzar inclusive gran escala, teniendo algunas de ellas el rol de empresas multinacionales y transnacionales, contando con bienes millonarios y una gran cantidad de recursos bajo su control, pero todo ello gira en torno al sueño o creatividad de una mente brillante.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recurring Income Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/recurring-income-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/recurring-income-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’re looking to boost your income, grow a loyal following and position your brand as the go-to source in your market, there is no easier way than by injecting a recurring revenue stream into your business.
With recurring revenue, you can create a strong foundation for your business while taking advantage of the opportunity to incorporate additional income streams into an ever-growing community.
Recurring revenue is consistent and predictable. Unlike other income streams, such as with one-off products or services, with a monthly or yearly recurring revenue platform you know what to expect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Side Hustle Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/side-hustle-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/side-hustle-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Most people have considered working on a side hustle in order to make more money each month, or perhaps save for retirement.

But unfortunately, many of those same people never took action because they weren&#39;t sure how to work on a side hustle while working on other projects, or perhaps they&#39;re still in a 9-5.

The issue is, there&#39;s a lot of confusion about what a side hustle really means.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digitale Produkte erfolgreich verkaufen mit Digistore 24</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digitale-produkte-erfolgreich-verkaufen-mit-digistore-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digitale-produkte-erfolgreich-verkaufen-mit-digistore-24/</guid>
      <description>Ich kann mich noch gut daran erinnern wie es war, meine ersten Online Produkte zu verkaufen.
Damals habe ich versucht, mit höherwertigen Kursen und Coachings Geld zu verdienen.
Allerdings hab ich damit gekämpft, ständig Rechnungen zu schreiben und den Überblick zu behalten.

So etwas frustriert und überfordert einen auf Dauer, und mir ging es genauso.
Dann ist etwas ziemlich Blödes passiert: Als ich mich nicht mehr um die Rechnungen (und auch Mahnungen) kümmern wollte, sind die Verkäufe natürlich eingebrochen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partnership Accounting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/partnership-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/partnership-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Partnership accounting will cover accounting topics related to a partnership form of business entity.
This partnership course will focus on the accounting issues that are different in a partnership as compared to other types of entities like a sole proprietorship or corporations. As we focus on the differences, we always want to keep in mind the similarities in accounting for different business entities. Most of what we have learned about the double entry accounting system and day to day accounting transactions in prior courses will remain the same.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
