<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Entrepreneurship on </title>
    <link>/tags/entrepreneurship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Entrepreneurship on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:15:12 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/entrepreneurship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kickstarter Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/kickstarter-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:15:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kickstarter-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve ever wanted to create something new with a community of enthusiastic people cheering you on, you’ve come to the right place.
This course is based on everything we’ve learned from reviewing over 200,000 projects — each of them created by someone like you. We hope it’ll help you get started with shaping your own project, whether it’s to make a movie, an album, a game, a gadget, a play, a restaurant, or pretty much anything else that springs from the imagination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emprendimiento Productivo</title>
      <link>/emprendimiento-productivo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/emprendimiento-productivo/</guid>
      <description>En un principio, el ser humano entendió que por sí solo no podía obtener mejores recursos y bienes, por lo que decidió aliarse a otros, formando aldeas y comunidades, la antesala de lo que fue evolucionando en las sociedades primitivas y la consecuente división de las tareas, dando lugar a los roles definidos dentro de una sociedad. Miles de años de evolución hacen que el mundo moderno estos emprendimientos sean compañías o empresas que pueden alcanzar inclusive gran escala, teniendo algunas de ellas el rol de empresas multinacionales y transnacionales, contando con bienes millonarios y una gran cantidad de recursos bajo su control, pero todo ello gira en torno al sueño o creatividad de una mente brillante.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Pro Desktop 2021, 2020, 2019, &amp; 2018</title>
      <link>/quickbooks-pro-desktop-2021-2020-2019-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quickbooks-pro-desktop-2021-2020-2019-2018/</guid>
      <description>This comprehensive course will provide an understanding of QuickBooks Pro Desktop 2021, 2020, 2019 &amp;amp; 2018 in a format beneficial to both beginners &amp;amp; advanced users.
We will start at the basics &amp;amp; go far beyond simple data entry, explaining how the software works in a clear step by step format.
We continually update this course, making it a community and recourse you can regularly return to and learn from. Current students will have access to the updates as they are created.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recurring Income Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/recurring-income-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recurring-income-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’re looking to boost your income, grow a loyal following and position your brand as the go-to source in your market, there is no easier way than by injecting a recurring revenue stream into your business.
With recurring revenue, you can create a strong foundation for your business while taking advantage of the opportunity to incorporate additional income streams into an ever-growing community.
Recurring revenue is consistent and predictable. Unlike other income streams, such as with one-off products or services, with a monthly or yearly recurring revenue platform you know what to expect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Side Hustle Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/side-hustle-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/side-hustle-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Most people have considered working on a side hustle in order to make more money each month, or perhaps save for retirement.

But unfortunately, many of those same people never took action because they weren&#39;t sure how to work on a side hustle while working on other projects, or perhaps they&#39;re still in a 9-5.

The issue is, there&#39;s a lot of confusion about what a side hustle really means.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digitale Produkte erfolgreich verkaufen mit Digistore 24</title>
      <link>/digitale-produkte-erfolgreich-verkaufen-mit-digistore-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/digitale-produkte-erfolgreich-verkaufen-mit-digistore-24/</guid>
      <description>Ich kann mich noch gut daran erinnern wie es war, meine ersten Online Produkte zu verkaufen.
Damals habe ich versucht, mit höherwertigen Kursen und Coachings Geld zu verdienen.
Allerdings hab ich damit gekämpft, ständig Rechnungen zu schreiben und den Überblick zu behalten.

So etwas frustriert und überfordert einen auf Dauer, und mir ging es genauso.
Dann ist etwas ziemlich Blödes passiert: Als ich mich nicht mehr um die Rechnungen (und auch Mahnungen) kümmern wollte, sind die Verkäufe natürlich eingebrochen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurship - Ft. Matthew Rolnick of Yaymaker, Groupon</title>
      <link>/entrepreneurship-ft.-matthew-rolnick-of-yaymaker-groupon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/entrepreneurship-ft.-matthew-rolnick-of-yaymaker-groupon/</guid>
      <description>**Update**
This course includes an exclusive interview session with a seasoned business veteran - Matthew Rolnick. Matthew is currently the VP&amp;nbsp;of Sales at Yaymaker, and former Divisional Sales Manager at Groupon. His key accomplishments including generating over 10 million in sales at Groupon.
YouAccel recently had the opportunity to conduct a comprehensive Q&amp;amp;A style interview with Matthew Rolnick. The interview was conducted as part of an initiative to add valuable new content to YouAccel’s line up of Entrepreneurship and Freelancing courses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partnership Accounting</title>
      <link>/partnership-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partnership-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Partnership accounting will cover accounting topics related to a partnership form of business entity.
This partnership course will focus on the accounting issues that are different in a partnership as compared to other types of entities like a sole proprietorship or corporations. As we focus on the differences, we always want to keep in mind the similarities in accounting for different business entities. Most of what we have learned about the double entry accounting system and day to day accounting transactions in prior courses will remain the same.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
