<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Finance Cert &amp; Exam Prep on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/finance-cert-exam-prep/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Finance Cert &amp; Exam Prep on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/finance-cert-exam-prep/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>APICS Certified Supply Chain Professional CSCP Practice Exam</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/apics-certified-supply-chain-professional-cscp-practice-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/apics-certified-supply-chain-professional-cscp-practice-exam/</guid>
      <description>Certified Supply Chain Professional (CSCP) Practice Exams
Get a passing grade in your CSCP exam on the first try
The questions in these practice exams are designed so you understand where your gaps are and how ready you are for the real one. The first three practice exams elaborate on the knowledge area and the other two exams are designed to determine your level of readiness.
If you are reading this sentence right now, you are in one of two groups of supply chain professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #1 Introduction &amp; Financial Statements</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#1-introduction-financial-statements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#1-introduction-financial-statements/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover the core concepts of corporate finance.
You will know the differences and similarities between the field of finance, accounting, and economics. Accounting is generally using past data to construct the financial statements in accordance with accounting standards. The financial statements are critical to the field of corporate finance but the the focus is different. Corporate finance will generally use data from the financial statements to make forecasts about future performance driving decision making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate CAMS Practice Tests | ACAMS 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-cams-practice-tests-acams-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 21:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ultimate-cams-practice-tests-acams-2022/</guid>
      <description>What is CAMS Exam?
Certified Anti-Money Laundering Specialist (CAMS) is the gold standard in AML certifications which is widely recognized and accepted by financial institutions, Banks, governments and international law enforcement agencies, with more than 40,000 CAMS graduates worldwide. The certification helps to land / boost your career in the field of Financial Crime Compliance.
With the recent spike in higher salaries for AML/CFT practitioners, a CAMS holder earns 42% more compared to non-CAMS certified counterpart!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cost &amp; Management Accounting Certification Training 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cost-management-accounting-certification-training-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cost-management-accounting-certification-training-2021/</guid>
      <description>Costing, as defined by the Institute of Cost and Works Accountants, England is basically “The technique and process of ascertaining costs.” It can also be described as classifying, recording and appropriate allocation of expenditure for the determination of the costs of products or services, and for presentation of suitably arranged data for the purposes of control, and guidance of management.
Cost Accounting is a method of accounting wherein all the costs involved in performing any process, project or product are noted and analyzed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Accounting &amp; Reporting Certification</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-reporting-certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-accounting-reporting-certification/</guid>
      <description>Uplatz provides this comprehensive training on Financial Accounting &amp;amp; Reporting.
This Financial Accounting &amp;amp; Financial Reporting course will demonstrate the key accounting concepts and principles to be able to prepare financial statements and unlock critical insights into business performance and potential. You will explore how financial advisors, managers, analysts, and entrepreneurs leverage accounting to drive strategic decision-making. The Financial Accounting course will help you master the functional and technical skills needed to analyze financial statements and disclosures for use in financial analysis, and learn how accounting standards and managerial incentives affect the financial reporting process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IIA-CIA-Part2 Practice Test Prep Exam</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/iia-cia-part2-practice-test-prep-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/iia-cia-part2-practice-test-prep-exam/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the pratice Tests: IIA-CIA-Part2 Certified Internal Auditor - Part 2, Conducting the Internal Audit Engagement.
I prepared the pratice tests to help you prepare for the real IIA-CIA-Part2 exam, you will test your knowledge with hours of simulated questions and answers giving great chances for you to improve your performance when taking the exam.
Our pratice Tests covers all references:
I. Managing the Internal Audit Activity
II. Planning the Engagement</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
