<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Management on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Management on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Social Engineering: Zero to Hero in Social Engineering!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/social-engineering-zero-to-hero-in-social-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/social-engineering-zero-to-hero-in-social-engineering/</guid>
      <description>This course will teach you the most common social engineering threats. At the end of the course you will understand why people are the weakest link in your organisations security posture. You will understand: 1) what the most common social engineering threats and are, 2) the impact per threat for your business, 3) how these threats can be executed and / or mitigated. You will able to understand the above-mentioned points without having to understand technical stuff (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Building for Business Success</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/team-building-for-business-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/team-building-for-business-success/</guid>
      <description>If you’re ready to start growing your work team, this course will give you the skills to find an incredible team and the knowledge to create a productive work environment.
If you’re a small business owner or entrepreneur, you know what it means to build a business from the ground up. It takes smart thinking, ingenuity, and a ton of hard work to create a successful business.
Many small business owners are very protective of their vision because they know exactly where they want to take their business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lean Six Sigma Black Belt practice Tests Certification 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/lean-six-sigma-black-belt-practice-tests-certification-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/lean-six-sigma-black-belt-practice-tests-certification-2021/</guid>
      <description>BSI&#39;s Lean Six Sigma certification is the opportunity
to prove that the skills you have acquired during your training, your exam and the successful execution of a project are rewarded through a globally recognized qualification. BSI certification helps ensure that current and potential employees have reached a defined and tested level of expertise in the use of Lean Six Sigma. this course provides additional information to help you understand the commitment and preparation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goal Setting For Businesses And Teams</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/goal-setting-for-businesses-and-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/goal-setting-for-businesses-and-teams/</guid>
      <description>About The Course 
This course is for anyone who wants to increase their results in a business environment, with goal-setting techniques based on solid psychology and workplace research. It is a practical, hands-on training programme providing tools and techniques for goal-setting in the workplace. It targets small business owners and team leaders who want to get the best out of their teams using evidence-based approaches. It will guide managers and business owners through the process of defining purpose, understanding effective goals, working on team dynamics and leadership, and evaluating and re-setting goals for optimal success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing And Working In Virtual And Hybrid Teams</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/managing-and-working-in-virtual-and-hybrid-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:35:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/managing-and-working-in-virtual-and-hybrid-teams/</guid>
      <description>Overview
Are you struggling to engage your virtual team or clients? This course is designed for anyone who needs to communicate virtually to influence – from virtual team leaders and remote team members to small business owners and entrepreneurs. When you can no longer meet colleagues, connections and customers face to face, a new suite of skills is required.
Who Is This Course For?
This course is designed for anyone who needs to communicate virtually to influence – from virtual team leaders and remote team members to small business owners and entrepreneurs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SUPPLY CHAIN SKILLS : Logistics Optimization Tools</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/supply-chain-skills-logistics-optimization-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/supply-chain-skills-logistics-optimization-tools/</guid>
      <description>Bienvenue dans ce cours qui vous permettra d’économiser des milliers de dollars chaque mois en appliquant certains outils appelés : Les outils d’optimisation logistique.

Mon nom est Hamza et je serai votre formateur.

Ceci est un cours d’introduction et d’analyse des différents outils logistiques afin de prendre les meilleures décisions dans les bons moments.
Ce cours est assez riche en information théorique et technique, c’est le fruit de 4 ans de recherche et d’apprentissage approfondi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Responsibility Accounting &amp; Performance Measurement</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/responsibility-accounting-performance-measurement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:43:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/responsibility-accounting-performance-measurement/</guid>
      <description>Responsibility accounting &amp;amp; performance measures.
We will describe the concept of decentralization, how it applies to businesses, and the pros and cons of a more decentralized organization from a centralized one.
The course will cover general managerial accounting concepts necessary to study responsibility accounting, comparing and contrasting managerial accounting and financial accounting.
We will explain what a responsibility accounting system looks like and the benefits of a responsibility accounting system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flexible Budgets, Standard Costs, &amp; Variance Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/flexible-budgets-standard-costs-variance-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/flexible-budgets-standard-costs-variance-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Managerial &amp;amp; cost accounting tools
The course will introduce managerial accounting topics that will be used throughout the course, contrasting managerial accounting to financial accounting so that we are in the correct mindset as we move forward.
We will discuss flexible budgets, contrasting flexible budgets with static or fixed budgets, demonstrating the benefits of flexible budgets and how they can be used. We will work example problems related to flexible budgets and provide step by step instructional videos to apply the concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISO 27001:2013 Teleworking</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/iso-270012013-teleworking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/iso-270012013-teleworking/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you&#39;ll learn about the fundamentals of teleworking in the context of ISO 27001:2013. Firstly, we&#39;ll be discussing what teleworking is. Then, its benefits &amp;amp; drawbacks. And, finally, we&#39;ll examine various factors involved in implementing such a system in an organization.
Teleworking is when an employee carries out their job away from the organization&#39;s main premises or office. It can be facilitated through technology, for example, the internet, smartphones, laptops, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISO 9001 2015 Risk Management</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/iso-9001-2015-risk-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/iso-9001-2015-risk-management/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you&#39;ll learn about the fundamentals of having a risk-based approach. This approach can be adopted during establishing, implementing, and maintaining ISO 9001:2015. Firstly, we&#39;ll be discussing what risk is. Then, we&#39;ll go through how an organization can approach meeting its purpose with risk-based thinking. And, finally, we&#39;ll examine what ISO 9001:2015 says about risk in various subclauses.
Risk is uncertainty about what the outcome of certain events will be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #3 Forecasting &amp; Budgeting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance-#3-forecasting-budgeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance-#3-forecasting-budgeting/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover the concepts of forecasting and budgeting from a finance perspective.
The course includes many example problems, both in presentation form, and many using Excel worksheets. Each Excel worksheet problem will include a downloadable Excel worksheet that has at least two tabs, one having the answer, the second including a preformatted worksheet that can be populated in a step-by-step process along with the instructional video.
To forecast and budget we need to make predictions and projections about the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMMP Exam: Brand Management --&gt;  Practice Test 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cmmp-exam-brand-management-practice-test-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cmmp-exam-brand-management-practice-test-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Exam in BRAND MANAGEMENT ? 
Don’t be stressed, Take our Brand Management Based Mock Test and prepare yourself for the Exam. Here you will get Brand Management based Multiple Choice Question for your Next Exam.
What you will get in These Mock Test ? 
It contains sample questions which are likely to be asked in the Exam.
These Brand Management based MCQ questions help you with self-study and self-assessment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Leadership Mastery Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-leadership-mastery-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-leadership-mastery-course/</guid>
      <description>The world has changed overnight and every dimension of our life got upended in an unprecedented manner. How we work, how we buy, how we live and how we study have gone through a metamorphosis. Live now revolves around a screen - yet, the world slowly grinds on..However, everything falls and rises on Leadership. Everything grows and shrinks on the efforts of a leader. Business growth, Corporate leadership or personal mastery is a result of concerted choices by a Leader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valutazione delle Prestazioni</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/valutazione-delle-prestazioni/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/valutazione-delle-prestazioni/</guid>
      <description>Lavori in un’Azienda e vuoi saperne di più sulla Valutazione?
Lavori presso le Risorse Umane (HR) e vuoi approfondire una tua competenza tecnica?
Vuoi sapere cos’è nel dettaglio il Sistema della Valutazione delle Prestazioni?? Qual è il suo scopo?? Le modalità di attuazione dalla sua iniziale fase di progettazione??

Bene!! Sei nel posto giusto…anzi…nell’aula virtuale giusta.
In questo corso ti parlerò di tutte le fasi della Valutazione delle Prestazioni, di chi sono gli Attori interessati e coinvolti, della differenza tra i diversi modelli da usare, delle variabili da tenere sempre in considerazione quando si ha a che fare con il capitale umano (non siamo dei Robot e tutto va adattato e modellato in base a determinati fattori) motivo per cui è importantissimo iniziare con un’ottima progettazione dettagliata della comunicazione del Sistema nonché verificare la situazione attuale dell’impresa.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
