<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Management on </title>
    <link>/tags/management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Management on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 12:58:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #3 Forecasting &amp; Budgeting</title>
      <link>/corporate-finance-#3-forecasting-budgeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 12:58:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/corporate-finance-#3-forecasting-budgeting/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover the concepts of forecasting and budgeting from a finance perspective.
The course includes many example problems, both in presentation form, and many using Excel worksheets. Each Excel worksheet problem will include a downloadable Excel worksheet that has at least two tabs, one having the answer, the second including a preformatted worksheet that can be populated in a step-by-step process along with the instructional video.
To forecast and budget we need to make predictions and projections about the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMMP Exam: Brand Management --&gt;  Practice Test 2021</title>
      <link>/cmmp-exam-brand-management-practice-test-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cmmp-exam-brand-management-practice-test-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Exam in BRAND MANAGEMENT ? 
Don’t be stressed, Take our Brand Management Based Mock Test and prepare yourself for the Exam. Here you will get Brand Management based Multiple Choice Question for your Next Exam.
What you will get in These Mock Test ? 
It contains sample questions which are likely to be asked in the Exam.
These Brand Management based MCQ questions help you with self-study and self-assessment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Leadership Mastery Course</title>
      <link>/the-complete-leadership-mastery-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-leadership-mastery-course/</guid>
      <description>The world has changed overnight and every dimension of our life got upended in an unprecedented manner. How we work, how we buy, how we live and how we study have gone through a metamorphosis. Live now revolves around a screen - yet, the world slowly grinds on..However, everything falls and rises on Leadership. Everything grows and shrinks on the efforts of a leader. Business growth, Corporate leadership or personal mastery is a result of concerted choices by a Leader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valutazione delle Prestazioni</title>
      <link>/valutazione-delle-prestazioni/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/valutazione-delle-prestazioni/</guid>
      <description>Lavori in un’Azienda e vuoi saperne di più sulla Valutazione?
Lavori presso le Risorse Umane (HR) e vuoi approfondire una tua competenza tecnica?
Vuoi sapere cos’è nel dettaglio il Sistema della Valutazione delle Prestazioni?? Qual è il suo scopo?? Le modalità di attuazione dalla sua iniziale fase di progettazione??

Bene!! Sei nel posto giusto…anzi…nell’aula virtuale giusta.
In questo corso ti parlerò di tutte le fasi della Valutazione delle Prestazioni, di chi sono gli Attori interessati e coinvolti, della differenza tra i diversi modelli da usare, delle variabili da tenere sempre in considerazione quando si ha a che fare con il capitale umano (non siamo dei Robot e tutto va adattato e modellato in base a determinati fattori) motivo per cui è importantissimo iniziare con un’ottima progettazione dettagliata della comunicazione del Sistema nonché verificare la situazione attuale dell’impresa.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
