<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Management on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Management on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #3 Forecasting &amp; Budgeting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#3-forecasting-budgeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#3-forecasting-budgeting/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover the concepts of forecasting and budgeting from a finance perspective.
The course includes many example problems, both in presentation form, and many using Excel worksheets. Each Excel worksheet problem will include a downloadable Excel worksheet that has at least two tabs, one having the answer, the second including a preformatted worksheet that can be populated in a step-by-step process along with the instructional video.
To forecast and budget we need to make predictions and projections about the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flexible Budgets, Standard Costs, &amp; Variance Analysis</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/flexible-budgets-standard-costs-variance-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/flexible-budgets-standard-costs-variance-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Managerial &amp;amp; cost accounting tools
The course will introduce managerial accounting topics that will be used throughout the course, contrasting managerial accounting to financial accounting so that we are in the correct mindset as we move forward.
We will discuss flexible budgets, contrasting flexible budgets with static or fixed budgets, demonstrating the benefits of flexible budgets and how they can be used. We will work example problems related to flexible budgets and provide step by step instructional videos to apply the concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Responsibility Accounting &amp; Performance Measurement</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/responsibility-accounting-performance-measurement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/responsibility-accounting-performance-measurement/</guid>
      <description>Responsibility accounting &amp;amp; performance measures.
We will describe the concept of decentralization, how it applies to businesses, and the pros and cons of a more decentralized organization from a centralized one.
The course will cover general managerial accounting concepts necessary to study responsibility accounting, comparing and contrasting managerial accounting and financial accounting.
We will explain what a responsibility accounting system looks like and the benefits of a responsibility accounting system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Sourcing: Agile Procurement in Practice</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adaptive-sourcing-agile-procurement-in-practice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adaptive-sourcing-agile-procurement-in-practice/</guid>
      <description>This course unites two worlds – IT and Procurement. Both functions are now going through significant business and technological transformation to comply with Industry 4.0 mandate. Our course is very practical - It is half exercises, case studies, and best practices to apply straight after learning.
Instead of talking about Agile procurement, we&#39;ll suggest actionable advice for its realization synthesized from classical theories and intuitive concepts. In 2022, the standardized &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project/ Product Management Frameworks &amp; Methods MasterClass</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project/-product-management-frameworks-methods-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:57:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project/-product-management-frameworks-methods-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>The demand for Product Management is increasing at an insane rate. More and more companies are finally figuring out how important this discipline and this role is to their success, making product management as one of the hottest jobs in the market. However, most people are unaware of what exactly a Product Manager does. Does the role require technical skills or business skills? And what is it about the role that demands extreme empathy with the customer?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Google Slides Course - Create Stunning Slides</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-google-slides-course-create-stunning-slides/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 20:40:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-google-slides-course-create-stunning-slides/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to The Complete Google Slides Course. This course will teach you to understand how to use and design stunning slideshows using the Google application Google Slides.
Google Slides is a free presentation software that allows you to design visually-appealing presentations for both a professional and casual setting. When compared to Microsoft Powerpoint, Slides offers the benefit of simplicity. With its various templates and themes, it can be as simple as plugging text into the provided text boxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Export Documents, Procedures, Policies &amp; Incentives in India</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/export-documents-procedures-policies-incentives-in-india/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 17:02:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/export-documents-procedures-policies-incentives-in-india/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to learn basic Export Documentation &amp;amp; Procedures, Export Policies, Export Incentive Schemes in India? And have you been looking for a concise but essential course that can help you understand the basic concepts of export documentation, procedures, policy and incentive for exports from India? Do you want to learn about customs export clearance, documentation related to international export transactions. Do you want to see all kinds of real export documents and learn about all the contents of these.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISO 9001 LEAD AUDITOR (Certiprof): examen REAL &#43; MATERIAL!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/iso-9001-lead-auditor-certiprof-examen-real--material/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 17:02:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/iso-9001-lead-auditor-certiprof-examen-real--material/</guid>
      <description>BIENVENIDO AL EXAMEN DE PREPARACIÓN PARA LA CERTIFICACIÓN DE ISO 9001 LEAD AUDITOR - CERTIPROF
Estos exámenes, tanto teóricos como prácticos te ayudarán a reforzar y poner en práctica tus conocimientos del tema. Al finalizarlos serás capaz de afrontar con éxito el examen real de certificación que brinda Certiprof. Dentro de este examen de preparación, podrás encontrar contenido referente a las preguntas reales que suelen venir en la prueba original; es decir, si llegas a responder correctamente las preguntas de este examen, estarías asegurando aprobar el examen real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Management :Agile Requirements using Product Backlog</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/product-management-agile-requirements-using-product-backlog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/product-management-agile-requirements-using-product-backlog/</guid>
      <description>*All Glory to GOD for giving me the knowledge and experience to create this course*
COURSE SUMMARY
&#34;Scrum Open, Professional Scrum™, Professional Scrum Product Owner™, (PSPO)™, Professional Scrum Master™, PSM, PSM I, PSM 1, etc. is the protected brand of Scrum . org. Our course and practice exams are neither endorsed by nor affiliated with Scrum . org.&#34;
Three reasons to TAKE THIS COURSE right now!
The unique reasons for taking this course are:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMP High Quality Simulator 2021® Mock Practice Test Exams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pmp-high-quality-simulator-2021-mock-practice-test-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 16:38:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pmp-high-quality-simulator-2021-mock-practice-test-exams/</guid>
      <description>Are you thinking of taking the PMP exam and a 95 % success guarantee, and you only need one source? You have reached your destination.
We all know about the updates that took place in the exam at the beginning of 2021, and according to the American Institute for Project Management, the seventh edition will not replace the other ten references that I talked about.
You have nothing to do with these matters, just regain your activity, join the course, and benefit from the permanent offer, because we read on your behalf, studied and researched to offer you an integrated course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(PMI-PBA) Professional in Business Analysis Practice Exams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pmi-pba-professional-in-business-analysis-practice-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:37:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pmi-pba-professional-in-business-analysis-practice-exams/</guid>
      <description>Practice Tests
Those practice exams completely prepare you for what it is like to take in(PMI-PBA) Professional in Business Analysis Certification Exam . These questions are collected
Written and answered by multiple Experts
Exam Questions similar to actual Certification Exam
Following the knowledge areas as required by the exam
There are five practice exam which is a great means to test your Business Analysis skills before appearing for the (PMI-PBA) Professional in Business Analysis Certification exam</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FMEA and RCM Failure Mode Risk Management Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fmea-and-rcm-failure-mode-risk-management-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:37:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fmea-and-rcm-failure-mode-risk-management-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>FMEA and RCM Failure Mode Risk Management Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn how to do FMEA and developing the Reliability Centered Maintenance ecosystem for your business.
I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on FMEA and RCM as well as how to apply it in real business applications.
If you are currently or working towards being a reliability or maintenance professional, you will find this course of great help to get the fundamental knowledge you need to kick start your professional career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn how to use Zapier to automate your Business</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-how-to-use-zapier-to-automate-your-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:37:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-how-to-use-zapier-to-automate-your-business/</guid>
      <description>Greetings, Friend
Do you wish you could spend less time working on your company and more time working in it?
I understand that this sounds challenging at this point because you&#39;re used to having everything under control.
Control, on the other hand, does not always imply that you must do everything yourself.
In truth, a simple program called &#34;Zapier&#34; can automate a lot of the operations you undertake online.
Have you heard of it before?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Prince2 Foundation Certification Training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-prince2-foundation-certification-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 12:41:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-prince2-foundation-certification-training/</guid>
      <description>This practice test course contains 6 complete timed tests, of at least 60 questions each, just like you will get in the official exam. That&#39;s over 360 questions to see how prepared you are for the real test. The quiz questions are balanced as per the domain weightings published in the candidate bulletin. In addition, after taking the exam you can review your answers compared against the correct answers including comprehensive explanations and documentation links of each question, the answer options and the recommended approach for getting the answers right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SUPPLY CHAIN SKILLS : Logistics Optimization Tools</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/supply-chain-skills-logistics-optimization-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 22:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/supply-chain-skills-logistics-optimization-tools/</guid>
      <description>Cette formation est qualifiée parmi les meilleurs cours d&#39;UDEMY. Vous pouvez visualiser cela à travers les avis positifs collectés pendant ces mois depuis sa publication. Les avis actuels s&#39;élèvent à 4,54/5*.
Bienvenue dans ce cours qui vous permettra d’économiser des milliers de dollars chaque mois en appliquant certains outils appelés : Les outils d’optimisation logistique.
Mon nom est Hamza et je serai votre formateur.
Ceci est un cours d’introduction et d’analyse des différents outils logistiques afin de prendre les meilleures décisions dans les bons moments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISTQB Foundation Level CTFL training for 2022 &#43; 1000 QUIZ</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/istqb-foundation-level-ctfl-training-for-2022--1000-quiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 13:47:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/istqb-foundation-level-ctfl-training-for-2022--1000-quiz/</guid>
      <description>Complete training package(only course which provides this)
ISTQB CTLF 2022 complete Training + reference book + Topic wise Quiz + Chapter Wise Quiz + NOTES + Previous year question paper : COMPLETE PACKAGE (you will not find this in any other course)
This course will help you to clear ISTQB Foundation level Testing exam and it is new and based on latest ISTQB syllabus.
First one hour video are provided for free, you can watch them to check the quality of the course an once satisfied can enroll to the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Governance of Enterprise IT Certification practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/governance-of-enterprise-it-certification-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 21:19:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/governance-of-enterprise-it-certification-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Certified in the Governance of Enterprise IT (CGEIT)
About Certified in the Governance of Enterprise (CGEIT)
Certified in the Governance of Enterprise, also known as CGEIT is a vendor-neutral certification offered through the ISACA. The certification is designed for IT professionals responsible for managing IT enterprise governance to validate their skills in the field.
Prerequisite for the exam
An applicant must have one year experience in managing the Frameworks that are required to establish an effective IT Governance program for an organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to ISO 14001:2015 EMS -Environmental Management System</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/intro-to-iso-140012015-ems-environmental-management-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 22:30:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/intro-to-iso-140012015-ems-environmental-management-system/</guid>
      <description>This course is an easy introductory overview of ISO 14001:2015. The teaching style is a presentation with voiceover. After completing this course you&#39;ll have a basic understanding of the Plan-Do-Check-Act methodology, how it&#39;s applied to create ISO 14001:2015, the purpose of the standard, and what it is comprised of.
The standard is detailed in a document consisting of 10 clauses as per Annex SL, just like all the other ISO management systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GMAT Graduate Management Admission Test Questions and Answer</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gmat-graduate-management-admission-test-questions-and-answer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 14:59:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gmat-graduate-management-admission-test-questions-and-answer/</guid>
      <description>GMAT Graduate Management Admission Test Questions and Answer
2022 Get Ready for your MBA and boost your CAREER
The Graduate Management Admission Test (GMAT) is a computer adaptive test (CAT) intended to assess certain analytical, writing, quantitative, verbal, and reading skills in written English for use in admission to a graduate management program, such as an MBA program. It requires knowledge of certain specific grammar and knowledge of certain specific algebra, geometry, and arithmetic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership &amp; Cultural Diversity (Accredited Oxford Diploma)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/leadership-cultural-diversity-accredited-oxford-diploma/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 14:59:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/leadership-cultural-diversity-accredited-oxford-diploma/</guid>
      <description>IMPORTANT: This course has an emphasis on discussion - the course is to a world-wide global class. We can all learn from one another. This long Diploma course is serious and workbooks and assignments are set. Leadership is not about watching videos alone but discussing, considering, suggesting and then making decisions. The Educational Announcements and the Q/A ensure that this course is always up to date.
Recent review:
&#34;love detailed oriented people, and this instructor not only has a vision, he takes the best time to explain himself and his method&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MANAGEMENT DU TRANSPORT INTERNATIONAL ET DE LA LOGISTIQUE</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/management-du-transport-international-et-de-la-logistique/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 23:02:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/management-du-transport-international-et-de-la-logistique/</guid>
      <description>Bienvenue dans ce cours qui vous permettra d’économiser des milliers de dollars chaque mois en appliquant certaines connaissances relatives au transport international de marchandises.
Mon nom est Meriem et je serai votre formateur.
Ceci est un cours d’introduction et d’analyse des différents volets logistiques relatives au transport international de marchandises afin de prendre les meilleures décisions dans les bons moments.
Ce cours est assez riche en information théorique et technique, c’est le fruit de 2 ans de recherche et d’apprentissage approfondi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership for Engineers: High-Impact Engineering Leadership</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/leadership-for-engineers-high-impact-engineering-leadership/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/leadership-for-engineers-high-impact-engineering-leadership/</guid>
      <description>Are you an Engineering Manager that wants to lead, not just manage? Do you want to take your leadership to the next level?
Leadership for Engineers will give you powerful and practical insights into the various dimensions of leadership: from Culture to Recruitment - from Strategy to Resilience - in an engineering context.
Whether you&#39;re a CEO or a Team Leader, you&#39;ll discover how to inspire those around you with a powerful Vision and how to create an environment in which everyone strives to be and do their best.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Engineering: Zero to Hero in Social Engineering!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/social-engineering-zero-to-hero-in-social-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/social-engineering-zero-to-hero-in-social-engineering/</guid>
      <description>This course will teach you the most common social engineering threats. At the end of the course you will understand why people are the weakest link in your organisations security posture. You will understand: 1) what the most common social engineering threats and are, 2) the impact per threat for your business, 3) how these threats can be executed and / or mitigated. You will able to understand the above-mentioned points without having to understand technical stuff (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Team Building for Business Success</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/team-building-for-business-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/team-building-for-business-success/</guid>
      <description>If you’re ready to start growing your work team, this course will give you the skills to find an incredible team and the knowledge to create a productive work environment.
If you’re a small business owner or entrepreneur, you know what it means to build a business from the ground up. It takes smart thinking, ingenuity, and a ton of hard work to create a successful business.
Many small business owners are very protective of their vision because they know exactly where they want to take their business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lean Six Sigma Black Belt practice Tests Certification 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lean-six-sigma-black-belt-practice-tests-certification-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lean-six-sigma-black-belt-practice-tests-certification-2021/</guid>
      <description>BSI&#39;s Lean Six Sigma certification is the opportunity
to prove that the skills you have acquired during your training, your exam and the successful execution of a project are rewarded through a globally recognized qualification. BSI certification helps ensure that current and potential employees have reached a defined and tested level of expertise in the use of Lean Six Sigma. this course provides additional information to help you understand the commitment and preparation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goal Setting For Businesses And Teams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/goal-setting-for-businesses-and-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/goal-setting-for-businesses-and-teams/</guid>
      <description>About The Course This course is for anyone who wants to increase their results in a business environment, with goal-setting techniques based on solid psychology and workplace research. It is a practical, hands-on training programme providing tools and techniques for goal-setting in the workplace. It targets small business owners and team leaders who want to get the best out of their teams using evidence-based approaches. It will guide managers and business owners through the process of defining purpose, understanding effective goals, working on team dynamics and leadership, and evaluating and re-setting goals for optimal success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing And Working In Virtual And Hybrid Teams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/managing-and-working-in-virtual-and-hybrid-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:35:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/managing-and-working-in-virtual-and-hybrid-teams/</guid>
      <description>Overview
Are you struggling to engage your virtual team or clients? This course is designed for anyone who needs to communicate virtually to influence – from virtual team leaders and remote team members to small business owners and entrepreneurs. When you can no longer meet colleagues, connections and customers face to face, a new suite of skills is required.
Who Is This Course For?
This course is designed for anyone who needs to communicate virtually to influence – from virtual team leaders and remote team members to small business owners and entrepreneurs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISO 27001:2013 Teleworking</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/iso-270012013-teleworking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/iso-270012013-teleworking/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you&#39;ll learn about the fundamentals of teleworking in the context of ISO 27001:2013. Firstly, we&#39;ll be discussing what teleworking is. Then, its benefits &amp;amp; drawbacks. And, finally, we&#39;ll examine various factors involved in implementing such a system in an organization.
Teleworking is when an employee carries out their job away from the organization&#39;s main premises or office. It can be facilitated through technology, for example, the internet, smartphones, laptops, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISO 9001 2015 Risk Management</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/iso-9001-2015-risk-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/iso-9001-2015-risk-management/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you&#39;ll learn about the fundamentals of having a risk-based approach. This approach can be adopted during establishing, implementing, and maintaining ISO 9001:2015. Firstly, we&#39;ll be discussing what risk is. Then, we&#39;ll go through how an organization can approach meeting its purpose with risk-based thinking. And, finally, we&#39;ll examine what ISO 9001:2015 says about risk in various subclauses.
Risk is uncertainty about what the outcome of certain events will be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMMP Exam: Brand Management --&gt;  Practice Test 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cmmp-exam-brand-management--practice-test-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cmmp-exam-brand-management--practice-test-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Exam in BRAND MANAGEMENT ? Don’t be stressed, Take our Brand Management Based Mock Test and prepare yourself for the Exam. Here you will get Brand Management based Multiple Choice Question for your Next Exam.
What you will get in These Mock Test ? It contains sample questions which are likely to be asked in the Exam.
These Brand Management based MCQ questions help you with self-study and self-assessment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Leadership Mastery Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-leadership-mastery-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-leadership-mastery-course/</guid>
      <description>The world has changed overnight and every dimension of our life got upended in an unprecedented manner. How we work, how we buy, how we live and how we study have gone through a metamorphosis. Live now revolves around a screen - yet, the world slowly grinds on..However, everything falls and rises on Leadership. Everything grows and shrinks on the efforts of a leader. Business growth, Corporate leadership or personal mastery is a result of concerted choices by a Leader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valutazione delle Prestazioni</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/valutazione-delle-prestazioni/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/valutazione-delle-prestazioni/</guid>
      <description>Lavori in un’Azienda e vuoi saperne di più sulla Valutazione?
Lavori presso le Risorse Umane (HR) e vuoi approfondire una tua competenza tecnica?
Vuoi sapere cos’è nel dettaglio il Sistema della Valutazione delle Prestazioni?? Qual è il suo scopo?? Le modalità di attuazione dalla sua iniziale fase di progettazione??
Bene!! Sei nel posto giusto…anzi…nell’aula virtuale giusta.
In questo corso ti parlerò di tutte le fasi della Valutazione delle Prestazioni, di chi sono gli Attori interessati e coinvolti, della differenza tra i diversi modelli da usare, delle variabili da tenere sempre in considerazione quando si ha a che fare con il capitale umano (non siamo dei Robot e tutto va adattato e modellato in base a determinati fattori) motivo per cui è importantissimo iniziare con un’ottima progettazione dettagliata della comunicazione del Sistema nonché verificare la situazione attuale dell’impresa.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
