<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Software Development Tools on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/software-development-tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Software Development Tools on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/software-development-tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Microservices</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-microservices/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-microservices/</guid>
      <description>Microservices architecture provides a modern way of building highly scalable applications. Normally in building cloud-native applications microservices-based architecture is used. In this course, I have explained microservices in the simplest possible way. We start with the explanation of traditional architecture such as Monolithic Architecture, then we discuss how it evolved via service-oriented architecture (SOA) to finally microservices architecture. We talk about the benefits and the challenges of these architectures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn CI/CD YAML pipelines with Azure DevOps</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-ci/cd-yaml-pipelines-with-azure-devops/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 13:24:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-ci/cd-yaml-pipelines-with-azure-devops/</guid>
      <description>LEARN THE FUNDAMENTALS OF CI/CD AND CREATE A CI/CD PIPELINE FROM SCRATCH
This is a unique course designed to help you to understand the CI/CD concept from the ground up. This means you do not need any upfront knowledge about CI/CD, DevOps or working with pipelines. I will explain everything in detail while I present it in practice. After learning basic knowledge, we create a fully automated CI/CD pipeline using Azure DevOps Pipelines to see how everything is implemented in practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git from Basics to Advanced: Practical Guide for Developers</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/git-from-basics-to-advanced-practical-guide-for-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/git-from-basics-to-advanced-practical-guide-for-developers/</guid>
      <description>From this course you can learn Git from basics to advanced concepts. 
This course created for software engineers who wants to learn how to track changes with the help of the Git. No matter what programming language you use - the git is equal for everyone :)
There are a lot of other courses in this topic. So, why would you choose exactly this course? Here just a few reasons:- Real-life cases &amp;amp; demo during the video lesson</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Articulate Storyline 360 eLearning Course || Mastery</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/create-articulate-storyline-360-elearning-course-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/create-articulate-storyline-360-elearning-course-mastery/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Complete Articulate Storyline 360 Course. My name is Anwer Khan and I will be your instructor through out this course. In this course we will talk straight to the point. Therefore, we will cover more in less time. Articulate Storyline is the industry&#39;s favorite software for creating interactive courses. It&#39;s simple enough for beginners, yet powerful enough for experts. And it lets you create virtually any interaction you can imagine, in minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git &amp; GitHub A Practical Course: Beginner To Advanced Level</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/git-github-a-practical-course-beginner-to-advanced-level/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/git-github-a-practical-course-beginner-to-advanced-level/</guid>
      <description>This is all about high level overview on Complete Git &amp;amp; GitHub both for the beginners and advanced software professionals.
If any one wants to develop their Open Source Project Or wants to contribute to the Open Source Project then learning Git and GitHub is must. Even if you are a student and wants to become a software developer Or website designer then learning Git and GitHub will help you achieve your goal with well designed infrastructure to get contribution for your project from different developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitLab</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/gitlab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/gitlab/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to code but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing websites and bring your ideas to life?
Then GitLab Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Programming is the most in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building websites like an expert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>python web scraping by arabic</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-web-scraping-by-arabic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-web-scraping-by-arabic/</guid>
      <description>in this course you will learn how to use python in web scraping and you will learn how to use some modules like (requests,bs4,re)
and you will learn ( regular expression ) and how to use it to make patterns for emails &amp;amp; phone number &amp;amp; ip and use it in scraping , i hope to get what you need from this course .
good luck..
thanks :)

 Ratings: 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Azure DevOps CI/CD pipelines</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-azure-devops-ci/cd-pipelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-azure-devops-ci/cd-pipelines/</guid>
      <description>Are you a developer and you want to learn more about DevOps ?
Are you looking for a practical guide to get you started with Continuous Integration and Continuous Deployment ?
Are you working on Web, Mobile, Container or Database projects and you want to implement CI/CD ?
This course will show you demos for how to create CI/CD pipelines for different type of projects.
You will start with web applications: Java, .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apache Zeppelin - Big Data Visualization Tool</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/apache-zeppelin-big-data-visualization-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/apache-zeppelin-big-data-visualization-tool/</guid>
      <description>Apache Zeppelin - Big Data Visualization Tool for Big data Engineers An Open Source Tool (Free Source for Data Visualization)
Learn the latest Big Data Technology - Apache Zeppelin! And learn to use it with one of the most popular programming Data Visualization Tool!
One of the most valuable technology skills is the ability to analyze huge data sets, and this course is specifically designed to bring you up to speed on one of the best technologies for this task, Apache Zeppelin!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jira Essentials</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/jira-essentials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 12:05:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/jira-essentials/</guid>
      <description>More than 65 000 companies use Jira nowadays and the number is growing. Whether you are already working in one of these companies and need to step up in your Jira game, or are planning a career change and need to add &#34;Jira expertise&#34; to your CV to increase your chances, this course is for you! After completing this course you will be able to confidently set up Jira projects, create and modify issues, set up filters, Scrum and Kanban boards and dashboards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash Course on Civil Engineering and AutoCAD: Part 2</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/crash-course-on-civil-engineering-and-autocad-part-2/</guid>
      <description>&#34;An estimate for any construction work may be defined as the actual process of calculating the quantities and costs of the various items required in connection with the specialised project - whatsoever&#34;.
Before the start of the project for its execution, the owner should have full knowledge of the volume of work that is to be carried out. The tiny details can help him understand if the actual work can be completed within the proposed time frame and budget.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
