<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sales on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/sales/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sales on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/sales/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Persuasion Psychology - Persuasion and Influence</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ultimate-persuasion-psychology-persuasion-and-influence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ultimate-persuasion-psychology-persuasion-and-influence/</guid>
      <description>LIKE ALL OTHER COURSES. UNLIKE ANY OTHER COURSE
Learn 56 state-of-the-art elite persuasion and influence techniques from my 5 years of influence and performance coaching for top executives in all different types of sales situations. I&#39;m a 2x MIT-backed entrepreneur turned persuasion psychology/negotiation skills coach who has worked with (and made better negotiators of) different profiles, and this course is for you if you&#39;re seeking to improve your influencing, for professional selling or just know more about how to win friends and influence people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copywriting &amp; SEO for Beginners: Complete Copywriting Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/copywriting-seo-for-beginners-complete-copywriting-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 10:06:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/copywriting-seo-for-beginners-complete-copywriting-course/</guid>
      <description>WANT YOUR BUSINESS TO GROW WITHOUT INCREASING YOUR MARKETING BUDGET? THEN MAKE SURE YOU PRODUCE SEO FRIENDLY CONTENT. LEARN SEO COPYWRITING AND USE EASY TO ADJUST PROFESSIONAL COPYWRITING TEMPLATES. THIS SEO &amp;amp; COPYWRITING COURSE MAKES LEARNING FUN! ENJOY ANIMATED VIDEOS &amp;amp; INTERACTIVE QUIZZES! BENEFIT FROM OUR EASY TO USE RESOURCES TO MAKE YOUR LIFE EASY!
SEO COPYWRITING MAKES YOUR WEBSITE MORE TRUSTWORTHY AND PROFESSIONAL.
Quality attracts the audience and adds authority to your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming A Sales Professional</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/becoming-a-sales-professional/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/becoming-a-sales-professional/</guid>
      <description>By caring about building relationships with potential customers and taking an interest in their world, it can significantly improve the odds of securing a sale and retaining that customer for the long-term.
Strategic friendships will make or break any business, no matter how big and no matter what kind of market.
So, in this course, our learning points will include:
Discover the benefits of developing a support network of connections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Marketing</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-marketing/</guid>
      <description>The Storyboard Initiative presents our Introduction to Marketing course, an introductory course that focuses on the basics and essentials of marketing. We cover a wide range of topics relating to marketing, from the marketing mix to color theory, go into the essentials and format of a marketing plan, and cover topics related to digital marketing in the modern world.
 Ratings: 4.01/5
Enrollments: 1552
Coupon Code: A2A3F5E3B0FD785DA0AB
Current Price: FREE</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Networking for Success and Company Growth: Part One</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/business-networking-for-success-and-company-growth-part-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 10:31:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/business-networking-for-success-and-company-growth-part-one/</guid>
      <description>Networking is both a Science and an Art. In this Networking Series, I’m going to cover the science of networking including the different types of networking groups, the different type of networking formats, and what to look for in networking groups. I’m also going to cover the Art of Networking so you can choose the right groups to spend your precious time at, build long-lasting relationships, and maximize your impact in your ever growing sphere of influence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Steps Into Selling Smarter</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/first-steps-into-selling-smarter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/first-steps-into-selling-smarter/</guid>
      <description>Broadly defined, today’s top salespeople are in the business of identifying needs and persuading potential customers to respond favorably to an idea that will result in mutual satisfaction for both the buyer and the seller.
So with this course, you will become a skilled salesperson, skilled at networking and learn the 80/20 rule. After today, you will know who to target and how to target them, and remember to do some prospecting every day through warming up cold calls, following up on leads, or networking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>B2B Lead Generation via Personalised Sales Videos &amp; LinkedIn</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/b2b-lead-generation-via-personalised-sales-videos-linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/b2b-lead-generation-via-personalised-sales-videos-linkedin/</guid>
      <description>Imagine if your B2B lead generation tactics were 20x MORE EFFECTIVE than they are now.
This course can help make it happen…
Wonder Leads is an innovative new approach to business development. It centres on individually personalised sales videos delivered through LinkedIn, where it’s proved to be almost 20x more effective than cold calling at generating warm leads.
Based on the Axiom award-winning sales book (previous winners include Seth Godin, Tony Robbins &amp;amp; Peter Drucker), entrepreneur and champion for positive communication Dave Holloway reveals a step-by-step approach to effective social selling that anyone can follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold Email Writing: Cold Emailing Cold Email Lead Generation</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cold-email-writing-cold-emailing-cold-email-lead-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cold-email-writing-cold-emailing-cold-email-lead-generation/</guid>
      <description>Master high-performing cold emails and email marketing!
I’m going to teach you…
How I secured a meeting with the CEO and executive team of a $30 million business off just one single automated cold email template
How achieve open rates over 50% and boost your clicks and responses
How to change people’s minds using certain copywriting words
The six big tips for writing effective, persuasive cold emails
The BEST copywriting frameworks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurship: Sales Training, Techniques and Methods</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/entrepreneurship-sales-training-techniques-and-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/entrepreneurship-sales-training-techniques-and-methods/</guid>
      <description>Entrepreneurship: Sales Training, Techniques and Methods
Have you tried to sell products and only failed, have you taken business in school and yet not able to learn how to get sales. Are you struggling with online sales and getting results?&amp;nbsp;If you answered yes to one or all of those questions then this class is right for you. I&amp;nbsp;created this class to help students just like yourself. Often I&amp;nbsp;am asked how you get all those sales, how is it done what are your secrets.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
