<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sales on </title>
    <link>/tags/sales/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sales on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/sales/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>B2B Lead Generation via Personalised Sales Videos &amp; LinkedIn</title>
      <link>/b2b-lead-generation-via-personalised-sales-videos-linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/b2b-lead-generation-via-personalised-sales-videos-linkedin/</guid>
      <description>Imagine if your B2B lead generation tactics were 20x MORE&amp;nbsp;EFFECTIVE than they are now.
This course can help make it happen…
Wonder Leads is an innovative new approach to business development. It centres on individually personalised sales videos delivered through LinkedIn, where it’s proved to be almost 20x more effective than cold calling at generating warm leads.
Based on the Axiom award-winning sales book (previous winners include Seth Godin, Tony Robbins &amp;amp; Peter Drucker), entrepreneur and champion for positive communication Dave Holloway reveals a step-by-step approach to effective social selling that anyone can follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold Email Writing: Cold Emailing Cold Email Lead Generation</title>
      <link>/cold-email-writing-cold-emailing-cold-email-lead-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cold-email-writing-cold-emailing-cold-email-lead-generation/</guid>
      <description>Master high-performing cold emails and email marketing!
I’m going to teach you…
How I secured a meeting with the CEO and executive team of a $30 million business off just one single automated cold email template
How achieve open rates over 50% and boost your clicks and responses
How to change people’s minds using certain copywriting words
The six big tips for writing effective, persuasive cold emails
The BEST copywriting frameworks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurship: Sales Training, Techniques and Methods</title>
      <link>/entrepreneurship-sales-training-techniques-and-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/entrepreneurship-sales-training-techniques-and-methods/</guid>
      <description>Entrepreneurship: Sales Training, Techniques and Methods
Have you tried to sell products and only failed, have you taken business in school and yet not able to learn how to get sales. Are you struggling with online sales and getting results?&amp;nbsp;If you answered yes to one or all of those questions then this class is right for you. I&amp;nbsp;created this class to help students just like yourself. Often I&amp;nbsp;am asked how you get all those sales, how is it done what are your secrets.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
