<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Programming Languages on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/programming-languages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Programming Languages on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/programming-languages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Java: Socket Programming Simplified</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/java-socket-programming-simplified/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/java-socket-programming-simplified/</guid>
      <description>Socket programming is an essential part of the language that enables you to understand how applications communicate over the network. This helps in enabling you to understand how client server communication works and also gives you more insights into how server applications are built. It is important for each and every application developer (including Java developers) to have an understanding of how socket communication works. Hence this course is an absolute necessity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>सीखें Javascript Programming हिन्दी में</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%96%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-javascript-programming-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%96%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-javascript-programming-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%A8%E0%A5%8D%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82/</guid>
      <description>नमस्कार दोस्तों!

जावास्क्रिप्ट(Javascript) वह भाषा है जिसे आधुनिक डेवलपर्स को जानना, और अच्छी तरह से जानना होगा। वास्तव में जावास्क्रिप्ट जानने से आपको नौकरी मिल जाएगी, और आप quality web application का निर्माण करने में सक्षम होंगे।
इस पाठ्यक्रम में, आप जावास्क्रिप्ट के मूल सिद्धांतों को सीखेंगे, variables, constants, conditionals, loop, function जैसे बुनियादी निर्णय प्रोग्रामिंग अवधारणाओं को सीखेंगे। आप इस भाषा की सुंदरता और शक्ति को सीखेंगे जो आज आधुनिक सॉफ्टवेयर विकास में सबसे आगे है।</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Introduction to C&#43;&#43; Programming</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-introduction-to-c-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-introduction-to-c-programming/</guid>
      <description>Learning the basics of programmation can be very complicated no matter the programming language espescially if you never did any programming before. Being able to program in C++ is not different. This is why this course is here to help you learn everything you need to know about C++ and master this programming language. If you :
- Want to create various projects with this programming language - Are in school and need to understand certain notions and concepts in C++</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete JAVASCRIPT with HTML5,CSS3 from zero to Expert-2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-javascript-with-html5css3-from-zero-to-expert-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 09:46:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-javascript-with-html5css3-from-zero-to-expert-2021/</guid>
      <description>Want to learn Web Design &amp;amp; Web Development Skills? Then this is the RIGHT course For you! Many languages came and disappear but JavaScript is language that is enjoying a high run and demand in the programming world. The very first things you need to learn HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript and JQuery to become a Web Developer and off-course some Web Design Guidelines. This course will exactly teach you all these New Skills to become a good Web Developer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Demonstrations For Practice Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-demonstrations-for-practice-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 21:40:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-demonstrations-for-practice-course/</guid>
      <description>Learn Python From Beginner To Advanced Level By Demonstrations
The course is created thorough, extensive, but easy to follow content which you’ll easily understand and absorb.
 The course starts with the basics, including Python fundamentals, programming, and user interaction.

The curriculum is going to be very hands-on as we walk you from start to finish becoming a professional Python developer. We will start from the very beginning by teaching you Python basics and programming fundamentals, and then going into advanced topics and different career fields in Python so you can get real-life practice and be ready for the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Object Oriented Programming in C&#43;&#43;  &amp;  Interview Preparation</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/object-oriented-programming-in-c-interview-preparation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/object-oriented-programming-in-c-interview-preparation/</guid>
      <description>Classroom like learning, Detailed Explanation of Question, Top Frequently Asked Questions
Concepts of C++ programming are made very simple and easy.

Curriculum:
Introduction
Why Object Oriented Programming
Example of OOP
Member Function and Member Variable
Access Specifiers
Characteristics Of OOP Top Frequently Asked Interview Question - Part 1
Top Frequently Asked Interview Question - Part 2
Top Frequently Asked Interview Question - Part 3

Topics Covered in Questions</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basics of Python in 2 Hours</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/basics-of-python-in-2-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/basics-of-python-in-2-hours/</guid>
      <description>Python Basics for Absolute Beginners
This course will help you master the basic concepts of Python 3.9.6 within just 2 hours. The Basics of Python course covers, the concepts of Python Programming in 2 hours, and then you&#39;ll be creating your own applications, working with coding quizzes and challenges to excel what you learned.
Why Python?
Python is one of the world&#39;s top 3 programming languages, and it&#39;s the most used language by businesses and enterprises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java for Beginners - Learn all the Basics of Java</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/java-for-beginners-learn-all-the-basics-of-java/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 12:19:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/java-for-beginners-learn-all-the-basics-of-java/</guid>
      <description>Learning the how to program in any programming language can be very complicated especially if you never did any programming before. Programming in java is not different, but this course is here to help master this programming language. If you : - Need to learn the basics of this programming language for work - Are in school and need to understand certain Java concepts
- Want to create various projects with this programming language - Simply are curious about this topic</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java from Zero to First Job - Practical Guide, 700&#43; examples</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/java-from-zero-to-first-job-practical-guide-700-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 07:41:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/java-from-zero-to-first-job-practical-guide-700-examples/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the fundamental and the most complete course &#39;Java from Zero to First Job&#39;. As it&#39;s declared in the course name, it&#39;s created for people who want to learn programming from scratch. You need to know how to turn on your computer, no other knowledge is required for this course :) The rest will be covered in lessons.
Before starting creation of this course, our team attentively investigated feedbacks for existing courses on Udemy platform and tried to focus on the feedbacks for the top-rated courses to understand what can be improved in this course and make it even more better from the quality standpoint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Programming: Complete Beginner to Advanced</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/java-programming-complete-beginner-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 07:41:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/java-programming-complete-beginner-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to learn real world programming skills that will help you get your first java programming job?
Java is one of the most popular programming languages used to create Web applications and platforms. It was designed for flexibility, allowing developers to write code that would run on any machine.
So it’s your time now to take advantage of a loads of jobs and freelance opportunities that are available for java programmers out there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript for Beginners - The Complete introduction to JS</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/javascript-for-beginners-the-complete-introduction-to-js/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:52:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/javascript-for-beginners-the-complete-introduction-to-js/</guid>
      <description>Learning how to properly program in any programming language can be very complicated espescially if you never did any programming before. having the capacity to program in JavaScript is not different. This is why, this course have been created, to helpyou learn, properly program and understand everything you need to know about JavaScript to be able to master this programming language. If you:
- Need to learn the basics of JavaScript for work</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL- The Complete Introduction to SQL programming</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sql-the-complete-introduction-to-sql-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:52:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sql-the-complete-introduction-to-sql-programming/</guid>
      <description>Programming can sometimes be very hard to learn especially if you have no experience in this field. But, this course have everything that you need to be able to start your programming career or improve your programming skills by learning all the basis of how to properly program with SQL. If you :
- Are in school and want to learn how to program in SQL
- Need to learn this programming language for work</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Python Programming Comprehensive Bootcamp</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-python-programming-comprehensive-bootcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:52:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-python-programming-comprehensive-bootcamp/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to The Python Programming Comprehensive Bootcamp.
In this Complete Bootcamp, we’ll teach you everything you need to know to become a Professional Python developer.
Variables, Representing Data Types, and using Computational Power.
Data Structure for data organization, management and storage formatting.
Practical Flow control and Iterable aspects.
Building software by composing pure functions process.
Object-Oriented Programming model to organize software design.
Application containers and Handling all files.
Playing with Exception events and analyzing Errors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Python Programming For Everyone Immersive Training</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-python-programming-for-everyone-immersive-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 19:52:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-python-programming-for-everyone-immersive-training/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to The Python Programming For Everyone Immersive Training Course for Beginners.
This Immersive Masterclass covers all the essential topics to become a Professional Python developer from the ground up Topics like: variables, data types, Strings, data structures, functional programming, different types of modules, files handling, object-oriented programming and many more.
You&#39;ll get A demonstration of each point in this training and an explanation of all theoretical and practical aspects in an easy way and in an easy language for anyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python 3 Master Course for 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-3-master-course-for-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 22:23:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-3-master-course-for-2021/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to Master Python? Then this is the course for you where I will take you from complete beginner to Advanced Python Programmer. Let me walk you through a detailed step by step process that will help you accomplish your goals and have fun learning on the way we will cover the following in detail:

Introduction
Documentation
What is Python
Getting Started with Python Documentation
Cover Summary of Python Beginner&#39;s Documentation</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermediate Python Immersive Training | Boost your career</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/intermediate-python-immersive-training-boost-your-career/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 16:04:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/intermediate-python-immersive-training-boost-your-career/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to The Intermediate Python Immersive Training | Boost your career
In this course, you will learn in depth the most important Python language topics for the intermediate level.
Once you have completed this course, you will be able to use all these techniques, which we will list in detail.
There is a wonderful feature in this course, as it explains in important detail all you need in these topics in a direct and practical way that saves you valuable time and effort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Python Developer Essentials 2021 Immersive Bootcamp</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-python-developer-essentials-2021-immersive-bootcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 16:04:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-python-developer-essentials-2021-immersive-bootcamp/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to The Python Developer Essentials 2021 Immersive Bootcamp
Learn the skills you need to become a Professional Certified Python Developer with this Complete Training Course.
You&#39;ll become a Certified Python Developer and Coding Rockstar in no time. This course covers all the following concepts theoretically and practically:
How to Program with Modern Python
The clean Python code
The core Python concepts needed to become A Dev Professional</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Python Programming A-Z Definitive Diploma in 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-python-programming-a-z-definitive-diploma-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 16:04:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-python-programming-a-z-definitive-diploma-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>Hi, Welcome to The Python Programming A-Z Definitive Diploma in 2021.
Your complete Guide to Python Programming.
Almost Python is currently used for everything in Software Engineering.
Although it is very easy to learn, but, it is very useful and powerful.
Its fields are so many, and by learning python, it will be very easy for you to get higher Jobs in the largest companies such as Google, Dropbox, Spotify and many more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python for beginners - Learn all the basics of python</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-for-beginners-learn-all-the-basics-of-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 10:29:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-for-beginners-learn-all-the-basics-of-python/</guid>
      <description>Programming can sometimes be very hard to learn especially if you have no experience in this field. But, this course have everything that you need to be able to start your programming career or improve your programming skills by learning all the basis of python. If you :
- Are in school and want to learn how to program in python
- Need to learn this programming language for work</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Programming From A-Z: Beginner To Expert Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-programming-from-a-z-beginner-to-expert-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 13:19:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-programming-from-a-z-beginner-to-expert-course/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Learn Python Programming From A-Z: Beginner To Expert Course
Where you’re going to learn how to become a professional Python Developer and create programs, apps, scripts, games and so much more...
In this practical, hands-on course our main objective is to give you the education not just to understand the ins and outs of Python Programming, but also to learn exactly how the software development industry works, the different roles within a team, and how to land a Python Programming job without a degree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three.js</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/three.js/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 12:05:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/three.js/</guid>
      <description>SO, YOU’RE LOOKING FOR A COURSE THAT WILL TEACH YOU THREEJS &amp;amp; IN A FUN MANNER?
I’ve got just the course for you!
Welcome, my name is Josh Werner with Learn Tech Plus and I’ve put this course together to help people just like you quickly master ThreeJS...Whether you’re a beginner or experienced with ThreeJS!
If your goal is to become a user of ThreeJS, then this course is perfect for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Kotlin Learning Guide [Arabic Edition]</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-kotlin-learning-guide-arabic-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 09:03:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-kotlin-learning-guide-arabic-edition/</guid>
      <description>هذه الدورة المفصلة في المستوى الاول والثاني من الكوتلن حيث افترض الشخص الذي امامي لا يعرف اي شي عن عالم البرمجة ستتمكن من خلال هذه الدورة من الدخول الى عالم البرمجة وفهم اساسيات اللغات البرمجية لا تحتاج الى اي مؤهلات للدخول الى هذه الدورة ،تتميز هذه الدورة بأنها مفصلة ولكن ليس فيها تشعبات وتفاصيل غير اساسية
Kotlin remains one of the most widely used and fastest-growing programming languages in recent years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R Studio: Empieza desde cero</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/r-studio-empieza-desde-cero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/r-studio-empieza-desde-cero/</guid>
      <description>¿Te gustaría aprender a programar en R pero no sabes por donde empezar?
En este curso iremos paso a paso desde lo más sencillo hasta lo más complejo. Después de cada video, aprendes un nuevo concepto valioso que puedes aplicar de inmediato. Y la mejor parte es que aprendes a través de ejemplos en vivo. Este curso te proporcionará las bases del lenguaje de programación estadística R. 
Si eres un estudiante o profesionista que quiere potenciar su carrera profesional te tengo una buena noticia:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C# Programlama Dili : Temel, Orta, İleri Seviye</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/c#-programlama-dili-temel-orta-ileri-seviye/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/c#-programlama-dili-temel-orta-ileri-seviye/</guid>
      <description>DeepLab.Bootcamp organizasyonu ile temelden ileri seviyeye birçok konuda profesyonel canlı yayın eğitimleri ve workshop&#39;lara katılmak için Discord kanalımızı ziyaret edebilirsiniz : discord .com/invite/eqgURvZdzj

&#34;Birisine bir şey öğretemezsiniz, ancak kendisinin onu keşfetmesine yardım edebilirsiniz.&#34; {Galileo Galilei}
Bu kurs C# programlama dilini öğretmeyi ve C# ile yazılım geliştirmeyi öğretmeyi hedeflemektedir.
Bu kurs C# Programlama dilini anlatmaktadır. Diğer gördüğünüz tüm başlıklar eğitmen tarafından öğrencilerinin daha çeşitli çevre teknolojileri hakkında bilgi sahibi olması için eklenmiştir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Programlama Dili : Standart Kütüphane</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/go-programlama-dili-standart-k%C3%BCt%C3%BCphane/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/go-programlama-dili-standart-k%C3%BCt%C3%BCphane/</guid>
      <description>DeepLab.Bootcamp organizasyonu ile temelden ileri seviyeye birçok konuda profesyonel canlı yayın eğitimleri ve workshop&#39;lara katılmak için Discord kanalımızı ziyaret edebilirsiniz : discord .com/invite/eqgURvZdzj
Kurs İçeriği
Go programlama dilinin geliştirici ekibi tarafından hazırlanan ve Go geliştiricilerinin kullanımına sunulan Standard Library(Kütüphane) kütüphanesi etkili bir şekilde kullanmak sizin daha az kod yazarak daha performanslı ve etkili projeler geliştirebilmenizde yardımcı olur. C, C++, Java, Python ve C# gibi tüm popüler programlama dillerinin kendisine ait bir küçük ya da geniş kod kütüphaneleri bulunur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build A Search Engine With Python: Computer Science &amp; Python</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/build-a-search-engine-with-python-computer-science-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 17:04:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/build-a-search-engine-with-python-computer-science-python/</guid>
      <description>AStateOfData.Com™ Computer Science With Python: An Absolute Beginners Guide To Computer Science
Introduction
WHY THIS COURSE IS DIFFERENT?	Many of the online courses teach you to code but not the theory/way of thinking behind it why would we choose a while but not a for loop, why should we pass 2 parameters to a function but not only one? This course will teach you how to think about solving coding problems throughout quizzes, there are 112 video format quizzes that aim to keep you engaged with the course and teach you the Python fundamentals in an easy to follow manner</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Programming Beginner to Advance &#43; Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-programming-beginner-to-advance-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-programming-beginner-to-advance-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>Looking to master Python for your job or as a career enhancement?
Go from beginner to advance in Python Programming! Apply your knowledge in Machine Learning Data Science &amp;amp; Data Analysis in this intensive course!
Python is the most widely used programming language on the planet. In the United States, the average pay for a Python developer is $116k. That&#39;s almost $30k more than the competition!
This course (Python Programming Beginner to Advance + Machine Learning) will help you reach your dreams!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python for Absolute Beginners® | Zero to Expert 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-for-absolute-beginners-zero-to-expert-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-for-absolute-beginners-zero-to-expert-2021/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of checking multiple courses on Python and not found even one which meets your actual requirements?

Most beginners study core part of the programming easily but actual programming starts after core programming is finished, since most of real world problems are solved by using programming paradigms such as iteration, recursion, comprehension, object oriented programming etc. 
Most of the preceding topics are heavily influenced by fundamental mathematics, I will try to teach you fundamental mathematics through these programming paradigm such as iteration and recursion through this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Development Using JAVA for Beginners - 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/project-development-using-java-for-beginners-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/project-development-using-java-for-beginners-2021/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to learn real world programming skills that will help you get your first java programming job?
Java is one of the most popular programming languages used to create Web applications and platforms. It was designed for flexibility, allowing developers to write code that would run on any machine.
So it’s your time now to take advantage of a loads of jobs and freelance opportunities that are available for java programmers out there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Python 3- Full Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-python-3-full-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-python-3-full-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Learn Python, a programming language with a wide variety of well-paying jobs in many fields, including data science and web development.
It is relatively easy to learn when compared to pretty much any other programming language since most of the time, using Python to do something will take less lines of code than with another programming language.
In this course, you will be taught the fundamentals of Python through high quality video and audio lectures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python for beginners - Learn all the basics of python</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/python-for-beginners-learn-all-the-basics-of-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/python-for-beginners-learn-all-the-basics-of-python/</guid>
      <description>Programming can sometimes be very hard to learn especially if you have no experience in this field. But, this course have everything that you need to be able to start your programming career or improve your programming skills by learning all the basis of python. If you :
- Are in school and want to learn how to program in python
- Need to learn this programming language for work</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical Bootcamp JWT Authentication with Java &amp; SpringBoot</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/practical-bootcamp-jwt-authentication-with-java-springboot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/practical-bootcamp-jwt-authentication-with-java-springboot/</guid>
      <description>JWT(Json web token) is a standard for securing API&#39;s in a Microservices architecture, using this standard we can secure API&#39;s built in any technology like Nodejs, Python, .NET etc but in this course we will building API&#39;s using Java and SpringBoot and than we will be securing them using JWT and Spring security, we will also use all the industry best practices and standards along the way.
We will start with learning concepts like:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Foundations of Python Programming | 2021 Training</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/advanced-foundations-of-python-programming-2021-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/advanced-foundations-of-python-programming-2021-training/</guid>
      <description>Hello and welcome to the Advanced Foundations of Python Programming | 2021 Training Masterclass.
Learn the Advanced foundations of modern python programming with this powerful, deep, direct to the point and interactive training.
For each concept in this course, you&#39;ll master the theory then you&#39;ll&amp;nbsp; practice with many real examples.
Do you want to Advance your Python development career?
Do you want to be able to create real programs using the advanced concepts of Python?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
