<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Parenting &amp; Relationships on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/parenting-relationships/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Parenting &amp; Relationships on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/parenting-relationships/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beyond common sense: A scientific positive parenting course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/beyond-common-sense-a-scientific-positive-parenting-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/beyond-common-sense-a-scientific-positive-parenting-course/</guid>
      <description>Parenting is not easy and children (unfortunately) do not come with a manual. Although parenting advice can be found anywhere, it is often difficult to determine the quality of these parenting tips. This course aims to provide you with high-quality knowledge and skills on positive parenting, fully based on scientific findings.
Gain Science-Based Knowledge and Master Skills to be a Positive Light in Children’s Life
· Learn about Positive Parenting based on the Self-Determination Theory</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ADHD Mums! Focus Your Morning &amp; Evenings For Your ADHD Child</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/adhd-mums-focus-your-morning-evenings-for-your-adhd-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/adhd-mums-focus-your-morning-evenings-for-your-adhd-child/</guid>
      <description>If you are a mum of an ADHD child, you must have realised by now that the traditional parenting methods don&#39;t work at best, or backfire at worst.
If you have an ADHD child, normal, regular household rules are almost impossible to create and maintain. Your success at parenting your ADHD child will largely depend on the severity of your ADHD child&#39;s symptoms, whether they have a comorbid condition, and most importantly how well you are managing your ADHD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Timers Guide to Approach A Girl - Basic Do&#39;s &amp; Don&#39;ts</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/first-timers-guide-to-approach-a-girl-basic-dos-donts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:47:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/first-timers-guide-to-approach-a-girl-basic-dos-donts/</guid>
      <description>If you want to start conversations with girls in different environments, get their phone numbers or add them on Instagram/Facebook/Snapchat, and begin dating them, then this is the course for you.
This course focuses on the basic question every guy has to get things going for him with a girl; be it the start of a friendship or the first step to a blossoming relationship; in different scenarios from parties to your empty high school corridors; and the different types of girls, be it shy or the obnoxious kind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness for Parents with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/mindfulness-for-parents-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/mindfulness-for-parents-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>Mindfulness For Parents is designed to support you to discover:

-What is Mindfulness and how it can help you and your family
-The 3 Pillars of Mindfulness
-How to bring Mindfulness into your daily activities
-How to practice Mindfulness with your child – or kids, if you have more than one
- How to develop more concentration
- How to increase kindness, self-compassion and wellbeing to your life and in the lives of the ones you love and care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Letter For Myself: Self-Affirmations with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/a-letter-for-myself-self-affirmations-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/a-letter-for-myself-self-affirmations-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>A Letter For Myself: 56 Days To Reprogram Your Subconscious Mind For A Healthy &amp;amp; Loving Relationship is developed to increase your love for yourself and for your partner or even for your future partner, if you don&#39;t have one yet.

“A Letter For Myself” is a self-development audio course from MRS JOY’s Academy, where you will find special narrations of MRS JOY, as you are talking with yourself. They help you to reprogram your subconscious mind and imprint the life you love to live.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
