<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Parenting &amp; Relationships on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/parenting-relationships/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Parenting &amp; Relationships on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/parenting-relationships/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Happy parents happy kids parenting course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/happy-parents-happy-kids-parenting-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/happy-parents-happy-kids-parenting-course/</guid>
      <description>This course will nurture a better, peaceful atmosphere at home. Enhance your well-being of you as a parent and, in turn, the well-being of your children that will enrich the quality of your relationship with your child/children. This course will create more room for understanding and less room for tension and conflicts, by promote healthier coping skills and constructive responses, to not only your children but people around you. This course will help you regulate and manage your own emotions, by providing techniques for feeling more grounded and in control of situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking for Parents - Teach Your Kids to Present 1Hr</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-for-parents-teach-your-kids-to-present-1hr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-for-parents-teach-your-kids-to-present-1hr/</guid>
      <description>Public Speaking for Parents - Teach Your Kids to Present - learn in less than 1Hour
You can teach your child or kid to become a confident and strong public speaker. Public speaking and presentation skills are essential for success in most careers, yet they are rarely taught in public or private schools.
TJ Walker has taught public speaking skills to top CEOs, presidents of countries, prime ministers, and business visionaries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypnosis for Natural Easy Childbirth  Hypnosis Program</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hypnosis-for-natural-easy-childbirth-hypnosis-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hypnosis-for-natural-easy-childbirth-hypnosis-program/</guid>
      <description>Hypnosis for Natural Easy Childbirth Hypnosis Program this has been created to simulate a complete collection of private hypnosis sessions with me as your guiding Hypnotherapist
Childbirth is one of the most natural experiences any woman can ever have and has to have been the first ever most precious of human experiences. All fears and most of the pain that you may have heard about giving birth or being in labor are created by those people who gave birth with fear in their minds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Up Creativity in Your Child</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fire-up-creativity-in-your-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fire-up-creativity-in-your-child/</guid>
      <description>**Course Updated - June 2022**
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; COURSE REGULARLY UPDATED: NEW TIPS, MORE LESSONS &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; CERTIFIED COACH, SPEAKER AND TRAINER &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; OVER 180,000 STUDENTS IN TOTAL &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------
What if I told you your child has special powers and latent abilities just waiting to be unleashed?? Sounds interesting?? Let’s go ahead and learn what this is all about…
Let me ask you a few questions? Do children today use their imaginations as much as we did when we were kids?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>تدريب الأزواج ( كيف تنقذ حياتك الزوجية ؟</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%AA%D8%AF%D8%B1%D9%8A%D8%A8-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A3%D8%B2%D9%88%D8%A7%D8%AC-%D9%83%D9%8A%D9%81-%D8%AA%D9%86%D9%82%D8%B0-%D8%AD%D9%8A%D8%A7%D8%AA%D9%83-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B2%D9%88%D8%AC%D9%8A%D8%A9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 16:26:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%AA%D8%AF%D8%B1%D9%8A%D8%A8-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A3%D8%B2%D9%88%D8%A7%D8%AC-%D9%83%D9%8A%D9%81-%D8%AA%D9%86%D9%82%D8%B0-%D8%AD%D9%8A%D8%A7%D8%AA%D9%83-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B2%D9%88%D8%AC%D9%8A%D8%A9/</guid>
      <description>كيفية تحديد المشكلات التي تواجهك مع شريك الحياة بدقة
تغيير المفاهيم الخاطئة الشائعة عن العلاقات الزوجية
الاعتراف بالصفات السيئة وتحجيمها
اصلاح جوهر الذات لاصلاح جوهر العلاقة وامتلاك قيم ترتقي بعلاقتك بشريك الحياة
وصفة النجاح في العلاقة بشريك الحياة
إعادة الاتصال بشريك الحياة بفعالية
تمرينات عملية في أربعة عشر يوما من الحب بإخلاص
الاسئلة الشائعة الخاصة بالعلاقة الحميمة
إدارة العلاقة Ratings: 4.38/5
Enrollments: 2407
Coupon Code: BBDE3D517C9796DD5ACF
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Nonverbal Communication Course - Body Language</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-nonverbal-communication-course-body-language/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-nonverbal-communication-course-body-language/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Nonverbal Communication Course - Body Language
Nonverbal Communication for Business, Public Speaking and Life - Display Confidence and High Self Esteem
Nonverbal communication can be the most memorable and most powerful way of communicating with other human beings. Whether you are meeting one-on-one with a friend, sitting in a business meeting, or giving a presentation, you need to know ho to use nonverbal communication to your benefit.
Here is what Udemy students say about this course:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contented Career Mom</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/contented-career-mom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 18:10:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/contented-career-mom/</guid>
      <description>Are you a mother on maternity leave who is feeling anxious about returning to work - wishing you could be focused on enjoying this time with your baby?
Wouldn’t it be amazing to breeze through your final weeks of maternity leave, relaxing and enjoying time with your baby, whilst confident that you already have a practical plan in place to prepare everything for your successful return to work?
I’ll take the guesswork out of how to tackle the transition, by teaching you my proven 30-day return to work method: leaving you feeling calmer, more confident and in control - as well as freeing up plenty of time for you to enjoy your final weeks of maternity leave.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morning and Evening Routines for Your ADHD Child</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/morning-and-evening-routines-for-your-adhd-child/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 16:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/morning-and-evening-routines-for-your-adhd-child/</guid>
      <description>WHAT WILL YOU LEARN IN THIS COURSE?
Is the morning rush choking you?
Are you fed up with being up till midnight with your child because they won’t go to bed?
Are you beyond exhausted?
As a mother of an ADHD child, you know how difficult the morning and evening rush can be. You know that traditional parenting methods don&#39;t work at best, and backfire at worst. You need specialist ADHD tools to support your ADHD child to unlock their potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FATHERHOOD MASTERY - How to be a Good Dad</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fatherhood-mastery-how-to-be-a-good-dad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 06:56:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fatherhood-mastery-how-to-be-a-good-dad/</guid>
      <description>Do you feel you can be a better father for your children?
Are you about to become a first time Dad?
The most fulfilling part of live is bring our children into the world, watching and guiding them as they grow. But many times we are conflicted in how we teach them and what behaviors we show them as they grow.
Your instructors, Ricky Shetty, father of three beautiful children under 6, and Scott Paton, with two sons over 25, share their wisdom and knowledge of raising their children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beyond common sense: A scientific positive parenting course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/beyond-common-sense-a-scientific-positive-parenting-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/beyond-common-sense-a-scientific-positive-parenting-course/</guid>
      <description>Parenting is not easy and children (unfortunately) do not come with a manual. Although parenting advice can be found anywhere, it is often difficult to determine the quality of these parenting tips. This course aims to provide you with high-quality knowledge and skills on positive parenting, fully based on scientific findings.
Gain Science-Based Knowledge and Master Skills to be a Positive Light in Children’s Life
· Learn about Positive Parenting based on the Self-Determination Theory</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Timers Guide to Approach A Girl - Basic Do&#39;s &amp; Don&#39;ts</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/first-timers-guide-to-approach-a-girl-basic-dos-donts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:47:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/first-timers-guide-to-approach-a-girl-basic-dos-donts/</guid>
      <description>If you want to start conversations with girls in different environments, get their phone numbers or add them on Instagram/Facebook/Snapchat, and begin dating them, then this is the course for you.
This course focuses on the basic question every guy has to get things going for him with a girl; be it the start of a friendship or the first step to a blossoming relationship; in different scenarios from parties to your empty high school corridors; and the different types of girls, be it shy or the obnoxious kind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mindfulness for Parents with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mindfulness-for-parents-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mindfulness-for-parents-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>Mindfulness For Parents is designed to support you to discover:
-What is Mindfulness and how it can help you and your family
-The 3 Pillars of Mindfulness
-How to bring Mindfulness into your daily activities
-How to practice Mindfulness with your child – or kids, if you have more than one
- How to develop more concentration
- How to increase kindness, self-compassion and wellbeing to your life and in the lives of the ones you love and care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Letter For Myself: Self-Affirmations with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/a-letter-for-myself-self-affirmations-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/a-letter-for-myself-self-affirmations-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>A Letter For Myself: 56 Days To Reprogram Your Subconscious Mind For A Healthy &amp;amp; Loving Relationship is developed to increase your love for yourself and for your partner or even for your future partner, if you don&#39;t have one yet.
“A Letter For Myself” is a self-development audio course from MRS JOY’s Academy, where you will find special narrations of MRS JOY, as you are talking with yourself. They help you to reprogram your subconscious mind and imprint the life you love to live.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
