<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Database Design &amp; Development on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/database-design-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Database Design &amp; Development on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:41 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/database-design-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MySQL Database Development Mastery</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/mysql-database-development-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/mysql-database-development-mastery/</guid>
      <description>Overview
This is a zero to hero course on MySQL Database Server and MySQL Workbench. There are no pre-requisites for this course. If you are looking to get acquainted with the concept of Databases and Queries then this is the right course for you. Why Learn MySQL
MySQL is the world’s most popular open source database. With its proven performance, reliability, and ease-of-use, MySQL has become the leading database choice for web-based applications, used by high profile web properties including Facebook, Twitter and YouTube.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft SQL Server Development for Everyone</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-sql-server-development-for-everyone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 10:08:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-sql-server-development-for-everyone/</guid>
      <description>Overview
This is a zero to hero course on Microsoft SQL Databases and Querying. There are no pre-requisites for this course. This course provides you with fundamental SQL Server training and is enough to get you started at a Database Developer or Junior Database Administrator. This course will teach you how to use the SQL language within Microsoft SQL Server, one of the most popular database engines in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MS SQL Server 2019. Programación de Bases de Datos con T-SQL</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ms-sql-server-2019.-programaci%C3%B3n-de-bases-de-datos-con-t-sql/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ms-sql-server-2019.-programaci%C3%B3n-de-bases-de-datos-con-t-sql/</guid>
      <description>Con este curso de Microsoft SQL Server 2019, partiremos de cero, para mostrar este gestor de bases de datos, al mismo tiempo que nos formaremos con SQL y la extensión de funcionalidades del lenguaje que hace Microsoft, llamado Transact-SQL.
Veremos todos los comandos y sentencias necesarios para poder trabajar con fluidez en un proyecto.
Desarrollaremos proyectos de bases de datos para poder trabajar elaboración de informes completos o scripts que puedan ser integrados en otros framework&#39;s de desarrollo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL Básico - Intermedio ¡Añade valor a tu CV en 2 horas!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sql-b%C3%A1sico-intermedio-a%C3%B1ade-valor-a-tu-cv-en-2-horas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sql-b%C3%A1sico-intermedio-a%C3%B1ade-valor-a-tu-cv-en-2-horas/</guid>
      <description>Aprenderás cómo leer y escribir consultas complejas en una base de datos usando una de las habilidades más demandadas. Estas habilidades también se aplican a cualquier otra base de datos como MySQL, Microsoft SQL Server, Oracle y mucho más. ¡Aprender SQL es una de las formas más rápidas de mejorar tus perspectivas profesionales ya que es una de las habilidades tecnológicas más demandadas! ¡En este curso aprenderás rápidamente y recibirás desafíos y pruebas en el camino para mejorar tu comprensión!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical Database Course for Beginners : 6 courses in 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/practical-database-course-for-beginners-6-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 18:00:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/practical-database-course-for-beginners-6-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>What our students says regarding this course! ---
&#34;I am a beginner with Databases and SQL and this course has been very informative and easy to follow.&#34; -- Eve Grant
&#34;The Course is very efficient i would highly recommend this course to all the newbies who are willing to learn Databases&#34; -- Ikram Khizer
&#34;Lovely! Compact course with proper guideline.&#34; -- Pensee Chouinard
&#34;Good information to get started.&#34; -- Debashish Majumda</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL Bootcamp with MySQL, PHP &amp; Python : 5 Courses in 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sql-bootcamp-with-mysql-php-python-5-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sql-bootcamp-with-mysql-php-python-5-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>=== Our students&#39; reviews regarding this course ===
&#34;it&#39;s good that the course focuses more on the application part rather than just giving some bookish theories or concepts which anyone can read for the plenty of textbooks.&#34; -- Deepanshu Kumar
&#34;Very clear and straight forward.&#34; -- Chakri Muthyala
&#34;really very explanatory and easy to understand&#34; -- Sekh
&#34;simply the best&#34; -- Frederick Ekow
&#34;Very Informative Course. Thank You&#34; -- Subrata Debnath</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oracle Veritabanı Programlama : SQL, PL/SQL, Oracle Mimarisi</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/oracle-veritaban%C4%B1-programlama-sql-pl/sql-oracle-mimarisi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/oracle-veritaban%C4%B1-programlama-sql-pl/sql-oracle-mimarisi/</guid>
      <description>Önemli Not : Bu kurs Türkiye&#39;nin ve Udemy&#39;nin ilk Oracle PL/SQL Programlama kursudur. 2011 yılında çekildi ve halen daha bu kadar kapsamlı başka bir Oracle kursu bulunmamaktadır. SQL ve PL/SQL dil özellikleri bilinenin aksine çok hızlı değişmez ve onlarca yıldır sektörde kullanılan bu dillerin özellikleri yok olmaz. Yeni Oracle versiyonlarında genellikle sadece yeni özellikler gelir(kullanıcı arayüzlerine ve dil özelliklerine). Yani bu kurs ilk ama halen günceldir. Bu kurs içerikleriyle hızlı şekilde dil ve genel mantığa hakim olduktan sonra zaman içinde gelen yeni özellikler için ayrıca güncel kitap ya da kurslar(kaliteli TR içerik yok, sadece İngilizce bulabilirsiniz) ile kendinizi daha da geliştirebilirsiniz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PostgreSQL Veritabanı Programlama (Part 1) - Temeller ve SQL</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/postgresql-veritaban%C4%B1-programlama-part-1-temeller-ve-sql/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/postgresql-veritaban%C4%B1-programlama-part-1-temeller-ve-sql/</guid>
      <description>DeepLab.University organizasyonu ile temelden ileri seviyeye birçok konuda profesyonel canlı yayın eğitimleri ve workshop&#39;lara katılmak için Discord kanalımızı ziyaret edebilirsiniz : discord .com/invite/eqgURvZdzj
Kurs İçeriği
SQL Server ve Oracle veritabanı yönetim sistemleri için hazırladığım derinlemesine anlatım yapan iki ayrı kurstan sonra, şimdi de uzun zamandır takipçilerimin beklediği PostgreSQL veritabanı yönetim sistemi eğitimi serisinin ilk kursunu yayına hazırladık.
ÖNEMLİ : PostgreSQL Veritabanı Programlama eğitimi iki farklı kurstan oluşuyor. Şuan incelediğiniz bu kurs, bu serinin ilk kursu olmakla birlikte, PostgreSQL&#39;in temellerini doğru ve hızlı bir şekilde anlatmayı hedeflemektedir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQLite Veritabanı Programlama</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sqlite-veritaban%C4%B1-programlama/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sqlite-veritaban%C4%B1-programlama/</guid>
      <description>Veritabanı teknolojileri, sektörel olarak farklı birçok sorunu çözmek için hazırlanmış birçok farklı marka ve girişime sahiptir. Bu kadar çeşit olmasının nedeni iş ve teknoloji dünyasında veri ile ilgili çözülmesi gereken sorunların çeşitlilik göstermesidir. Klasik veri depolama gibi ihtiyaçları çözmek için, onlarca yıldır Oracle, SQL Server, PostgreSQL, MySQL vb. gibi gelişmiş VTYS&#39;ler kullanılmaya devam ediliyor. Ancak günümüz teknolojilerinin çok daha karmaşık ihtiyaçlara sahip olması nedeniyle bu veritabanı teknolojileri artık yeterli değildir. Bu nedenle NoSQL kategorisi altında MongoDB, Redis, Cassandra ve daha farklı onlarca alt veritabanı teknolojisi geliştirilmiştir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basics of Database Design &amp; Development</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/basics-of-database-design-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/basics-of-database-design-development/</guid>
      <description>Database design is the process of producing a detailed data model of a database. This data model contains all the needed logical and physical design choices and physical storage parameters needed to generate a design. Through this tutorial we will try to teach the basis components of database design and explains how to make a good database design.
Designing a database is in fact fairly easy, but there are a few rules to stick to.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
