<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web Development on </title>
    <link>/tags/web-development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web Development on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/web-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Go ile RESTful API Programlama</title>
      <link>/go-ile-restful-api-programlama/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/go-ile-restful-api-programlama/</guid>
      <description>DeepLab.Bootcamp organizasyonu ile temelden ileri seviyeye birçok konuda profesyonel canlı yayın eğitimleri ve workshop&#39;lara katılmak için Discord kanalımızı ziyaret edebilirsiniz : discord .com/invite/eqgURvZdzj
Kurs İçeriği
Yazılım teknolojilerinin gelişmesiyle birlikte ortaya çıkan en güçlü ve performans programlama dillerinden birisi olan Golang ile web uygulamalar geliştirebilmek hem Türkiye hem de global olarak büyük bir kariyer adımı olacaktır.
Google, SpaceX, Tesla, Docker, Kubernetes, Koding, Dropbox, Apple ve daha birçok küresel çaptaki girişim ve firmanın altyapısını Go ile geliştirdiğini biliyor muydunuz?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP Crash Course For Absolute Beginners 2021</title>
      <link>/php-crash-course-for-absolute-beginners-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/php-crash-course-for-absolute-beginners-2021/</guid>
      <description>PHP is a general-purpose scripting language especially suited to web development. Learn about the basics of PHP.This course teaches you all of the concepts from absolute scratch. You do not require any prior knowledge of PHP. This course is created for absolute beginners.1. Introduction to PHP - Explains about what is PHP, its origin and uses of PHP2. Writing your first php code - Echo, Variables, Strings 3. Strings - Use of Single and Double Quotes4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup a Virtual Web Server using Linode or Digital Ocean</title>
      <link>/setup-a-virtual-web-server-using-linode-or-digital-ocean/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/setup-a-virtual-web-server-using-linode-or-digital-ocean/</guid>
      <description>This course offers an in-depth, hands-on overview of setting up and configuring a production web server, using Linode or Digital Ocean. Virtual Cloud Servers have become the industry standard for hosting web applications of all sizes and complexity. This includes small static web pages, to dynamic, database driven web sites that handle thousands of simultaneous processes. Regardless of the project, virtual servers offer a solution that provides web developers a scalable infrastructure that can easily adapt to a changing environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cssSelector Tutorial from basic to advance level.</title>
      <link>/cssselector-tutorial-from-basic-to-advance-level./</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cssselector-tutorial-from-basic-to-advance-level./</guid>
      <description>~ Learn to write cssSelector from scratch and be an expert in cssSelector Writing~ In this cssSelector Tutorial series, we will learn all about cssSelector from basic to advance level with real time scenarios and its importance in automation like with selenium, cypress etc. We will learn about the different cssSelector functions in very simple way which will be very easy to understand and will make you perfect in cssSelector writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>React Redux Toolkit complete guide</title>
      <link>/react-redux-toolkit-complete-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/react-redux-toolkit-complete-guide/</guid>
      <description>Course description:
This course is all about managing the state in react application using the redux toolkit. Each topic included in this course is added incrementally, to make sure that you have a solid foundation of knowledge. You&#39;ll find plenty of discussions added in to help you understand exactly when and where to use each feature of React and Redux.
What will you build?
To get the most from this course we will demonstrate a redux toolkit by building two apps</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NGINX, Apache, SSL Encryption - Certification Course</title>
      <link>/nginx-apache-ssl-encryption-certification-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 17:04:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nginx-apache-ssl-encryption-certification-course/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our latest course, which will guide you through the process of installing, securing, and configuring NGINX or Apache on an Ubuntu web server. You will also learn to encrypt all web traffic, using a Free SSL certificate from Let’s Encrypt.
APACHE Section:
This course begins with exploring the most widely used web server technology available, Apache. Statistics show that Apache is used to run over 65% of all web servers around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap &amp; jQuery - Certification Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>/bootstrap-jquery-certification-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 12:13:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bootstrap-jquery-certification-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Bootstrap &amp;amp; jQuery – Certification Course for BeginnersWith over 64% of the world using mobile devices to browse web pages, it’s no surprise that Bootstrap and jQuery have become the industry leaders in front-end scripting languages.This course starts right from the foundational concepts and gradually progresses to intermediate topics. Through a project-style learning approach, students will have the opportunity to build mobile-responsive web pages, complete with animation and interactivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a Members Only Blog using PHP, MySQL, &amp; AJAX</title>
      <link>/create-a-members-only-blog-using-php-mysql-ajax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 12:13:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/create-a-members-only-blog-using-php-mysql-ajax/</guid>
      <description>This course offers a hands-on approach in learning how to develop web applications using PHP, MySQL, and AJAX. Students will develop a blog with MySQL database integration. The project aims to cover the following key concepts:
Creating Dynamic Web Pages in PHP
Creating a MySQL Database to store Member Data.
Creating PHP &amp;amp; AJAX Validated Member Registration Forms
Creating PHP &amp;amp; AJAX Validated Member Login Authentication
Working with Session Variables – Login/Logout Functionality</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the Internet Works &amp; the Web Development Process</title>
      <link>/how-the-internet-works-the-web-development-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 12:13:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-the-internet-works-the-web-development-process/</guid>
      <description>This course explores how the internet works, including the composition and transmission of data packets over both Local and Wide Area Networks. We take a look at the HTTP and HTTPS protocols as applicable to client and server side communications - including DNS Lookups. This course will also teach students how email exchange works over SMTP and IMAP. The role of Network Ports and Firewalls are also introduced.The course comes complete with two bonus sections which offer a quick guide for aspiring Web Developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML, CSS, &amp; JavaScript - Certification Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>/html-css-javascript-certification-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 12:13:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/html-css-javascript-certification-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the HTML, CSS, &amp;amp; JavaScript - Certification Course for Beginners.
If you are interested in mastering the art of front-end development, look no further. This course is the complete beginners guide to developing cutting-edge web pages that are fully mobile responsive. The course branches into three sections. We start by exploring HTML5, students learn the composition of a web page and how a web browser interprets html code to display the visual elements of a page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML, JavaScript, &amp; Bootstrap - Certification Course</title>
      <link>/html-javascript-bootstrap-certification-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 12:13:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/html-javascript-bootstrap-certification-course/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the HTML, JavaScript, &amp;amp; Bootstrap – Certification Course for BeginnersThis course gives students the knowledge necessary to take their front-end development skills to the next level. This course, is meant for beginners who have little, to no experience with coding. We start right from the foundational concepts and work our way up to intermediate level topics. By the end of this course, students will be able to create stunning, mobile responsive web pages using the latest scripting languages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Domain Names and Web Hosting - Quick Guide</title>
      <link>/introduction-to-domain-names-and-web-hosting-quick-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 12:13:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/introduction-to-domain-names-and-web-hosting-quick-guide/</guid>
      <description>Domain Names Section:
We provide an overview of the domain name registration process. This includes the role of registrars and TLD (Top Level Domain) administration by ICANN. ccTLD&#39;s (Country Code Top Level Domains) are also explored.
Students will gain hands-on experience with the registration process using popular domain registrars. We will provide a comparison of different registrars and register a sample domain name using GoDaddy. Other topics of discussion will include: domain name privacy and administration, auto-renewal, domain forwarding, and name server assignment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript &amp; jQuery - Certification Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>/javascript-jquery-certification-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 12:13:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/javascript-jquery-certification-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the JavaScript &amp;amp; jQuery – Certification Course for BeginnersThis course offers a comprehensive guide into the fundamentals of coding using JavaScript and jQuery. These powerful languages can be used to add animated, dynamic client-side functionality to any web page.The JavaScript section of the course takes students on a journey that starts right from the basics. This includes JavaScript placement, and embedding External JavaScript code. From there, we move into variable declaration and operators for performing arithmetic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript, Bootstrap, &amp; PHP - Certification for Beginners</title>
      <link>/javascript-bootstrap-php-certification-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/javascript-bootstrap-php-certification-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the JavaScript, Bootstrap, &amp;amp; PHP - Certification Course for Beginners.
This course offers an excellent introduction into three of the most widely used programming languages available for both front-end and back-end development.
Students will start with adding client-side interactivity to web pages using JavaScript. JavaScript is a powerful language that can be used to add numerous functions to web pages, ranging from form validation to animated objects. By using the Document Object Model, students will manipulate individual html and css elements using JS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP for Beginners: PHP Crash Course 2021</title>
      <link>/php-for-beginners-php-crash-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/php-for-beginners-php-crash-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the informative PHP crash course for 2021 where learn modern PHP.
I put this crash course together for beginners and it was supposed to be less in the amount of time, but honestly, it got kind of far because the PHP is big, nonetheless, I promise you you will have great knowledge and confidence in your PHP skills after you finish this course. 

So look at what I am offering here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gatsby JS | Build a personal blog using gatsbyJS</title>
      <link>/gatsby-js-build-a-personal-blog-using-gatsbyjs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gatsby-js-build-a-personal-blog-using-gatsbyjs/</guid>
      <description>Learn to build blazing fast apps and websites with React using Gatsby, a static PWA (Progressive Web App) generator! Starting from scratch, you’ll learn to build a full blog app
Gatsby is a React-based, GraphQL powered static site generator. It combines together the best parts of React, webpack, react-router, GraphQL, and other front end tools to provide excellent developer experience. Gatsby is far more than typical static site generator though. You can think of it more like a modern front-end framework.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MERN Stack with Blog Project</title>
      <link>/mern-stack-with-blog-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 13:08:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mern-stack-with-blog-project/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to &#34;MERN Stack with Blog Project&#34;. In this course, we will be building an in-depth full-stack Blog project application using Node.js, Express, React, and MongoDB along with ES6+. We will start with a blank text editor and end with a deployed full-stack application. This course includes...
Building an extensive backend API with Node.js &amp;amp; Express
Extensive API testing with Postman
Integrating React with our backend in an elegant way, creating a great workflow</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn HTML5 In-Depth - With Real-World Examples</title>
      <link>/learn-html5-in-depth-with-real-world-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-html5-in-depth-with-real-world-examples/</guid>
      <description>HTML is the main markup language for web pages. 
HTML elements are the basic building-blocks of web pages. 
Learning HTML is your first step to become a web developer. 
HTML concepts will help you learn other web development technologies faster.

In this course you will learn how to create web pages using HTML5.

Which is foundation for web development.

You will learn HTML5 elements including images, videos, lists, tables, forms, Iframes and much more with Real-world Examples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build a To-Do List App with Node, Express, React and MongoDB</title>
      <link>/build-a-to-do-list-app-with-node-express-react-and-mongodb/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/build-a-to-do-list-app-with-node-express-react-and-mongodb/</guid>
      <description>React is the most popular JavaScript library of the last five years, and the job market is still hotter than ever. Companies large and small hire engineers who understand React, and salaries for engineers are high all the time. So, it&#39;s a great time to learn React! This course starts with zero knowledge assumed! All you need is basic web development and JavaScript knowledge.

In this course, you&#39;ll start with the basics of React and React Hooks and then expand your knowledge by building a fun to-do list app, both the front-end and the back-end, which puts you in a state of learning in a practical way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jQuery for Absolute Beginners : From Beginning to Advanced</title>
      <link>/jquery-for-absolute-beginners-from-beginning-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 17:46:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/jquery-for-absolute-beginners-from-beginning-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Our students review about this course --
&#34;Best course to get started with jQuery, Thankyou :) &#34; -- Vipinraj KT
&#34;It is easy to understand for beginners in JQuery. Simple and clear explanation.&#34; -- Irina Zakharova
&#34;taking everything into the details and steps by steps, I love the course so far&#34; -- Maher Mahbouby
&#34;Loved this course. I had zero knowledge on jQuery and now I just love it!&#34; -- Sachin Satish Pai</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML &amp; CSS - Certification Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>/html-css-certification-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 20:19:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/html-css-certification-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the HTML &amp;amp; CSS – Certification Course for BeginnersThis two-part series provides an in-depth look at the fundamentals of coding in HTML and CSS. We start by exploring HTML Development using some of the most commonly used tags and attributes. Students will learn the composition of an HTML file, and some of the essential components. Students will work with HTML Spacing, Text Formatting, Lists, Images, Embedding Videos, Link Creation, Tables, and Forms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS3 and Bootstrap for Absolute Beginners : 4 courses in 1</title>
      <link>/css3-and-bootstrap-for-absolute-beginners-4-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/css3-and-bootstrap-for-absolute-beginners-4-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>By completing this course, you will become a master in Web Design Technologies like CSS3 and Bootstrap and more. This course gives you hands-on and practical experience on detailed CSS3 and Bootstrap and more.
Contents of this tutorial # 
Interactive CSS3: Basics What is CSS? Why we need it?
What&#39;s new in CSS3
CSS Selectors, properties and attributes ID Selectors Class Selectors Element Selectors All Selectors Inline style sheets External Style sheets Interactive CSS3: Advanced The Box model Adding Color Working with fonts Background images Styling ID tags</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Wordpress Website Developer Course</title>
      <link>/complete-wordpress-website-developer-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-wordpress-website-developer-course/</guid>
      <description>This is one of the best WordPress course you will ever find. WordPress is now powering more than 29% of all websites in the world, there&#39;s never been a better time to build an income and a business around it.
This is the course of our students. New lecture are added every month and, at anytime on the request of the student. You&#39;re here because you want to master WordPress, right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Front End Web Development Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>/front-end-web-development-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/front-end-web-development-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Hi and Welcome to Front End Web Development Ultimate Course 2021
I&#39;m you instructor Josh Werner and I&#39;ll be leading you through this course
Have you always wanted to learn how to code but don&#39;t know where to start?	Would you like to make amazing websites and bring your ideas to life?	Then Front End Web Development Ultimate Course 2021 is for you!
Programming is the most in-demand skill in 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Bootstrap - For Beginners</title>
      <link>/learn-bootstrap-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-bootstrap-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Students learn to create the front-end component of mobile-responsive web applications, using the Bootstrap framework.
The techniques explored in this course will ensure your web applications adhere to strict development standards to avoid cross-browser and cross-device compatibility issues.
The course starts with the fundamental concepts, including embedding Bootstrap into web pages. We then explore the Bootstrap Grid system and popular mobile responsive web layouts.
Students will gain a solid understanding of almost every Bootstrap component available, from typography, carousels, panels, drop-down menus, and collapsible nav-bars to forms, popovers, modals and tool tips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn CSS - For Beginners</title>
      <link>/learn-css-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-css-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Students learn to harness the true power of front-end development using CSS (Cascading Style Sheets). Through comprehensive, hands-on exercises, students will develop stylish, responsive web layouts using CSS properties and style definitions.
We start with basic concepts such as the parts of a CSS rule and working with Classes, Divisions and IDs. Next we explore an intensive collection of style definition, from working with text, backgrounds and transparency, right to CSS positioning, link styling, and popular layout development techniques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn HTML - For Beginners</title>
      <link>/learn-html-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-html-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Students will learn how to create engaging web pages using HTML5, which is an integral part of the development process.
The material covers an intensive array of HTML5 elements including images, videos, lists, tables, forms, iframes and much more.
The course includes several hands-on projects to ensure comprehension of course materials.
By the end of the training, students will be proficient with coding in HTML and ready to tackle the more advanced scripting languages that follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn JavaScript - For Beginners</title>
      <link>/learn-javascript-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-javascript-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Students learn to add dynamic, interactivity to web pages using JavaScript.
We start with exploring the fundamental concepts, including JavaScript placement and output functions. We then transition to working with arithmetic operators, math functions, arrays, sorting, conditional statements and loops. Students also learn to work with events and functions.
The course includes several hands-on exercises to help students master this essential scripting language.
 Ratings: 4.24/5
Enrollments: 173172
Coupon Code: YOUACCEL12105</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn PHP - For Beginners</title>
      <link>/learn-php-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-php-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Students learn to integrate client-server communication into web pages to create dynamic functionality using PHP.
We start with the fundamentals, including PHP syntax and variable declaration. The course transitions into working with objects, arithmetic operators, conditional statements, loops, functions and arrays.
Students will also learn to utilize server side form validation techniques to maintain data integrity.
 Ratings: 4.23/5
Enrollments: 154451
Coupon Code: YOUACCEL12105
Current Price: FREE
Enroll Now: Click Here  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP &amp; MySQL - Certification Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>/php-mysql-certification-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/php-mysql-certification-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the PHP &amp;amp; MySQL Certification Course for Beginners.This course offers a comprehensive guide to learning how to code in PHP. We also explore integrating MySQL Databases into your PHP Projects for dynamic, user driven functionality.We start with PHP basics, including variable declaration and data output. The lessons then transition into working with objects, conditional statements, loops, functions, arrays, form validation, sorting, and much more.After the PHP Section, students learn to unleash the true power of dynamic page development with MySQL database integration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PHP for Beginners 2021: The Complete PHP MySQL PDO Course</title>
      <link>/php-for-beginners-2021-the-complete-php-mysql-pdo-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/php-for-beginners-2021-the-complete-php-mysql-pdo-course/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my full stack PHP, MySQL, and PDO course where you will learn everything you need to know about one of the most three hot technologies right now. This course is organized systematically from the programming language (PHP) to The most well-known database (MySQL) to the best PHP tool to connect to this database which is (PDO) to give the most interesting, fun, informative, and worthy opportunity for learning web development the right way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS &amp; JavaScript - Certification Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>/css-javascript-certification-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/css-javascript-certification-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the CSS &amp;amp; JavaScript – Certification Course for BeginnersThis two part series provides a detailed overview of the fundamentals of coding using CSS and JavaScript. Students will learn how to create responsive web pages using project based learning. The CSS section explores almost every aspect of CSS development. This includes:
Working with IDs, Classes, and Divisions.
CSS Text Properties, Borders and Backgrounds
Styling Images and Links
CSS Display Properties</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML &amp; CSS - Certification Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>/html-css-certification-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/html-css-certification-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the HTML &amp;amp; CSS – Certification Course for BeginnersThis two part series provides an in-depth look at the fundamentals of coding in HTML and CSS. We start with exploring HTML Development using some of the most commonly used tags and attributes. Students will learn the composition of an HTML file, and some of the essential components. Students will work with HTML Spacing, Text Formatting, Lists, Images, Embedding Videos, Link Creation, Tables, and Forms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build Laravel Applications fast using blueprint</title>
      <link>/build-laravel-applications-fast-using-blueprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/build-laravel-applications-fast-using-blueprint/</guid>
      <description>What you&#39;ll learn
Initialization of a Laravel app using blueprint
Building blueprint yml file
Autocreation of migrations , models
Autocreation of Controllers , and actions
Autocreation of Mailable , Jobs , Events .. Change you whole way of thinking of Laravel application building
Configure your blueprint to work better for you
Increase development speed
Promote Laravel conventions
Move from your ERD to your fully-functioning Data Access Layer
Get rid of repetitive tasks and routine debugging process</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Domain Names &amp; Web Hosting(Free Domain Name)</title>
      <link>/introduction-to-domain-names-web-hostingfree-domain-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/introduction-to-domain-names-web-hostingfree-domain-name/</guid>
      <description>Domain Names Section:
We provide an overview of the domain name registration process. This includes the role of registrars and TLD (Top Level Domain) administration by ICANN. ccTLD&#39;s (Country Code Top Level Domains) are also explored.
Students will gain hands-on experience with the registration process using popular domain registrars such as GoDaddy/Namecheap. We will provide a comparison of different registrars and register a sample domain name using GoDaddy/Namecheap. Other topics of discussion will include: domain name privacy and administration, auto-renewal, domain forwarding, and name server assignment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Basic HTML, CSS &amp; Javascript (Typescript) with Vue</title>
      <link>/learn-basic-html-css-javascript-typescript-with-vue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-basic-html-css-javascript-typescript-with-vue/</guid>
      <description>If you&#39;re tired of long courses and just want to learn basic web development this course is for you.

We focus on teaching you only what you need to know and keeping the videos short. The main focus of this course is to teach the basics of HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, and Vue JS. By the end of this course, you should be able to create a basic website, understand how styling a website works and how to get data from a server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern JavaScript for React JS - ES6.</title>
      <link>/modern-javascript-for-react-js-es6./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/modern-javascript-for-react-js-es6./</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to extend your knowledge in Javascript programming by learning the concepts of modern javascript - ES6?
If you want to start your journey to become a React or Angular developer, then this is the perfect course for you. What&#39;s this course about?
This course is specifically designed for those who want to get a quick start with Modern Javascript, especially ES6 concepts. It covers all the basic concepts of ES6: how the javascript has evolved, how to use its latest features that come under ES6 topics, what is babel, and how it is used to compile the ES6 code to make it browser compatible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern React JS Hooks e Context com a Edição Mais Recente</title>
      <link>/modern-react-js-hooks-e-context-com-a-edi%C3%A7%C3%A3o-mais-recente/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/modern-react-js-hooks-e-context-com-a-edi%C3%A7%C3%A3o-mais-recente/</guid>
      <description>Olá,
Bem-vindo ao Curso Modern React JS Hooks e Context com a Edição Mais Recente.
Você quer aprender React JS, mas não tem experiência alguma? Nosso curso React JS Hooks e Context é perfeito para você começar. Neste curso, desenvolvemos o curso React JS para fornecer tudo o que você precisa aprender para dominar o Hooks e Context.

Neste curso, mostraremos tudo o que você precisa saber para dominar o web development usando ReactJS, fornecendo um conhecimento poderoso por meio de uma mistura de diagramas e da criação de um aplicativo simples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NodeJs: Build The Complete E-Commerce Web API [2021]</title>
      <link>/nodejs-build-the-complete-e-commerce-web-api-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/nodejs-build-the-complete-e-commerce-web-api-2021/</guid>
      <description>What is Node.js?
Node.js, or Node, is a runtime environment for executing JavaScript code outside of a browser. It is ideal for building highly-scalable, data-intensive backend services (APIs) that power your client’s apps (web or mobile apps).

Why Should learn Node?
Node is great for prototyping and agile development as well as building super fast and highly scalable apps; Companies like Uber and PayPal use Node in production to build applications because it requires fewer people and less code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Solidity Course  - Blockchain - Zero to Expert</title>
      <link>/the-complete-solidity-course-blockchain-zero-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-solidity-course-blockchain-zero-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Solidity is the most popular blockchain language in the world designed to build DApplications (Smart Contracts). It powers Ethereum and there is an in demand exponential growth of high-paying jobs all over the world which is changing the way we conduct business.
Learning Solidity can be likened to learning web development languages years ago - You are very much ahead of the game starting today -and that&#39;s why you want to learn Solidity too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Development with Bootstrap, Python &amp; Django</title>
      <link>/web-development-with-bootstrap-python-django/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/web-development-with-bootstrap-python-django/</guid>
      <description>Hello there, Welcome to Web Development with Bootstrap, Python &amp;amp; Django course.
This course will be your gateway to learn web design with blank HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap files with a step-by-step approach.&amp;nbsp; We can assure you that only this course will enough for you to learn web development from scratch to intermediate. Then you will learn Python Programming step-by-step. I made Python 3 programming simple and easy with exercises, challenges, and lots of real-life examples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate WordPress Quiz for Beginners and Advanced Users</title>
      <link>/the-ultimate-wordpress-quiz-for-beginners-and-advanced-users/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-ultimate-wordpress-quiz-for-beginners-and-advanced-users/</guid>
      <description>WordPress has surely come a long way since it was first released long back&amp;nbsp; — so too do the WordPress numbers (stats, basically) that serve to characterize this popular tech platform. Because of its user-friendly interface, WordPress users can easily publish their content on the Internet - meaning it simplifies the website building efforts of designers and developers using the platform. A significant segment of the WordPress user community needs to learn more about the platform so that they can not only publish content but also design, customize, and manipulate their WordPress themes to make their websites look amazing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Development Masterclass - Complete Certificate Course</title>
      <link>/web-development-masterclass-complete-certificate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/web-development-masterclass-complete-certificate-course/</guid>
      <description>This course is fully compatible with the latest versions of Ubuntu (20.04 LTS, 18.04 LTS). You can also continue using 14.04 LTS or 16.04 LTS if you prefer, as the content is compatible with all versions.
This course offers a comprehensive look into the entire web development process - from local server configuration using WAMP and MAMP (Apache, MySQL, PHP)&amp;nbsp;to production deployment using the latest web technologies including: LAMP Stack (Linux, Apache, PHP and MySQL) for Ubuntu, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, XML, and AJAX.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
