<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SAP on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/sap/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SAP on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/sap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SAP Project Essentials: Implementing SAP S/4HANA and SAP ERP</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sap-project-essentials-implementing-sap-s/4hana-and-sap-erp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sap-project-essentials-implementing-sap-s/4hana-and-sap-erp/</guid>
      <description>SAP S/4HANA is here, and the stakes are high. Get your project right with this guide to SAP Activate and Accelerated SAP (ASAP).
Help your business team prepare for and participate in the SAP project journey!
Get an early read on timelines, processes, responsibilities, and potential setbacks. Understand how your implementation, upgrade, or migration is structured, how to assemble the deliverables, and how to dodge common pitfalls. With this preview of what to expect, what questions to ask, and when to take which steps, you can execute planning, go-live, and post-go-live activities without tripping up or getting lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete SAP S/4HANA Bootcamp 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-sap-s/4hana-bootcamp-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-sap-s/4hana-bootcamp-2021/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for a course that will help you land that elusive 6-figure salary?
With so many different options out there it can be hard to know where to turn, so why not focus all your efforts on something a select few have been profiting from for years?
Every large business is working constantly on streamlining their processes and improving their efficiency, and they all use the SAP ERP platform to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete SAP Analytics Cloud Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-sap-analytics-cloud-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:42:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-sap-analytics-cloud-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Become an SAP Analytics Cloud master by setting up BI, planning, and making prediction through real-world projects
SAP analytics cloud consultant is one of the hottest careers in tech. Have you ever wondered what&#39;s the best path for me or what&#39;s my first step in building a technical career in SAP business analysis?
I&#39;m going to take you through the process of understanding how to use SAP analytics cloud. Whether you&#39;re looking to discover the core BI features or use planning module at work, this course will get you ready to plan and start to use SAP analytics cloud quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP Business Analytics Essential Training</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sap-business-analytics-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sap-business-analytics-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>If you have been looking to move to business analyst, this video will provide you with enough information to do so. Not only understanding the basics, but how to make your first business analytics project successful.
Being a great data analyst is about helping your organization make better and more informed decisions.
According to Gartner research, Bl platform software and services sales will be tallied at $30 billion in 2020, and SAP Business intelligence solution has taken up to 10% of market share, so mastering SAP Bl platform is a must.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
