<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SAP on </title>
    <link>/tags/sap/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SAP on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:42:45 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/sap/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Complete SAP Analytics Cloud Course 2021</title>
      <link>/the-complete-sap-analytics-cloud-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:42:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-sap-analytics-cloud-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Become an SAP Analytics Cloud master by setting up BI, planning, and making prediction through real-world projects
SAP analytics cloud consultant is one of the hottest careers in tech. Have you ever wondered what&#39;s the best path for me or what&#39;s my first step in building a technical career in SAP business analysis?
I&#39;m going to take you through the process of understanding how to use SAP analytics cloud. Whether you&#39;re looking to discover the core BI features or use planning module at work, this course will get you ready to plan and start to use SAP analytics cloud quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP Business Analytics Essential Training</title>
      <link>/sap-business-analytics-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sap-business-analytics-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>If you have been looking to move to business analyst, this video will provide you with enough information to do so. Not only understanding the basics, but how to make your first business analytics project successful.
Being a great data analyst is about helping your organization make better and more informed decisions.
According to Gartner research, Bl platform software and services sales will be tallied at $30 billion in 2020, and SAP Business intelligence solution has taken up to 10% of market share, so mastering SAP Bl platform is a must.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
