<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business on </title>
    <link>/tags/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:15:05 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2022 Amazon FBA PL Product Hunting &amp; KW Research in One Hour</title>
      <link>/2022-amazon-fba-pl-product-hunting-kw-research-in-one-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:15:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022-amazon-fba-pl-product-hunting-kw-research-in-one-hour/</guid>
      <description>Take this Amazon FBA Private Label Product Hunting &amp;amp; Product Research Course to earn a six-figure income on Amazon
Many new sellers don&#39;t even know the potential of choosing a great product or what is the criteria for a great product to launch on Amazon which can generate 6 figure income. In this 60 minutes Amazon FBA private label product hunting or product research course, you will learn step by step,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Dropshipping Masterclass: Das NEUE Geschäftsmodell</title>
      <link>/digital-dropshipping-masterclass-das-neue-gesch%C3%A4ftsmodell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:15:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/digital-dropshipping-masterclass-das-neue-gesch%C3%A4ftsmodell/</guid>
      <description>Du bist unprofitabel mit deinem Dropshipping Shop oder hast noch nicht einmal angefangen? Dann sei einer der ersten und lerne hier das neue Geschäftsmodell Digital Dropshipping !
Keine unseriösen chinesischen Händler, keine Produkteinkaufskosten und auch keine Lieferkosten / langen Lieferzeiten mehr. Ich zeige dir hier Schritt für Schritt wie du dir Rechte an fertigen, digitalen Produkten kaufst, ein profitablen Shopify Shop aufbaust und gezielte Online Werbung schaltest. Das alles machen wir live am PC zusammen und du siehst meine professionellen Produkte, Onlineshops und Werbekampagnen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Steps Into Public Speaking</title>
      <link>/first-steps-into-public-speaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:15:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/first-steps-into-public-speaking/</guid>
      <description>First Steps into Public Speaking
Do you get nervous when presenting at company meetings?
Do you find it hard to make conversation at gatherings and social events?
Do you lock up in awkward social situations?
If so, this course is just for you!
It’s aimed at anybody who wants to improve their speaking skills in informal or formal situations.
We’ll give you the confidence and the skills to interact with others, and to speak in front of small or large groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Shopify Print on Demand Dropshipping With Live Proof</title>
      <link>/learn-shopify-print-on-demand-dropshipping-with-live-proof/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:15:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-shopify-print-on-demand-dropshipping-with-live-proof/</guid>
      <description>Summary:
Follow along with my lectures that show you how to build your own E-Commerce Business from A to Z. I have documented the entire process, from the initial steps, all the way up through to the first sales!

About Your Instructor:
Rio Wick has been in the E-Commerce &amp;amp; Internet Marketing / Affiliate Marketing space for years. With his passion for teaching others, he creates courses on many different topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management: Cost &amp; Schedule Monitoring using EVM</title>
      <link>/project-management-cost-schedule-monitoring-using-evm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:15:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project-management-cost-schedule-monitoring-using-evm/</guid>
      <description>The course will help you understand the basic concepts of Earned Value Management which is one of the most important technique for effective Project Management.
By the end of this course you will learn the key terms of Earned Value Management, their definitions and the various formulas used to analyze whether the project is getting executed on track with respect to cost and schedule.
The course lets you understand the concept of Budget, Planned Value, Earned Value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Referral System - How To Create A Successful One!</title>
      <link>/referral-system-how-to-create-a-successful-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:15:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/referral-system-how-to-create-a-successful-one/</guid>
      <description>This is a no-fluff actionable course on &#34;How To Create A Successful Referral System&#34;. I want to unpack for you the exact system that I&#39;ve used to grow, one of my current businesses. I&#39;m telling you now that it works. If you will take action and follow what you learn on this course if you would create the systems, the way that I will describe it for you in the next half an hour or so then you will be able to grow your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kickstarter Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/kickstarter-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:15:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/kickstarter-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve ever wanted to create something new with a community of enthusiastic people cheering you on, you’ve come to the right place.
This course is based on everything we’ve learned from reviewing over 200,000 projects — each of them created by someone like you. We hope it’ll help you get started with shaping your own project, whether it’s to make a movie, an album, a game, a gadget, a play, a restaurant, or pretty much anything else that springs from the imagination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Business Productivity Training Course</title>
      <link>/best-business-productivity-training-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/best-business-productivity-training-course/</guid>
      <description>In This Online Course You Will Learn About The Major Productivity Challenges Facing Companies Today … These Challenges Can Make Or Break A Businesses. This Amazing Online Training Will Give Your Business Or Career An Unfair Advantage Against The Competition.
In This Productivity Training Course You Will Discover Specific Tools, Strategies And Techniques To Beat These Challenges. By Learning How To Think Like A Top Producer … You Can Make Massive Advances In Your Business Or Career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emprendimiento Productivo</title>
      <link>/emprendimiento-productivo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/emprendimiento-productivo/</guid>
      <description>En un principio, el ser humano entendió que por sí solo no podía obtener mejores recursos y bienes, por lo que decidió aliarse a otros, formando aldeas y comunidades, la antesala de lo que fue evolucionando en las sociedades primitivas y la consecuente división de las tareas, dando lugar a los roles definidos dentro de una sociedad. Miles de años de evolución hacen que el mundo moderno estos emprendimientos sean compañías o empresas que pueden alcanzar inclusive gran escala, teniendo algunas de ellas el rol de empresas multinacionales y transnacionales, contando con bienes millonarios y una gran cantidad de recursos bajo su control, pero todo ello gira en torno al sueño o creatividad de una mente brillante.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Steps Into Selling Smarter</title>
      <link>/first-steps-into-selling-smarter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/first-steps-into-selling-smarter/</guid>
      <description>Broadly defined, today’s top salespeople are in the business of identifying needs and persuading potential customers to respond favorably to an idea that will result in mutual satisfaction for both the buyer and the seller.
So with this course, you will become a skilled salesperson, skilled at networking and learn the 80/20 rule. After today, you will know who to target and how to target them, and remember to do some prospecting every day through warming up cold calls, following up on leads, or networking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Air Logistics Management in Supply Chain Management</title>
      <link>/global-air-logistics-management-in-supply-chain-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/global-air-logistics-management-in-supply-chain-management/</guid>
      <description>This Course will prove to be a boon to you and help you boost your logistics and supply chain management knowledge as it is a specialized course on Aviation Logistics in Supply chain management as Air Logistics Management is very important if your aim is to move your cargo on urgent basis with minimum risk, As in International Trade , Supply chain management &amp;amp; Shipping there are many risks involved.Its a base for inventory Movement and is ideal for Amazon FBA, Drop Shipping, Outsourcing , Retail business owners, Inventory, Logistics and Supply chain management professionals as it is prepared with focus on practical knowledge which you can use in you day to day work as the instructor himself is a Supply Chain and Logistics Management professional managing Shipping, Freight Forwarding, Surface Transport, Aviation Logistics for many exporters and importers and has a professional qualification in then Feild of Logistics Management and Supply Chain Management</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantity Surveying Templates for Effective Cost Management</title>
      <link>/quantity-surveying-templates-for-effective-cost-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quantity-surveying-templates-for-effective-cost-management/</guid>
      <description>This course explains the different Quantity Surveying templates created by me for effective post contract cost management.
You can download these templates and use it in your professional life.
By the end of this course, you will learn the below :
Prepare a perfect payment application summary for the interim payment applications.
Able to properly track both the inward and outward payments specific to the project.
Efficiently monitor and update the variations and claims status of the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Leadership Mastery Course</title>
      <link>/the-complete-leadership-mastery-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-leadership-mastery-course/</guid>
      <description>The world has changed overnight and every dimension of our life got upended in an unprecedented manner. How we work, how we buy, how we live and how we study have gone through a metamorphosis. Live now revolves around a screen - yet, the world slowly grinds on..However, everything falls and rises on Leadership. Everything grows and shrinks on the efforts of a leader. Business growth, Corporate leadership or personal mastery is a result of concerted choices by a Leader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon FBA Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/amazon-fba-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/amazon-fba-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Make money with the FBA program from the world&#39;s biggest store!
Amazon is the world’s biggest and most popular ecommerce website, and the 8th most popular website in the United States. Millions of people shop the site every day, and Quantcast estimates over 71,000,000 people visit the website each month. Unlike most other ecommerce websites, Amazon isn’t actually self-contained. A large number of the products sold through their website are sold by other companies and individuals, making it an incredible opportunity to reach a built-in audience that shops there religiously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Fundamentals &amp; Questions to Answer Before Launching</title>
      <link>/business-fundamentals-questions-to-answer-before-launching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/business-fundamentals-questions-to-answer-before-launching/</guid>
      <description>Business Fundamentals &amp;amp; 36 Questions to Answer Before LaunchingBusiness Fundamentals - Business Strategy - Fundamental Question You Must Ask and Answer to Succeed at Business
You can save yourself mass amounts of time and headaches by establishing your new business upon a solid foundation. This 1-hour beginners course teaches you the 36 questions that are essential for any new business leader to answer before beginning a new venture.
Your business fundamentals instructor, TJ Walker, is a serial entrepreneur who has worked closely with thousands of business leaders to help them create and build their businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAPM  Practice Tests: 3 Real CAPM Exams (UPDATED JULY 2021)</title>
      <link>/capm-practice-tests-3-real-capm-exams-updated-july-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/capm-practice-tests-3-real-capm-exams-updated-july-2021/</guid>
      <description>PMI&#39;s Certified Associate in Project Management (CAPM) is an entry-level certification for project practitioners, designed for those with less experience.
The CAPM Certification tests an individual’s knowledge of the Project Management Body of Knowledge (PMBOK® Guide).
Overview of the CAPM Certification 
The CAPM certification offers recognition to practitioners who are interested in or are just starting a career in project management, as well as project team members who wish to demonstrate their project management knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diversity At Workplace</title>
      <link>/diversity-at-workplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/diversity-at-workplace/</guid>
      <description>Diversity in the workplace is vital for employees because it manifests itself in building a great reputation for the company, leading to increased profitability and opportunities for workers.
Workplace diversity is important within the organization as well as outside.
Diversity in the workplace means that a company’s workforce includes people of varying gender, age, religion, race, ethnicity, cultural background, sexual orientation, religion, languages, education, abilities, etc.
Why is workplace diversity so important?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foreclosure Success for Real Estate Investors by Jay Conner</title>
      <link>/foreclosure-success-for-real-estate-investors-by-jay-conner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/foreclosure-success-for-real-estate-investors-by-jay-conner/</guid>
      <description>Foreclosure is a legal process in which a lender attempts to recover the balance of a loan from a borrower who has stopped making payments to the lender by forcing the sale of the asset used as the collateral for the loan.
It creates a unique opportunity for real estate investors to acquire properties for a steep discount, while helping the owners get out of a tough situation. In this fast paced course based on Jay&#39;s live presentations to a small group of dedicated real estate investors, you will discover:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HVAC Ductwork Quantity Take off for Quantity Surveyors</title>
      <link>/hvac-ductwork-quantity-take-off-for-quantity-surveyors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/hvac-ductwork-quantity-take-off-for-quantity-surveyors/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this course on HVAC Duct Quantity Take off.
HVAC stands for Heating, Cooling, Air Conditioning. It forms a part of MEP Services.
Ducts are used as a medium for transmission of air from the equipment&#39;s to different rooms in a building.
Accurate estimation of DUCT quantities is critical for an effective cost management of a construction project. In this course you will understand how to take off the HVAC duct quantity using different unit of measurements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMP Practice Test Exam 2021-PMBOK6</title>
      <link>/pmp-practice-test-exam-2021-pmbok6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pmp-practice-test-exam-2021-pmbok6/</guid>
      <description>In the Practice Tests for PMP, you&#39;ll be challenged with 560 PMP practice exam questions based on the PMBOK Guide, sixth edition. These question have been collated to emulate the PMP exam and are based on the PMP exam objectives as provided by PMI and are current keeping in mind the current updates to the PMP exam in 2021.
This course has been updated to reflect the new PMP Exam domains</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practice Tests for SHRM-CP and SHRM-SCP Exam Questions(2021)</title>
      <link>/practice-tests-for-shrm-cp-and-shrm-scp-exam-questions2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/practice-tests-for-shrm-cp-and-shrm-scp-exam-questions2021/</guid>
      <description>HR certifications such as the SHRM-CP/SCP® can help you with job advancements and pay raises as well as enhance the chance of new applicants getting a job. They improve the employer&#39;s perception of you and your human resources expertise. Passing an SHRM certification exam will keep your knowledge and skills fresh and give you a boost of confidence as an HR professional.
In addition, The SHRM now shares a partnership with CPHR; hence you will be able to transfer your SHRM certification to gain the CPHR designation if required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Pro Desktop 2021, 2020, 2019, &amp; 2018</title>
      <link>/quickbooks-pro-desktop-2021-2020-2019-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quickbooks-pro-desktop-2021-2020-2019-2018/</guid>
      <description>This comprehensive course will provide an understanding of QuickBooks Pro Desktop 2021, 2020, 2019 &amp;amp; 2018 in a format beneficial to both beginners &amp;amp; advanced users.
We will start at the basics &amp;amp; go far beyond simple data entry, explaining how the software works in a clear step by step format.
We continually update this course, making it a community and recourse you can regularly return to and learn from. Current students will have access to the updates as they are created.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recurring Income Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/recurring-income-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/recurring-income-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’re looking to boost your income, grow a loyal following and position your brand as the go-to source in your market, there is no easier way than by injecting a recurring revenue stream into your business.
With recurring revenue, you can create a strong foundation for your business while taking advantage of the opportunity to incorporate additional income streams into an ever-growing community.
Recurring revenue is consistent and predictable. Unlike other income streams, such as with one-off products or services, with a monthly or yearly recurring revenue platform you know what to expect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Side Hustle Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/side-hustle-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/side-hustle-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Most people have considered working on a side hustle in order to make more money each month, or perhaps save for retirement.

But unfortunately, many of those same people never took action because they weren&#39;t sure how to work on a side hustle while working on other projects, or perhaps they&#39;re still in a 9-5.

The issue is, there&#39;s a lot of confusion about what a side hustle really means.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-Shirt Business Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/t-shirt-business-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/t-shirt-business-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>You can make BIG MONEY selling your T-shirt designs online!
The T-Shirt Business Course For EVERY Level
This course is your fast track to T-Shirt Business success and will provide long-lasting value from your very first product designed right through to advanced sales and marketing campaigns. This course is your fast track to T-Shirt Business success and will provide long-lasting value from your very first product designed right through to advanced sales and marketing campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 PMP Mock Practice Tests</title>
      <link>/2021-pmp-mock-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021-pmp-mock-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>These mock tests are specially created to assist PMP® aspirants to get familiar with the new 2021 PMP® Exam format and test their understanding of the PMP® Exam syllabus.
After taking these prep tests, you will get a clear idea about your readiness for the real exam and you will be able to identify and focus on your weakness points. This preparation course includes a sum of 380 questions to make sure you’ll be able to face all possibilities and scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>B2B Lead Generation via Personalised Sales Videos &amp; LinkedIn</title>
      <link>/b2b-lead-generation-via-personalised-sales-videos-linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/b2b-lead-generation-via-personalised-sales-videos-linkedin/</guid>
      <description>Imagine if your B2B lead generation tactics were 20x MORE EFFECTIVE than they are now.
This course can help make it happen…
Wonder Leads is an innovative new approach to business development. It centres on individually personalised sales videos delivered through LinkedIn, where it’s proved to be almost 20x more effective than cold calling at generating warm leads.
Based on the Axiom award-winning sales book (previous winners include Seth Godin, Tony Robbins &amp;amp; Peter Drucker), entrepreneur and champion for positive communication Dave Holloway reveals a step-by-step approach to effective social selling that anyone can follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Culture</title>
      <link>/business-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/business-culture/</guid>
      <description>About The Course
In a world of ever-lowering employee engagement levels, ever-reducing staff retention levels and ever-increasing levels of staff turnover, combined with higher levels of employee expectations, the need for a culture that creates, supports and enables committed, motivated and effective people has never been so crucial.
This course takes you through proven processes to establish and embed the culture you want to live and the behaviours you want to see from your people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming A Sales Professional</title>
      <link>/becoming-a-sales-professional/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/becoming-a-sales-professional/</guid>
      <description>By caring about building relationships with potential customers and taking an interest in their world, it can significantly improve the odds of securing a sale and retaining that customer for the long-term.
Strategic friendships will make or break any business, no matter how big and no matter what kind of market.
So, in this course, our learning points will include:
Discover the benefits of developing a support network of connections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freelancing: 37 Ways to Make Money From Home as a Freelancer</title>
      <link>/freelancing-37-ways-to-make-money-from-home-as-a-freelancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/freelancing-37-ways-to-make-money-from-home-as-a-freelancer/</guid>
      <description>Do you wanna have the FREEDOM to work at your own schedule?
Do you wanna have the FREEDOM to work anywhere you want?
Do you wanna have the FREEDOM of your life?
Then this is the right course for you.
You&#39;re gonna learn 37 Ways to Make Money From Home as a Freelancer.
But actually, you don&#39;t even need to be at home. You can be anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming A Recruitment And Selection Specialist</title>
      <link>/becoming-a-recruitment-and-selection-specialist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/becoming-a-recruitment-and-selection-specialist/</guid>
      <description>A good recruitment process can reduce the time involved in searching, interviewing, recruiting, and training. It can streamline these procedures and make your search more efficient for viable candidates.
Remember, top talent will not always find you.
You must seek out people to fill the positions that you have open. So, in this course, we&#39;ll learn together, the following:
Defining recruitment
Understanding the selection process
Recognising the GROW model
Interview and question process</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contracts Management in Construction Projects</title>
      <link>/contracts-management-in-construction-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contracts-management-in-construction-projects/</guid>
      <description>Every construction project is bound by a Contract. Proper Contract Management plays a major role in the effective management of your construction projects. Adhering to all the Contractual obligations, the terms and conditions can save both cost and time. There are a few standard Contract Forms that is followed in a Construction project mainly FIDIC (International Federation of Consulting Engineers), NRM (New Rules of Measurement), JCT (The Joint Contracts Tribunal). The procedures to commence work, the documents required at each stage of the project, variation procedures, payment terms, basis for termination and suspension of works by either parties, completion of work, roles and responsibilities of all the stake holders and their staffs, dispute resolution methods, Arbitration procedures etc are all mentioned in the contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Course: Learn to Make Money Online WORLDWIDE!</title>
      <link>/cryptocurrency-course-learn-to-make-money-online-worldwide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cryptocurrency-course-learn-to-make-money-online-worldwide/</guid>
      <description>Last years have been HUGE for cryptocurrencies. Many millionaires were made all over the world. Technologies went forward and new innovations were created. On the other hand, many people lost money because they didn&#39;t know what they were doing. They threw money here and there because other people were doing so.
If you want to make money with cryptocurrencies you need to learn important action steps that I teach you in this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Level PMP Mock Questions</title>
      <link>/advanced-level-pmp-mock-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/advanced-level-pmp-mock-questions/</guid>
      <description>2021 Advanced PMP Exam Simulator: Boost your confidence and proficiency before taking the PMP certification exam.

This course offers a simulation of the updated 2021 PMP exam, providing 180 highly realistic mock questions to help you test your understanding of project management knowledge areas &amp;amp; approaches.

These practice tests were created to prepare you for the real PMP Exam, identifying any knowledge gaps and clearing any hard-to-understand concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management Essential Training</title>
      <link>/project-management-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project-management-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>Project management is a start-to-finish approach to getting things done and making projects more successful. It&#39;s a profession, but it&#39;s also a set of techniques that anyone can apply to achieve goals and manage project work more effectively. Project management can be used to guide small, simple projects as well as complex enterprise-wide initiatives.
In this course you&#39;ll be fascinated by how things work and how to make things work better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Confluence Masterclass for Project Managers</title>
      <link>/atlassian-confluence-masterclass-for-project-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/atlassian-confluence-masterclass-for-project-managers/</guid>
      <description>Confluence is a powerful enterprise collaboration tool that brings people, knowledge, and ideas together in a shared workspace, so you can do your best work. Through this course &#34;Atlassian Confluence Masterclass&#34;, you will learn how to use Confluence to transform the way your team works.
This course is structured to guide you through all the key aspects of managing and using Confluence.
Whether you’re new to Confluence, training your teammates, or ready to take your Confluence skills to the next level, this guide covers everything from the basics to in-depth best practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/blockchain-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blockchain-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve not tried using Blockchain and invest the next generation currency, then today is the time to start!

Never before has there been an technology platform of this magnitude that will allow you to reach an audience of billions and rapidly grow your business online at next to zero cost!

Become The Ultimate Blockchain Master and join this course today to learn the same PROVEN success strategy Henry Zhang , the Crypto Currency expert and world-leading trader used to build this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold Email Writing: Cold Emailing Cold Email Lead Generation</title>
      <link>/cold-email-writing-cold-emailing-cold-email-lead-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cold-email-writing-cold-emailing-cold-email-lead-generation/</guid>
      <description>Master high-performing cold emails and email marketing!
I’m going to teach you…
How I secured a meeting with the CEO and executive team of a $30 million business off just one single automated cold email template
How achieve open rates over 50% and boost your clicks and responses
How to change people’s minds using certain copywriting words
The six big tips for writing effective, persuasive cold emails
The BEST copywriting frameworks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/content-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/content-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Content marketing is currently one of the biggest trends in digital marketing as a whole and is an area that many website owners and brands are investing in heavily right now thanks to the impressive returns that they are seeing.
But content marketing is a complex and broad term that encompasses a number of different strategies and activities.
In order for it to be successful, you need to have a good understanding of what it is, how it works and how you can best adapt it to work for your particular brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digitale Produkte erfolgreich verkaufen mit Digistore 24</title>
      <link>/digitale-produkte-erfolgreich-verkaufen-mit-digistore-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/digitale-produkte-erfolgreich-verkaufen-mit-digistore-24/</guid>
      <description>Ich kann mich noch gut daran erinnern wie es war, meine ersten Online Produkte zu verkaufen.
Damals habe ich versucht, mit höherwertigen Kursen und Coachings Geld zu verdienen.
Allerdings hab ich damit gekämpft, ständig Rechnungen zu schreiben und den Überblick zu behalten.

So etwas frustriert und überfordert einen auf Dauer, und mir ging es genauso.
Dann ist etwas ziemlich Blödes passiert: Als ich mich nicht mehr um die Rechnungen (und auch Mahnungen) kümmern wollte, sind die Verkäufe natürlich eingebrochen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dropshipping Hurdles Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/dropshipping-hurdles-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dropshipping-hurdles-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>With drop shipping, most of the heavy-lifting has been done for you. In fact, not only is it one of the easiest business formats to get involved in, but it’s also one of the lowest-cost startup solutions you’ll ever find.
With little upfront work involved, you can build your very own ecommerce store within minutes, fully loaded with high-quality products that your customers will love.
This course will help you to ensure a smooth customer experience from start to finish, significantly reduce the number of returns, and make the process easier for both you and your buyers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurship - Ft. Matthew Rolnick of Yaymaker, Groupon</title>
      <link>/entrepreneurship-ft.-matthew-rolnick-of-yaymaker-groupon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/entrepreneurship-ft.-matthew-rolnick-of-yaymaker-groupon/</guid>
      <description>**Update**
This course includes an exclusive interview session with a seasoned business veteran - Matthew Rolnick. Matthew is currently the VP&amp;nbsp;of Sales at Yaymaker, and former Divisional Sales Manager at Groupon. His key accomplishments including generating over 10 million in sales at Groupon.
YouAccel recently had the opportunity to conduct a comprehensive Q&amp;amp;A style interview with Matthew Rolnick. The interview was conducted as part of an initiative to add valuable new content to YouAccel’s line up of Entrepreneurship and Freelancing courses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurship: Sales Training, Techniques and Methods</title>
      <link>/entrepreneurship-sales-training-techniques-and-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/entrepreneurship-sales-training-techniques-and-methods/</guid>
      <description>Entrepreneurship: Sales Training, Techniques and Methods
Have you tried to sell products and only failed, have you taken business in school and yet not able to learn how to get sales. Are you struggling with online sales and getting results?&amp;nbsp;If you answered yes to one or all of those questions then this class is right for you. I&amp;nbsp;created this class to help students just like yourself. Often I&amp;nbsp;am asked how you get all those sales, how is it done what are your secrets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management Consulting Essential Training</title>
      <link>/management-consulting-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/management-consulting-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>**Updated for 2021!**
Imagine you could learn the techniques taught by the world’s top consulting firms such as McKinsey and BCG without ever working at a firm! What if you could put yourself in a position to earn a six-figure salary, not to mention maximize the efficiency of any business interests you have, all from the comfort of your own home?
Management consulting involves identifying and suggesting important changes to what a company does and how they do it—developing a working strategic plan and guiding its execution with optimum effectiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management Consulting Skills Mastery</title>
      <link>/management-consulting-skills-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/management-consulting-skills-mastery/</guid>
      <description>**Updated for 2021!**
The most complete course available on management consultant. 8+hours of videos, activities, templates, case studies, articles and more.
Everything you need to know about management consulting tools and techniques from problem solving to presentation skills, from corporate strategic analysis to financial analysis.
Learn management consulting skills step-by-step. Real life consulting projects, business cases, and templates included. Learn by doing!
Management consulting involves identifying and suggesting important changes to what a company does and how they do it—developing a working strategic plan and guiding its execution with optimum effectiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing Strategies Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/pricing-strategies-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pricing-strategies-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Your price structure plays an important role in your ability to convert a prospect into a loyal customer, but assigning value to your offer goes well beyond that. Positioning your business so that it is geared towards a tight market is equally important.
Doing this will help you better tailor your offers so they meet market expectations, but it will make it easier for you to create a powerful marketing message that sets you apart from the competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopify Bootcamp: Increase Your Sales and Conversion rate</title>
      <link>/shopify-bootcamp-increase-your-sales-and-conversion-rate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/shopify-bootcamp-increase-your-sales-and-conversion-rate/</guid>
      <description>​Learning how to work with Shopify is not always easy and can sometimes be very complicated espescially if you never worked with this program before. This is why this course have been created and is here to help you achieve your goals and teach you everything you need to know in order to increase your conversion rate on shopify. If you:
- Have just started out with shopify and don&#39;t know what app to use</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopify Guide: Start your own clothing brand with Shopify</title>
      <link>/shopify-guide-start-your-own-clothing-brand-with-shopify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/shopify-guide-start-your-own-clothing-brand-with-shopify/</guid>
      <description>Starting out your first online business is not always easy especially if you have no knowledge about this topic. If you also want your business to be in the clothing industry it&#39;s even more complicated. Indeed, this is why this is why this course have been designed and this is exactly what you need to stat out in the business world online. If you:
- Are interested by the clothing industry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopify guide: The complete shopify store creation course</title>
      <link>/shopify-guide-the-complete-shopify-store-creation-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/shopify-guide-the-complete-shopify-store-creation-course/</guid>
      <description>Launching your first business is definitely not an easy task, especially if you are launching an online business and you have no prior knowledge about this topic. Also, learning by yourself without a course is not always an easy task because it&#39;s not always easy to filter good information from bad information online. This is why this course have been created. Indeed, this course will teach you all the basics of starting an online store to sell different products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systems Thinking: Enterprise Wide Change Fundamentals</title>
      <link>/systems-thinking-enterprise-wide-change-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/systems-thinking-enterprise-wide-change-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Systems Thinking: Enterprise Wide Change Fundamentals Course is a comprehensive video course where you can learn all about the fundamental knowledge about Systems Thinking that are essential in conducting changes in business.

I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on System Thinking as well as how to apply it in the business world. Learning Systems Thinking allows you to have solid understanding of how corporations work and allows you to effectively deploy enterprise wide changes in a strategic manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talento Humano 3.0 analizando lo nuevo de recursos humanos</title>
      <link>/talento-humano-3.0-analizando-lo-nuevo-de-recursos-humanos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talento-humano-3.0-analizando-lo-nuevo-de-recursos-humanos/</guid>
      <description>Las ciencias administrativas han desarrollado importantes investigaciones sobre los individuos y grupos en las organizaciones, que quizás pareciera un tema nuevo. Por tanto, al referirse al Talento Humano se hace mención a ese recurso importante desde una concepción más actualizada considerando los cambios y avances en la sociedad del siglo XXI, con matices más específicos dentro de una organización social. Como resultado, se han presentado diversas posiciones y conceptos, en relación a ese individuo con características muy concretas y complejas que interactúa en una organización bien sea pública, privada, pequeña mediana o gran empresa, pero que algunos gerentes parecieran no valorar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete eBay Dropshipping University</title>
      <link>/the-complete-ebay-dropshipping-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/the-complete-ebay-dropshipping-university/</guid>
      <description>Akın Yılmaz is Founde r&amp;amp; Ceo of OKYANUSI. After coming UK, he had nothing but books, so he decided to sell them and now he is running with his e-commerce empire. Akin Yilmaz also helps his customers to grow their business with a team of 50 people on digitalmarketing. com. At the same time, Akın Yılmaz’s helping young people to grow their own businesses by telling his experiences and stories to more than 10000 students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valutazione delle Prestazioni</title>
      <link>/valutazione-delle-prestazioni/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/valutazione-delle-prestazioni/</guid>
      <description>Lavori in un’Azienda e vuoi saperne di più sulla Valutazione?
Lavori presso le Risorse Umane (HR) e vuoi approfondire una tua competenza tecnica?
Vuoi sapere cos’è nel dettaglio il Sistema della Valutazione delle Prestazioni?? Qual è il suo scopo?? Le modalità di attuazione dalla sua iniziale fase di progettazione??

Bene!! Sei nel posto giusto…anzi…nell’aula virtuale giusta.
In questo corso ti parlerò di tutte le fasi della Valutazione delle Prestazioni, di chi sono gli Attori interessati e coinvolti, della differenza tra i diversi modelli da usare, delle variabili da tenere sempre in considerazione quando si ha a che fare con il capitale umano (non siamo dei Robot e tutto va adattato e modellato in base a determinati fattori) motivo per cui è importantissimo iniziare con un’ottima progettazione dettagliata della comunicazione del Sistema nonché verificare la situazione attuale dell’impresa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management Consulting Presentation Essential Training</title>
      <link>/management-consulting-presentation-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/management-consulting-presentation-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>In today&#39;s job market, you are only as good as your presentation skills. As the competition for high-level consulting and management positions becomes increasingly cutthroat, you need a powerful way to make your message stand out from the rest.
My name is John Burress and I&#39;m excited to introduce you to the McKinsey presentation system. During my time as a corporate strategist, I&#39;ve used McKinsey presentations to significantly grow many leading businesses using the same techniques you&#39;ll learn under my instruction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partnership Accounting</title>
      <link>/partnership-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/partnership-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Partnership accounting will cover accounting topics related to a partnership form of business entity.
This partnership course will focus on the accounting issues that are different in a partnership as compared to other types of entities like a sole proprietorship or corporations. As we focus on the differences, we always want to keep in mind the similarities in accounting for different business entities. Most of what we have learned about the double entry accounting system and day to day accounting transactions in prior courses will remain the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Pro-Business &amp; Personal-One QuickBooks File</title>
      <link>/quickbooks-pro-business-personal-one-quickbooks-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quickbooks-pro-business-personal-one-quickbooks-file/</guid>
      <description>Both business and personal financial, bookkeeping, and tax information in one QuickBooks file using class tracking. 
This course will demonstrate how to use the class tracking feature in QuickBooks Pro Desktop 2019, applying the feature to tracking both business and personal financial information in one QuickBooks file. 
Note that tracking both business and personal data in one QuickBooks file will not be the best option for many businesses but is a good option for small businesses who want one location to track and analyze financial data and generate financial reports that can be used for tax preparation, budgeting, and business planning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Intelligence using Tableau</title>
      <link>/business-intelligence-using-tableau/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/business-intelligence-using-tableau/</guid>
      <description>This course focuses on how business intelligence in Tableau uses business analytics tools that make it easy to combine data from multiple sources, analyze and visualize information. It helps trainees in making more informed and better decisions to guide the business. After the completion of the course trainee will be through with all the concepts of business intelligence and Tableau.
The objective of this course is to assist the folks in running a business strategically.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
