<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 10:00:22 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HVAC Ductwork Quantity Take off for Quantity Surveyors</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/hvac-ductwork-quantity-take-off-for-quantity-surveyors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 10:00:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/hvac-ductwork-quantity-take-off-for-quantity-surveyors/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this course on HVAC Duct Quantity Take off.
HVAC stands for Heating, Cooling, Air Conditioning. It forms a part of MEP Services.
Ducts are used as a medium for transmission of air from the equipment&#39;s to different rooms in a building.
Accurate estimation of DUCT quantities is critical for an effective cost management of a construction project. In this course you will understand how to take off the HVAC duct quantity using different unit of measurements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Project Management: Agile, Scrum, Kanban &amp; XP</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/agile-project-management-agile-scrum-kanban-xp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/agile-project-management-agile-scrum-kanban-xp/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Course on Agile Project Management!
Software industry is going crazy on agile methods. It is rapidly becoming the choice for software development where requirements are unpredictable or is expected to change over time. This course will help you explore how working on an Agile project has benefits for your development team, your end users, and your organization as a whole.
Here is a list of the topics we will cover in this course:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazo Quickstart: Amazing No-Risk No-Capital Amazon Selling</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/amazo-quickstart-amazing-no-risk-no-capital-amazon-selling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/amazo-quickstart-amazing-no-risk-no-capital-amazon-selling/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s Amazing...
Everyone dreams of selling products on the world biggest eCommerce platform: Amazon. Especially when they discover that even a common everyday potato peeler can sell 1,746 units and bring in over $17,373 a month... each and every month! In fact, the same is true for millions of physical products. Yet thousands of sellers are failing miserably on Amazon every day... Why? Amazo-Quickstart teaches how to create multiple streams of income through this amazing selling machine we call Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contracts Management in Construction Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/contracts-management-in-construction-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/contracts-management-in-construction-projects/</guid>
      <description>Every construction project is bound by a Contract. Proper Contract Management plays a major role in the effective management of your construction projects. Adhering to all the Contractual obligations, the terms and conditions can save both cost and time. There are a few standard Contract Forms that is followed in a Construction project mainly FIDIC (International Federation of Consulting Engineers), NRM (New Rules of Measurement), JCT (The Joint Contracts Tribunal). The procedures to commence work, the documents required at each stage of the project, variation procedures, payment terms, basis for termination and suspension of works by either parties, completion of work, roles and responsibilities of all the stake holders and their staffs, dispute resolution methods, Arbitration procedures etc are all mentioned in the contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foreclosure Success for Real Estate Investors by Jay Conner</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/foreclosure-success-for-real-estate-investors-by-jay-conner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/foreclosure-success-for-real-estate-investors-by-jay-conner/</guid>
      <description>Foreclosure is a legal process in which a lender attempts to recover the balance of a loan from a borrower who has stopped making payments to the lender by forcing the sale of the asset used as the collateral for the loan.
It creates a unique opportunity for real estate investors to acquire properties for a steep discount, while helping the owners get out of a tough situation. In this fast paced course based on Jay&#39;s live presentations to a small group of dedicated real estate investors, you will discover:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence Expert Course: Platinum Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/artificial-intelligence-expert-course-platinum-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/artificial-intelligence-expert-course-platinum-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the first course in Term 2 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Artificial Intelligence Expert Course: Platinum Edition
Artificial Intelligence (AI) seems to be a unique technology of making a machine, a robot fully autonomous. AI is an analysis of how the machine is thinking, studying, determining, and functioning when it is trying to solve problems.
These kinds of problems are present in all fields, the most emerging ones, and even beyond.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming A Recruitment And Selection Specialist</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/becoming-a-recruitment-and-selection-specialist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/becoming-a-recruitment-and-selection-specialist/</guid>
      <description>A good recruitment process can reduce the time involved in searching, interviewing, recruiting, and training. It can streamline these procedures and make your search more efficient for viable candidates.
Remember, top talent will not always find you.
You must seek out people to fill the positions that you have open. So, in this course, we&#39;ll learn together, the following:
Defining recruitment
Understanding the selection process
Recognising the GROW model
Interview and question process</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google BigQuery &amp; PostgreSQL : Big Query for Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/google-bigquery-postgresql-big-query-for-data-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/google-bigquery-postgresql-big-query-for-data-analysis/</guid>
      <description>6 Reasons why you should choose this PostgreSQL and BigQuery course
Carefully designed curriculum teaching you everything in SQL and Google BigQuery that you will need for Data analysis in businesses
Comprehensive - covers basic and advanced SQL statements in both PostgreSQL and Google BigQuery
Business related examples and case studies on SQL and Google BigQuery
Ample practice exercises on Google BigQuery because SQL and Google BigQuery require practice
Downloadable resources on SQL and Google BigQuery</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Business – Work from Home</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/online-business-work-from-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/online-business-work-from-home/</guid>
      <description>This course gives learners the tools to create an online business, taking their current skills, and applying them to a structured business model.
There is a lot of useful information about building an online business, but much of the information is provided by professional marketers, making it difficult for many individuals to see how to apply their skills, their industry expertise, to an online business.
This course is not taught by a marketing professional.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SEO for Wordpress: Our Real Beginner&#39;s Google Success Guide</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/seo-for-wordpress-our-real-beginners-google-success-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 21:18:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/seo-for-wordpress-our-real-beginners-google-success-guide/</guid>
      <description>What this Course is All About
When it comes to getting to number 1 on Google you can search everywhere and you’ll always find the same thing, Jargon filled marketers telling you just how difficult it is to stay up to the trends on Google’s latest “algorithm changes” at which point you ask yourself what the hell an algorithm is and forget the whole process. These people want you to get in touch with them, but you don’t need to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Steps Into Selling Smarter</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/first-steps-into-selling-smarter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 09:38:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/first-steps-into-selling-smarter/</guid>
      <description>Broadly defined, today’s top salespeople are in the business of identifying needs and persuading potential customers to respond favorably to an idea that will result in mutual satisfaction for both the buyer and the seller.
So with this course, you will become a skilled salesperson, skilled at networking and learn the 80/20 rule. After today, you will know who to target and how to target them, and remember to do some prospecting every day through warming up cold calls, following up on leads, or networking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Modern Marketing Analytics with Oribi</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-modern-marketing-analytics-with-oribi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:35:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-modern-marketing-analytics-with-oribi/</guid>
      <description>Getting lost in endless piles of data? Wondering where your visitors are coming from? Looking for a way to turn your data into action?

Well... this might be just the course for you!

Welcome to Modern Marketing Analytics with Oribi, your comprehensive guide to using marketing analytics in the data-abundant world of today. In this course, you will become familiar with what marketing analytics are, how they can be measured effectively, and the implications they can have on your business&#39;s success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management Consulting Essential Training</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/management-consulting-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:35:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/management-consulting-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>**Updated for 2021!**
Imagine you could learn the techniques taught by the world’s top consulting firms such as McKinsey and BCG without ever working at a firm! What if you could put yourself in a position to earn a six-figure salary, not to mention maximize the efficiency of any business interests you have, all from the comfort of your own home?
Management consulting involves identifying and suggesting important changes to what a company does and how they do it—developing a working strategic plan and guiding its execution with optimum effectiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing And Working In Virtual And Hybrid Teams</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/managing-and-working-in-virtual-and-hybrid-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:35:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/managing-and-working-in-virtual-and-hybrid-teams/</guid>
      <description>Overview
Are you struggling to engage your virtual team or clients? This course is designed for anyone who needs to communicate virtually to influence – from virtual team leaders and remote team members to small business owners and entrepreneurs. When you can no longer meet colleagues, connections and customers face to face, a new suite of skills is required.
Who Is This Course For?
This course is designed for anyone who needs to communicate virtually to influence – from virtual team leaders and remote team members to small business owners and entrepreneurs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotfire Interview Tech Questions Answered with Explanation</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/spotfire-interview-tech-questions-answered-with-explanation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:35:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/spotfire-interview-tech-questions-answered-with-explanation/</guid>
      <description>Get that dream Business Intelligence Job in Spotfire..!
Welcome to this course on Spotfire Technical interview Questions and Answers where you are going to excel the Spotfire Technical job interview. Take the course, learn the material and go into interview with a confidence that you are prepared!
This course will take your knowledge in Spotfire to a different level, making you 100% prepared for the Technical Round. The Questions here are the actual questions being asked in Interviews and a Detail explanation is given for each, so you just not know, but understand the whole concept, making you well prepared for any Interview.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diversity At Workplace</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/diversity-at-workplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 11:41:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/diversity-at-workplace/</guid>
      <description>Diversity in the workplace is vital for employees because it manifests itself in building a great reputation for the company, leading to increased profitability and opportunities for workers.
Workplace diversity is important within the organization as well as outside.
Diversity in the workplace means that a company’s workforce includes people of varying gender, age, religion, race, ethnicity, cultural background, sexual orientation, religion, languages, education, abilities, etc.
Why is workplace diversity so important?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Printable Business Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/printable-business-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 11:41:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/printable-business-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’re looking for a profitable side hustle that could easily turn into a full-time income, selling printables online is one of the easiest ways to get started.
Printables are in demand across all markets. People use them to funnel traffic to blogs, content pages, squeeze pages and even as training components.
Printables sell a dream of a better life: they represent organized, creative and successful people.
They’re designed to help people improve the quality of their lives in some way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conflict Resolution and De-Escalation for Upset Customers</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/conflict-resolution-and-de-escalation-for-upset-customers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/conflict-resolution-and-de-escalation-for-upset-customers/</guid>
      <description>CLIENT MANAGEMENT IS CONFLICT MANAGEMENT
Client management is not an easy position. In fact, any relationship management position is tough.
Namely, because clients are frequently angry or disappointed at your company.
And whose job is it to fix the mess? Yours.
Not to mention that you have to both make the company AND the client satisfied.
All in all, it&#39;s not a very easy position.
What most professionals underestimate, however, is the role of conflict management in client management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conflict Resolution and De-Escalation Skills</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/conflict-resolution-and-de-escalation-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/conflict-resolution-and-de-escalation-skills/</guid>
      <description>MULTIPLE CONFLICTS, ONE SINGLE CONFLICT
Conflict is something present in our lives.
Conflicts may occur big and small, in our personal or professional lives, and for multiple reasons.
But despite these reasons, one thing is true - and a constant.
Knowing how to solve conflicts is crucial.
This is what we will explore in this course.


WHY THIS COURSE?
Naturally, you will find multiple courses on social skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete eBay Dropshipping University</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-ebay-dropshipping-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-ebay-dropshipping-university/</guid>
      <description>Akın Yılmaz is Founde r&amp;amp; Ceo of OKYANUSI. After coming UK, he had nothing but books, so he decided to sell them and now he is running with his e-commerce empire. Akin Yilmaz also helps his customers to grow their business with a team of 50 people on digitalmarketing. com. At the same time, Akın Yılmaz’s helping young people to grow their own businesses by telling his experiences and stories to more than 10000 students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Persuasion Psychology - Persuasion and Influence</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ultimate-persuasion-psychology-persuasion-and-influence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ultimate-persuasion-psychology-persuasion-and-influence/</guid>
      <description>LIKE ALL OTHER COURSES. UNLIKE ANY OTHER COURSE
Learn 56 state-of-the-art elite persuasion and influence techniques from my 5 years of influence and performance coaching for top executives in all different types of sales situations. I&#39;m a 2x MIT-backed entrepreneur turned persuasion psychology/negotiation skills coach who has worked with (and made better negotiators of) different profiles, and this course is for you if you&#39;re seeking to improve your influencing, for professional selling or just know more about how to win friends and influence people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SUPPLY CHAIN SKILLS : Logistics Optimization Tools</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/supply-chain-skills-logistics-optimization-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/supply-chain-skills-logistics-optimization-tools/</guid>
      <description>Bienvenue dans ce cours qui vous permettra d’économiser des milliers de dollars chaque mois en appliquant certains outils appelés : Les outils d’optimisation logistique.

Mon nom est Hamza et je serai votre formateur.

Ceci est un cours d’introduction et d’analyse des différents outils logistiques afin de prendre les meilleures décisions dans les bons moments.
Ce cours est assez riche en information théorique et technique, c’est le fruit de 4 ans de recherche et d’apprentissage approfondi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Stories for Agile Scrum&#43;Product Owner&#43;Business Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/user-stories-for-agile-scrum-product-owner-business-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/user-stories-for-agile-scrum-product-owner-business-analysis/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Scrum Open, Professional Scrum™, Professional Scrum Master™, PSM, PSM I, PSM 1, etc. is the protected brand of Scrum . org. Our course and practice exams are neither endorsed by nor affiliated with Scrum . org.&#34;
Three reasons to TAKE THIS COURSE right now!
The unique reasons for taking this course are:
Complete, Concise, Confident Overview of User Stories - I cover all of the theory and give you examples of how the theory is used in industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiring Process: Talent Management</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/hiring-process-talent-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 11:17:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/hiring-process-talent-management/</guid>
      <description>By adopting a structured and comprehensive hiring process, you&#39;re taking the first step in positioning your business for success by attracting the right talent. The type of talent that will help build the company culture, drive sales and ultimately position the company as a leader in the industry.
So in this course we will learn:
Learn how to present the current open position
Develop a workable hiring strategy
Know how to determine which candidates to interview</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Money From Home: 45 Work From Home Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/make-money-from-home-45-work-from-home-opportunities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 11:17:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/make-money-from-home-45-work-from-home-opportunities/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to Make Money From Home?
Do you want to find a flexible Work From Home Job?
Then this is the PERFECT COURSE FOR YOU.
You&#39;re going to see over 45 make money from home opportunities.
I&#39;ve shown steps to make money for 100,000&#39;s people worldwide and every single month around 500,000 people watch my videos on my YouTube channel called &#34;Learn to Make Honest Money Online&#34;.
It will be my privilege to help YOU to make money online too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management: Cost &amp; Schedule Monitoring using EVM</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/project-management-cost-schedule-monitoring-using-evm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 11:17:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/project-management-cost-schedule-monitoring-using-evm/</guid>
      <description>The course will help you understand the basic concepts of Earned Value Management which is one of the most important technique for effective Project Management.
By the end of this course you will learn the key terms of Earned Value Management, their definitions and the various formulas used to analyze whether the project is getting executed on track with respect to cost and schedule.
The course lets you understand the concept of Budget, Planned Value, Earned Value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Production and Inventory Management professional</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-production-and-inventory-management-professional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:50:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-production-and-inventory-management-professional/</guid>
      <description>2021 Production and Inventory Management professional
TOP common and Most Frequent questions with answers for Production and Inventory Management professional

This course will qualify you with the latest and most common questions about Production and Inventory Management

Inventory management refers to the process of ordering, storing and using a company&#39;s inventory. This includes the management of raw materials, components and finished products, as well as warehousing and processing such items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Confluence Masterclass for Project Managers</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/atlassian-confluence-masterclass-for-project-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:50:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/atlassian-confluence-masterclass-for-project-managers/</guid>
      <description>Confluence is a powerful enterprise collaboration tool that brings people, knowledge, and ideas together in a shared workspace, so you can do your best work. Through this course &#34;Atlassian Confluence Masterclass&#34;, you will learn how to use Confluence to transform the way your team works.
This course is structured to guide you through all the key aspects of managing and using Confluence.
Whether you’re new to Confluence, training your teammates, or ready to take your Confluence skills to the next level, this guide covers everything from the basics to in-depth best practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Authority Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/authority-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:50:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/authority-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you want to increase your sales and expand your outreach, you need to position yourself as an authority in your market.
Authority marketing is about positioning your business in a way that you become the logical choice when someone is making the decision who to turn to for help, advice, products or services.
Your goal is to become the go-to person in your niche, or at the very least, one of the first names that come to mind when someone thinks about who to turn to for help with specific topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Course: Learn to Make Money Online WORLDWIDE!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cryptocurrency-course-learn-to-make-money-online-worldwide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:50:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cryptocurrency-course-learn-to-make-money-online-worldwide/</guid>
      <description>Last years have been HUGE for cryptocurrencies. Many millionaires were made all over the world. Technologies went forward and new innovations were created. On the other hand, many people lost money because they didn&#39;t know what they were doing. They threw money here and there because other people were doing so.
If you want to make money with cryptocurrencies you need to learn important action steps that I teach you in this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consulting Business Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/consulting-business-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:47:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/consulting-business-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’re looking to make some fast cash, or you’re interested in building a long-term sustainable business, consulting is one of the most lucrative opportunities available online.
The dictionary defines consultant as: “a person who provides expert advice professionally.”
As a consultant or coach, you’ll be responsible for guiding your students or clients through a learning curve until they’ve accomplished a specific goal.
This is one of those rare businesses where you don’t need a lot of clients to make a full-time income.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Local SEO &amp; Facebook ADS as PROJECT &amp; FUN: 10 Days CHALLENGE</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/local-seo-facebook-ads-as-project-fun-10-days-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:47:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/local-seo-facebook-ads-as-project-fun-10-days-challenge/</guid>
      <description>PLEASE, ACCEPT OUR 10 DAYS CHALLENGE AND LEARN LOCAL SEO, FACEBOOK ADS &amp;amp; CONTENT MARKETING!!! DIGITAL MARKETING SKILLS ARE NOT OPTIONAL ANYMORE AND YOU NEED TO KNOW WHAT TO DO IN ORDER TO AVOID WASTING PRECIOUS TIME, EFFORT, AND MONEY NOW IS THE TIME TO UPSKILL, GROW YOUR REACH, AND BUILD MOMENTUM. IF YOU TAKE TIME NOW TO PUT IN SOME EFFORT, YOU’LL ENJOY HUGE REWARDS LATER, AS THE WORLD MAKES THE SHIFT INTO A MOSTLY DIGITAL ECONOMY!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copywriting &amp; SEO for Beginners: Complete Copywriting Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/copywriting-seo-for-beginners-complete-copywriting-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 10:06:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/copywriting-seo-for-beginners-complete-copywriting-course/</guid>
      <description>WANT YOUR BUSINESS TO GROW WITHOUT INCREASING YOUR MARKETING BUDGET? THEN MAKE SURE YOU PRODUCE SEO FRIENDLY CONTENT. LEARN SEO COPYWRITING AND USE EASY TO ADJUST PROFESSIONAL COPYWRITING TEMPLATES. THIS SEO &amp;amp; COPYWRITING COURSE MAKES LEARNING FUN! ENJOY ANIMATED VIDEOS &amp;amp; INTERACTIVE QUIZZES! BENEFIT FROM OUR EASY TO USE RESOURCES TO MAKE YOUR LIFE EASY!
SEO COPYWRITING MAKES YOUR WEBSITE MORE TRUSTWORTHY AND PROFESSIONAL.
Quality attracts the audience and adds authority to your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Money Online: Mindset Training &#43; Real-Life Examples</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/make-money-online-mindset-training-real-life-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/make-money-online-mindset-training-real-life-examples/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to have an UNSHAKEABLE CONFIDENCE that you WILL make a life-changing income online?
I&#39;ve shown the steps to make money online to 100,000&#39;s of people.
But even though many people know how to make money, very few of them actually take action.
It&#39;s not because they wouldn&#39;t know what to do but because they are AFRAID!
Most people don&#39;t have the right mindset and that&#39;s why they don&#39;t start even though they know step-by-step how to make money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management Consulting Skills Mastery</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/management-consulting-skills-mastery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/management-consulting-skills-mastery/</guid>
      <description>**Updated for 2021!**
The most complete course available on management consultant. 8+hours of videos, activities, templates, case studies, articles and more.
Everything you need to know about management consulting tools and techniques from problem solving to presentation skills, from corporate strategic analysis to financial analysis.
Learn management consulting skills step-by-step. Real life consulting projects, business cases, and templates included. Learn by doing!
Management consulting involves identifying and suggesting important changes to what a company does and how they do it—developing a working strategic plan and guiding its execution with optimum effectiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL Masterclass: SQL for Data Analytics</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sql-masterclass-sql-for-data-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 11:42:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sql-masterclass-sql-for-data-analytics/</guid>
      <description>6 Reasons why you should choose this SQL course
Carefully designed curriculum teaching you everything in SQL that you will need for Data analysis in businesses
Comprehensive - covers basics, advanced SQL statements, PostgreSQL, mySQL, interview tips and performance tuning tips as well
Business related examples and case studies based on SQL techniques, PostgreSQL, mySQL, data analysis techniques
Ample practice exercises because, like any other data analysis tools, SQL requires practice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basics of Venture Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/basics-of-venture-capital/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/basics-of-venture-capital/</guid>
      <description>Venture capital is a type of financing that investors provide to startup companies and small businesses that are believed to have long-term growth potential.

As companies grow, they go through the different stages of venture capital. Additionally, firms or investors may focus specifically on certain stages—which impacts how they invest.

In a number of critical areas, including legal, tax and strategic matters, a VC firm can provide active support, which is all the more important at a key stage in the growth of a young company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business of Logistics - Cargo and inventory management</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/business-of-logistics-cargo-and-inventory-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/business-of-logistics-cargo-and-inventory-management/</guid>
      <description>This course will give you a good understanding of the Business of Logistics and what is the role of it from our daily operational experience. You will learn what is logistics Management, supply chain management, and procurement as well as we will discuss the transportation of cargo processes via Air cargo and Ocean Cargo. Topics like inventory and warehouse management will be covered.
Business of logistics is your guide to develop your logistics skills by knowing what is the role of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurship - Ft. Matthew Rolnick of Yaymaker, Groupon</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/entrepreneurship-ft.-matthew-rolnick-of-yaymaker-groupon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/entrepreneurship-ft.-matthew-rolnick-of-yaymaker-groupon/</guid>
      <description>**Update**
This course includes an exclusive interview session with a seasoned business veteran - Matthew Rolnick. Matthew is currently the VP of Sales at Yaymaker, and former Divisional Sales Manager at Groupon. His key accomplishments including generating over 10 million in sales at Groupon.YouAccel recently had the opportunity to conduct a comprehensive Q&amp;amp;A style interview with Matthew Rolnick. The interview was conducted as part of an initiative to add valuable new content to YouAccel’s line up of Entrepreneurship and Freelancing courses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Budgets – Managerial Accounting/Cost Accounting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/master-budgets-managerial-accounting/cost-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/master-budgets-managerial-accounting/cost-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Master budget construction, including demonstration problems, excel worksheets, practice test questions, discussion questions, and a comprehensive problem we work together using Excel in a step by step format.
The course will provide a managerial accounting overview, comparing managerial accounting and financial accounting, and providing essential managerial accounting tools we will need in the budgeting process.
We will discuss methods of budget timing and the pros and cons of each technique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Persuasive Writing Ft. Two Forbes Contributors &amp; Copywriters</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/persuasive-writing-ft.-two-forbes-contributors-copywriters/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/persuasive-writing-ft.-two-forbes-contributors-copywriters/</guid>
      <description>What has the power to spark revolutions, empower people, express thoughts, emotions, love, hate, and fear, and is only bound by the limits of our imagination? – Words. Words are undoubtedly one of the most powerful tools that mankind possesses. However, mastering the art of articulating thoughts into meaningful written expressions, is no simple undertaking. If done correctly, words can be used as a mechanism of persuasion. Words can be used to further career goals, relationships, business goals, and just about any other facet of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Estate Investment &amp; Finance</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/real-estate-investment-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/real-estate-investment-finance/</guid>
      <description>This course will provide many useful tools for real estate investors and home buyers.
Real estate investing in a complex topic for many reasons. Real estate is a large investment, often requiring a significant part of an and individual’s asset portfolio. Real estate investing often requires financing which increases the complexity. The reason for purchasing real estate varies greatly form person to person, some looking for a long-term home, others looking primarily for an investment, most wanting some mixture of both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopify guide: The complete shopify store creation course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/shopify-guide-the-complete-shopify-store-creation-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/shopify-guide-the-complete-shopify-store-creation-course/</guid>
      <description>Launching your first business is definitely not an easy task, especially if you are launching an online business and you have no prior knowledge about this topic. Also, learning by yourself without a course is not always an easy task because it&#39;s not always easy to filter good information from bad information online. This is why this course have been created. Indeed, this course will teach you all the basics of starting an online store to sell different products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming A Sales Professional</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/becoming-a-sales-professional/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/becoming-a-sales-professional/</guid>
      <description>By caring about building relationships with potential customers and taking an interest in their world, it can significantly improve the odds of securing a sale and retaining that customer for the long-term.
Strategic friendships will make or break any business, no matter how big and no matter what kind of market.
So, in this course, our learning points will include:
Discover the benefits of developing a support network of connections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kickstarter Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/kickstarter-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/kickstarter-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve ever wanted to create something new with a community of enthusiastic people cheering you on, you’ve come to the right place.
This course is based on everything we’ve learned from reviewing over 200,000 projects — each of them created by someone like you. We hope it’ll help you get started with shaping your own project, whether it’s to make a movie, an album, a game, a gadget, a play, a restaurant, or pretty much anything else that springs from the imagination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Money From Home: 12 EASY Options to Make Money Now</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/make-money-from-home-12-easy-options-to-make-money-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/make-money-from-home-12-easy-options-to-make-money-now/</guid>
      <description>If YOU have been looking for easy options to make money from home, this course is the right one for you.
I&#39;ll show you CLICK-BY-CLICK 12 easy ways to make money online.
This will also give YOU confidence that anyone can earn money from home.
Everything in this course is extremely simple and easy-to-follow.
If you are looking for more advanced strategies to make money online, I advise that you take my other Udemy courses where I&#39;ll show you more profitable strategies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sıfırdan PTTAvm Mağaza Açma, Panel ve Satış Eğitimi</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/s%C4%B1f%C4%B1rdan-pttavm-ma%C4%9Faza-a%C3%A7ma-panel-ve-sat%C4%B1%C5%9F-e%C4%9Fitimi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 21:16:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/s%C4%B1f%C4%B1rdan-pttavm-ma%C4%9Faza-a%C3%A7ma-panel-ve-sat%C4%B1%C5%9F-e%C4%9Fitimi/</guid>
      <description>PTTAvm eğitimlerimizde sizlere trendyol ile ilgili tüm detayların olduğu ürün eklemeden sipariş yönetimine, kampanyalardan ödemelere, tüm detayların bulunduğu özellikle ürün ekleme konusundaki püf noktalar, reklam yönetimi gibi bir çok konunun da içerisinde yer aldığı eğitim setimiz şimdiye kadar edinmiş olduğumuz E-Ticaret tecrübelerimizi de içerisine katarak sizler için hazırladık. Verdiğimiz eğitimin temel amaçlarından bir tanesi de DOĞRU E-Ticaret mantığını aktarabilmek. &#34;Bu eğitim setini almamın bana nasıl bir faydası olacak?&#34; diyecek olursanız sizlere aşağıda maddeler halinde sıralıyorum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GET on TOP of Real Estate Business with Facebook Ads in 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/get-on-top-of-real-estate-business-with-facebook-ads-in-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/get-on-top-of-real-estate-business-with-facebook-ads-in-2021/</guid>
      <description>My course will level up your Real Estate Facebook Ads &amp;amp; Facebook Marketing knowledge even if you’ve never used Facebook to conduct Real Estate business before. MASTER REAL ESTATE FACEBOOK MARKETING, DRIVE TRAFFIC TO YOUR WEBSITE, &amp;amp; SELL YOUR PROPERTIES using my successful, tested and proven Facebook Marketing and Facebook Ads techniques! Get POWERFUL Blueprints and walkthroughs for your Real Estate Facebook Ads Strategy that you can start to follow IMMEDIATELY!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Networking for Real Estate Investors For Profits &amp; Funds</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/networking-for-real-estate-investors-for-profits-funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/networking-for-real-estate-investors-for-profits-funds/</guid>
      <description>Jay Conner shares how to Network for success as a real estate investor. At this live event, Jay, and his coaches, teach you powerful strategies for getting in front of your ideal prospect and have them breaking down the doors to fund your deals.
Funding deals are a major problem for real estate investors.
Banks often stop funding your deal with little notice. Hard money can be expensive. Private money is faster, less expensive, and easier to use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming Biggest Challenges to Business Success Fast</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/overcoming-biggest-challenges-to-business-success-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/overcoming-biggest-challenges-to-business-success-fast/</guid>
      <description>Biggest challenges to success...
1) Comfort Zone - No sense of Urgency
 No BURNING Desire
2) Fear - of failure, success, unknown
 Paralysis Analysis
 No Action
3) Lack of Belief in oneself
 Constantly questioning
 Giving up
4) No Plan of Action - No Strategy
 No Consistency
 No Persistence
5) No Coach, guide, mentor
6) Not taking responsibility for your own life.
 Blaming others and other things</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audiobook Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/audiobook-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/audiobook-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>In today&#39;s age of virtual social interaction, the line between personal usage and sales is non-existent.
There are over two million self-published books released every year, and most of those books are sold predominantly online.
Once your book is narrated, perfected, and published, you have to get it out there to listeners.
Just like your digital and print versions, there are specific tactics you can use to generate traffic, reach new listeners, and maximize your profits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HR Analytics using MS Excel for Human Resource Management</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/hr-analytics-using-ms-excel-for-human-resource-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/hr-analytics-using-ms-excel-for-human-resource-management/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re looking for a complete course on understanding HR Analytics using Excel to drive business decisions, right?
You&#39;ve found the right HR Analytics using MS Excel course! HR analytics provides scientific support to decision-making concerning a firm&#39;s human resources. This course on HR analytics addresses the topic of HR analytics with a practical focus, focusing especially on demystifying analytics for Human Resource managers, from both statistical and computing point of view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Membership Site: Membership Recurring Home Business Model</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/membership-site-membership-recurring-home-business-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/membership-site-membership-recurring-home-business-model/</guid>
      <description>Two Certificates for the Price of One! Finish your Udemy course and Contact us to get your Continuing Professional Development (CPD) Certificate!

Why Membership Sites Are Perfect For Passive Income?
If you’re interested in making money online, then it’s probably because you like the idea of having more freedom to live and work wherever and however you want. The benefits of working online are many and varied and extend into every aspect of your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pentaho for ETL &amp; Data Integration Masterclass 2021- PDI 9.0</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pentaho-for-etl-data-integration-masterclass-2021-pdi-9.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pentaho-for-etl-data-integration-masterclass-2021-pdi-9.0/</guid>
      <description>What is ETL?
The ETL (extract, transform, load) process is the most popular method of collecting data from multiple sources and loading it into a centralized data warehouse. ETL is an essential component of data warehousing and analytics.
Why Pentaho for ETL?
Pentaho has phenomenal ETL, data analysis, metadata management and reporting capabilities. Pentaho is faster than other ETL tools (including Talend). Pentaho has a user-friendly GUI which is easier and takes less time to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Responsibility Accounting &amp; Performance Measurement</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/responsibility-accounting-performance-measurement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:43:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/responsibility-accounting-performance-measurement/</guid>
      <description>Responsibility accounting &amp;amp; performance measures.
We will describe the concept of decentralization, how it applies to businesses, and the pros and cons of a more decentralized organization from a centralized one.
The course will cover general managerial accounting concepts necessary to study responsibility accounting, comparing and contrasting managerial accounting and financial accounting.
We will explain what a responsibility accounting system looks like and the benefits of a responsibility accounting system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogging For Beginners: Start a Blog Discover Passive Income</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/blogging-for-beginners-start-a-blog-discover-passive-income/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/blogging-for-beginners-start-a-blog-discover-passive-income/</guid>
      <description>Two Certificates for the Price of One! Finish your Udemy course and Contact us to get your Continuing Professional Development (CPD) Certificate!

No matter what you end up doing, working online is a marvellous opportunity and a magnificent way to enjoy more freedom and potentially greater earnings.
If you work online, means working from anywhere, that you can set your own pace to work at and that you can determine your salary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified LinkedIn Marketing Professional | CPD Accredited</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/certified-linkedin-marketing-professional-cpd-accredited/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/certified-linkedin-marketing-professional-cpd-accredited/</guid>
      <description>Two LinkedIn Marketing Certificates for the Price of One! Finish your Udemy course and Contact us to get your Continuing Professional Development (CPD) Certificate! Check out &#34;This is How You Earn Your CPD Accrdeited Certificate!&#34; Lecture for more information!

LinkedIn Marketing has become the most popular method for success-hungry marketers to make the most from their promoting efforts. If not given sufficient importance to, it can prove disastrous for your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Associates Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/amazon-associates-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/amazon-associates-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Amazon Affiliate Marketing 2021 - NO Website Needed! is the ONLY guide you’ll ever need for starting your lucrative affiliate marketing career from scratch with ZERO prior experience or skill.
Learn all the inside hacks and proven strategies that will maximize your earning potential from visitors to your website with little or no cost and effort.
Set yourself apart from the competition and make sure your leads convert every time for long-lasting sustainable success and a steady income stream!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Products Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-products-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-products-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve been looking for a fast and easy way to build a profitable online business, look no further than digital products.
Digital products are not only easy to create, but they can be easily replicated and turned into multiple product lines that fuel an unlimited number of sales funnels.
They’re also consistently in demand, easy to deliver, and if you never want to write a line of content yourself, you can affordably outsource everything!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ecommerce Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ecommerce-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ecommerce-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>You’re probably fed on top of the instructions that inform you ways to create immediate earnings on the internet, only to be sent to absurd survey internet sites that pay out pennies hourly.
Thankfully, there really are genuine ways to generate income online that don’t consider time and effort, and often, quite hardly any upfront investment. And that’s what this unique statement is all about.
It’s centered on just one quick income opportunity and you may discover fast and easy way to make money on the internet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Steps Into Public Speaking</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/first-steps-into-public-speaking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/first-steps-into-public-speaking/</guid>
      <description>First Steps into Public Speaking
Do you get nervous when presenting at company meetings?
Do you find it hard to make conversation at gatherings and social events?
Do you lock up in awkward social situations?
If so, this course is just for you!
It’s aimed at anybody who wants to improve their speaking skills in informal or formal situations.
We’ll give you the confidence and the skills to interact with others, and to speak in front of small or large groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instant Affiliate Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/instant-affiliate-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/instant-affiliate-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>You’re probably fed on top of the instructions that inform you ways to create immediate earnings on the internet, only to be sent to absurd survey internet sites that pay out pennies hourly.
Thankfully, there really are genuine ways to generate income online that don’t consider time and effort, and often, quite hardly any upfront investment. And that’s what this unique statement is all about.
It’s centered on just one quick income opportunity and you may discover fast and easy way to make money on the internet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selling on Amazon Complete Course: FBA, FBM, Sponsored Ads</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/selling-on-amazon-complete-course-fba-fbm-sponsored-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 21:40:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/selling-on-amazon-complete-course-fba-fbm-sponsored-ads/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to make the most of selling on Amazon – the world’s largest online marketplace and an unparalleled opportunity for entrepreneurs. Start an Amazon business and boost your income or escape the 9-to-5! You don&#39;t need any prior knowledge of Amazon or any technical skills - if you can use a web browser, you are good to go!!
This course is taught by Trevor Ginn a successful online retailing entrepreneur who runs an Amazon business that sells over $3million/year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create your online course now</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/create-your-online-course-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/create-your-online-course-now/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to Earn Money From Your Knowledge?
Then this is the course for you!
Key Benefits of Building An Online Course:
Having an Online Course to support your business is such a great idea at this time and age. We automate so many things in our business, so doing the same for the knowledge we share is essential to help your business grow and spend your time more intentionally and efficiently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flexible Budgets, Standard Costs, &amp; Variance Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/flexible-budgets-standard-costs-variance-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/flexible-budgets-standard-costs-variance-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Managerial &amp;amp; cost accounting tools
The course will introduce managerial accounting topics that will be used throughout the course, contrasting managerial accounting to financial accounting so that we are in the correct mindset as we move forward.
We will discuss flexible budgets, contrasting flexible budgets with static or fixed budgets, demonstrating the benefits of flexible budgets and how they can be used. We will work example problems related to flexible budgets and provide step by step instructional videos to apply the concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFT for Dummies</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/nft-for-dummies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/nft-for-dummies/</guid>
      <description>Dear students and others interested in Non- Fungible Tokens,

Whereas most NFT courses highlight technological components, our course introduces NFTs from both the IT and financial / legal perspective. It is a how-to user guide that covers trading in the NFT markets, understanding the legal issues involved with NFTs (non - fungible tokens), and the technological solutions that NFT can offer in order to create what is called a DIGITAL ASSET.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Online 2021 &amp; 2020 Start to Finish</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-online-2021-2020-start-to-finish/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-online-2021-2020-start-to-finish/</guid>
      <description>QuickBooks Online 2021 updates are being prepared. The current course community will have access to the updates as we create them.
We will update this course each year at no additional cost, so the course community has access to the latest look and feel of QuickBooks Online and can also look back to see the changes that have been made.
We have received a lot of positive feedback and suggestions for improvements that we will put into place as we update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEST of Google SEO 2021: SEO &amp; Copywriting Made Simple &amp; Fun</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/best-of-google-seo-2021-seo-copywriting-made-simple-fun/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 10:48:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/best-of-google-seo-2021-seo-copywriting-made-simple-fun/</guid>
      <description>2021’s MOST ENJOYABLE SEO &amp;amp; COPYWRITING COURSE!!! THIS SEO COURSE IS FILLED WITH QUIZZES, ANIMATED VIDEOS, ASSIGNMENTS, SCREEN RECORDINGS AND OVER MY SHOULDER EXPLANATIONS!!! WATCH AS I WALK YOU THROUGH EVERYTHING YOU WILL NEED TO KNOW TO BECOME A SEO, AND COPYWRITING PRO IN 2021!!! MAX SEO TRAFFIC &amp;amp; SALES, BOOST SEARCH RANKING, OR LAND YOUR DREAM MARKETING JOB!!!
YOU’LL ACHIEVE SEO MASTERY FAST WITH OUR 3-PART FAST LEARN COURSE STRUCTURE - JOIN 0VER 450,000+ SATISFIED STUDENTS BY ENROLLING AND ENJOY THE EASIEST WAY TO GO FROM BEGINNER TO PRO:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Dropshipping Masterclass: Das NEUE Geschäftsmodell</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-dropshipping-masterclass-das-neue-gesch%C3%A4ftsmodell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 22:18:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digital-dropshipping-masterclass-das-neue-gesch%C3%A4ftsmodell/</guid>
      <description>Du bist unprofitabel mit deinem Dropshipping Shop oder hast noch nicht einmal angefangen? Dann sei einer der ersten und lerne hier das neue Geschäftsmodell Digital Dropshipping !
Keine unseriösen chinesischen Händler, keine Produkteinkaufskosten und auch keine Lieferkosten / langen Lieferzeiten mehr. Ich zeige dir hier Schritt für Schritt wie du dir Rechte an fertigen, digitalen Produkten kaufst, ein profitablen Shopify Shop aufbaust und gezielte Online Werbung schaltest. Das alles machen wir live am PC zusammen und du siehst meine professionellen Produkte, Onlineshops und Werbekampagnen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress Site Super Easy Crash Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/wordpress-site-super-easy-crash-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 21:56:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/wordpress-site-super-easy-crash-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>You don&#39;t need to worry about getting a Paid Domain and Paid Hosting in this course because we are going to learn all things via Local Hosting first which is Free. Once you have understood how to control all the features of WordPress then at the end of tutorial i will show you how you can create a WordPress site on live Hosting using Free Hosting and Domain Method. And then we will also learn how we can transfer our entire locally created site to the newly created live WordPress Site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real Estate Investing: Foreclosures, Flipping Houses Profits</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/real-estate-investing-foreclosures-flipping-houses-profits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 12:19:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/real-estate-investing-foreclosures-flipping-houses-profits/</guid>
      <description>With 15 years experience investing in homes in his small (Pop. 9,768) town of Morehead City, North Carolina, Jay Conner has perfected systems which anyone with persistence, determination and willingness to work can do.
Real estate investing is one of the tried and proven paths to wealth. Ninety percent of millionaires used real estate as at least one of their paths to making their fortune. For the average investor, real estate offers the best way to develop significant wealth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISO 27001:2013 Teleworking</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/iso-270012013-teleworking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/iso-270012013-teleworking/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you&#39;ll learn about the fundamentals of teleworking in the context of ISO 27001:2013. Firstly, we&#39;ll be discussing what teleworking is. Then, its benefits &amp;amp; drawbacks. And, finally, we&#39;ll examine various factors involved in implementing such a system in an organization.
Teleworking is when an employee carries out their job away from the organization&#39;s main premises or office. It can be facilitated through technology, for example, the internet, smartphones, laptops, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ISO 9001 2015 Risk Management</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/iso-9001-2015-risk-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/iso-9001-2015-risk-management/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you&#39;ll learn about the fundamentals of having a risk-based approach. This approach can be adopted during establishing, implementing, and maintaining ISO 9001:2015. Firstly, we&#39;ll be discussing what risk is. Then, we&#39;ll go through how an organization can approach meeting its purpose with risk-based thinking. And, finally, we&#39;ll examine what ISO 9001:2015 says about risk in various subclauses.
Risk is uncertainty about what the outcome of certain events will be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jetpack 1.0: Artificial Intelligence and Automation in HR</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/jetpack-1.0-artificial-intelligence-and-automation-in-hr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/jetpack-1.0-artificial-intelligence-and-automation-in-hr/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the third course in Term 3 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Today, we are seeing an increasing number of applications of AI-based solutions across fields like eCommerce Marketing, Personalised Recommendations, Targeted Marketing, Finance Industry, etc. Artificial Intelligence (AI) seemed to be a distant reality for the HR function, until today. Artificial Intelligence (AI) usage for Human Resources (HR) seemed to be a narrative similar to every support function across organizations across India and the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digistore 24 Provisionen erhöhen mit Cross Device Tracking</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digistore-24-provisionen-erh%C3%B6hen-mit-cross-device-tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 16:04:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digistore-24-provisionen-erh%C3%B6hen-mit-cross-device-tracking/</guid>
      <description>Ich erinnere mich ungern an die Zeit, als ich kaum Affiliates bei Digistore24 hatte.
Damals habe ich verzweifelt versucht, endlich eine zuverlässige &#34;Affiliate-Armee&#34; aufzubauen, um dauerhaft mehr Umsatz zu machen.
Allerdings gab es ein Problem, denn Affiliates können sich nie 100%ig sicher sein, ob das Tracking funktioniert.
Das hat auch mich immer mehr frustriert, denn ich konnte ihnen keine klare Antwort geben.

Am schlimmsten wurde es, als ich tatsächlich nachgewiesen habe, dass das Standard-Tracking nicht richtig funktioniert und deswegen die Affiliates abspringen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn 47 Different Ways to Make Money Online!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-47-different-ways-to-make-money-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 16:04:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-47-different-ways-to-make-money-online/</guid>
      <description>Imagine having the FREEDOM to make money just by using your smartphone or laptop.
That&#39;s what I&#39;ve been doing already for several years and now I have a privilege to help YOU too.
In this course, I&#39;ll show you +47 ways to make money online.
Learn just 1 strategy to make money and you&#39;ll earn your course price back. The rest will be pure profits for you!
Over the course of years, I&#39;ve helped 1,000&#39;s of ordinary people to start their &#39;Make Money Online&#39; journeys and you&#39;ll be the next one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Tech Startup 102 - Managing Human Resources</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-build-a-tech-startup-102-managing-human-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-build-a-tech-startup-102-managing-human-resources/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wanted to build your own technology Startup? But you had no idea where to start? Maybe you are from a software engineering background and have no idea what to do next. No problem!
Course Content
The course is structured as follows:
Basics of Human Resource Management
Why it is important to build teams
How to hire people on a budget
Developing job descriptions, interviewing people How to on-board people and train them</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cadena de suministro y análisis de datos con Excel</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cadena-de-suministro-y-an%C3%A1lisis-de-datos-con-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cadena-de-suministro-y-an%C3%A1lisis-de-datos-con-excel/</guid>
      <description>Existen muchas funciones y herramientas en Excel para analizar y trabajar con la información, algunas de las mas usadas son las siguientes:
Función BuscarV, BuscarH
Función Indice combinado con la funcion coincidir
Función Si, SiError
Funciones de Texto (Extrae, Izquierda, Derecha, Remplazar)
Función Contara, ContarSi, ContarSiConjunto
Función SumarSi, SumarSiConjunto
Funciones matematicas (sumar, restar, promedios, subtotales, redondear, redondear.mas, redondear.menosetc)
Formatos Condicionales
Tablas dinámicas
Creación de diferentes tipos gráficos
Combinación de funciones, tablas y graficas dinámicas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #2 Financial Ratios</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance-#2-financial-ratios/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance-#2-financial-ratios/</guid>
      <description>We will learn how to use ratio analysis to help with decision making from a corporate finance perspective. The financial statements, including the balance sheet and income statement, are the primary tools used for ratio analysis. The financial statements help us understand past performance and where the organization stands at this time. Ratio analysis helps us project future performance and where the organization may stand in the future. This course will demonstrate concepts using many practice problems, including problems using Microsoft Excel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #3 Forecasting &amp; Budgeting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance-#3-forecasting-budgeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance-#3-forecasting-budgeting/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover the concepts of forecasting and budgeting from a finance perspective.
The course includes many example problems, both in presentation form, and many using Excel worksheets. Each Excel worksheet problem will include a downloadable Excel worksheet that has at least two tabs, one having the answer, the second including a preformatted worksheet that can be populated in a step-by-step process along with the instructional video.
To forecast and budget we need to make predictions and projections about the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Marketing</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-marketing/</guid>
      <description>The Storyboard Initiative presents our Introduction to Marketing course, an introductory course that focuses on the basics and essentials of marketing. We cover a wide range of topics relating to marketing, from the marketing mix to color theory, go into the essentials and format of a marketing plan, and cover topics related to digital marketing in the modern world.
 Ratings: 4.01/5
Enrollments: 1552
Coupon Code: A2A3F5E3B0FD785DA0AB
Current Price: FREE</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Business</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 09:03:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-business/</guid>
      <description>This course is designed to teach anyone new to business with the basic understandings of the four fields of business (marketing, business administration/management, finance, and hospitality &amp;amp; tourism). The four sections of this course each pertain to one of the four area. In total this course has eighteen videos that total nearly an hour of covering some of the specifics of each field. We also have included over fifteen pages of in-depth information about distinct topics pertaining to a certain field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Pro Desktop 2021, 2020, 2019, &amp; 2018</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-pro-desktop-2021-2020-2019-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 08:36:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-pro-desktop-2021-2020-2019-2018/</guid>
      <description>This comprehensive course will provide an understanding of QuickBooks Pro Desktop 2021, 2020, 2019 &amp;amp; 2018 in a format beneficial to both beginners &amp;amp; advanced users.
We will start at the basics &amp;amp; go far beyond simple data entry, explaining how the software works in a clear step by step format.
We continually update this course, making it a community and recourse you can regularly return to and learn from. Current students will have access to the updates as they are created.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Individual Income Tax Form 1040 Comprehensive Problem</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/individual-income-tax-form-1040-comprehensive-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/individual-income-tax-form-1040-comprehensive-problem/</guid>
      <description>This is a project based income tax course. We will construct a complex tax return in a step by step format, beginning with a basic return &amp;amp; building complexity as we move forward. The course will demonstrate the data input within 2020 income tax forms as well as the use of an Excel worksheet to check the numbers and demonstrate the use of tax software. Using tax software &amp;amp; an Excel worksheet, formatted as the income tax equation, are common, and best practices for many tax professionals, practices that greatly increase understanding and accuracy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Money In Excel - Income Tax Sch. C &amp; Personal Financials</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/money-in-excel-income-tax-sch.-c-personal-financials/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/money-in-excel-income-tax-sch.-c-personal-financials/</guid>
      <description>Money in Excel is an Excel template provided by Microsoft that has bank connectivity similar to many accounting software applications such a QuickBooks, bank connectivity allowing for the download of financial data directly from the financial institutions.
Money in Excel can be used to construct a small business income statement which could be useful when preparing an income tax return Schedule C Profit or Loss From Business.
The Money in Excel template can also be used to complement accounting software such as QuickBooks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tableau: Empieza desde cero</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tableau-empieza-desde-cero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/tableau-empieza-desde-cero/</guid>
      <description>¡Vuélvete un experto en el Business Intelligence con TableauI!
Si eres un estudiante o profesionista que quiere potenciar su carrera profesional te tengo una buena noticia:
¡Encontraste el curso indicado!

¿Sientes que tu carrera profesional esta estancada?
¿Tu perfil no destaca entre el de los demás?
¿Sientes que en la escuela no aprendiste nada útil para el mundo laboral?
¿Crees que Excel es la única herramienta para analizar datos y hacer gráficas?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Networking for Success and Company Growth: Part One</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/business-networking-for-success-and-company-growth-part-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 10:31:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/business-networking-for-success-and-company-growth-part-one/</guid>
      <description>Networking is both a Science and an Art. In this Networking Series, I’m going to cover the science of networking including the different types of networking groups, the different type of networking formats, and what to look for in networking groups. I’m also going to cover the Art of Networking so you can choose the right groups to spend your precious time at, build long-lasting relationships, and maximize your impact in your ever growing sphere of influence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Plan: Learn It Fast! - Business Planning &amp; Writing</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/business-plan-learn-it-fast-business-planning-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/business-plan-learn-it-fast-business-planning-writing/</guid>
      <description>Business Plan - Quick Start 
If you are looking for a quick jumpstart into writing a comprehensive Business Plan then this course will help you achieve that goal. You can learn how to create a business plan in just one hour!
++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++ 
Let me explain
What makes this course different is that it summarizes all the important element that is necessary to write a great business plan and delivers it to you in a short; 1-hour training program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Money From Home As a Transcriptionist: 10 Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/make-money-from-home-as-a-transcriptionist-10-opportunities/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/make-money-from-home-as-a-transcriptionist-10-opportunities/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to make money from home typing what you hear?
Do you like to make money online with flexible hours wherever you want?
Then this is the PERFECT UDEMY Course for you!
You&#39;re gonna find out the details about Making Money Online with 10 Transcription Jobs From Home and spot the best opportunities for you.
Over the years, I&#39;ve seen dozens of transcription jobs from home and you need to know the differences:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Cultural Management Made Easy</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cross-cultural-management-made-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cross-cultural-management-made-easy/</guid>
      <description>Do you know the cost of failure of cross-cultural awareness and lack of cross-cultural competence? The cost for cultural integration of Upjohn Pharmaceutical Company of USA to integrate the newly acquired company (in 1995), Pharmacia of Sweden was close to 1 Bn $ almost 300 Million $ above expectations. Despite such huge costs the company disintegrated and vanished from the world market within a decade of the merger.
When handled properly world cultural diversity can be converted to the key success factor of a business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Management Consulting Presentation Essential Training</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/management-consulting-presentation-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 17:21:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/management-consulting-presentation-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>In today&#39;s job market, you are only as good as your presentation skills. As the competition for high-level consulting and management positions becomes increasingly cutthroat, you need a powerful way to make your message stand out from the rest.
My name is John Burress and I&#39;m excited to introduce you to the McKinsey presentation system. During my time as a corporate strategist, I&#39;ve used McKinsey presentations to significantly grow many leading businesses using the same techniques you&#39;ll learn under my instruction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startup Marketing 0 to 1 Million Startup Entrepeneur Revenue</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/startup-marketing-0-to-1-million-startup-entrepeneur-revenue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 09:16:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/startup-marketing-0-to-1-million-startup-entrepeneur-revenue/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to grow your startup from the early to mid stages with an 11-year marketing veteran from a family of successful entrepreneurs. Learn the easiest marketing techniques get real results without a lot of budget. This course is for entrepreneurs and marketers selling business OR consumer products/services.
Some of the key learnings in this startup marketing course:
Growth hacking for entrepreneurs Customer acquisition marketing techniques for startups
Including real examples of successful campaigns I ran + other sample case studies</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMMP Exam: Brand Management --&gt;  Practice Test 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cmmp-exam-brand-management-practice-test-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cmmp-exam-brand-management-practice-test-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Exam in BRAND MANAGEMENT ? 
Don’t be stressed, Take our Brand Management Based Mock Test and prepare yourself for the Exam. Here you will get Brand Management based Multiple Choice Question for your Next Exam.
What you will get in These Mock Test ? 
It contains sample questions which are likely to be asked in the Exam.
These Brand Management based MCQ questions help you with self-study and self-assessment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/blockchain-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/blockchain-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve not tried using Blockchain and invest the next generation currency, then today is the time to start!

Never before has there been an technology platform of this magnitude that will allow you to reach an audience of billions and rapidly grow your business online at next to zero cost!

Become The Ultimate Blockchain Master and join this course today to learn the same PROVEN success strategy Henry Zhang , the Crypto Currency expert and world-leading trader used to build this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Content Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/smart-content-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/smart-content-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Even in the age of video, live streaming, and social media, content marketing is still the reigning King when it comes to building successful campaigns that will drive in traffic, and bolster sales and prospect activity. It’s also still the most effective way for both new and seasoned marketers to connect with potential leads, and to build organic traffic funnels from the major search engines.
Successful content marketing requires more effort and thought, and it requires a more complex strategy than ever before, but it’s certainly not difficult to do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopify Bootcamp: Increase Your Sales and Conversion rate</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/shopify-bootcamp-increase-your-sales-and-conversion-rate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/shopify-bootcamp-increase-your-sales-and-conversion-rate/</guid>
      <description>​Learning how to work with Shopify is not always easy and can sometimes be very complicated espescially if you never worked with this program before. This is why this course have been created and is here to help you achieve your goals and teach you everything you need to know in order to increase your conversion rate on shopify. If you:
- Have just started out with shopify and don&#39;t know what app to use</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corp Finance #10 Cost of Capital–Debt &amp; Equity Financing</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/corp-finance-#10-cost-of-capitaldebt-equity-financing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/corp-finance-#10-cost-of-capitaldebt-equity-financing/</guid>
      <description>This course will discusses weighted average cost of capital, debt, and equity financing from a corporate finance perspective.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Project 2019 Course for beginners to advanced</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-project-2019-course-for-beginners-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-project-2019-course-for-beginners-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Our objective is to present you the course in a easiest way, make you feel it is easy to use, easy to grasp, easy to learn and easy to implement in your project management goals.
 This course is developed keeping in considerations about growing requirements and aspirations of students, mid-professionals, young-professionals in learning the project management skills. The planning is pre-requisite before starting any meaningful project nowadays for all kind of industries such as construction, software and manufacturing sectors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2022 Amazon FBA PL Product Hunting &amp; KW Research in One Hour</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/2022-amazon-fba-pl-product-hunting-kw-research-in-one-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:28:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/2022-amazon-fba-pl-product-hunting-kw-research-in-one-hour/</guid>
      <description>Take this Amazon FBA Private Label Product Hunting &amp;amp; Product Research Course to earn a six-figure income on Amazon
Many new sellers don&#39;t even know the potential of choosing a great product or what is the criteria for a great product to launch on Amazon which can generate 6 figure income. In this 60 minutes Amazon FBA private label product hunting or product research course, you will learn step by step,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Shopify Print on Demand Dropshipping With Live Proof</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-shopify-print-on-demand-dropshipping-with-live-proof/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:28:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-shopify-print-on-demand-dropshipping-with-live-proof/</guid>
      <description>Summary:
Follow along with my lectures that show you how to build your own E-Commerce Business from A to Z. I have documented the entire process, from the initial steps, all the way up through to the first sales!

About Your Instructor:
Rio Wick has been in the E-Commerce &amp;amp; Internet Marketing / Affiliate Marketing space for years. With his passion for teaching others, he creates courses on many different topics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Referral System - How To Create A Successful One!</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/referral-system-how-to-create-a-successful-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 11:28:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/referral-system-how-to-create-a-successful-one/</guid>
      <description>This is a no-fluff actionable course on &#34;How To Create A Successful Referral System&#34;. I want to unpack for you the exact system that I&#39;ve used to grow, one of my current businesses. I&#39;m telling you now that it works. If you will take action and follow what you learn on this course if you would create the systems, the way that I will describe it for you in the next half an hour or so then you will be able to grow your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Business Productivity Training Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/best-business-productivity-training-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/best-business-productivity-training-course/</guid>
      <description>In This Online Course You Will Learn About The Major Productivity Challenges Facing Companies Today … These Challenges Can Make Or Break A Businesses. This Amazing Online Training Will Give Your Business Or Career An Unfair Advantage Against The Competition.
In This Productivity Training Course You Will Discover Specific Tools, Strategies And Techniques To Beat These Challenges. By Learning How To Think Like A Top Producer … You Can Make Massive Advances In Your Business Or Career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emprendimiento Productivo</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/emprendimiento-productivo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/emprendimiento-productivo/</guid>
      <description>En un principio, el ser humano entendió que por sí solo no podía obtener mejores recursos y bienes, por lo que decidió aliarse a otros, formando aldeas y comunidades, la antesala de lo que fue evolucionando en las sociedades primitivas y la consecuente división de las tareas, dando lugar a los roles definidos dentro de una sociedad. Miles de años de evolución hacen que el mundo moderno estos emprendimientos sean compañías o empresas que pueden alcanzar inclusive gran escala, teniendo algunas de ellas el rol de empresas multinacionales y transnacionales, contando con bienes millonarios y una gran cantidad de recursos bajo su control, pero todo ello gira en torno al sueño o creatividad de una mente brillante.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Air Logistics Management in Supply Chain Management</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/global-air-logistics-management-in-supply-chain-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/global-air-logistics-management-in-supply-chain-management/</guid>
      <description>This Course will prove to be a boon to you and help you boost your logistics and supply chain management knowledge as it is a specialized course on Aviation Logistics in Supply chain management as Air Logistics Management is very important if your aim is to move your cargo on urgent basis with minimum risk, As in International Trade , Supply chain management &amp;amp; Shipping there are many risks involved.Its a base for inventory Movement and is ideal for Amazon FBA, Drop Shipping, Outsourcing , Retail business owners, Inventory, Logistics and Supply chain management professionals as it is prepared with focus on practical knowledge which you can use in you day to day work as the instructor himself is a Supply Chain and Logistics Management professional managing Shipping, Freight Forwarding, Surface Transport, Aviation Logistics for many exporters and importers and has a professional qualification in then Feild of Logistics Management and Supply Chain Management</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantity Surveying Templates for Effective Cost Management</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quantity-surveying-templates-for-effective-cost-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quantity-surveying-templates-for-effective-cost-management/</guid>
      <description>This course explains the different Quantity Surveying templates created by me for effective post contract cost management.
You can download these templates and use it in your professional life.
By the end of this course, you will learn the below :
Prepare a perfect payment application summary for the interim payment applications.
Able to properly track both the inward and outward payments specific to the project.
Efficiently monitor and update the variations and claims status of the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Leadership Mastery Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-leadership-mastery-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 16:12:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-leadership-mastery-course/</guid>
      <description>The world has changed overnight and every dimension of our life got upended in an unprecedented manner. How we work, how we buy, how we live and how we study have gone through a metamorphosis. Live now revolves around a screen - yet, the world slowly grinds on..However, everything falls and rises on Leadership. Everything grows and shrinks on the efforts of a leader. Business growth, Corporate leadership or personal mastery is a result of concerted choices by a Leader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon FBA Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/amazon-fba-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/amazon-fba-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Make money with the FBA program from the world&#39;s biggest store!
Amazon is the world’s biggest and most popular ecommerce website, and the 8th most popular website in the United States. Millions of people shop the site every day, and Quantcast estimates over 71,000,000 people visit the website each month. Unlike most other ecommerce websites, Amazon isn’t actually self-contained. A large number of the products sold through their website are sold by other companies and individuals, making it an incredible opportunity to reach a built-in audience that shops there religiously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Fundamentals &amp; Questions to Answer Before Launching</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/business-fundamentals-questions-to-answer-before-launching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/business-fundamentals-questions-to-answer-before-launching/</guid>
      <description>Business Fundamentals &amp;amp; 36 Questions to Answer Before LaunchingBusiness Fundamentals - Business Strategy - Fundamental Question You Must Ask and Answer to Succeed at Business
You can save yourself mass amounts of time and headaches by establishing your new business upon a solid foundation. This 1-hour beginners course teaches you the 36 questions that are essential for any new business leader to answer before beginning a new venture.
Your business fundamentals instructor, TJ Walker, is a serial entrepreneur who has worked closely with thousands of business leaders to help them create and build their businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CAPM  Practice Tests: 3 Real CAPM Exams (UPDATED JULY 2021)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/capm-practice-tests-3-real-capm-exams-updated-july-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/capm-practice-tests-3-real-capm-exams-updated-july-2021/</guid>
      <description>PMI&#39;s Certified Associate in Project Management (CAPM) is an entry-level certification for project practitioners, designed for those with less experience.
The CAPM Certification tests an individual’s knowledge of the Project Management Body of Knowledge (PMBOK® Guide).
Overview of the CAPM Certification 
The CAPM certification offers recognition to practitioners who are interested in or are just starting a career in project management, as well as project team members who wish to demonstrate their project management knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PMP Practice Test Exam 2021-PMBOK6</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pmp-practice-test-exam-2021-pmbok6/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pmp-practice-test-exam-2021-pmbok6/</guid>
      <description>In the Practice Tests for PMP, you&#39;ll be challenged with 560 PMP practice exam questions based on the PMBOK Guide, sixth edition. These question have been collated to emulate the PMP exam and are based on the PMP exam objectives as provided by PMI and are current keeping in mind the current updates to the PMP exam in 2021.
This course has been updated to reflect the new PMP Exam domains</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practice Tests for SHRM-CP and SHRM-SCP Exam Questions(2021)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/practice-tests-for-shrm-cp-and-shrm-scp-exam-questions2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/practice-tests-for-shrm-cp-and-shrm-scp-exam-questions2021/</guid>
      <description>HR certifications such as the SHRM-CP/SCP® can help you with job advancements and pay raises as well as enhance the chance of new applicants getting a job. They improve the employer&#39;s perception of you and your human resources expertise. Passing an SHRM certification exam will keep your knowledge and skills fresh and give you a boost of confidence as an HR professional.
In addition, The SHRM now shares a partnership with CPHR; hence you will be able to transfer your SHRM certification to gain the CPHR designation if required.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recurring Income Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/recurring-income-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/recurring-income-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you’re looking to boost your income, grow a loyal following and position your brand as the go-to source in your market, there is no easier way than by injecting a recurring revenue stream into your business.
With recurring revenue, you can create a strong foundation for your business while taking advantage of the opportunity to incorporate additional income streams into an ever-growing community.
Recurring revenue is consistent and predictable. Unlike other income streams, such as with one-off products or services, with a monthly or yearly recurring revenue platform you know what to expect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Side Hustle Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/side-hustle-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/side-hustle-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Most people have considered working on a side hustle in order to make more money each month, or perhaps save for retirement.

But unfortunately, many of those same people never took action because they weren&#39;t sure how to work on a side hustle while working on other projects, or perhaps they&#39;re still in a 9-5.

The issue is, there&#39;s a lot of confusion about what a side hustle really means.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-Shirt Business Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/t-shirt-business-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/t-shirt-business-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>You can make BIG MONEY selling your T-shirt designs online!
The T-Shirt Business Course For EVERY Level
This course is your fast track to T-Shirt Business success and will provide long-lasting value from your very first product designed right through to advanced sales and marketing campaigns. This course is your fast track to T-Shirt Business success and will provide long-lasting value from your very first product designed right through to advanced sales and marketing campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 PMP Mock Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-pmp-mock-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-pmp-mock-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>These mock tests are specially created to assist PMP® aspirants to get familiar with the new 2021 PMP® Exam format and test their understanding of the PMP® Exam syllabus.
After taking these prep tests, you will get a clear idea about your readiness for the real exam and you will be able to identify and focus on your weakness points. This preparation course includes a sum of 380 questions to make sure you’ll be able to face all possibilities and scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>B2B Lead Generation via Personalised Sales Videos &amp; LinkedIn</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/b2b-lead-generation-via-personalised-sales-videos-linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/b2b-lead-generation-via-personalised-sales-videos-linkedin/</guid>
      <description>Imagine if your B2B lead generation tactics were 20x MORE EFFECTIVE than they are now.
This course can help make it happen…
Wonder Leads is an innovative new approach to business development. It centres on individually personalised sales videos delivered through LinkedIn, where it’s proved to be almost 20x more effective than cold calling at generating warm leads.
Based on the Axiom award-winning sales book (previous winners include Seth Godin, Tony Robbins &amp;amp; Peter Drucker), entrepreneur and champion for positive communication Dave Holloway reveals a step-by-step approach to effective social selling that anyone can follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Culture</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/business-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/business-culture/</guid>
      <description>About The Course
In a world of ever-lowering employee engagement levels, ever-reducing staff retention levels and ever-increasing levels of staff turnover, combined with higher levels of employee expectations, the need for a culture that creates, supports and enables committed, motivated and effective people has never been so crucial.
This course takes you through proven processes to establish and embed the culture you want to live and the behaviours you want to see from your people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freelancing: 37 Ways to Make Money From Home as a Freelancer</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/freelancing-37-ways-to-make-money-from-home-as-a-freelancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/freelancing-37-ways-to-make-money-from-home-as-a-freelancer/</guid>
      <description>Do you wanna have the FREEDOM to work at your own schedule?
Do you wanna have the FREEDOM to work anywhere you want?
Do you wanna have the FREEDOM of your life?
Then this is the right course for you.
You&#39;re gonna learn 37 Ways to Make Money From Home as a Freelancer.
But actually, you don&#39;t even need to be at home. You can be anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Level PMP Mock Questions</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/advanced-level-pmp-mock-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/advanced-level-pmp-mock-questions/</guid>
      <description>2021 Advanced PMP Exam Simulator: Boost your confidence and proficiency before taking the PMP certification exam.

This course offers a simulation of the updated 2021 PMP exam, providing 180 highly realistic mock questions to help you test your understanding of project management knowledge areas &amp;amp; approaches.

These practice tests were created to prepare you for the real PMP Exam, identifying any knowledge gaps and clearing any hard-to-understand concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Management Essential Training</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/project-management-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/project-management-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>Project management is a start-to-finish approach to getting things done and making projects more successful. It&#39;s a profession, but it&#39;s also a set of techniques that anyone can apply to achieve goals and manage project work more effectively. Project management can be used to guide small, simple projects as well as complex enterprise-wide initiatives.
In this course you&#39;ll be fascinated by how things work and how to make things work better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold Email Writing: Cold Emailing Cold Email Lead Generation</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cold-email-writing-cold-emailing-cold-email-lead-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cold-email-writing-cold-emailing-cold-email-lead-generation/</guid>
      <description>Master high-performing cold emails and email marketing!
I’m going to teach you…
How I secured a meeting with the CEO and executive team of a $30 million business off just one single automated cold email template
How achieve open rates over 50% and boost your clicks and responses
How to change people’s minds using certain copywriting words
The six big tips for writing effective, persuasive cold emails
The BEST copywriting frameworks</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/content-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/content-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Content marketing is currently one of the biggest trends in digital marketing as a whole and is an area that many website owners and brands are investing in heavily right now thanks to the impressive returns that they are seeing.
But content marketing is a complex and broad term that encompasses a number of different strategies and activities.
In order for it to be successful, you need to have a good understanding of what it is, how it works and how you can best adapt it to work for your particular brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digitale Produkte erfolgreich verkaufen mit Digistore 24</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/digitale-produkte-erfolgreich-verkaufen-mit-digistore-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/digitale-produkte-erfolgreich-verkaufen-mit-digistore-24/</guid>
      <description>Ich kann mich noch gut daran erinnern wie es war, meine ersten Online Produkte zu verkaufen.
Damals habe ich versucht, mit höherwertigen Kursen und Coachings Geld zu verdienen.
Allerdings hab ich damit gekämpft, ständig Rechnungen zu schreiben und den Überblick zu behalten.

So etwas frustriert und überfordert einen auf Dauer, und mir ging es genauso.
Dann ist etwas ziemlich Blödes passiert: Als ich mich nicht mehr um die Rechnungen (und auch Mahnungen) kümmern wollte, sind die Verkäufe natürlich eingebrochen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dropshipping Hurdles Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/dropshipping-hurdles-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/dropshipping-hurdles-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>With drop shipping, most of the heavy-lifting has been done for you. In fact, not only is it one of the easiest business formats to get involved in, but it’s also one of the lowest-cost startup solutions you’ll ever find.
With little upfront work involved, you can build your very own ecommerce store within minutes, fully loaded with high-quality products that your customers will love.
This course will help you to ensure a smooth customer experience from start to finish, significantly reduce the number of returns, and make the process easier for both you and your buyers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurship: Sales Training, Techniques and Methods</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/entrepreneurship-sales-training-techniques-and-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/entrepreneurship-sales-training-techniques-and-methods/</guid>
      <description>Entrepreneurship: Sales Training, Techniques and Methods
Have you tried to sell products and only failed, have you taken business in school and yet not able to learn how to get sales. Are you struggling with online sales and getting results?&amp;nbsp;If you answered yes to one or all of those questions then this class is right for you. I&amp;nbsp;created this class to help students just like yourself. Often I&amp;nbsp;am asked how you get all those sales, how is it done what are your secrets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing Strategies Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pricing-strategies-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pricing-strategies-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Your price structure plays an important role in your ability to convert a prospect into a loyal customer, but assigning value to your offer goes well beyond that. Positioning your business so that it is geared towards a tight market is equally important.
Doing this will help you better tailor your offers so they meet market expectations, but it will make it easier for you to create a powerful marketing message that sets you apart from the competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopify Guide: Start your own clothing brand with Shopify</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/shopify-guide-start-your-own-clothing-brand-with-shopify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/shopify-guide-start-your-own-clothing-brand-with-shopify/</guid>
      <description>Starting out your first online business is not always easy especially if you have no knowledge about this topic. If you also want your business to be in the clothing industry it&#39;s even more complicated. Indeed, this is why this is why this course have been designed and this is exactly what you need to stat out in the business world online. If you:
- Are interested by the clothing industry</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systems Thinking: Enterprise Wide Change Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/systems-thinking-enterprise-wide-change-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/systems-thinking-enterprise-wide-change-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Systems Thinking: Enterprise Wide Change Fundamentals Course is a comprehensive video course where you can learn all about the fundamental knowledge about Systems Thinking that are essential in conducting changes in business.

I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on System Thinking as well as how to apply it in the business world. Learning Systems Thinking allows you to have solid understanding of how corporations work and allows you to effectively deploy enterprise wide changes in a strategic manner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talento Humano 3.0 analizando lo nuevo de recursos humanos</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/talento-humano-3.0-analizando-lo-nuevo-de-recursos-humanos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/talento-humano-3.0-analizando-lo-nuevo-de-recursos-humanos/</guid>
      <description>Las ciencias administrativas han desarrollado importantes investigaciones sobre los individuos y grupos en las organizaciones, que quizás pareciera un tema nuevo. Por tanto, al referirse al Talento Humano se hace mención a ese recurso importante desde una concepción más actualizada considerando los cambios y avances en la sociedad del siglo XXI, con matices más específicos dentro de una organización social. Como resultado, se han presentado diversas posiciones y conceptos, en relación a ese individuo con características muy concretas y complejas que interactúa en una organización bien sea pública, privada, pequeña mediana o gran empresa, pero que algunos gerentes parecieran no valorar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valutazione delle Prestazioni</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/valutazione-delle-prestazioni/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/valutazione-delle-prestazioni/</guid>
      <description>Lavori in un’Azienda e vuoi saperne di più sulla Valutazione?
Lavori presso le Risorse Umane (HR) e vuoi approfondire una tua competenza tecnica?
Vuoi sapere cos’è nel dettaglio il Sistema della Valutazione delle Prestazioni?? Qual è il suo scopo?? Le modalità di attuazione dalla sua iniziale fase di progettazione??

Bene!! Sei nel posto giusto…anzi…nell’aula virtuale giusta.
In questo corso ti parlerò di tutte le fasi della Valutazione delle Prestazioni, di chi sono gli Attori interessati e coinvolti, della differenza tra i diversi modelli da usare, delle variabili da tenere sempre in considerazione quando si ha a che fare con il capitale umano (non siamo dei Robot e tutto va adattato e modellato in base a determinati fattori) motivo per cui è importantissimo iniziare con un’ottima progettazione dettagliata della comunicazione del Sistema nonché verificare la situazione attuale dell’impresa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partnership Accounting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/partnership-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/partnership-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Partnership accounting will cover accounting topics related to a partnership form of business entity.
This partnership course will focus on the accounting issues that are different in a partnership as compared to other types of entities like a sole proprietorship or corporations. As we focus on the differences, we always want to keep in mind the similarities in accounting for different business entities. Most of what we have learned about the double entry accounting system and day to day accounting transactions in prior courses will remain the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Pro-Business &amp; Personal-One QuickBooks File</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-pro-business-personal-one-quickbooks-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-pro-business-personal-one-quickbooks-file/</guid>
      <description>Both business and personal financial, bookkeeping, and tax information in one QuickBooks file using class tracking. 
This course will demonstrate how to use the class tracking feature in QuickBooks Pro Desktop 2019, applying the feature to tracking both business and personal financial information in one QuickBooks file. 
Note that tracking both business and personal data in one QuickBooks file will not be the best option for many businesses but is a good option for small businesses who want one location to track and analyze financial data and generate financial reports that can be used for tax preparation, budgeting, and business planning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Intelligence using Tableau</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/business-intelligence-using-tableau/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 01:50:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/business-intelligence-using-tableau/</guid>
      <description>This course focuses on how business intelligence in Tableau uses business analytics tools that make it easy to combine data from multiple sources, analyze and visualize information. It helps trainees in making more informed and better decisions to guide the business. After the completion of the course trainee will be through with all the concepts of business intelligence and Tableau.
The objective of this course is to assist the folks in running a business strategically.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
