<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Health &amp; Fitness on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/health-fitness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Health &amp; Fitness on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/health-fitness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Healthy living with &#39;No Oil&#39; Recipes - Non Vegetarian</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/healthy-living-with-no-oil-recipes-non-vegetarian/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/healthy-living-with-no-oil-recipes-non-vegetarian/</guid>
      <description>**Course Updated - June 2022**
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; COURSE REGULARLY UPDATED: NEW TIPS, MORE LESSONS &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; CERTIFIED COACH, SPEAKER AND TRAINER &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; OVER 180,000 STUDENTS IN TOTAL &amp;lt;&amp;lt;
Life is all about compromises, right? Well, if you think you can ignore your bad eating habits just because you exercise regularly, think again. Unfortunately, spending an hour of rigorous exercise in the gym for a greasy double cheeseburger or relying on a good metabolism to take the place of healthy eating habits completely misses the point of living a healthy lifestyle…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>virology 4 you</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/virology-4-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/virology-4-you/</guid>
      <description>in scientific fiction and reality virus is a June premiere virus was the most mysterious subject in medicine bacterial filter discovery electron microscope we unveil this mystery in this course we speak about history of discovery virus structure virus classifications virus multiplication virus pathogenesis zoonosis some important viruses hepatitis
Rabies is a vaccine preventable, zoonotic, viral disease. Once clinical symptoms appear, rabies is. Vaccinating dogs is the most
cost effective strategy for preventing rabies in people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kick Out Depression -Complete Treatment 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kick-out-depression-complete-treatment-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kick-out-depression-complete-treatment-2022/</guid>
      <description>Depression (major depressive disorder) is a common and serious medical illness that negatively affects how you feel, think, and act. Fortunately, it is also treatable. Depression causes feelings of sadness and/or a loss of interest in activities you once enjoyed. It can lead to various emotional and physical problems and decrease your ability to function at work and home.
You will learn in this course:-
1. About Depression.
2. How Depression affects your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STOP HEART ATTACKS AND STROKES IN WOMEN.</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/stop-heart-attacks-and-strokes-in-women./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/stop-heart-attacks-and-strokes-in-women./</guid>
      <description>Notice: Please do NOT enrol on this course on impulse, thinking you might watch it later. Maybe show an interest on impulse, yes, but before you enrol, watch the Preview videos, read the Course Description and then make a decision. If you then enrol then please start the course as soon as possible. Watch the lectures, look at the workbooks and join in the discussions. Joining my courses is a serious business and I want you to get the most out of your study – but I also want you to enjoy the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why not help prevent a stroke and/or a heart attack?</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/why-not-help-prevent-a-stroke-and/or-a-heart-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/why-not-help-prevent-a-stroke-and/or-a-heart-attack/</guid>
      <description>Notice: Please do NOT enrol on this course on impulse, thinking you might watch it later. Maybe show an interest on impulse, yes, but before you enrol, watch the Preview videos, read the Course Description and then make a decision. If you then enrol then please start the course as soon as possible. Watch the lectures, look at the workbooks and join in the discussions. Joining my courses is a serious business and I want you to get the most out of your study – but I also want you to enjoy the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medical Device Regulations</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/medical-device-regulations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/medical-device-regulations/</guid>
      <description>The medical device industry is growing rapidly, providing great opportunities for innovators, experts and entrepreneurs. This course will provide a detailed overview of the way in which new devices go from concept to product, providing you with a starting point to develop a deep understanding of this complex and fast-moving business space. We will cover all of the key components of bringing a new device to market, including:
Paths to Market, including the 510K, PMA, HDE and other commonly used pathways</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditation For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/meditation-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/meditation-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Meditation is one of the most powerful things that you can do, as a human being. It trains you to be in control of you mind and your emotions, in ways that you never knew were possible. It allows you to be happy just to be alive, even in the most difficult of circumstances; even when you&#39;re injured, or suffering a loss, stressed out at work, overwhelmed, depressed or anxious. It allows you to find the basic happiness of being alive, and that pervades everything else, so that you can deal with everything else much better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditation Masterclass: meditation teacher certification</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/meditation-masterclass-meditation-teacher-certification/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/meditation-masterclass-meditation-teacher-certification/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you&#39;ll learn meditations from all around the world!
From mindfulness to zen to breath-work, chakras, Tibetan bowls, and everything in between, you&#39;ll even be certified to teach meditation by the end of the course!
From new meditators to zen masters alike, no matter what your level of experience, you can gain a lot from exploring this course. By the end, you&#39;ll have experience with over a dozen different styles of meditation!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guaranteed weight loss and Fitness with lifestyle changes</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/guaranteed-weight-loss-and-fitness-with-lifestyle-changes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/guaranteed-weight-loss-and-fitness-with-lifestyle-changes/</guid>
      <description>Across the globe many people are suffering from overweight and obesity.
The longer the obesity persists, the higher the risks
Overweight people are 2-6 times more likely to develop hypertension, increased risk for stroke, deep vein thrombosis, impaired cardiac function, high blood triglycerides, low HDL, insulin resistance and type 2 diabetes
Obesity can be a risk factor for development of cancer. Obese people are more likely to have degenerative joint disease, sleep apnea and mechanical breathing constraints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hypnosis for help to Relieve heal Psoriasis Hypnosis Program</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hypnosis-for-help-to-relieve-heal-psoriasis-hypnosis-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/hypnosis-for-help-to-relieve-heal-psoriasis-hypnosis-program/</guid>
      <description>5 Star Review
He does a good job with hypnosis, I had a good experience and I appreciate the bonuses he adds. I would definitely recommend any course Alan Kirwin produces.
Darlene Wolf
Hypnosis for help to Relieve heal Psoriasis Hypnosis Program has been created to simulate a private therapy session with me Learn how to relieve Psoriasis that for many can have symptoms triggered by everyday highs and lows hypnosis will help to give you relief from those symptoms by giving you a more relaxed attitude to all of what used to upset you and cause your psoriasis symptoms to flare up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deciphering Multi Orgasmic Man – Important Prior Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/deciphering-multi-orgasmic-man-important-prior-knowledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/deciphering-multi-orgasmic-man-important-prior-knowledge/</guid>
      <description>Normally it is thought that sex education courses are only for young people, but in this case, Tantric and Taoist knowledge teach us that: The older a person is; his body will naturally transform into Orgasmic! So men and women between 30 and 70 years of age are going to be the biggest beneficiaries.
According to Eastern wisdom, the orgasmic capacity must be taken advantage of! And the first step that men must take is to understand what &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBT and Nutrition Ultimate Certification Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cbt-and-nutrition-ultimate-certification-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cbt-and-nutrition-ultimate-certification-course/</guid>
      <description>Research in the medical and behavioural sciences and information about cognitive behavioural therapy and pharmacological treatments for mental disorders is rapidly changing. Furthermore, medical and health concerns are unique to each individual and require individual attention and care.
Cognitive-behavioural therapy (CBT) holds a unique status in the field of mental health – CBT is effective for many psychological problems, is relatively brief, and is well received by individuals
A large volume of research has been published regarding CBT, including a number of well-designed studies involving people in “real world” clinical settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CBT: Complete psychotherapy Certificate Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cbt-complete-psychotherapy-certificate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cbt-complete-psychotherapy-certificate-course/</guid>
      <description>CBT is an intensive, short-term, problem-oriented approach. It was designed to be quick, practical and goal-oriented and to provide people with long-term skills to keep them healthy. The focus of cbt is on the problems that come up in a person’s day-to-day life. cbt helps people to look at how they interpret and evaluate what is happening around them and the effects these perceptions have on their emotional experience.
Childhood experiences and events, while not the focus of cbt, may also be reviewed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sports Nutrition for Athletes and Fitness Enthusiasts</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sports-nutrition-for-athletes-and-fitness-enthusiasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sports-nutrition-for-athletes-and-fitness-enthusiasts/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that research by the University of South Carolina revealed that 91% of athletes and 63% of coaches have little knowledge about sports nutrition?
And indeed, most athletes and fitness enthusiasts are rushing through their daily exercise routine without even knowing the basic difference between proteins and carbs.
But conducting purposeful physical exercise without sports nutrition knowledge is like running around in a dark forest. Blindfolded.
And because those athletes and fitness enthusiasts reach far-from optimal results they are trying to compensate their knowledge BLIND SPOT by turning to crazy expensive supplements that hardly ever work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media Training for Doctors/Healthcare Pros: Master the Media</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/media-training-for-doctors/healthcare-pros-master-the-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/media-training-for-doctors/healthcare-pros-master-the-media/</guid>
      <description>Media Training. Imagine that every time you speak to a healthcare reporter, you get the exact message and even the exact quotes you wanted in the final story. Wouldn&#39;t it be great if your medical expertise got into the final story without any distortions? In this Media Training for Doctors and Healthcare Professionals course, you will learn the following: * How to look your best on camera * How to shape a media message * How to answer health reporters&#39; questions * How to speak in sound bites * How to get the exact quote you want in the final story This media training course is delivered primarily through spoken lectures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use breakdancing moves in dance fitness</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-use-breakdancing-moves-in-dance-fitness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-use-breakdancing-moves-in-dance-fitness/</guid>
      <description>What is breakdance?
Breakdancing is a style of street dancing that incorporates coordination, acrobatic and intricate body movements, style, and aesthetics. It evolved from the hip hop movement during the early 1970s and is the most widely known of all hip hop dance styles. Interested in learning how to breakdance? This popular, energetic form of dancing includes everything from spinning on your hands or head to using stylized footwork. Not only does breakdancing involve moves that are more complex and acrobatic than many other forms of dance, but it also has its own unique culture, lingo, and history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction To Swedish Body Massage</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-swedish-body-massage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-swedish-body-massage/</guid>
      <description>This course is aimed at assisting you on your journey to become a massage therapist. If you don&#39;t know where to start, this IS FOR YOU. You will learn all the theory you need before you can begin your practical lessons. As a student of Body massage, I was perplexed when I enrolled in school and was taught massage theory. I thought I was simply going to be taught practical lessons but after my lessons, i understood why learning the theory was essential before we explored practical lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sports Nutrition for Soccer Players</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sports-nutrition-for-soccer-players/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 21:50:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sports-nutrition-for-soccer-players/</guid>
      <description>In the last Big Count, by sports governing body FIFA in 2006, it was estimated that there are 265 million people who play soccer along with more than 5 million referees. At the time of the count that equated to 4% of the world’s population!
That makes soccer the largest sport on the globe in terms of participation and there is no evidence that its popularity is on the decline. Unfortunately, the nutrition knowledge of the average football player does not reflect the popularity of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weight Loss:  A Girlfriend&#39;s Plan for Losing 5 Pounds Quick!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/weight-loss-a-girlfriends-plan-for-losing-5-pounds-quick/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:30:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/weight-loss-a-girlfriends-plan-for-losing-5-pounds-quick/</guid>
      <description>Are you a girlfriend who has a wedding, graduation or vacation coming up? or perhaps you just had a baby? or are welcoming a new grandbaby? Do you want to feel and look better in your jeans and swim suit? Do you want to be able to get on the floor and play with your child, niece or grandchild? Do you want to be active and enjoy life again? Then this course is for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overcome Depression with Cognitive Behavioural Therapy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/overcome-depression-with-cognitive-behavioural-therapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/overcome-depression-with-cognitive-behavioural-therapy/</guid>
      <description>Deal with your Depression and Live a More Fulfilled Life
264 million people around the world suffer from major depression. Depression is fully treatable and people can recover from it and live fulfilling lives.
Does this sound like you?
I feel drained of my physical and mental energy
I’m no longer interested in things I used to enjoy
My body weight has increased/decreased rapidly
My sleep pattern has changed - I’m not sleeping enough/I’m sleeping more than usual</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurship: Healthy Lifestyle - The Untold Story</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/entrepreneurship-healthy-lifestyle-the-untold-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 19:27:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/entrepreneurship-healthy-lifestyle-the-untold-story/</guid>
      <description>Updated: January 2022
Weight Loss – Big Secret
You’ve heard a lot of bad publicity about weight loss and fitness. But here’s something you may not have known.
________________________________________________________________________
Why is this weight loss program different from others and Why should I believe it will work?
I must admit that there are 1000’s of weight loss programs and ideas on how to shed those unwanted fatty parts of the body.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stress Management - 1-Hour Intro Course - Reduce Stress Now</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/stress-management-1-hour-intro-course-reduce-stress-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/stress-management-1-hour-intro-course-reduce-stress-now/</guid>
      <description>Stress Management - 1-Hour Intro Course - Reduce Stress NowStress Management Strategies to Improves Your Quality of Life Now - Mindfulness - Anxiety Management - Resilience
You can manage your stress today. Stop going through life in a stressful, harried and hurried manner.
Best selling personal development course creator TJ Walker takes you through the fastest and easiest steps to regain control of your life and to reduce harmful stress. Some stress is unavoidable, but you can eliminate needless stress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Health and Nutrition Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/health-and-nutrition-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 20:24:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/health-and-nutrition-basics/</guid>
      <description>Health and Nutrition Basics is about giving you a basic understanding of what food can do for your body. This course was designed using my experiences with health and fitness in mind. Using what you are going to learn in this course, I have successfully lost over 40 pounds of fat from my body in just over a year, and kept it off.
This information will help you because it&#39;s the same information that helped me and that I continue to implement daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditation, Breathwork, Yoga &amp; Mindfulness For Inner Peace</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/meditation-breathwork-yoga-mindfulness-for-inner-peace/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 22:09:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/meditation-breathwork-yoga-mindfulness-for-inner-peace/</guid>
      <description>Hi friend,
Welcome to the Meditation, Breathwork, Yoga &amp;amp; Mindfulness For Inner Peace class.
We like to think about this class as an online retreat, a safe place where you can connect deeper to your true self, cultivate inner peace and reset your mind and body. In a fast-paced and constantly changing world, finding your inner peace and balance is essential to your mental and physical well-being. This class offers a unique opportunity to step back and get in touch with yourself at your home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Workout Habits in 10 Min - Fitness for Busy-Lazy People</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/home-workout-habits-in-10-min-fitness-for-busy-lazy-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 20:10:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/home-workout-habits-in-10-min-fitness-for-busy-lazy-people/</guid>
      <description>Fitness - The 10 Minutes or Less Home Workout Habit for Lazy People
You Can Improve Fitness, Muscle Building, Fat Loss and Weight Loss by Doing a Simple and Short Home Workout Daily If you’re not ready to sign up for the next Iron Man competition but you are ready to get in better shape, in as little time as possible, then this course is for you.
You do not have to spend hours a day working out just to maintain proper fitness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Good Sleep Habits Course - Sleep Better Tonight!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-good-sleep-habits-course-sleep-better-tonight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:15:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-good-sleep-habits-course-sleep-better-tonight/</guid>
      <description>Complete Good Sleep Habits Course - Sleep Better Tonight!
Build Healthy Sleep Habits - Eliminate Insomnia - Learn Strong Habits to Sleep Better - Become Well Rested Again
You can increase your odds of getting a good night&#39;s sleep. Most people who are poor sleepers have poor sleep habits. Personal development and habit expert TJ Walker will teach you how to build strong sleep habits effortlessly. In this course, TJ Walker will cover every important habit you need to develop in order to have a solid and restful night&#39;s sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2022 Test of Essential Academic Skills TEAS</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2022-test-of-essential-academic-skills-teas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 21:10:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2022-test-of-essential-academic-skills-teas/</guid>
      <description>Welcome ! Test of Essential Academic Skills TEAS
Salary Potential: $72,000 per year
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily
What does TEAS stand for?
TEAS stands for Test of Essential Academic Skills. It is a standardized admissions test used by many nursing schools to evaluate potential candidates for possible acceptance into their program. The TEAS exam assesses knowledge and skills in reading, math, science and English language use.
A Free Professional quiz that is designed to help you with your TEAS test prep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy 7-DAY MEAL PLAN for Lifelong Weight LOST</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/easy-7-day-meal-plan-for-lifelong-weight-lost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 15:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/easy-7-day-meal-plan-for-lifelong-weight-lost/</guid>
      <description>Find the foods that work for YOU to finally LOSE THE WEIGHT - and KEEP IT OFF FOR LIFE - without exercise, counting calories or strict dieting!
Sounds like a bold statement - right?
Well, it should be because I&#39;ve read the books, tried the programs and diets; and, when I looked at what foods work the best for millions of others, I found a plan that will work for YOU too…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yoga, Pranayam and Meditation for Women</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/yoga-pranayam-and-meditation-for-women/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/yoga-pranayam-and-meditation-for-women/</guid>
      <description>Every one is a fitness freak these days. Generally women are a little more conscious, as beauty is directly proportional to health. A technique called &#39;Yoga&#39; which has the oldest history of knowledge which dates back to 15000 years old as per some Indian scholarly articles has truly tested the test of time as a proven technique to sustain health of the body and the mind and often even called as a health panacea for the soul too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eczema Solution - Discover The Secrets Of Beating Eczema</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/eczema-solution-discover-the-secrets-of-beating-eczema/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 12:27:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/eczema-solution-discover-the-secrets-of-beating-eczema/</guid>
      <description>“Eczema Solution” is your ultimate guide on everything you need to know about handling &amp;amp; controlling this skin condition. While eczema is not a disease — and there is no immediate cure for it … You can get rid of the unbearable itch and inflammation of the skin with the strategies revealed in this training.Whether you are diagnosed with eczema or if you are living with a person who suffers from this skin condition … This is the training that you’ve been looking for!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work from home; work at work...or play?</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/work-from-home-work-at-work...or-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 22:00:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/work-from-home-work-at-work...or-play/</guid>
      <description>This course is in two sections:
Working from home
Working at work
In the first section we go through various ways - using Art Therapy - self-care can be practised at home to reduce stress, help focus and improve overall wellbeing. This includes visualisations as well as Art Therapy exercises.
In the second section we go through a series of games that can be played at work. These will remove tension but BEWARE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Binge-Free Healthy Lifestyle Diet</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/binge-free-healthy-lifestyle-diet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 13:38:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/binge-free-healthy-lifestyle-diet/</guid>
      <description>In This Online Binge-Free Healthy Lifestyle Diet Burning Course You Will Learn How The Pros Teach People How To Melt Away The Pounds And Boost Their Health &amp;amp; Longevity. This Course Is Not Medical Advice ... But Is Based On Scientific Research &amp;amp; Principles That Are Known To Get Results Fast! Having These Tools &amp;amp; Strategies Will Make Eating Less And Losing The Weight So Much Easier, Dramatically Increase The Results You Get &amp;amp; Help You Achieve Your Goals In Less Time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthy Heart - Strengthen, Heal &amp; Protect Your Heart</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/healthy-heart-strengthen-heal-protect-your-heart/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 21:08:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/healthy-heart-strengthen-heal-protect-your-heart/</guid>
      <description>In This Online Healthy Heart Course You Will Learn How To Handle A Heart Attack, Should It Occur. You Will Also Learn Specific Strategies To Make Your Heart Healthier And Help Prevent Heart Attacks.
This Self-Help Course Covers ALL The Major Skills You Need To Strengthen Your Heart .,. And Live A Full And Productive Life.
Also Great For Family Members &amp;amp; Loved Ones Who Want To Learn More In This Area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Immunity Boosting Foods - Protect &amp; Boost Your Immune System</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/immunity-boosting-foods-protect-boost-your-immune-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 17:47:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/immunity-boosting-foods-protect-boost-your-immune-system/</guid>
      <description>Immunity Boosting Foods: In This Immunity Course You Will Learn Proven Strategies You Can Implement Right Away To Make Your Immune System Stronger And Body Healthier. This Immunity Training Makes Boosting Your Immune System Fast, Simple &amp;amp; Easy! Gain this HUGE Advantage In Life … One That Could Literally SAVE Your Life!
Here’s Why:Inside This Course You Will Learn The Secrets Of Boosting Your Immune System And Preventing Many Diseases. This Will Protect Your Health And Extend Your Life At The Same Time … All The While Felling Better Than Ever!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ketogenic Diet – Look &amp; Feel Amazing The Keto Diet Way!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ketogenic-diet-look-feel-amazing-the-keto-diet-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 17:47:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ketogenic-diet-look-feel-amazing-the-keto-diet-way/</guid>
      <description>Keto Diet: If you’ve been struggling to lose weight, even if you’ve been exercising regularly, this could be the ONLY solution for you.Here’s why:
No matter how frequently you exercise ... You will NOT lose weight if your body is NOT in a Fat-burning mode.
Sadly, most people start exercising with the expectation to lose weight fast.
Of course, exercising will help you to lose weight and be healthy, but it is NOT the fastest way to lose weight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple &amp; Easy Ways To Cure Insomnia: Sleep Better! (Deep)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/simple-easy-ways-to-cure-insomnia-sleep-better-deep/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 17:47:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/simple-easy-ways-to-cure-insomnia-sleep-better-deep/</guid>
      <description>In This Online Insomnia Solutions Course You Will Learn How Can Transform Your Life By Beating Insomnia! This Self-Help Course Covers All The Major Skills You Need To Beat Insomnia ... And Get Your Life Back! Insomnia Is Horrible … And Nobody Should Have To Live With It. Unfortunately … We Were Never Taught How To Beat Insomnia. Now You Will Have Those Skills With This One Simple Course! You deserve better sleep - deep sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vegan Diet - Healthy Lifestyle (Practical Vegan Diet)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/vegan-diet-healthy-lifestyle-practical-vegan-diet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 17:47:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/vegan-diet-healthy-lifestyle-practical-vegan-diet/</guid>
      <description>In this online Vegan diet course you will learn how the pros use a vegan diet to get healthy and strong!
In 2009, only 1% of the US population was vegetarian or vegan.
In 2019 6% of Americans are vegan or vegetarian
And of all these vegans, the majority are women.
But that&#39;s not all... Because soon after that, men started following this lifestyle
At 2012, overall meat consumption decreased by 12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Juicing – For Health &amp; Longevity</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/juicing-for-health-longevity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 13:37:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/juicing-for-health-longevity/</guid>
      <description>WHY JUICE?
Did you know that fruit juices are the cleansers of the human system … and vegetable juices are the builders that revitalize the body?
No one doubts that eating vegetables are good for you. But the problem with vegetables are ... They’re so boring! Nothing is more boring than chewing on a carrot for what seems like hours.
Plus, if you’re like me, then you know that vegetables like kale, ginger, and brussel sprouts are good for you, but you just can’t stand the taste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep hacking: Parapsychology tips for Sleep Better</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sleep-hacking-parapsychology-tips-for-sleep-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 23:11:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sleep-hacking-parapsychology-tips-for-sleep-better/</guid>
      <description>Sleep is one of the most important stages of daily life. Sleep will help you regain energy and get things done. Having a good night&#39;s sleep will give you peace of mind and creativity in your mind throughout the day. As a result, you can perform better in life.
If you can&#39;t sleep well at night and stay up until the morning, don&#39;t worry because you are not alone. In this course, I will teach you how to solve all your sleep problems with scientific and logical methods that have been tested for years, so that you can sleep more easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2022 Registered Medical Assistant RMA Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2022-registered-medical-assistant-rma-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 17:51:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2022-registered-medical-assistant-rma-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Registered Medical Assistant RMA Practice Tests
97% Pass in First Attempt Easily
Preparing for your RMA (Registered Medical Assistant) exam by taking practice tests has many benefits. Using sample questions to study for your test is the most effective study practice you can use. The advantages of using RMA sample tests include:
Increasing Your Speed – The RMA exam has a three hour time limit. Although most students who take the RMA feel that there is sufficient time, taking the practice tests with self-imposed timers help you budget your time effectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become Depression Counselor - Major Depressive Disorder</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/become-depression-counselor-major-depressive-disorder/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 22:42:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/become-depression-counselor-major-depressive-disorder/</guid>
      <description>Become Depression Counsellor - Major Depressive Disorder
Depression Counseling made Simpler and Effective - MDD
Provide Effective Depression Counseling to Clients with MDD. A result-oriented approach to improve your counselling skill
In this course, I share the unique insights that I have learned through my years in counselling depressive clients. Knowledge builds upon the knowledge, so it is always a good idea to learn from other mental health professionals. I share useful analogies, mindset shifts, tools &amp;amp; techniques in this course that you can directly use in your counselling sessions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Body&amp;Mind Health Masterclass: A Complete Guide to BodyDetox</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bodymind-health-masterclass-a-complete-guide-to-bodydetox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 15:56:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/bodymind-health-masterclass-a-complete-guide-to-bodydetox/</guid>
      <description>This online detoxification course will teach you how to detox efficiently and professionally and even lose weight, whatever your age, weight or sex.
This detox course is designed to teach you the ins and outs of detoxification, even if you have little to no experience with it and to restart your system so that you stand out from the crowd.
Master Detox Techniques to reset your system!
While there are plenty of detox courses that focus on specific diets or how to lose weight, it&#39;s hard to find a comprehensive course like this one, which is for beginner to advanced detoxers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Counseling clients with Insomnia to Sleep Better</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/counseling-clients-with-insomnia-to-sleep-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 22:30:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/counseling-clients-with-insomnia-to-sleep-better/</guid>
      <description>Counselling clients with Insomnia to Sleep Better
Overcome Insomnia &amp;amp; common sleep problems by understanding the principles of deep sleep, habits and lifestyle choices
You may have difficulty sleeping or you may have difficulty shutting off your mind when you want to sleep. If your sleep problems have led to trouble during the day, such as difficulty with everyday activities, or if they cause you to distress then this course is for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Massaggio Decontratturante Vol1 &#43; Vol2: Test di Valutazione</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/massaggio-decontratturante-vol1--vol2-test-di-valutazione/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 14:59:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/massaggio-decontratturante-vol1--vol2-test-di-valutazione/</guid>
      <description>Ok..hai seguito i miei corsi oppure sei già un massaggiatore esperto...
Ma se ti chiedessi la differenza tra muscolo e tendine? Dove si trova l&#39;organo tendine del Golgi e a cosa serve?
Sapresti rispondermi a menadito o ci stai ancora pensando? Sei pronto per metterti alla prova? Con questo test di 100 domande avrai modo di testare le conoscenze acquisite durante i miei corsi di massaggio decontratturante. Avrai la possibilità di annotare e approfondire nuovi aspetti che nelle lezioni frontali possono sfuggire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sıfırdan Shuffle,HipHop,Popping,DanceHall ve House Dansı</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/s%C4%B1f%C4%B1rdan-shufflehiphoppoppingdancehall-ve-house-dans%C4%B1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 12:00:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/s%C4%B1f%C4%B1rdan-shufflehiphoppoppingdancehall-ve-house-dans%C4%B1/</guid>
      <description>Dans etmek istiyorsun ancak kursa gitmekten mi çekiniyorsun yada vaktin mi yok ?
12 Yıllık dans tecrübeme dayanarak sizler için her seviyeye uygun basit ve eğlenceli eğitim seti hazırladım.
Bu kursu diğer kurslardan ayıran en büyük özelliği daha önce dans eğitimi almamış kişilere özel olarak hazırlanması Yani sıfırdan başlayıp adım adım kendimizi geliştireceğiz.
Ne Tür Danslar Sizleri bekliyor ;
Türkiyenin bir çok yerinde araştırmalar yaptın ama bir sonuca varmadın Biliyorum Hazır ol !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Herbalism: Herbalism Certification Diploma Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/herbalism-herbalism-certification-diploma-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 16:32:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/herbalism-herbalism-certification-diploma-course/</guid>
      <description>This is the place to start if you have ever dreamed of working in the field of Natural-Complementary Medicine and Herbalism.
We have created this course to bring our combined years of experience in the field to you in the comfort of your own home. This course is filled with educational and career insights and opportunities, with each one more exciting than the next.
There are so many ways to create a career in Natural and Complementary Medicine and whether your passion is Medicinal Plants, Homeopathy or People, the practice of Natural and Complementary Medicine is the vital bridge between all of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a profitable online fitness bootcamp</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-create-a-profitable-online-fitness-bootcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 16:32:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-create-a-profitable-online-fitness-bootcamp/</guid>
      <description>You will learn how to create a profitable online fitness bootcamp geared for all levels. You will learn everything about how to set up your bootcamp from lighting to music , to program design and marketing. This course will provide you with the knowledge to be able to start your very own brand in the most cost efficient way. The course will walk you through the steps and give you the confidence to be able operate your own business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inflammation - The Hidden Source of Disease and Chronic Pain</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/inflammation-the-hidden-source-of-disease-and-chronic-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 06:56:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/inflammation-the-hidden-source-of-disease-and-chronic-pain/</guid>
      <description>It starts with well meaning doctors injecting you with toxic vaccinations, and good relatives using sweets-as-rewards. Followed by the food processors adding neurotoxins to your drink or food, and farmers growing hollow foods on depleted soils. Then grocers soaking their carrots in chlorinated water to keep them clean, and teachers sterilizing every surface with antibacterials, or soap makers adding &#34;fragrance&#34; to your detergent, and everybody else asking you to sit, take a ride, and avoid hard work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K-POP Dance Hits 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/k-pop-dance-hits-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 06:56:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/k-pop-dance-hits-2021/</guid>
      <description>Shoutout to all the KPOP fans out there! JNA is a Korean dancer who has participated and featured in many KPOP idols music videos and dance broadcasts. She is famously known for her work as a BLACKPINK stage dancer! You will be learning choreography to the hottest 2021 K-POP hits from JNA who has long experience working in the K-POP industry. She will be teaching you not only the choreography, but also tips and dance moves helpful for mastering idol group dances overall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yoga Sutras of Patañjali: Ashtanga Yoga, Asanas, Pranayama</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/yoga-sutras-of-pata%C3%B1jali-ashtanga-yoga-asanas-pranayama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 21:07:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/yoga-sutras-of-pata%C3%B1jali-ashtanga-yoga-asanas-pranayama/</guid>
      <description>The Yoga Sūtras of Patañjali are 196 Indian sutras (aphorisms). The Yoga Sutras were compiled prior to 400 CE by Sage Patanjali, taking materials about yoga from older traditions. The Yoga Sūtras of Patañjali was the most translated ancient Indian text in the medieval era, having been translated into about forty Indian languages and two non-Indian languages: Old Javanese and Arabic. The text fell into obscurity for nearly 700 years from the 12th to 19th century, and began to regain popularity in late 19th century due to the efforts of Swami Vivekananda, the Theosophical Society and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Guide To Health</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/your-guide-to-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 12:41:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/your-guide-to-health/</guid>
      <description>Do you ache all day every day?
Do you find that your energy levels are always on empty?
Do you suffer from pain all over or in specific places?
Are you tired of hearing: &#34;It&#39;s all in your head&#34;?
Then this course will change your life. Martin Pytela, Life Enthusiast Health Coach, and Co-instructor, Scott Paton, share the foundational causes of your chronic illnesses, the impact they have on your body and finally proven steps to deal with your health challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Massaggio Decontratturante: schiena, spalle, collo.</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/massaggio-decontratturante-schiena-spalle-collo./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 01:45:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/massaggio-decontratturante-schiena-spalle-collo./</guid>
      <description>Hai problemi con la cervicale e vorresti capirne qualcosa in più sul funzionamento del tuo stesso corpo?
Sei un allenatore e vorresti contribuire al benessere della tua squadra?
Pratichi già massaggi e vorresti ampliare le tue conoscenze??
Sei un appassionato e di massaggi??
Bene!!! Sei nell&#39;aula virtuale giusta!
In questo corso spiegherò dalla A alla Z tutto ciò che c&#39;è da sapere per poter effettuare un ottimo massaggio decontratturante agli arti superiori.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lemak dan Kesehatan</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lemak-dan-kesehatan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lemak-dan-kesehatan/</guid>
      <description>Lipida atau lemak sering kali mendapatkan konotasi yang buruk di masyarakat, membuat gemuk, menyebabkan penyakit dan sebagainya. Padahal lemak adalah zat gizi essensial yang penting bagi tubuh. Lemak terdapat pada banyak bahan makanan, meskipun terdapat variasi jumlah, jenis dan kualitasnya. Untuk mendapatkan kesehatan yang optimal kita perlu mengenal kebutuhan lemak, jenis lemak yang baik serta jumlah yang sesuai. Beberapa lemak diketahui memiliki manfaat kesehatan dan dapat melindungi dari penyakit tidak menular seperti penyakit jantung dan stroke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Yourself Up For Sustainable Sobriety</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/setting-yourself-up-for-sustainable-sobriety/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/setting-yourself-up-for-sustainable-sobriety/</guid>
      <description>A lot of people can decide to quit drinking but maintaining sobriety is another story. If you&#39;ve struggled with the recovery roller coaster of quitting, relapsing, cutting back, and relapsing more times than you remember then you&#39;re not alone. It&#39;s incredibly difficult to stay sober when we don&#39;t have the tools or our mindset is in the dumps after our battle with addiction. This course is here to guide you on your path to recovery so you can build a solid foundation to keep you on your feet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secrets Of Reverse Aging &amp; Longevity</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/secrets-of-reverse-aging-longevity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 13:13:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/secrets-of-reverse-aging-longevity/</guid>
      <description>This Online Course On “Reverse Aging” You Will Show You How To Transform Your Body, Mind &amp;amp; Turn Back The Clock! This Anti-Aging Course Covers ALL The Major Strategies You Need To Turn Back The Biological Clock &amp;amp; Be Younger. Try These Techniques … And Feel Amazing!
These Techniques &amp;amp; Strategies ALSO Reduce Your Chance Of Getting MOST Ailments! WOW!!! You Can’t Beat That! Get Your Energy, Youth &amp;amp; Vitality Back!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TAbs от школы похудения Активно Хорошеем</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tabs-%D0%BE%D1%82-%D1%88%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%BB%D1%8B-%D0%BF%D0%BE%D1%85%D1%83%D0%B4%D0%B5%D0%BD%D0%B8%D1%8F-%D0%B0%D0%BA%D1%82%D0%B8%D0%B2%D0%BD%D0%BE-%D1%85%D0%BE%D1%80%D0%BE%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B5%D0%BC/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 13:13:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tabs-%D0%BE%D1%82-%D1%88%D0%BA%D0%BE%D0%BB%D1%8B-%D0%BF%D0%BE%D1%85%D1%83%D0%B4%D0%B5%D0%BD%D0%B8%D1%8F-%D0%B0%D0%BA%D1%82%D0%B8%D0%B2%D0%BD%D0%BE-%D1%85%D0%BE%D1%80%D0%BE%D1%88%D0%B5%D0%B5%D0%BC/</guid>
      <description>ТАБС (от слияния английских слов Tabata и Abs) - это уникальная серия обучающих высоко интенсивных интервальных видео-тренировок построенных по типу Табата с акцентом на талию и пресс. Такой тип тренировок более эффективен, по сравнению с обычными тренировками, так как процесс жиросжигания происходит не только во время тренировки, но и продолжается после тренировки. Курс состоит из 3х полноценных домашних тренировок по 30 минут, включающих в себя и разминку и отдых между подходами и заминку после тренировки, так что вам не нужно ничего дополнительно придумывать.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biohacking Secrets: Boost Your Physical &amp; Mental Health</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/biohacking-secrets-boost-your-physical-mental-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/biohacking-secrets-boost-your-physical-mental-health/</guid>
      <description>Biohacking ... The Science Of Improving YOU! How Cool Is That! What a Major Life-Advantage!
BioHacking Can Help You Perform Better &amp;amp; Live Longer ... What Could Be Better Than That? The Funny Thing is How EASY It Is To Do ... You Just Have To Know The Secrets. Jump Into This Course ... We Will Hold Nothing Back!
Want To Feel Better &amp;amp; Have More Energy? Want To Boost Your Focus &amp;amp; Memory?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eating Healthy – Explode Your Physical &amp; Mental Health</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/eating-healthy-explode-your-physical-mental-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/eating-healthy-explode-your-physical-mental-health/</guid>
      <description>In this online healthy diet course you will learn discover the many benefits of simply making better diet choices. Doing this can transform your body &amp;amp; mind. Using these secrets can add many healthy years to your life, help you be more productive and prevent illnesses. Many find that existing conditions also improve or go way completely … Once they have a proper diet full of life giving nutrients.
This online course will give you hidden diet &amp;amp; nutrition secrets such as: 1) How healthy eating can be made simple &amp;amp; easy 2) How your pH level affects your health … and the foods to eat or avoid to fix this level 3) Learn about “good &amp;amp; “bad” fats 4) Discover how to cook simple healthy meals fast 5) Discover easy tricks to maintain your healthy eating &amp;amp; prevent “backsliding” 6) .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secrets To Burning Fat – How To Melt Fat Away!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-secrets-to-burning-fat-how-to-melt-fat-away/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-secrets-to-burning-fat-how-to-melt-fat-away/</guid>
      <description>In this online fat burning course you will learn how burn fat the way the top pros teach it. Consider this course to be your training pro guiding you to the most effective methods for fat burning &amp;amp; a healthy lifestyle. We are NOT giving medical advice … but this course contains tips, tools &amp;amp; strategies based on sound principles &amp;amp; scientific research.
This course will give you the hidden fat burning secrets of the following areas: 1) Healthy eating 2) The proper way to exercise and 3) The use of supplements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dieting - Nutrition -Weight Loss Tips for Good Healthy Life</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/dieting-nutrition-weight-loss-tips-for-good-healthy-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/dieting-nutrition-weight-loss-tips-for-good-healthy-life/</guid>
      <description>Dieting - Nutrition -Weight Loss Tips for Good Healthy LifeDieting for Weight Loss - Solid Nutrition - Fitness and a Healthy Life - Building a Diet that Works for You - Forever!
Are you tired of dieting and never seeing any long-term results?
Have you already tried the Atkins Diet, the South Beach Diet, the Paleo Diet, Milkshake Diet, the Twinkie Diet, and all the others and they didn’t work?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Functional Fitness Training – Easy Way To Get Shape At Home</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/functional-fitness-training-easy-way-to-get-shape-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/functional-fitness-training-easy-way-to-get-shape-at-home/</guid>
      <description>In this online functional fitness course you will learn how to get in shape gently, without killing yourself. This functional fitness course will be your guide, teaching you simple ways to feel and look better than you have in years without grunting, sweating and straining. If you want to get in shape, but don’t want to be a gym rat, this is the perfect fitness course for you.
This functional fitness course teaches you how to tone stretch muscles to give yourself the shape, strength, balance and movement of somebody years younger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kettlebell Fitness Training – Easy Way To Maximum Fitness</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kettlebell-fitness-training-easy-way-to-maximum-fitness/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/kettlebell-fitness-training-easy-way-to-maximum-fitness/</guid>
      <description>In this online kettlebell Fitness video training course you will learn how tone up &amp;amp; burn fat the way the top pros teach it. Consider this video course to be your “Personal Trainer” guiding you to the most effective methods for fat burning, muscle building, toning and strength.
Kettlebell Fitness training has 5 main benefits: 1) Tones the muscles &amp;amp; problem areas 2) Greatly improves strength &amp;amp; endurance 3) Can help you build muscle 4) Improves balance &amp;amp; stability 5) Hits muscles other exercises miss!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muscle Building - How To Workout For Increasing Muscle Mass</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/muscle-building-how-to-workout-for-increasing-muscle-mass/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/muscle-building-how-to-workout-for-increasing-muscle-mass/</guid>
      <description>In This Muscle Building Course You Will Learn How The Pros Teach People How To Pack On Muscle Fast. This Course Is Not Medical Advice ... But Is Based On Scientific Research &amp;amp; Principles That Are Known To Get Results Fast! Having These Tools &amp;amp; Strategies Will Make Gaining Muscle So Much Easier, Dramatically Increasing The Results You Get &amp;amp; Helping You Achieve Your Goals In Less Time.
In This Online Muscle Building Course For Men &amp;amp; Women You Will Learn How To Build Muscle And Strength The Way The Top Pros Teach It.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Fitness &amp; Health Masterclass - 21 Courses in 1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-fitness-health-masterclass-21-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-fitness-health-masterclass-21-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>If You Only Buy ONE Course This Year … It GOT To Be This One!
With over 22 hours of video content, downloadable resources and bonuses - this is one of the most comprehensive fitness &amp;amp; health masterclass available!
You&#39;ll also get access to:
Lifetime Access to course updates
Fast &amp;amp; Friendly Support in the Q&amp;amp;A section
Udemy Certificate of Completion Ready for Download
To make sure you find the information you are looking for the easiest, we have divided our Masterclass to 21 main sections:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weight loss Certification Diploma: weight loss crash course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/weight-loss-certification-diploma-weight-loss-crash-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 10:00:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/weight-loss-certification-diploma-weight-loss-crash-course/</guid>
      <description>This course is designed for anyone who wants to lose fat, be healthy, and feel great.
My Weight Loss &amp;amp; Nutrition Course is not some random fad diet that tells you which foods you should and shouldn&#39;t eat. Instead, I will take you through each of the steps involved in setting up and following through with your diet.
Unfortunately, the internet is full of false health gurus that sell you all kinds of diet plans and supplements that are overpriced and don&#39;t work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mediation Made Simple: Learn how to Calm your Mind</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mediation-made-simple-learn-how-to-calm-your-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 11:41:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mediation-made-simple-learn-how-to-calm-your-mind/</guid>
      <description>Do you find it difficult to calm your mind?
Do you feel that you are a slave to your thoughts?
Do you want to overcome overthinking, anxiety, or constant rumination?
Change is available more quickly than you can imagine. It just requires you to take that first step...
In this short course, we start from the very beginning. We learn what meditation is, why we shouldn’t fear the practice and we understand what the real benefits are of mediation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nutrition Summary: 3 Weight Loss Methods for Becoming Slim</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/nutrition-summary-3-weight-loss-methods-for-becoming-slim/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 21:16:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/nutrition-summary-3-weight-loss-methods-for-becoming-slim/</guid>
      <description>If you ever imagined that one day you would change your life, behave different, feel different, like it isn’t you anymore – here’s your chance. I’m sure if you follow those 3 weight loss methods, you won’t feel the same anymore. You will feel better than ever and your body is going to thank you in advance.
Developing a healthy eating habit is hard, but it pays off way too much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Home Health Aide HHA Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2021-home-health-aide-hha-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2021-home-health-aide-hha-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Welcome !
2021 Home Health Aide HHA Practice Tests
Home Health Aide (HHA) certificate programs provide courses on patient care, basic medical care, emergency response and housekeeping duties. Certificate programs usually require one semester of study where students learn how to take care of residents by administering medications, cooking, cleaning, organizing household goods and assisting with personal hygiene. Additionally they learn how to take vital signs like pulse and blood pressure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditation For Beginners with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/meditation-for-beginners-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 12:19:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/meditation-for-beginners-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>Meditation for Beginners with MRS JOY is designed to provide emotional and mental health skills through the practice of meditation, to help people all over the world to learn this essential self-regulation tool, so they can improve their lives for the better. It&#39;s also an additional tool for those supporting friends and loved ones that are passing through stress and hard times at the moment. Meditation is important for each one of us, as a healthy habit for a successful lifestyle, free of stress and its symptoms, like anxiety and depression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fully Accredited Certification in Mindfulness Practice</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fully-accredited-certification-in-mindfulness-practice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fully-accredited-certification-in-mindfulness-practice/</guid>
      <description>This course is designed, keeping in mind that you don&#39;t have any prior knowledge and understanding of Mindfulness/ Mindfulness Meditation. So we have completely avoided medical jargon and have simplified it for you.
This course will cover Mindfulness/ Mindfulness Meditation as a whole and enable you to use the methods and techniques.
The accredited certification will be provided by India&#39;s leading CPD provider.
Ratings: 4.85/5
Enrollments: 643
Coupon Code: TOTAL-OFF</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heal From Within - 14 Guided Meditations with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/heal-from-within-14-guided-meditations-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:42:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/heal-from-within-14-guided-meditations-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>Embrace The Power Of Guided Meditation
Let The Healing Begin
Experts advise that most of the population suffers from some form of dysfunction and issues…
According to eNotAlone...
&#34;In the United States today, more people come from dysfunctional families than healthy families. It is estimated that approximately 70 to 80 percent come from dysfunctional families.&#34;
According to DoSomething…
&#34;About 20% of teens will experience depression before they reach adulthood.&#34;
7 in 10 girls believe they&#39;re not good enough in some way (Dove Self-Esteem Fund, 2008)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tai Chi Chen Style 38 Form -to Sharp Mind &amp; Physical Fitness</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tai-chi-chen-style-38-form-to-sharp-mind-physical-fitness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tai-chi-chen-style-38-form-to-sharp-mind-physical-fitness/</guid>
      <description>In this courses, I will show you through breath control exercise and Tai Chi Skill to regain the peace of mind. Tai Chi Chen Style 38 Forms (陈式38式太极拳) combines the most of the postures from Chen Style Traditional 74 Forms, cut repeating movements. Comparing with Basic Tai Chi Chen Style 22 Forms and the commonly seen Tai Chi Yang Style, Tai Chi Chen Style 38 Forms keep the kicking, jumping and leaping movements which will apply in fighting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop Teeth Grinding Bruxism  Program your Mind with Hypnosis</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/stop-teeth-grinding-bruxism-program-your-mind-with-hypnosis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/stop-teeth-grinding-bruxism-program-your-mind-with-hypnosis/</guid>
      <description>Stop Teeth Grinding Bruxism Program your Mind with Hypnosis
Student Review
Having gone through each lesson once and the hypnosis meditation several times I feel I have already learnt some extremely beneficial strategies..... The sessions are short but very easy to follow, Alan is an extremely good presenter and explains everything well. I will continue to listen to the hypnosis session daily for the next 21 days as he suggests and revisit the rest of the course too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pharmacy Assistants In Canada Preparation Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pharmacy-assistants-in-canada-preparation-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pharmacy-assistants-in-canada-preparation-course/</guid>
      <description>** Last updated on Aug 24 2021 **
**This course will also help US students in the clinical part as there are a lot of similarities**
** Your Certificate Will Be Available As Soon As You Finish The Course **
**We will mostly use Ontario, federal, and students insurances to empower your billing skills**
Are you looking for a career as a pharmacy assistant in Canada (especially in Ontario)? Are you a pharmacy assistant and would like to improve your skills and take your career to the next level?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art Therapy for Men (Oxford Diploma)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/art-therapy-for-men-oxford-diploma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/art-therapy-for-men-oxford-diploma/</guid>
      <description>Note: this course does not qualify the recipient to perform any form of therapy or counseling for any other person
This is an unusual course as it is designed to be of use/application to men in particular. Of course it is not &#39;exclusive&#39; just a slight bias. Studies are referenced where appropriate.
Please remember that this course includes:
a. the lectures themselves
b. the Q/A section - make full use of it!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
