<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Health &amp; Fitness on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/health-fitness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Health &amp; Fitness on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/health-fitness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Functional Fitness Training – Easy Way To Get Shape At Home</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/functional-fitness-training-easy-way-to-get-shape-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/functional-fitness-training-easy-way-to-get-shape-at-home/</guid>
      <description>In this online functional fitness course you will learn how to get in shape gently, without killing yourself. This functional fitness course will be your guide, teaching you simple ways to feel and look better than you have in years without grunting, sweating and straining. If you want to get in shape, but don’t want to be a gym rat, this is the perfect fitness course for you.
This functional fitness course teaches you how to tone stretch muscles to give yourself the shape, strength, balance and movement of somebody years younger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kettlebell Fitness Training – Easy Way To Maximum Fitness</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/kettlebell-fitness-training-easy-way-to-maximum-fitness/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/kettlebell-fitness-training-easy-way-to-maximum-fitness/</guid>
      <description>In this online kettlebell Fitness video training course you will learn how tone up &amp;amp; burn fat the way the top pros teach it. Consider this video course to be your “Personal Trainer” guiding you to the most effective methods for fat burning, muscle building, toning and strength.
Kettlebell Fitness training has 5 main benefits: 1) Tones the muscles &amp;amp; problem areas 2) Greatly improves strength &amp;amp; endurance 3) Can help you build muscle 4) Improves balance &amp;amp; stability 5) Hits muscles other exercises miss!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muscle Building - How To Workout For Increasing Muscle Mass</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/muscle-building-how-to-workout-for-increasing-muscle-mass/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/muscle-building-how-to-workout-for-increasing-muscle-mass/</guid>
      <description>In This Muscle Building Course You Will Learn How The Pros Teach People How To Pack On Muscle Fast. This Course Is Not Medical Advice ... But Is Based On Scientific Research &amp;amp; Principles That Are Known To Get Results Fast! Having These Tools &amp;amp; Strategies Will Make Gaining Muscle So Much Easier, Dramatically Increasing The Results You Get &amp;amp; Helping You Achieve Your Goals In Less Time.
In This Online Muscle Building Course For Men &amp;amp; Women You Will Learn How To Build Muscle And Strength The Way The Top Pros Teach It.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Fitness &amp; Health Masterclass - 21 Courses in 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-fitness-health-masterclass-21-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:56:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-fitness-health-masterclass-21-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>If You Only Buy ONE Course This Year … It GOT To Be This One!
With over 22 hours of video content, downloadable resources and bonuses - this is one of the most comprehensive fitness &amp;amp; health masterclass available!
You&#39;ll also get access to:
Lifetime Access to course updates
Fast &amp;amp; Friendly Support in the Q&amp;amp;A section
Udemy Certificate of Completion Ready for Download
To make sure you find the information you are looking for the easiest, we have divided our Masterclass to 21 main sections:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weight loss Certification Diploma: weight loss crash course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/weight-loss-certification-diploma-weight-loss-crash-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 10:00:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/weight-loss-certification-diploma-weight-loss-crash-course/</guid>
      <description>This course is designed for anyone who wants to lose fat, be healthy, and feel great.
My Weight Loss &amp;amp; Nutrition Course is not some random fad diet that tells you which foods you should and shouldn&#39;t eat. Instead, I will take you through each of the steps involved in setting up and following through with your diet.
Unfortunately, the internet is full of false health gurus that sell you all kinds of diet plans and supplements that are overpriced and don&#39;t work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mediation Made Simple: Learn how to Calm your Mind</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/mediation-made-simple-learn-how-to-calm-your-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 11:41:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/mediation-made-simple-learn-how-to-calm-your-mind/</guid>
      <description>Do you find it difficult to calm your mind?
Do you feel that you are a slave to your thoughts?
Do you want to overcome overthinking, anxiety, or constant rumination?
Change is available more quickly than you can imagine. It just requires you to take that first step...
In this short course, we start from the very beginning. We learn what meditation is, why we shouldn’t fear the practice and we understand what the real benefits are of mediation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nutrition Summary: 3 Weight Loss Methods for Becoming Slim</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/nutrition-summary-3-weight-loss-methods-for-becoming-slim/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 21:16:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/nutrition-summary-3-weight-loss-methods-for-becoming-slim/</guid>
      <description>If you ever imagined that one day you would change your life, behave different, feel different, like it isn’t you anymore – here’s your chance. I’m sure if you follow those 3 weight loss methods, you won’t feel the same anymore. You will feel better than ever and your body is going to thank you in advance.
Developing a healthy eating habit is hard, but it pays off way too much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Home Health Aide HHA Practice Tests</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-home-health-aide-hha-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-home-health-aide-hha-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Welcome !
2021 Home Health Aide HHA Practice Tests

Home Health Aide (HHA) certificate programs provide courses on patient care, basic medical care, emergency response and housekeeping duties. Certificate programs usually require one semester of study where students learn how to take care of residents by administering medications, cooking, cleaning, organizing household goods and assisting with personal hygiene. Additionally they learn how to take vital signs like pulse and blood pressure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secrets Of Reverse Aging &amp; Longevity</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/secrets-of-reverse-aging-longevity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/secrets-of-reverse-aging-longevity/</guid>
      <description>This Online Course On “Reverse Aging” You Will Show You How To Transform Your Body, Mind &amp;amp; Turn Back The Clock! This Anti-Aging Course Covers ALL The Major Strategies You Need To Turn Back The Biological Clock &amp;amp; Be Younger. Try These Techniques … And Feel Amazing!
These Techniques &amp;amp; Strategies ALSO Reduce Your Chance Of Getting MOST Ailments! WOW!!! You Can’t Beat That! Get Your Energy, Youth &amp;amp; Vitality Back!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditation For Beginners with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/meditation-for-beginners-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 12:19:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/meditation-for-beginners-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>Meditation for Beginners with MRS JOY is designed to provide emotional and mental health skills through the practice of meditation, to help people all over the world to learn this essential self-regulation tool, so they can improve their lives for the better. It&#39;s also an additional tool for those supporting friends and loved ones that are passing through stress and hard times at the moment. 
Meditation is important for each one of us, as a healthy habit for a successful lifestyle, free of stress and its symptoms, like anxiety and depression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fully Accredited Certification in Mindfulness Practice</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fully-accredited-certification-in-mindfulness-practice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 14:28:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fully-accredited-certification-in-mindfulness-practice/</guid>
      <description>This course is designed, keeping in mind that you don&#39;t have any prior knowledge and understanding of Mindfulness/ Mindfulness Meditation. So we have completely avoided medical jargon and have simplified it for you.
This course will cover Mindfulness/ Mindfulness Meditation as a whole and enable you to use the methods and techniques.
The accredited certification will be provided by India&#39;s leading CPD provider.
 Ratings: 4.85/5
Enrollments: 643
Coupon Code: TOTAL-OFF</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditation Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/meditation-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 10:29:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/meditation-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you&#39;ll learn meditations from all around the world, from mindfulness to zen to breath-work, chakras, Tibetan bowls, and everything in between.
This course is for anyone who&#39;s interested in meditation, from n00bs to zen masters alike; no matter what your level of experience, you can gain a lot from exploring this course. By the end, you&#39;ll have experience with over a dozen different styles of meditation.
This course is accredited by The Meditation Organization as a Certified Teacher Training Course -- AMC (Accredited Meditation Course) #39283 -- so once you receive your diploma at the end of this course, you&#39;ll be able to teach meditation to others as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heal From Within - 14 Guided Meditations with MRS JOY</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/heal-from-within-14-guided-meditations-with-mrs-joy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:42:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/heal-from-within-14-guided-meditations-with-mrs-joy/</guid>
      <description>Embrace The Power Of Guided Meditation
Let The Healing Begin

Experts advise that most of the population suffers from some form of dysfunction and issues…

According to eNotAlone...
&#34;In the United States today, more people come from dysfunctional families than healthy families. It is estimated that approximately 70 to 80 percent come from dysfunctional families.&#34;

According to DoSomething…
&#34;About 20% of teens will experience depression before they reach adulthood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tai Chi Chen Style 38 Form -to Sharp Mind &amp; Physical Fitness</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tai-chi-chen-style-38-form-to-sharp-mind-physical-fitness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/tai-chi-chen-style-38-form-to-sharp-mind-physical-fitness/</guid>
      <description>In this courses, I will show you through breath control exercise and Tai Chi Skill to regain the peace of mind. Tai Chi Chen Style 38 Forms (陈式38式太极拳) combines the most of the postures from Chen Style Traditional 74 Forms, cut repeating movements. Comparing with Basic Tai Chi Chen Style 22 Forms and the commonly seen Tai Chi Yang Style, Tai Chi Chen Style 38 Forms keep the kicking, jumping and leaping movements which will apply in fighting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stop Teeth Grinding Bruxism  Program your Mind with Hypnosis</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/stop-teeth-grinding-bruxism-program-your-mind-with-hypnosis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/stop-teeth-grinding-bruxism-program-your-mind-with-hypnosis/</guid>
      <description>Stop Teeth Grinding Bruxism Program your Mind with Hypnosis
Student Review
Having gone through each lesson once and the hypnosis meditation several times I feel I have already learnt some extremely beneficial strategies..... The sessions are short but very easy to follow, Alan is an extremely good presenter and explains everything well. I will continue to listen to the hypnosis session daily for the next 21 days as he suggests and revisit the rest of the course too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dieting - Nutrition -Weight Loss Tips for Good Healthy Life</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/dieting-nutrition-weight-loss-tips-for-good-healthy-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/dieting-nutrition-weight-loss-tips-for-good-healthy-life/</guid>
      <description>Dieting - Nutrition -Weight Loss Tips for Good Healthy LifeDieting for Weight Loss - Solid Nutrition - Fitness and a Healthy Life - Building a Diet that Works for You - Forever!
Are you tired of dieting and never seeing any long-term results?
Have you already tried the Atkins Diet, the South Beach Diet, the Paleo Diet, Milkshake Diet, the Twinkie Diet, and all the others and they didn’t work?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BodyDetox Masterclass: A Complete Guide to BodyDetox</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/bodydetox-masterclass-a-complete-guide-to-bodydetox/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/bodydetox-masterclass-a-complete-guide-to-bodydetox/</guid>
      <description>This online detoxification course will teach you how to detox efficiently and professionally and even lose weight, whatever your age, weight or sex.
This detox course is designed to teach you the ins and outs of detoxification, even if you have little to no experience with it and to restart your system so that you stand out from the crowd.
Master Detox Techniques to reset your system!
While there are plenty of detox courses that focus on specific diets or how to lose weight, it&#39;s hard to find a comprehensive course like this one, which is for beginner to advanced detoxers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditation For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/meditation-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/meditation-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Meditation is one of the most powerful things that you can do, as a human being. It trains you to be in control of you mind and your emotions, in ways that you never knew were possible. It allows you to be happy just to be alive, even in the most difficult of circumstances; even when you&#39;re injured, or suffering a loss, stressed out at work, overwhelmed, depressed or anxious. It allows you to find the basic happiness of being alive, and that pervades everything else, so that you can deal with everything else much better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pharmacy Assistants In Canada Preparation Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/pharmacy-assistants-in-canada-preparation-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/pharmacy-assistants-in-canada-preparation-course/</guid>
      <description>** Last updated on Aug 24 2021 **
**This course will also help US students in the clinical part as there are a lot of similarities**
** Your Certificate Will Be Available As Soon As You Finish The Course **
**We will mostly use Ontario, federal, and students insurances to empower your billing skills**
Are you looking for a career as a pharmacy assistant in Canada (especially in Ontario)? Are you a pharmacy assistant and would like to improve your skills and take your career to the next level?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art Therapy for Men (Oxford Diploma)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/art-therapy-for-men-oxford-diploma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/art-therapy-for-men-oxford-diploma/</guid>
      <description>Note: this course does not qualify the recipient to perform any form of therapy or counseling for any other person
This is an unusual course as it is designed to be of use/application to men in particular. Of course it is not &#39;exclusive&#39; just a slight bias. Studies are referenced where appropriate.
Please remember that this course includes:
a. the lectures themselves
b. the Q/A section - make full use of it!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
