<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Health &amp; Fitness on </title>
    <link>/tags/health-fitness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Health &amp; Fitness on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/health-fitness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stop Teeth Grinding Bruxism  Program your Mind with Hypnosis</title>
      <link>/stop-teeth-grinding-bruxism-program-your-mind-with-hypnosis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stop-teeth-grinding-bruxism-program-your-mind-with-hypnosis/</guid>
      <description>Stop Teeth Grinding Bruxism Program your Mind with Hypnosis
Student Review
Having gone through each lesson once and the hypnosis meditation several times I feel I have already learnt some extremely beneficial strategies..... The sessions are short but very easy to follow, Alan is an extremely good presenter and explains everything well. I will continue to listen to the hypnosis session daily for the next 21 days as he suggests and revisit the rest of the course too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Home Health Aide HHA Practice Tests</title>
      <link>/2021-home-health-aide-hha-practice-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021-home-health-aide-hha-practice-tests/</guid>
      <description>Welcome !
2021 Home Health Aide HHA Practice Tests

Home Health Aide (HHA) certificate programs provide courses on patient care, basic medical care, emergency response and housekeeping duties. Certificate programs usually require one semester of study where students learn how to take care of residents by administering medications, cooking, cleaning, organizing household goods and assisting with personal hygiene. Additionally they learn how to take vital signs like pulse and blood pressure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dieting - Nutrition -Weight Loss Tips for Good Healthy Life</title>
      <link>/dieting-nutrition-weight-loss-tips-for-good-healthy-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/dieting-nutrition-weight-loss-tips-for-good-healthy-life/</guid>
      <description>Dieting - Nutrition -Weight Loss Tips for Good Healthy LifeDieting for Weight Loss - Solid Nutrition - Fitness and a Healthy Life - Building a Diet that Works for You - Forever!
Are you tired of dieting and never seeing any long-term results?
Have you already tried the Atkins Diet, the South Beach Diet, the Paleo Diet, Milkshake Diet, the Twinkie Diet, and all the others and they didn’t work?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BodyDetox Masterclass: A Complete Guide to BodyDetox</title>
      <link>/bodydetox-masterclass-a-complete-guide-to-bodydetox/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bodydetox-masterclass-a-complete-guide-to-bodydetox/</guid>
      <description>This online detoxification course will teach you how to detox efficiently and professionally and even lose weight, whatever your age, weight or sex.
This detox course is designed to teach you the ins and outs of detoxification, even if you have little to no experience with it and to restart your system so that you stand out from the crowd.
Master Detox Techniques to reset your system!
While there are plenty of detox courses that focus on specific diets or how to lose weight, it&#39;s hard to find a comprehensive course like this one, which is for beginner to advanced detoxers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditation For Beginners</title>
      <link>/meditation-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/meditation-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Meditation is one of the most powerful things that you can do, as a human being. It trains you to be in control of you mind and your emotions, in ways that you never knew were possible. It allows you to be happy just to be alive, even in the most difficult of circumstances; even when you&#39;re injured, or suffering a loss, stressed out at work, overwhelmed, depressed or anxious. It allows you to find the basic happiness of being alive, and that pervades everything else, so that you can deal with everything else much better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditation Masterclass</title>
      <link>/meditation-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/meditation-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you&#39;ll learn meditations from all around the world, from mindfulness to zen to breath-work, chakras, Tibetan bowls, and everything in between.
This course is for anyone who&#39;s interested in meditation, from n00bs to zen masters alike; no matter what your level of experience, you can gain a lot from exploring this course. By the end, you&#39;ll have experience with over a dozen different styles of meditation.
This course is accredited by The Meditation Organization as a Certified Teacher Training Course -- AMC (Accredited Meditation Course) #39283 -- so once you receive your diploma at the end of this course, you&#39;ll be able to teach meditation to others as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pharmacy Assistants In Canada Preparation Course</title>
      <link>/pharmacy-assistants-in-canada-preparation-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pharmacy-assistants-in-canada-preparation-course/</guid>
      <description>** Last updated on Aug 24 2021 **
**This course will also help US students in the clinical part as there are a lot of similarities**
** Your Certificate Will Be Available As Soon As You Finish The Course **
**We will mostly use Ontario, federal, and students insurances to empower your billing skills**
Are you looking for a career as a pharmacy assistant in Canada (especially in Ontario)? Are you a pharmacy assistant and would like to improve your skills and take your career to the next level?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art Therapy for Men (Oxford Diploma)</title>
      <link>/art-therapy-for-men-oxford-diploma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/art-therapy-for-men-oxford-diploma/</guid>
      <description>Note: this course does not qualify the recipient to perform any form of therapy or counseling for any other person
This is an unusual course as it is designed to be of use/application to men in particular. Of course it is not &#39;exclusive&#39; just a slight bias. Studies are referenced where appropriate.
Please remember that this course includes:
a. the lectures themselves
b. the Q/A section - make full use of it!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
