<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Marketing on </title>
    <link>/tags/digital-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital Marketing on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/digital-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BEST of SEO: #1 SEO Training &amp; Content Marketing Course 2021</title>
      <link>/best-of-seo-#1-seo-training-content-marketing-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/best-of-seo-#1-seo-training-content-marketing-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>In our increasingly online world, if you want to be successful, you need the latest digital skills. In this SEO &amp;amp; CONTENT MARKETING MASTERY course, I bring you CONSTANTLY UPDATED CUTTING-EDGE STRATEGIES AND TECHNIQUES so you can THRIVE in Content Marketing and SEO. This is my brand new 2021 SEO Training and Content Marketing Course! Now UPDATED to include many more topics to give you EVEN MORE VALUE and ensure your and SEO Success, with input from multiple experts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copywriting &amp; Content Marketing Course: Be a PRO Copywriter</title>
      <link>/copywriting-content-marketing-course-be-a-pro-copywriter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/copywriting-content-marketing-course-be-a-pro-copywriter/</guid>
      <description>UPSKILL YOURSELF AND ENSURE YOU&#39;RE NEVER OUT OF WORK OR OUT OF CLIENTS, WITH THE CONTENT MARKETING &amp;amp; COPYWRITING COURSE 2021. LEARN EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO KNOW TO BECOME A PROFESSIONAL CONTENT CREATOR, AND START A NEW CAREER ONLINE, OR BOOST YOUR LOCAL OR E-COMMERCE BUSINESS.
&#34;I wanted to tell you that I have a job in a digital marketing company! I&#39;m working as a copywriter and account manager for a team of developers and graphic designers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction into Facebook Marketing &amp; Facebook Advertising</title>
      <link>/introduction-into-facebook-marketing-facebook-advertising/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 04:18:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/introduction-into-facebook-marketing-facebook-advertising/</guid>
      <description>&#34;The BEST, authentic, great and very precise course on Facebook Marketing and Facebook Advertising. Though the course is just 10 hours, it covers the topics beyond anyone&#39;s expectations. I would rank this course #1 because the instructor Tomas takes the systematic and a very organized approach in training the students. I will enrol for another courses because it&#39;s JUST WORTH IT. The course brilliantly and generously covers the entire topic without biases or prejudice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Digital Marketing Course for Local Businesses 2021</title>
      <link>/complete-digital-marketing-course-for-local-businesses-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-digital-marketing-course-for-local-businesses-2021/</guid>
      <description>&#34;This Digital Marketing Course is amazing. I have learned a lot of from this course. I like the explanation style of the teacher. So, please everyone join this course to change your life....&#34; Kamran
&#34;The complete content was brilliantly explained. Thank you.&#34; Riya
&#34;The course content is amazing. I have learned many new things, especially new tips and tricks in digital marketing. One thing I have to tell that the trainer is awesome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Online Business Marketing Tool - Guide to Systeme</title>
      <link>/complete-online-business-marketing-tool-guide-to-systeme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-online-business-marketing-tool-guide-to-systeme/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Complete Online Business Marketing Tool - Guide to Systeme!
For a long time, marketers have had to piece together various tools and software tools in order to achieve their goals. But these days, marketers are constantly being confronted with new platforms, new startup companies, and old favorites that are constantly re-tooling themselves and shifting their strategies.
In this rapid-fire internet era of marketing, it can be hard for even the most seasoned professionals to keep up with everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversion Rate Optimization CRO: B2B Conversion Rate CRO</title>
      <link>/conversion-rate-optimization-cro-b2b-conversion-rate-cro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/conversion-rate-optimization-cro-b2b-conversion-rate-cro/</guid>
      <description>Learn B2B (business-to-business) conversation rate optimization (conversion rate optimisation / CRO) to maximize leads and paying customers. Optimize the entire growth marketing funnel using tactical and strategic conversion maximization approaches from a top MBA with Fortune 100 experience and master&#39;s level analytics training. -&amp;gt; Real examples from my own experience in driving growth for companies of various sizes including Sony and a Google-accelerator startup
-&amp;gt; Advice from my colleagues who drove growth for top companies including LinkedIn and Sephora</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing Agency: Grow Your Digital Marketing Agency</title>
      <link>/digital-marketing-agency-grow-your-digital-marketing-agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/digital-marketing-agency-grow-your-digital-marketing-agency/</guid>
      <description>This is the ultimate course on growing your digital marketing agency &amp;amp; getting more clients. I worked for a digital marketing agency for 5 years. I also worked as an independent consultant. As a global marketing manager for Sony, I worked with some of the top marketing agencies in the world including Digitas, Mediacom, and Publicis. I taught college level digital marketing and I have an MBA from the top business school for marketing--the Kellogg School of Management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Money Online With Digital Product Launch</title>
      <link>/make-money-online-with-digital-product-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/make-money-online-with-digital-product-launch/</guid>
      <description>take this 9 Days Journey with me to create, craft and launch your digital course product and program. start selling Instantly.

Do you want to overcome your all financial problems? and start your business online?
Have you always sought to create and launch a digital product but stuck with the process?
Are you having a hard time doing it as it requires a huge Investment, Time and Energy?
Would you prefer a better, Simpler, Easier and Faster way to launch your digital product or program?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storytelling Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/storytelling-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/storytelling-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Story telling can be a powerful component in a marketing strategy. It can be the driving force behind developing, and more importantly, establishing a brand that connects and resonates with your target audience.
It’s also the easiest way to express emotions and illustrate your commitment to providing value.
There’s nothing more powerful than a carefully crafted story that fulfills the needs of your core market.
In this special course, you will learn top story-telling methods, how to best use these strategies and how you can use storytelling to strengthen your brand or launch a new one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Driving Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/traffic-driving-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/traffic-driving-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>You’ve likely heard about the power of viral sharing. When enough people share content and it goes viral, the traffic is virtually unstoppable.
And it’s targeted, FREE traffic!
When you inject viral sharing into your sales copy or funnel, you’ll immediately maximize exposure with very little work involved. Instead of spending hours setting up traffic campaigns and ads on social media networks, you motivate your visitors into doing all the work for you!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
