<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Marketing on </title>
    <link>/tags/digital-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital Marketing on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 13:19:24 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/digital-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Conversion Optimization Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/conversion-optimization-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 13:19:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/conversion-optimization-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Increasing your website’s traffic is already a time-consuming task that will take up enough of your time. So, you need to make sure that traffic converts into sales, right?
There are simple ways of capturing attention, boosting conversion rates and ultimately, maximizing your profits without breaking the bank, or spending a lot of time tweaking your traffic campaigns.
The conversion boosting hacks featured in this report are ones that you can easily implement into your existing website without spending more than a couple of hours tightening up a few weak areas so that you can transform your business in just a matter of a few short days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing Ultimate Course Bundle - 13 Courses in 1</title>
      <link>/digital-marketing-ultimate-course-bundle-13-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 13:19:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/digital-marketing-ultimate-course-bundle-13-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Digital Marketing Ultimate Course Bundle - 13 Courses in 1 (Over 27 hours of content)
In this practical hands-on training, you’re going to learn to become a digital marketing expert with this ultimate course bundle that includes 13 digital marketing courses in 1!
Blending practical work with solid theoretical training, this course takes you from the basics of Digital Marketing to mastery, giving you the training you need not just to build Sales funnels, generate leads using Email, Facebook ads, Google ads, LinkedIn and SEO but also how to build websites and create amazing videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mit Online Marketing Dein Business aufbauen ohne Vorwissen!</title>
      <link>/mit-online-marketing-dein-business-aufbauen-ohne-vorwissen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 13:19:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mit-online-marketing-dein-business-aufbauen-ohne-vorwissen/</guid>
      <description>Letzte Aktualisierung: 11.9.2021
*** DER KURS WIRD LAUFEND ERWEITERT -&amp;gt; neue Inhalte jeden Monat! *** 

Digitales Marketing und insbesondere Online Marketing boomen seit einigen Jahren. Es herrscht eine Goldgräberstimmung, und genau JETZT hat es Sinn, sich mit Online Marketing auseinanderzusetzen - bevor es zu spät ist. Besonders jetzt, im Jahr 2021 explodiert der Online Traffic und die Werbepreise gehen herunter.
Der Einzelhandel, Unternehmer und Selbständige sind aufgrund der aktuellen Lage gezwungen, ihre Produkte immer mehr online zu verkaufen - und kaum jemand ist wirklich darauf vorbereitet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEST of GOOGLE ADS 2021: Set Up Google Search Campaign Today</title>
      <link>/best-of-google-ads-2021-set-up-google-search-campaign-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 20:22:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/best-of-google-ads-2021-set-up-google-search-campaign-today/</guid>
      <description>LEARN GOOGLE ADS AND SETUP YOUR GOOGLE SEARCH CAMPAIGN TODAY!!!! LEARN HOW TO SET UP YOUR GOOGLE ADS ACCOUNT, USE GOOGLE COUPON, WRITE YOUR GOOGLE AD COPY, CREATE YOUR FIRST CAMPAIGN, AND GET YOUR ADVERTISING UP &amp;amp; RUNNING. IN THIS GOOGLE ADS COURSE YOU WILL WALK-THROUGH SETUP, CONFIGURATION, CREATING AD COPY, ADDING YOUR KEYWORDS, AND OPTIMISING YOUR ADS TO DRIVE TRAFFIC TO YOUR WEBSITE. YOU WILL LEARN HOW TO SETUP RETARGETING AND GOOGLE SHOPPING (GOOGLE MERCHANT CENTRE).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction into Facebook Marketing &amp; Facebook Advertising</title>
      <link>/introduction-into-facebook-marketing-facebook-advertising/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/introduction-into-facebook-marketing-facebook-advertising/</guid>
      <description>&#34;The BEST, authentic, great and very precise course on Facebook Marketing and Facebook Advertising. Though the course is just 10 hours, it covers the topics beyond anyone&#39;s expectations. I would rank this course #1 because the instructor Tomas takes the systematic and a very organized approach in training the students. I will enrol for another courses because it&#39;s JUST WORTH IT. The course brilliantly and generously covers the entire topic without biases or prejudice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sales Funnel, Email Marketing All-in-One Tool: Systeme Guide</title>
      <link>/sales-funnel-email-marketing-all-in-one-tool-systeme-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sales-funnel-email-marketing-all-in-one-tool-systeme-guide/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Complete Online Business Marketing Tool - Guide to Systeme!
For a long time, marketers have had to piece together various tools and software tools in order to achieve their goals. But these days, marketers are constantly being confronted with new platforms, new startup companies, and old favorites that are constantly re-tooling themselves and shifting their strategies.
In this rapid-fire internet era of marketing, it can be hard for even the most seasoned professionals to keep up with everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Digital Marketing Course for Local Businesses 2021</title>
      <link>/complete-digital-marketing-course-for-local-businesses-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 20:51:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-digital-marketing-course-for-local-businesses-2021/</guid>
      <description>&#34;This Digital Marketing Course is amazing. I have learned a lot of from this course. I like the explanation style of the teacher. So, please everyone join this course to change your life....&#34; Kamran
&#34;The complete content was brilliantly explained. Thank you.&#34; Riya
&#34;The course content is amazing. I have learned many new things, especially new tips and tricks in digital marketing. One thing I have to tell that the trainer is awesome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics For Beginners</title>
      <link>/google-analytics-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 13:08:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/google-analytics-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>This course will teach Google Analytics from scratch. Here is the overview of what you are going to learn,
Setup Google Analytics Account
Installing Tracking Code on your website
Configure Marketing Goals
Setup Filters
UTM Parameters
Generating Reports ( Audience, Real-time, Acquisition, etc. )
Who this course is for:
Bloggers
Webmasters
Online Business Owners
Marketing Professionals
Intermediate level Digital Marketers
Beginners in Web Analytics
College Students
 Ratings: 4.39/5
Enrollments: 41912</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing Strategy Course 2021. Start from scratch!</title>
      <link>/digital-marketing-strategy-course-2021.-start-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/digital-marketing-strategy-course-2021.-start-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my digital marketing course!
What is digital marketing?
Digital marketing is an innovative way to attract a large audience to your online project. There are a wide variety of online marketing techniques that you can use, such as social media marketing, content marketing, email marketing, search engine optimization, affiliate marketing, inbound marketing, mobile marketing, display advertising, paid search, web analytics, conversion optimization, etc. In this digital marketing course, we will discuss how to make these marketing techniques work in sync with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sales Funnels Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/sales-funnels-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 15:50:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sales-funnels-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>If you want to maximize your income so you can squeeze every possible dollar from your product launches,you absolutely need to master the art of creating high-converting sales funnels.
Because a well-constructed sales funnel that’s based on proven techniques can take a simple product launch and retain the momentum weeks, even months after the launch.
This special report was written to provide you with a step-by-step quick start blueprint to creating outstanding sales funnels that not only maximize your profits but are aimed at keeping the money rolling in long after your initial launch phase is over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing B2B: Ultimate B2B Digital Marketing Course</title>
      <link>/digital-marketing-b2b-ultimate-b2b-digital-marketing-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/digital-marketing-b2b-ultimate-b2b-digital-marketing-course/</guid>
      <description>ATTENTION B2B DIGITAL MARKETING STUDENTS: Learn the strategies and nitty-gritty tactical details of acquiring business customers cheaply and quickly through digital marketing and modern social media marketing. Get executive-level training from a former VP of Marketing and college instructor with Fortune 100 experience--at a fraction of the cost of an executive digital marketing training courses!This is the ultimate course on B2B digital marketing. I was a global marketing manager for Sony and a Vice President of Marketing for a Google accelerator startup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn 6 SIMPLE Steps to Make Money on TikTok App!</title>
      <link>/learn-6-simple-steps-to-make-money-on-tiktok-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/learn-6-simple-steps-to-make-money-on-tiktok-app/</guid>
      <description>How would you feel like when making $10,000&#39;s just by using your smartphone?
Benefits of Making Money on TikTok App:
You can do this worldwide!
You can make money for 100% FREE!
TikTok is the most downloaded app in the world right now!
Steps are really SIMPLE!
The earning potential is HUGE!
--
While I can&#39;t guarantee you any money (by law) but let me tell you a short story from my own life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing Agency Elite Consultants Masterclass</title>
      <link>/digital-marketing-agency-elite-consultants-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:15:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/digital-marketing-agency-elite-consultants-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>LEARN HOW YOU CAN GROW A SUCCESSFUL​ MARKETING AGENCY... in as little as 30 days or less as Juan pulls back the curtain on how you can get paid high monthly retainers and even if you have no prior marketing experience.
I&#39;ve done the painful leg work so that you don&#39;t have to. When I first started, I struggled to get clients because I had no confidence. I was unsure how to get results or even how to sell and close clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Email Monetization Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/email-monetization-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/email-monetization-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Turning your email list into a passive income money maker isn’t as difficult, or time consuming as you may think.
Every day, thousands of online marketers are transforming their mailing lists into powerful cash funnels, and quite often, they don’t even have their own product line!
This course will make it easy for you to start making money with your subscriber base even if you’re just starting out.
It will show you how you can join the ranks of successful list builders quickly and easily, while increasing engagement, building your tribe and positioning yourself as a thought leader in your market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEST of SEO: #1 SEO Training &amp; Content Marketing Course 2021</title>
      <link>/best-of-seo-#1-seo-training-content-marketing-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/best-of-seo-#1-seo-training-content-marketing-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>In our increasingly online world, if you want to be successful, you need the latest digital skills. In this SEO &amp;amp; CONTENT MARKETING MASTERY course, I bring you CONSTANTLY UPDATED CUTTING-EDGE STRATEGIES AND TECHNIQUES so you can THRIVE in Content Marketing and SEO. This is my brand new 2021 SEO Training and Content Marketing Course! Now UPDATED to include many more topics to give you EVEN MORE VALUE and ensure your and SEO Success, with input from multiple experts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copywriting &amp; Content Marketing Course: Be a PRO Copywriter</title>
      <link>/copywriting-content-marketing-course-be-a-pro-copywriter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 22:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/copywriting-content-marketing-course-be-a-pro-copywriter/</guid>
      <description>UPSKILL YOURSELF AND ENSURE YOU&#39;RE NEVER OUT OF WORK OR OUT OF CLIENTS, WITH THE CONTENT MARKETING &amp;amp; COPYWRITING COURSE 2021. LEARN EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO KNOW TO BECOME A PROFESSIONAL CONTENT CREATOR, AND START A NEW CAREER ONLINE, OR BOOST YOUR LOCAL OR E-COMMERCE BUSINESS.
&#34;I wanted to tell you that I have a job in a digital marketing company! I&#39;m working as a copywriter and account manager for a team of developers and graphic designers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversion Rate Optimization CRO: B2B Conversion Rate CRO</title>
      <link>/conversion-rate-optimization-cro-b2b-conversion-rate-cro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/conversion-rate-optimization-cro-b2b-conversion-rate-cro/</guid>
      <description>Learn B2B (business-to-business) conversation rate optimization (conversion rate optimisation / CRO) to maximize leads and paying customers. Optimize the entire growth marketing funnel using tactical and strategic conversion maximization approaches from a top MBA with Fortune 100 experience and master&#39;s level analytics training. -&amp;gt; Real examples from my own experience in driving growth for companies of various sizes including Sony and a Google-accelerator startup
-&amp;gt; Advice from my colleagues who drove growth for top companies including LinkedIn and Sephora</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing Agency: Grow Your Digital Marketing Agency</title>
      <link>/digital-marketing-agency-grow-your-digital-marketing-agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/digital-marketing-agency-grow-your-digital-marketing-agency/</guid>
      <description>This is the ultimate course on growing your digital marketing agency &amp;amp; getting more clients. I worked for a digital marketing agency for 5 years. I also worked as an independent consultant. As a global marketing manager for Sony, I worked with some of the top marketing agencies in the world including Digitas, Mediacom, and Publicis. I taught college level digital marketing and I have an MBA from the top business school for marketing--the Kellogg School of Management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Money Online With Digital Product Launch</title>
      <link>/make-money-online-with-digital-product-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/make-money-online-with-digital-product-launch/</guid>
      <description>take this 9 Days Journey with me to create, craft and launch your digital course product and program. start selling Instantly.

Do you want to overcome your all financial problems? and start your business online?
Have you always sought to create and launch a digital product but stuck with the process?
Are you having a hard time doing it as it requires a huge Investment, Time and Energy?
Would you prefer a better, Simpler, Easier and Faster way to launch your digital product or program?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storytelling Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/storytelling-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/storytelling-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Story telling can be a powerful component in a marketing strategy. It can be the driving force behind developing, and more importantly, establishing a brand that connects and resonates with your target audience.
It’s also the easiest way to express emotions and illustrate your commitment to providing value.
There’s nothing more powerful than a carefully crafted story that fulfills the needs of your core market.
In this special course, you will learn top story-telling methods, how to best use these strategies and how you can use storytelling to strengthen your brand or launch a new one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Driving Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>/traffic-driving-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/traffic-driving-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>You’ve likely heard about the power of viral sharing. When enough people share content and it goes viral, the traffic is virtually unstoppable.
And it’s targeted, FREE traffic!
When you inject viral sharing into your sales copy or funnel, you’ll immediately maximize exposure with very little work involved. Instead of spending hours setting up traffic campaigns and ads on social media networks, you motivate your visitors into doing all the work for you!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
