<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Marketing on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/digital-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital Marketing on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/digital-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Email Monetization Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/email-monetization-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/email-monetization-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>Turning your email list into a passive income money maker isn’t as difficult, or time consuming as you may think.
Every day, thousands of online marketers are transforming their mailing lists into powerful cash funnels, and quite often, they don’t even have their own product line!
This course will make it easy for you to start making money with your subscriber base even if you’re just starting out.
It will show you how you can join the ranks of successful list builders quickly and easily, while increasing engagement, building your tribe and positioning yourself as a thought leader in your market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sales Funnels Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sales-funnels-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sales-funnels-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>If you want to maximize your income so you can squeeze every possible dollar from your product launches, you absolutely need to master the art of creating high-converting sales funnels.
Because a well-constructed sales funnel that’s based on proven techniques can take a simple product launch and retain the momentum weeks, even months after the launch.
This special course was made to provide you with a step-by-step quick start blueprint to creating outstanding sales funnels that not only maximize your profits but are aimed at keeping the money rolling in long after your initial launch phase is over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lead Generation Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lead-generation-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lead-generation-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>If you have an online business, you’re selling something. It might be a product of your own, a service you provide, an affiliate product (or most likely multiple affiliate products), etc. Whatever it is you’re selling, you need leads.
A lead is a potential buyer. And more importantly, a qualified prospect that has been proven to be interested in your products or services.
With this course, you will learn more about how to start generating leads through steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Driving Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/traffic-driving-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/traffic-driving-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>You’ve likely heard about the power of viral sharing. When enough people share content and it goes viral, the traffic is virtually unstoppable.
And it’s targeted, FREE traffic!
When you inject viral sharing into your sales copy or funnel, you’ll immediately maximize exposure with very little work involved. Instead of spending hours setting up traffic campaigns and ads on social media networks, you motivate your visitors into doing all the work for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-analytics-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-analytics-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>This course will teach Google Analytics from scratch. Here is the overview of what you are going to learn,
Setup Google Analytics Account
Installing Tracking Code on your website
Configure Marketing Goals
Setup Filters
UTM Parameters
Generating Reports ( Audience, Real-time, Acquisition, etc. )
Who this course is for:
Bloggers
Webmasters
Online Business Owners
Marketing Professionals
Intermediate level Digital Marketers
Beginners in Web Analytics
College Students
Ratings: 4.21/5
Enrollments: 77278</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Traffic Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/online-traffic-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/online-traffic-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>Whether you have a personal blog, business website, or are making money through online advertising, today&#39;s currency of success relies, almost exclusively, on the science of cultivating more significant traffic to your website.
The traffic that you bring to your website is crucial because it helps you increase your rankings on the various search engines, which is how potential customers can find your company.
Unfortunately bringing more traffic to your site these days can be a challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copywriting &amp; Content Marketing Course: Be a Pro Copywriter</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/copywriting-content-marketing-course-be-a-pro-copywriter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/copywriting-content-marketing-course-be-a-pro-copywriter/</guid>
      <description>This Copywriting &amp;amp; Content Marketing Course has been Completely Updated with Writing Assignments &amp;amp; Quizzes Making Learning Fun. Upskill yourself and ensure you&#39;re never out of work or out of clients, with the content marketing &amp;amp; copywriting course. Learn everything you need to know to become a professional content creator, and start a new career online, or boost your local or e-commerce business. &#34;I wanted to tell you that I have a job in a digital marketing company!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing Strategy Bundle: 7 practical courses in 1!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-marketing-strategy-bundle-7-practical-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-marketing-strategy-bundle-7-practical-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to grow your business online? Do you need to get complete knowledge of digital marketing strategy to increase traffic, conversion, and sales? This is a complete course “Digital Marketing Strategy Bundle: 7 practical courses in 1” for you to master digital marketing.
This Bundle of 7-in-1 practical digital marketing courses includes:
1. DIGITAL MARKETING STRATEGY. How to grow your business with digital marketing?
Strategical 7 questions to answer to build a successful online presence: Mission, Vision, Product, Target Audience, Competitors, Traffic Sources, Metrics, and Optimization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shopify eCommerce Store Masterclass - Start a Business!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/shopify-ecommerce-store-masterclass-start-a-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/shopify-ecommerce-store-masterclass-start-a-business/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to create an eCommerce store on Shopify – the world&#39;s leading eCommerce platform and an unparalleled opportunity for entrepreneurs.
Start a business on Shopify and boost your income or escape the 9-to-5! You don&#39;t need any prior knowledge of eCommerce or any technical skills - if you can use a web browser, you are good to go!
This course is by Trevor Ginn, a successful online retailing entrepreneur who runs an online business that sells over $3million/year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Digital Marketing Course for Local Businesses 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-digital-marketing-course-for-local-businesses-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:33:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-digital-marketing-course-for-local-businesses-2022/</guid>
      <description>Learn Everything you need to Become a Local Digital Marketing Expert with this Comprehensive Course, Created by an Internet Efficiency Award-Winning Instructor. Updated with the latest Digital Marketing Strategies &amp;amp; 180+ Interactive Quizzes Making Learning Fun.
Get Pro Techniques to Get Found Fast in Your Local Area Using Facebook Ads, and Drive a Stream of New Traffic to Your Website and To your Location. This Course Contains All the Knowledge you’ll Ever Require to Successfully Market a Local Business Online using Facebook Ads, Facebook Business Manager, your Website, Google, Youtube, Bing, Instagram Ads, Local SEO, Google My Business, Trip Advisor, and More.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing Course as Project &amp; Fun: 88 Days Challenge</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-marketing-course-as-project-fun-88-days-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-marketing-course-as-project-fun-88-days-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Accept Our 88 Days Digital Marketing Challenge &amp;amp; Learn Digital Marketing With Our Easy &amp;amp; Fun Learning System - HQ Video Animated Explainers, Screen Recordings, Over My Shoulder Explanations, Quizzes, &amp;amp; Assignments That Make Learning Fun, Fast, &amp;amp; Easy!!! Get Pro 23 Content Creation Templates You Can Customise!!! Max Leads &amp;amp; Sales, Boost Search Ranking, Or Land Your Dream Marketing Job!!! Become Digital Marketing Nomad And Attract High Value Clients!!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Analytics Certification 3 in 1 [Practice Test]</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-analytics-certification-3-in-1-practice-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-analytics-certification-3-in-1-practice-test/</guid>
      <description>Hey there!
Welcome to this Practice test on &#34;Google Analytics Certification: 3 in 1 Practice test from Beginners to Advanced&#34;.
Google Analytics is one of the best tools considered for the overall analysis of your website’s activities. These activities may be organic or driven through any Ad; Analytics does a recording of every step taken. Along with this analysis task, Google Analytics also provides a certification course for beginners and advanced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sales &amp; Marketing Funnel To Grow Business- Digital Marketing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sales-marketing-funnel-to-grow-business-digital-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sales-marketing-funnel-to-grow-business-digital-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone, Welcome to the course! I am thrilled to have you on board. You&#39;re going to be a valuable asset, and I can&#39;t wait to see all that you accomplish. In this course, I&#39;m going to talk about everything related sales funnel. what is it, how to build one, and what kind of content you would require for each step of your funnel?
For a sales funnel to work, you need the perfect platform to execute your strategies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unique Selling Proposition Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/unique-selling-proposition-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/unique-selling-proposition-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>USP stands for Unique Selling Proposition (or Point) and every business needs one.
It’s easy to spot a USP once you see one in action. It’s the service or product that you offer which no other business is currently offering to their clients.
Your USP is why consumers should do business with you, versus the competition. It’ll also be the reason they keep coming back to your business.
In this course, will discover a few examples of winning USP’s so you can see what a USP is, and how to create one for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace your career with the Power of Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ace-your-career-with-the-power-of-artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ace-your-career-with-the-power-of-artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Ace your career with the Power of Artificial Intelligence&#34;
Artificial intelligence (AI) is real science that deals with building intelligent machines or automated robots that can think and respond like a human being. Nevertheless, AI tech holds exceptional future opportunities in digital marketing and the trend is changing day by day. The impact of AI in digital marketing actually goes far beyond what one can ever imagine. More and more companies are leaning on AI tech for cutting-edge applications to create a great impact on their business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Futuristic Digital Marketing Course: 2022 Student Edition</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/futuristic-digital-marketing-course-2022-student-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/futuristic-digital-marketing-course-2022-student-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Futuristic Digital Marketing Course: 2022 Student Edition&#34;.
The digital marketing world is evolving day by day with the rise of new technologies. Currently, in the city of Bangalore, there has been an advent of new companies or startups which have emerged this year. As Bill Gates said–&#34;If your company isn&#39;t on the internet, your business will be out of business,&#34;. Each businessman is trying their best to catch online users &#39; interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viral Marketing Masterclass (2022 Virality Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/viral-marketing-masterclass-2022-virality-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/viral-marketing-masterclass-2022-virality-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the course titled &#34;Viral Marketing Masterclass (2022 Virality Edition)&#34;
&#34;A business strategy or technique that utilises existing social networks like Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter, Quora, Reddit etc. to advertise a product with the sole aim of going viral is termed as viral marketing or viral advertising. Its name refers to how customers distribute knowledge about a product to other individuals as it spreads from one person to another like a viral chain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction into Facebook Marketing &amp; Facebook Advertising</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-into-facebook-marketing-facebook-advertising/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 20:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-into-facebook-marketing-facebook-advertising/</guid>
      <description>&#34;The best, authentic, great and very precise course on Facebook Marketing and Facebook Advertising. Though the course is just 10 hours, it covers the topics beyond anyone&#39;s expectations. I would rank this course #1 because the instructor Tomas takes the systematic and a very organized approach in training the students. I will enrol for another courses because it&#39;s just worth it. The course brilliantly and generously covers the entire topic without biases or prejudice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing B2B: Ultimate Digital Marketing Course B2B</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-marketing-b2b-ultimate-digital-marketing-course-b2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 13:36:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-marketing-b2b-ultimate-digital-marketing-course-b2b/</guid>
      <description>ATTENTION B2B DIGITAL MARKETING STUDENTS: Learn the strategies and nitty-gritty tactical details of acquiring business customers cheaply and quickly through digital marketing and modern social media marketing. Get executive-level training from a former VP of Marketing and college digital marketing instructor with Fortune 100 experience--at a fraction of the cost of an executive digital marketing training courses!This is the ultimate course on B2B digital marketing. I was a global marketing manager for Sony and a Vice President of Marketing for a Google accelerator startup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Digital Marketing Ad Using Google Adwords Express 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/run-digital-marketing-ad-using-google-adwords-express-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 21:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/run-digital-marketing-ad-using-google-adwords-express-2022/</guid>
      <description>If Google Adwords seems complicated then is course is for you ! We teach you how to market your business online with Google Adwords Express &amp;amp; grow business like a piece of cake!
Launch PPC ads campaign &amp;amp; advertise on Search, Display &amp;amp; Mobile Ads for traffic, sales, leads &amp;amp; calls for any business
Get more phone calls. Get more store visits. Direct potential customers to your website with optimized advertising</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Ads Google My Business &amp; Google Ads (Adwords) 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/facebook-ads-google-my-business-google-ads-adwords-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 16:38:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/facebook-ads-google-my-business-google-ads-adwords-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this course where you will learn to create your presence on Google Maps &amp;amp; Google searches. (Take this course so your business can appear on Google Map) Run facebook ads quick and easy and google ads aswell
Google’s search engine will ensure highest visibility for your business and will help you get customers when they are looking for you!We design this course for anyone seeking to launch a career in online marketing, Or anyone seeking to add a digital component to their existing marketing skill set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mit Online Marketing Dein Business aufbauen ohne Vorwissen!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mit-online-marketing-dein-business-aufbauen-ohne-vorwissen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 20:24:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mit-online-marketing-dein-business-aufbauen-ohne-vorwissen/</guid>
      <description>Letzte Aktualisierung: 28.4.2022
*** DER KURS WIRD LAUFEND ERWEITERT -&amp;gt; neue Inhalte jeden Monat! *** Digitales Marketing und insbesondere Online Marketing boomen seit einigen Jahren. Es herrscht eine Goldgräberstimmung, und genau JETZT hat es Sinn, sich mit Online Marketing auseinanderzusetzen - bevor es zu spät ist. Besonders jetzt, im Jahr 2022 explodiert der Online Traffic und die Werbepreise gehen herunter.
Der Einzelhandel, Unternehmer und Selbständige sind aufgrund der aktuellen Lage gezwungen, ihre Produkte immer mehr online zu verkaufen - und kaum jemand ist wirklich darauf vorbereitet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Digital Marketing Strategy For 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-digital-marketing-strategy-for-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 20:24:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-digital-marketing-strategy-for-2022/</guid>
      <description>Learn and master powerful Digital Marketing Strategy to become successful at any marketing campaigns, attracting people and making them your customer.
This Complete Digital Marketing Strategy For 2022 course will help you develop the skills needed to create a winning strategy for any business. This course serves as an introduction to digital marketing strategy and will familiarize you with the digital marketing landscape. By the end of this free course you will know how to use digital technologies to help identify opportunities at a minimum risk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversion Optimization Mastery 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/conversion-optimization-mastery-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 20:10:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/conversion-optimization-mastery-2022/</guid>
      <description>Increasing your website’s traffic is already a time-consuming task that will take up enough of your time. So, you need to make sure that traffic converts into sales, right?
There are simple ways of capturing attention, boosting conversion rates and ultimately, maximizing your profits without breaking the bank, or spending a lot of time tweaking your traffic campaigns.
The conversion boosting hacks featured in this report are ones that you can easily implement into your existing website without spending more than a couple of hours tightening up a few weak areas so that you can transform your business in just a matter of a few short days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lead Generation Mastery with Facebook Lead &amp; Messenger Ads</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lead-generation-mastery-with-facebook-lead-messenger-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 19:20:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/lead-generation-mastery-with-facebook-lead-messenger-ads/</guid>
      <description>Discover how to Quickly Attract a Constant Stream of New Customers with Targeted Facebook Messenger Ads, Facebook Lead Generation Ads, and Facebook Conversion Ads.
&#34;It is comprehensively structured Facebook Ads course giving clear guidance to get leads through different Facebook Ads strategies. It also explains different aspects highly helping to get more leads.&#34; Mirek
Dearest Student,
Hi, I’m Tomas Moravek, Internet Efficiency Awarded Digital Strategist and Professional Marketer, here to present my Facebook Lead, Messenger, and Conversion Ads Mastery Guide, so you can benefit from these Powerfully Effective automated marketing tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certified Lead Generation Professional | List Building Easy!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-lead-generation-professional-list-building-easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/certified-lead-generation-professional-list-building-easy/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to get visitors hooked on your brand and drive targeted leads with the Certified Lead Generation Professional | List Building Easy training course.
Still struggling to build a huge responsive list of targeted buyers to boost sales and profits?
This is your Ultimate Chance to Generate Tons Of Targeted Traffic To Your Offers &amp;amp; Boost Sales &amp;amp; Profits Without Spending Much…
Now you too can take your business to the next level with the best use of Certified Lead Generation Professional | List Building Easy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Email Marketing 2022. Increase sales with Email Marketing!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/email-marketing-2022.-increase-sales-with-email-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 13:12:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/email-marketing-2022.-increase-sales-with-email-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Email marketing is one of the most effective tools that exist for repeat customer communication. It solves many tasks, such as getting feedback, repeating sales, building loyalty, and delivering content to the consumer.
With SendPulse Academy we prepared for you an Email Marketing course to help you to implement this instrument in your business or digital marketing career.
In this Email Marketing course you will learn:
Why do businesses need email marketing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn 6 SIMPLE Steps to Make Money on TikTok App!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-6-simple-steps-to-make-money-on-tiktok-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:37:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-6-simple-steps-to-make-money-on-tiktok-app/</guid>
      <description>How would you feel like when making $10,000&#39;s just by using your smartphone?
Benefits of Making Money on TikTok App:
You can do this worldwide!
You can make money for 100% FREE!
TikTok is the most downloaded app in the world right now!
Steps are really SIMPLE!
The earning potential is HUGE!
--
While I can&#39;t guarantee you any money (by law) but let me tell you a short story from my own life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>التسويق الالكتروني: احترف عمل الإعلانات باستخدام علم النفس</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AA%D8%B3%D9%88%D9%8A%D9%82-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%83%D8%AA%D8%B1%D9%88%D9%86%D9%8A-%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D9%81-%D8%B9%D9%85%D9%84-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A5%D8%B9%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%86%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D8%A8%D8%A7%D8%B3%D8%AA%D8%AE%D8%AF%D8%A7%D9%85-%D8%B9%D9%84%D9%85-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%86%D9%81%D8%B3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:37:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AA%D8%B3%D9%88%D9%8A%D9%82-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%83%D8%AA%D8%B1%D9%88%D9%86%D9%8A-%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D9%81-%D8%B9%D9%85%D9%84-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A5%D8%B9%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%86%D8%A7%D8%AA-%D8%A8%D8%A7%D8%B3%D8%AA%D8%AE%D8%AF%D8%A7%D9%85-%D8%B9%D9%84%D9%85-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%86%D9%81%D8%B3/</guid>
      <description>الهدف من هذا الكورس هو تحقيق نتائج أفضل من الإعلانات علي الإنترنت، وهو مصمم بشكل خاص للمهتمين بمجال التسويق الالكتروني، التجارةالالكترونية، و أصحاب المشاريع الصغيرة
الكورس مبني علي مئات الأبحاث الخاصة بسلوك المستهلكين والإعلانات علي الإنترنت مع أمثلة واقعية لإعلانات من كبري الشركات العالمية... والكورس مكون من 7 فصول، خلاها ستتم مناقشة 7 مواضيع مهمة بأي اعلان علي الانترنت:
1- الصور: ستعرف كيف تختار الصور الأفضل لإعلانك، ومن خلال هذه الصور يمكنك أن تشد انتباه المشاهدين وتزيد من تفاعلهم مع الإعلان بشكل أفضل</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogging &amp; Affiliate Mastery in 2022 [ HINDI ]</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/blogging-affiliate-mastery-in-2022-hindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 18:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/blogging-affiliate-mastery-in-2022-hindi/</guid>
      <description>What Students have to say about this course from Reviews ..!! &#34;I am a beginner in blogging that&#39;s why I watch lots of video on digital marketing but in this course, I found very useful and some very good ideas, strategies to start my career in blogging field if you a beginner or thinking to start blogging you will be registered this course and gain very useful knowledge &#34; - Siddhant Jain</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power of Quora : A to Z of Earning from Quora  &amp; Ads (HINDI)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/power-of-quora-a-to-z-of-earning-from-quora-ads-hindi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/power-of-quora-a-to-z-of-earning-from-quora-ads-hindi/</guid>
      <description>This course is in HINDI and covers A to Z on Quora with 2 Sections covering Quora Earning, Quora marketing &amp;amp; Quora Ads.
Earning using Quora
Quora helps in getting traffic to your money sites which can be your business website or blog website or YouTube channel known as Quora Marketing.
Quora has earning options within using which content creator on Quora Profile and Quora Spaces can start earning money directly from Quora.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systeme Sales Funnels - Free Sales Funnels Tool Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/systeme-sales-funnels-free-sales-funnels-tool-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/systeme-sales-funnels-free-sales-funnels-tool-guide/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Complete Online Business Marketing Tool - Guide to Systeme!
For a long time, marketers have had to piece together various tools and software tools in order to achieve their goals. But these days, marketers are constantly being confronted with new platforms, new startup companies, and old favorites that are constantly re-tooling themselves and shifting their strategies.
In this rapid-fire internet era of marketing, it can be hard for even the most seasoned professionals to keep up with everything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Text-To-Video Creation Course (2021 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-text-to-video-creation-course-2021-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-text-to-video-creation-course-2021-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the ninth course in the series &#34;MBA in Creative Arts, Design and Animation&#34;.
One of the best things about podcasts is the ability to explore things in-depth, without boiling it all down into a 30 or 60-second sound bite. But typically podcasts pose a subsequent challenge for everyone. The challenge of conversions. What is the best way to encourage those longer social media conversations?
The answer to this is &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Artificial Intelligence in Digital Marketing Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-artificial-intelligence-in-digital-marketing-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:30:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-artificial-intelligence-in-digital-marketing-course/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the second course in Term 1 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;. This superb and highly Advanced Artificial Intelligence in Digital Marketing Course is set to put a ding in the world of digital marketing in 2021 and beyond. Did you know? During the projection period of 2021-2026, the global Artificial Intelligence Market size and share revenue is predicted to expand at a 35.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turn Your Idea into a Stunning Marketing Video in minutes!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/turn-your-idea-into-a-stunning-marketing-video-in-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 17:47:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/turn-your-idea-into-a-stunning-marketing-video-in-minutes/</guid>
      <description>Videos are critical for your marketing. A short promotional video can increase your sales by 200% according Udemy report. How to create engaging video or Promotion video for your Udemy course, your social media? Learn to create marketing videos for Instagram stories, Facebook videos, Whatsapp videos, etc. to promote your business, Take the cost, time etc. into consideration, here are the best we know for you! Turn Your Idea into a Stunning Video in minutes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Automatisierung mit Webinaris</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/marketing-automatisierung-mit-webinaris/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 12:36:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/marketing-automatisierung-mit-webinaris/</guid>
      <description>Wie Du Webinare nutzt, um Deinen Umsatz zu verdreifachen...
... und das vollautomatisiert, ohne Dein ständiges Zutun.
Webinare sind zur Zeit eins der verkaufsstärkste Umsatzkanal
Wenn Du ein Coaching, ein Produkt oder eine Dienstleistung verkaufen willst, bist Du hier goldrichtig!
Wenn Du Deine Marke oder Firma bekannter machen willst, bist Du hier goldrichtig!
Wenn Du das Vertrauen Deiner Kunden gewinnen willst, bist Du hier goldrichtig!
Wenn Du Deine Mitarbeiter schnell und reibungslos schulen willst, bist Du hier goldrichtig!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Online Marketing: Mehr Umsatz mit erfolgreichen Split Tests!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/online-marketing-mehr-umsatz-mit-erfolgreichen-split-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 21:20:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/online-marketing-mehr-umsatz-mit-erfolgreichen-split-tests/</guid>
      <description>Vielleicht fragst Du Dich, warum ich Dich mit dieser Webseite überhaupt anspreche. Am besten, ich erzähle Dir kurz meine Geschichte:
Ich war lange im Online Marketing aktiv und hatte irgendwann das Gefühl, keine echte Kontrolle über meine Aktivitäten zu haben. Ich versuchte die ganze Zeit, meine Lead-Kosten zu senken, aber viel zu viele Gründe sorgten für die hohen Preise.
Mit der Zeit war ich ziemlich überwältigt und frustriert, weshalb trotz hoher Kosten meine Conversion Rate so niedrig war.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ActiveCampaign Email Automation Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/activecampaign-email-automation-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 11:05:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/activecampaign-email-automation-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Get your FREEDOM back as a business owner by putting your business on autopilot!
Using automation software like ActiveCampaign significantly improves your CUSTOMER SERVICE experience, make your customer RESPONSE TIMES immediate and remove almost all of the admin in your business once implemented.
ActiveCampaign is an incredibly powerful piece of software, for online business owners and entrepreneurs, that does far more for you and your business than just sending emails.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cursul complet de marketing digital - 15 cursuri în 1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cursul-complet-de-marketing-digital-15-cursuri-%C3%AEn-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 14:59:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cursul-complet-de-marketing-digital-15-cursuri-%C3%AEn-1/</guid>
      <description>Cu peste 16 ore de videoclipuri, teste și pași practici pe care îi puteți urma - acesta este cel mai cuprinzător curs de marketing digital în română. Vom acoperi SEO, YouTube Marketing, Facebook Marketing, Google Ads, Google Analytics și multe altele!
Învață prin practică!
Cursul este extrem de interactiv, cu proiecte, liste de verificare și lecții acționabile în fiecare secțiune.
Află pas cu pas cum să comercializezi o afacere online de la zero pe toate canalele majore de marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merch By Amazon/Doğrudan Çin&#39;den Destek ile CJ Dropshipping</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/merch-by-amazon/do%C4%9Frudan-%C3%A7inden-destek-ile-cj-dropshipping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 20:28:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/merch-by-amazon/do%C4%9Frudan-%C3%A7inden-destek-ile-cj-dropshipping/</guid>
      <description>Selamlar, Ben Akın Yılmaz... “Merch By Amazon/Doğrudan Çin&#39;den Destek ile CJ Dropshipping ” kursuna hoş geldiniz.
Merch By Amazoni;
Pazarlamacı, tasarımcı mısınız yoksa sadece evde t-shirt satarak ek gelir elde etmek isteyenler mi?
O halde doğru yerdesiniz! Bu kursta, çevrimiçi bir iş kurmanın yeni ve sıcak bir yolunu sizinle paylaşacağım -
Merch by Amazon ile t-shirt fikirlerinizi Amazon&#39;da herhangi bir envanter olmadan satabileceksiniz. Tek yapmanız gereken bir bilgisayar ve Amazon hesabından bir ürün , tasarımınızı yüklemek , ziyaretçileri çekmek , sonra biraz kar etmeye başlamak.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Automation in Digital Marketing (2021 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/extreme-automation-in-digital-marketing-2021-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 21:51:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/extreme-automation-in-digital-marketing-2021-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the third course in Term 1 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
What things actually come to mind when you think of the term &#34;Extreme Marketing Automation&#34;? Automation is not as easy as clicking over and off to watch the employed marketing robot workers do the work, but rather is an ongoing process to track and develop our web marketing strategy. Like all other aspects of the online marketing environment, automation must be accompanied by a tested approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern Niche Marketing: Niche Website for Beginners!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/modern-niche-marketing-niche-website-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 18:49:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/modern-niche-marketing-niche-website-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Two Certificates for the Price of One! Finish your Udemy course and Contact us to get your Continuing Professional Development (CPD) Certificate!
Are You Ready For Niche Marketing Profits?
It&#39;s About Time For You To Master Niche Marketing!
Don&#39;t believe the hype – niche marketing does work if you do it accurately.
Niche websites are being traded every day for vast amounts of money.
Indeed, there is infinite competition these days which means that you have to be intelligent to succeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10X Amazon/eBay/Etsy Dropshipping Envanter ve Satış Yönetimi</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/10x-amazon/ebay/etsy-dropshipping-envanter-ve-sat%C4%B1%C5%9F-y%C3%B6netimi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 23:02:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/10x-amazon/ebay/etsy-dropshipping-envanter-ve-sat%C4%B1%C5%9F-y%C3%B6netimi/</guid>
      <description>Selamlar, Ben Akın Yılmaz... “10X Amazon/eBay/Etsy Dropshipping Envanter ve Satış Yönetimi” kursuna hoş geldiniz.
Yalnızca eBay&#39;de, yalnızca Etsy&#39;de veya yalnızca Amazon&#39;da satış yapmak isteyebilirsiniz. İstersen neden üçünü de başarılı bir şekilde satmayı öğrenmiyorsun? Bu, yalnızca bu sitelerin her birinde satış yapmakla ilgili bilgilerle doludur. Başlamak için gerekli bilgileri içerir. Kazanç potansiyeliniz sınırsızdır. Adım adım talimatları ve bu sitelerde satışta başarılı olmak için gerekenleri inceleyeceğiz.
Bilmeniz gerekenler ve dikkat etmeniz gerekenler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home Business: The Complete CPA Marketing Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/home-business-the-complete-cpa-marketing-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/home-business-the-complete-cpa-marketing-course/</guid>
      <description>Subtitles / Closed-Captions are available for ALL lectures!Even if you&#39;re a complete beginner, this course will teach you how to use CPA (Cost Per Action) to create a business that makes money while you sleep.
You&#39;ll be able to generate profits without having to sell any products, and you&#39;ll set up a legitimate online business quickly and easily.
Use CPA to Establish a Successful Online Business and Generate Consistent Income</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete List Building Course: All Levels</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-list-building-course-all-levels/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-list-building-course-all-levels/</guid>
      <description>&#34;SUPER-FAST &amp;amp; TOP-SECRET, EFFECTIVE LIST BUILDING TECHNIQUES THAT I USE TO GET 10,000+ SUBSCRIBERS EACH AND EVERY MONTH! - THIS WORKS NO MATTER WHERE YOU LIVE IN THE WORLD!&#34; You can get thousands of HUNGRY BUYERS waiting for YOUR OFFERS within a FEW DAYS! I am going to reveal to you the exact strategies I have been using to build my lists and collect thousands of subscribers in no time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing Ultimate Course Bundle - 13 Courses in 1</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-marketing-ultimate-course-bundle-13-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 13:24:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-marketing-ultimate-course-bundle-13-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Digital Marketing Ultimate Course Bundle - 13 Courses in 1 (Over 27 hours of content)
In this practical hands-on training, you’re going to learn to become a digital marketing expert with this ultimate course bundle that includes 13 digital marketing courses in 1!
Blending practical work with solid theoretical training, this course takes you from the basics of Digital Marketing to mastery, giving you the training you need not just to build Sales funnels, generate leads using Email, Facebook ads, Google ads, LinkedIn and SEO but also how to build websites and create amazing videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Powerful Instagram Sales Funnel to Grow Your Business</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/powerful-instagram-sales-funnel-to-grow-your-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 13:42:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/powerful-instagram-sales-funnel-to-grow-your-business/</guid>
      <description>Instagram has over 700 million active users ready to discover your brand. However, there’s no clear way to drive traffic back to your website and get sales. The solution lays in building powerful Instagram sales funnel to convert someone browsing into a customer. In this class, we will discuss: How you can transition a customer from discovering your brand to following you &amp;amp; eventually purchasing from you
How to track your customer&#39;s behavior &amp;amp; retarget them until they purchase from you</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing Agency Elite Consultants Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-marketing-agency-elite-consultants-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:15:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-marketing-agency-elite-consultants-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>LEARN HOW YOU CAN GROW A SUCCESSFUL​ MARKETING AGENCY... in as little as 30 days or less as Juan pulls back the curtain on how you can get paid high monthly retainers and even if you have no prior marketing experience.
I&#39;ve done the painful leg work so that you don&#39;t have to. When I first started, I struggled to get clients because I had no confidence. I was unsure how to get results or even how to sell and close clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEST of SEO: #1 SEO Training &amp; Content Marketing Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/best-of-seo-#1-seo-training-content-marketing-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/best-of-seo-#1-seo-training-content-marketing-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>In our increasingly online world, if you want to be successful, you need the latest digital skills. In this SEO &amp;amp; CONTENT MARKETING MASTERY course, I bring you CONSTANTLY UPDATED CUTTING-EDGE STRATEGIES AND TECHNIQUES so you can THRIVE in Content Marketing and SEO. This is my brand new 2021 SEO Training and Content Marketing Course! Now UPDATED to include many more topics to give you EVEN MORE VALUE and ensure your and SEO Success, with input from multiple experts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversion Rate Optimization CRO: B2B Conversion Rate CRO</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/conversion-rate-optimization-cro-b2b-conversion-rate-cro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/conversion-rate-optimization-cro-b2b-conversion-rate-cro/</guid>
      <description>Learn B2B (business-to-business) conversation rate optimization (conversion rate optimisation / CRO) to maximize leads and paying customers. Optimize the entire growth marketing funnel using tactical and strategic conversion maximization approaches from a top MBA with Fortune 100 experience and master&#39;s level analytics training. -&amp;gt; Real examples from my own experience in driving growth for companies of various sizes including Sony and a Google-accelerator startup
-&amp;gt; Advice from my colleagues who drove growth for top companies including LinkedIn and Sephora</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Marketing Agency: Grow Your Digital Marketing Agency</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-marketing-agency-grow-your-digital-marketing-agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digital-marketing-agency-grow-your-digital-marketing-agency/</guid>
      <description>This is the ultimate course on growing your digital marketing agency &amp;amp; getting more clients. I worked for a digital marketing agency for 5 years. I also worked as an independent consultant. As a global marketing manager for Sony, I worked with some of the top marketing agencies in the world including Digitas, Mediacom, and Publicis. I taught college level digital marketing and I have an MBA from the top business school for marketing--the Kellogg School of Management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Money Online With Digital Product Launch</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/make-money-online-with-digital-product-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/make-money-online-with-digital-product-launch/</guid>
      <description>take this 9 Days Journey with me to create, craft and launch your digital course product and program. start selling Instantly.
Do you want to overcome your all financial problems? and start your business online?
Have you always sought to create and launch a digital product but stuck with the process?
Are you having a hard time doing it as it requires a huge Investment, Time and Energy?
Would you prefer a better, Simpler, Easier and Faster way to launch your digital product or program?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storytelling Marketing Mastery 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/storytelling-marketing-mastery-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/storytelling-marketing-mastery-2021/</guid>
      <description>Story telling can be a powerful component in a marketing strategy. It can be the driving force behind developing, and more importantly, establishing a brand that connects and resonates with your target audience.
It’s also the easiest way to express emotions and illustrate your commitment to providing value.
There’s nothing more powerful than a carefully crafted story that fulfills the needs of your core market.
In this special course, you will learn top story-telling methods, how to best use these strategies and how you can use storytelling to strengthen your brand or launch a new one.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
