<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Accounting &amp; Bookkeeping on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/accounting-bookkeeping/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Accounting &amp; Bookkeeping on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/accounting-bookkeeping/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Aplos Not for Profit Accounting Software</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/aplos-not-for-profit-accounting-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/aplos-not-for-profit-accounting-software/</guid>
      <description>Learners will understand how to set up Aplos, software specifically designed for Not for Profit Organizations.
The course will show how to use free resources to optimize learning.
We will demonstrate the use of funds and tags to generate Not for Profit reports.
The course will demonstrate how to enter and track restricted resources.
We will enter month end adjusting entries.
Learners will see how to allocate expenses to programs and administrative categories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xero Not for Profit Organization</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/xero-not-for-profit-organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/xero-not-for-profit-organization/</guid>
      <description>Learners will understand how to set up Xero for a Not for Profit Organization.
The course will show how to use free resources to optimize learning.
We will demonstrate the use of category tracking to generate Not for Profit reports.
Learners will see how to create and use donation receipt forms.
We will show how to create and use pledge receipt forms.
The course will demonstrate how to enter and track restricted resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GST Returns 2021 Course (Live Working) : Get Certified Today</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/gst-returns-2021-course-live-working-get-certified-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 10:47:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/gst-returns-2021-course-live-working-get-certified-today/</guid>
      <description>Aim &amp;amp; Future Prospects:
The aim of the course is to help individuals, businessman, accountants, CAs and other professionals to upgrade their knowledge regarding the Goods and Services Tax by offering most of the real time practical knowledge on GST Portal in an updated and systematic approach that help them to accelerate their skills and knowledge required for self-employment &amp;amp; employment at industrial level as well.
Benefits of the course:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop Multiple Currencies</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-desktop-multiple-currencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 10:06:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-desktop-multiple-currencies/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to get access to QuickBooks Desktop including a possible free 30-day trial version often offered by Intuit, the owner of QuickBooks Desktop.
The course will discuss accounting for multiple currencies, outlining the process in Excel to provide a more transparent look at the process. Then we will enter the transactions into QuickBooks, the software automating some of the steps required.
We will learn how to turn multicurrency on, and which accounts will be affected most by multicurrency transactions including cash account types, accounts receivable account types, and accounts payable account types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Inventory Management in Microsoft Excel &amp;TALLY ERP9</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-inventory-management-in-microsoft-excel-tally-erp9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-inventory-management-in-microsoft-excel-tally-erp9/</guid>
      <description>Recent Student&#39;s Reviews

*** This course is well detailed in inventory management. I really learnt how to make practical use of excel, tally ERP9 and good inventory valuation (Williams Oguamah) ***

**Yes it is a good match for me. It will help me in my career path ( Dineo ) ***

*** it was awesome to learn &amp;amp; get insights from this course (Haritha.L) ***

*** Very Helpful (JULIUS IGNACIO)***</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank Feeds-QuickBooks Online, Xero, Sage, Wave (Comparison)</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/bank-feeds-quickbooks-online-xero-sage-wave-comparison/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/bank-feeds-quickbooks-online-xero-sage-wave-comparison/</guid>
      <description>Bank Feed Options
This course will compare and contrast the top accounting software applications, focusing on the use of bank feeds.
We will provide practice data that learners can import into the software applications.
Learners will understand the process of setting up each online software package. We will also discuss purchase options.
Most of the software applications will include a free test drive, an excellent tool for learning accounting and bank feeds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process Costing System-Cost Accounting-Managerial Accounting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/process-costing-system-cost-accounting-managerial-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/process-costing-system-cost-accounting-managerial-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Process costing system – Cost Accounting – Managerial Accounting
We will start by introducing managerial accounting or cost accounting topics that apply to companies that manufacture using either a job cost system or a process cost system.
The course will describe classifications for costs and the importance of being able to classify costs in different ways.
We will list and describe an outline of the process costs go through as they flow through the accounting process in a manufacturing company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate TallyPrime With GST Step By Step Guide - 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/ultimate-tallyprime-with-gst-step-by-step-guide-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/ultimate-tallyprime-with-gst-step-by-step-guide-2021/</guid>
      <description>Recent Student&#39;s Reviews

***Clearly understand what is tally prime in this full lecture.Thank you so much sir.(Rizwan Mohamed Y)***

***Covers every chapter, step by step learning for everyone (Vivekanandan Jayakumar)***

*** 1. Short and crisp to the point and no beating around the bush.
2. Very clear explanation with relevant examples
Course updated to the latest version
3. Those who are well aware of accounting concepts and manual accounting, may choose to skip section 2&amp;amp;3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Governmental Accounting 200 Capital Projects &amp; Debt Service</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/governmental-accounting-200-capital-projects-debt-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/governmental-accounting-200-capital-projects-debt-service/</guid>
      <description>The course will focus on larger capital projects and the use of a capital project fund and debt service fund to track them.
We will cover governmental accounting objective, which will be a review from governmental accounting 100.
The course will discuss what capital assets are and how they are recorded in governmental accounting, comparing governmental accounting to for-profit accounting.
Students will learn to record transactions for the issuance of bonds used to finance capital projects, recording transactions at the government-wide level and in the capital project fund, debts service fund, and general fund.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accounting–Financial Accounting Total-Beginners to Advanced</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/accountingfinancial-accounting-total-beginners-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 11:43:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/accountingfinancial-accounting-total-beginners-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Recently updated with A LOT of added content.
Includes downloadable e-book in multiple formats so you can open it on your tablet or Kindle - Formats (EPUB, MOBI, PDF).
This course is an excellent supplement for students or anybody who wants to learn accounting and also have something they can refer back to in the future. Udemy generally provides lifetime access to the course.
Many accounting students do not receive a physical book, they get to keep from their school, and even if they did, the information could become dated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audit - Financial Statement</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/audit-financial-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/audit-financial-statement/</guid>
      <description>Audit-Financial Accounting will discuss, in detail, the auditing process of financial statements.
The course will start by discussing what an audit is, as well as what the terms attest engagement and assurances services mean.
We will discuss the audit environment, the general format of a public accounting firm, and the general format of an audit team that would conduct the procedures related to an audit. The course will also discuss regulations and regulatory institutions related to the audit process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Relevant Costs - Managerial Accounting Decisions &amp; Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/relevant-costs-managerial-accounting-decisions-scenarios/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/relevant-costs-managerial-accounting-decisions-scenarios/</guid>
      <description>Apply relevant cost methods to common managerial decisions.
Managers often need to make decisions that are not routine, not part of the normal day to day process, and that can have a long-term effect on the organization. Individuals often need to make similar decisions and can apply similar tools when making decisions of a large dollar amount that can affect multiple years.
Although the specifics of each decision differ, the concept of relevant costs helps us put together a process for gathering and analyzing data, picking up the information that matters, and removing all the excess data that does not matter to our decision.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tally Erp 9 &#43; Tally Prime &#43; GST  2021 - Certificate Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tally-erp-9-tally-prime-gst-2021-certificate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 22:18:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/tally-erp-9-tally-prime-gst-2021-certificate-course/</guid>
      <description>Complete Tally Course from Zero to Hero in Tally Erp 9 + Tally Prime with Advance GST Course
Get Constant Growth in your career/Business with Advance Tally GST Online Course
Best Seller Course
What you’ll learn in this Tally Erp9 + Tally Prime Online Training
Accounting of Any Company with GST Independently in Tally Erp9 &amp;amp; Tally Prime
From Manual Accounting to Advance GST Reports in Tally Erp9 &amp;amp; Tally Prime</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tally Prime Erp &#43;GST 2021 : Certificate Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tally-prime-erp-gst-2021-certificate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 22:18:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/tally-prime-erp-gst-2021-certificate-course/</guid>
      <description>--**New in Tally Prime Erp with GST **--
-&amp;gt;Better Control Over Cash Flow
-&amp;gt;Enhanced Business Efficiency
-&amp;gt;Tax Compliance Made Easy

From the Bestseller of Tally Erp9 with GST
Best Rated for Eway Bill
Best Rated for GST Returns

Complete Tally Course from Zero to Hero in Tally Prime Erp with Advance GST Course
Get Constant Growth in your career/Business with Advance Tally PRIME GST Online Course
Best Seller Course</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wave Accounting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/wave-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/wave-accounting/</guid>
      <description>This course will use free accounting software which is an excellent tool to practice with.
This course will jump right into bank feeds and how to use them.
Many accounting software courses will spend a lot of time talking about how a full-service accounting system works. We do recommend spending time learning the full accounting process, and we do have courses that do just that.
However, many small businesses want to get right down to data input as fast as possible, and others already have a good understanding of the system and want to focus specifically on bank feeds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Financial Accounting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/advanced-financial-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/advanced-financial-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Advanced financial accounting will focus heavily on intercorporate acquisitions and investments in other entities.
Why learn advanced accounting?
Even if we do not work in an area that applies advanced accounting concepts directly, learning them is very useful, because it refines our skills on the understanding of double-entry accounting, its concepts, and practical application.
Advanced financial accounting is also a standardized topic often found on exams like the CPA exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop Not for Profit Organizations</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-desktop-not-for-profit-organizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-desktop-not-for-profit-organizations/</guid>
      <description>QuickBooks Desktop Not for Profit Organizations will provide the tools to enter data into QuickBooks for a not for profit organization.
This QuickBooks course will consist of three comprehensive practice problems. One problem will be for a charitable organization, one for a health care organization, and one for a not for profit school.
We will learn how to set up a QuickBooks file for a not for profit organization.
The course will show how to create a chart of accounts and items list for a not for profit organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not-for-Profit Accounting-Charities, Colleges, &amp; Health Care</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/not-for-profit-accounting-charities-colleges-health-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/not-for-profit-accounting-charities-colleges-health-care/</guid>
      <description>Not for Profit Accounting-Charities, Colleges, &amp;amp; Health Care will cover accounting principles related to not for profit organizations.
Our concentration will be on nongovernmental not-for-profit organizations. However, we will discuss the differences between nongovernmental not for profit organization and governmental not-for-profit organizations. We will also discuss accounting concepts for both governmental and nongovernmental organizations related to health care and colleges.
The course will start by introducing what a not for profit organization is.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
