<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Accounting &amp; Bookkeeping on </title>
    <link>/tags/accounting-bookkeeping/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Accounting &amp; Bookkeeping on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/accounting-bookkeeping/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Wave Accounting</title>
      <link>/wave-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 22:31:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/wave-accounting/</guid>
      <description>This course will use free accounting software which is an excellent tool to practice with.
This course will jump right into bank feeds and how to use them.
Many accounting software courses will spend a lot of time talking about how a full-service accounting system works. We do recommend spending time learning the full accounting process, and we do have courses that do just that.
However, many small businesses want to get right down to data input as fast as possible, and others already have a good understanding of the system and want to focus specifically on bank feeds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Financial Accounting</title>
      <link>/advanced-financial-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/advanced-financial-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Advanced financial accounting will focus heavily on intercorporate acquisitions and investments in other entities.
Why learn advanced accounting?
Even if we do not work in an area that applies advanced accounting concepts directly, learning them is very useful, because it refines our skills on the understanding of double-entry accounting, its concepts, and practical application.
Advanced financial accounting is also a standardized topic often found on exams like the CPA exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop Not for Profit Organizations</title>
      <link>/quickbooks-desktop-not-for-profit-organizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/quickbooks-desktop-not-for-profit-organizations/</guid>
      <description>QuickBooks Desktop Not for Profit Organizations will provide the tools to enter data into QuickBooks for a not for profit organization.
This QuickBooks course will consist of three comprehensive practice problems. One problem will be for a charitable organization, one for a health care organization, and one for a not for profit school.
We will learn how to set up a QuickBooks file for a not for profit organization.
The course will show how to create a chart of accounts and items list for a not for profit organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate TallyPrime With GST Step By Step Guide - 2021</title>
      <link>/ultimate-tallyprime-with-gst-step-by-step-guide-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2021 18:00:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ultimate-tallyprime-with-gst-step-by-step-guide-2021/</guid>
      <description>Recent Student&#39;s Reviews

***Clearly understand what is tally prime in this full lecture.Thank you so much sir.(Rizwan Mohamed Y)***

***Covers every chapter, step by step learning for everyone (Vivekanandan Jayakumar)***

*** 1. Short and crisp to the point and no beating around the bush.
2. Very clear explanation with relevant examples
Course updated to the latest version
3. Those who are well aware of accounting concepts and manual accounting, may choose to skip section 2&amp;amp;3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accounting–Financial Accounting Total-Beginners to Advanced</title>
      <link>/accountingfinancial-accounting-total-beginners-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 23:49:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/accountingfinancial-accounting-total-beginners-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Recently updated with A LOT of added content.
Includes downloadable e-book in multiple formats so you can open it on your tablet or Kindle - Formats (EPUB, MOBI, PDF).
This course is an excellent supplement for students or anybody who wants to learn accounting and also have something they can refer back to in the future. Udemy generally provides lifetime access to the course.
Many accounting students do not receive a physical book, they get to keep from their school, and even if they did, the information could become dated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Inventory Management in Microsoft Excel &amp;TALLY ERP9</title>
      <link>/complete-inventory-management-in-microsoft-excel-tally-erp9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/complete-inventory-management-in-microsoft-excel-tally-erp9/</guid>
      <description>Recent Student&#39;s Reviews

*** This course is well detailed in inventory management. I really learnt how to make practical use of excel, tally ERP9 and good inventory valuation (Williams Oguamah) ***

**Yes it is a good match for me. It will help me in my career path ( Dineo ) ***

*** it was awesome to learn &amp;amp; get insights from this course (Haritha.L) ***

*** Very Helpful (JULIUS IGNACIO)***</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Governmental Accounting 200 Capital Projects &amp; Debt Service</title>
      <link>/governmental-accounting-200-capital-projects-debt-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/governmental-accounting-200-capital-projects-debt-service/</guid>
      <description>The course will focus on larger capital projects and the use of a capital project fund and debt service fund to track them.
We will cover governmental accounting objective, which will be a review from governmental accounting 100.
The course will discuss what capital assets are and how they are recorded in governmental accounting, comparing governmental accounting to for-profit accounting.
Students will learn to record transactions for the issuance of bonds used to finance capital projects, recording transactions at the government-wide level and in the capital project fund, debts service fund, and general fund.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Not-for-Profit Accounting-Charities, Colleges, &amp; Health Care</title>
      <link>/not-for-profit-accounting-charities-colleges-health-care/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/not-for-profit-accounting-charities-colleges-health-care/</guid>
      <description>Not for Profit Accounting-Charities, Colleges, &amp;amp; Health Care will cover accounting principles related to not for profit organizations.
Our concentration will be on nongovernmental not-for-profit organizations. However, we will discuss the differences between nongovernmental not for profit organization and governmental not-for-profit organizations. We will also discuss accounting concepts for both governmental and nongovernmental organizations related to health care and colleges.
The course will start by introducing what a not for profit organization is.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
