<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Other Business on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/other-business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Other Business on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/other-business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Accounting-Bonds Payable, Notes Payable, Liabilities</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/accounting-bonds-payable-notes-payable-liabilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/accounting-bonds-payable-notes-payable-liabilities/</guid>
      <description>Bonds payable, notes payable, and liabilities will introduce the concept of bonds from a corporate perspective and explain how to record the issuance of bonds and notes payable. We will discuss the journal entry for issuing bonds at par value, at a discount, and at a premium. The course will cover present value calculations in multiple formats. Present value calculations are often confusing to learners partially because the topic can be introduced in many ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #8 Time Value of Money (PV &amp; FV)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#8-time-value-of-money-pv-fv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#8-time-value-of-money-pv-fv/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover time value of money concepts from a Corporate Finance perspective.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.
Time value of money concepts become more and more important as we consider decisions that will extend further into the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Course: Learn to Make Money Online WORLDWIDE!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cryptocurrency-course-learn-to-make-money-online-worldwide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cryptocurrency-course-learn-to-make-money-online-worldwide/</guid>
      <description>Last years have been HUGE for cryptocurrencies. Many millionaires were made all over the world. Technologies went forward and new innovations were created. On the other hand, many people lost money because they didn&#39;t know what they were doing. They threw money here and there because other people were doing so.
If you want to make money with cryptocurrencies you need to learn important action steps that I teach you in this course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence Expert Course &#43; Live Class</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-expert-course--live-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-expert-course--live-class/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience a mind-blowing &#34;Artificial Intelligence Expert Course&#34; in 2022.
Artificial Intelligence Expert Course: Platinum Edition - The course has now launched.
Artificial Intelligence (AI) seems to be a unique technology for making a machine, a robot fully autonomous. AI is an analysis of how the machine is thinking, studying, determining, and functioning when it is trying to solve problems.
These kinds of problems are present in all fields, the most emerging ones, and even beyond.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Individual Income Tax Form 1040 Comprehensive Problem</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/individual-income-tax-form-1040-comprehensive-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/individual-income-tax-form-1040-comprehensive-problem/</guid>
      <description>This is a project based income tax course. We will construct a complex tax return in a step by step format, beginning with a basic return &amp;amp; building complexity as we move forward. The course will demonstrate the data input within 2020 income tax forms as well as the use of an Excel worksheet to check the numbers and demonstrate the use of tax software. Using tax software &amp;amp; an Excel worksheet, formatted as the income tax equation, are common, and best practices for many tax professionals, practices that greatly increase understanding and accuracy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Market Research Test Quiz For Business Analysts (BAs)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/market-research-test-quiz-for-business-analysts-bas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/market-research-test-quiz-for-business-analysts-bas/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the quiz course &#34;Market Research Test Quiz For Business Analysts (BAs)&#34;.
Put your skills to the test by taking this incredible Business Analysis quiz that is focused primarily on market research!
Business Analysis (as you know it) is a research discipline of identifying business needs and determining appropriate solutions to business problems. Get ready to challenge yourself in this topic by taking this practice test course created by Marketing Legend &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accounting for Corporations</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/accounting-for-corporations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/accounting-for-corporations/</guid>
      <description>Accounting for corporations will cover components of corporate accounting that are unique to corporations, elements of corporate accounting that differ from financial accounting for other business entities like a sole proprietorship or partnership.
As we focus on the arias where corporate accounting differs from other business entities we want to keep in mind that most normal accounting transactions will be the same for any business entity type. We will have a comprehensive problem at the end of the course to allow us to take a step back and see the areas of accounting for corporations that differ in perspective with the areas that are the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innovation &amp; Startups: AB Testing Of KPI With Lean Startup</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/innovation-startups-ab-testing-of-kpi-with-lean-startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 20:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/innovation-startups-ab-testing-of-kpi-with-lean-startup/</guid>
      <description>1) Learn to start an innovative startup.
2) Learn to identify the right factors that will catalyze growth.
3) Use Google Analytics to monitor the correct metrics and KPI.
4) Use that data and insight to focus on and fix the right things.
5) Grow and succeed with your innovation or startup.
HOW TO GROW A STARTUP
Startup and innovative businesses must focus on growth. Most entrepreneurs focus on money too quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundraising: 10&#43; Fundraising Ideas For Raising Capital</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundraising-10-fundraising-ideas-for-raising-capital/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2022 20:40:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundraising-10-fundraising-ideas-for-raising-capital/</guid>
      <description>10+ unique and actionable ways to raise money and learn to use each strategy to get closer to your dreams. Includes my 200-page business plan book, which is used by a number of universities.
If you are in the process of raising money for your business or wondering how to begin the fundraising process, this course will give you a wide range of fundraising strategies, help you get organized and maximize your chances of success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Internet of Things (IoT): 2022 Trends and the Future</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-internet-of-things-iot-2022-trends-and-the-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 16:26:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-internet-of-things-iot-2022-trends-and-the-future/</guid>
      <description>A grand welcome to learn &#34;The Internet of Things (IoT): 2022 Trends and the Future&#34;.
Did you know? Learning the topic of &#39;Internet of Things (IoT)&#39; can prove to be vital to help in your career. An exciting stream of future IoT applications will arise starting from 2022-2025 that would bring computer interactivity to life. The new-age concept of IoT will allow people to interact over great distances in real-time – both with each other and with machines – and this may create sensory experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Personal Assistant Development (2022 Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/virtual-personal-assistant-development-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 16:26:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/virtual-personal-assistant-development-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>These days chatbots are the talk of the town. In Facebook Messenger, you&#39;ll see them in abundance. What may be the reason behind this unexpected surge in chatbots? How did they become so popular? What are the benefits of using them? These are real questions to ponder about. Chatbots strive to assist and scale company teams in their customer relationships. Doing that lets companies save a lot of time, which is why this approach is being embraced by top business owners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digishock 3.0: The Future of Artificial Intelligence (AI)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digishock-3.0-the-future-of-artificial-intelligence-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:30:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/digishock-3.0-the-future-of-artificial-intelligence-ai/</guid>
      <description>Let&#39;s get this straight and to the point.
Man has long feared the rise of the machine, fearing that his own creation might become really smarter or intelligent and more sophisticated than he is. However, while AI and machine learning are rapidly altering our environment and propelling the Fourth Industrial Revolution, humanity does not need to be concerned. Artificial Intelligence (AI) will provide people with the ability to focus on the aspects of their occupations or jobs that are most rewarding to them and the time is coming soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Money From Home As a Transcriptionist: 10 Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/make-money-from-home-as-a-transcriptionist-10-opportunities/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 12:27:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/make-money-from-home-as-a-transcriptionist-10-opportunities/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to make money from home typing what you hear?
Do you like to make money online with flexible hours wherever you want?
Then this is the PERFECT UDEMY Course for you!
You&#39;re gonna find out the details about Making Money Online with 10 Transcription Jobs From Home and spot the best opportunities for you.
Over the years, I&#39;ve seen dozens of transcription jobs from home and you need to know the differences:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Freelancing: 37 Ways to Make Money From Home as a Freelancer</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/freelancing-37-ways-to-make-money-from-home-as-a-freelancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 21:51:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/freelancing-37-ways-to-make-money-from-home-as-a-freelancer/</guid>
      <description>Do you wanna have the FREEDOM to work at your own schedule?
Do you wanna have the FREEDOM to work anywhere you want?
Do you wanna have the FREEDOM of your life?
Then this is the right course for you.
You&#39;re gonna learn 37 Ways to Make Money From Home as a Freelancer.
But actually, you don&#39;t even need to be at home. You can be anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Money Online: Mindset Training &#43; Real-Life Examples</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/make-money-online-mindset-training--real-life-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 12:41:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/make-money-online-mindset-training--real-life-examples/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to have an UNSHAKEABLE CONFIDENCE that you WILL make a life-changing income online?
I&#39;ve shown the steps to make money online to 100,000&#39;s of people.
But even though many people know how to make money, very few of them actually take action.
It&#39;s not because they wouldn&#39;t know what to do but because they are AFRAID!
Most people don&#39;t have the right mindset and that&#39;s why they don&#39;t start even though they know step-by-step how to make money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundraising: Ask and Raise Contributions for Your Charity</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundraising-ask-and-raise-contributions-for-your-charity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 13:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fundraising-ask-and-raise-contributions-for-your-charity/</guid>
      <description>Fundraising. Imagine rising thousands or even millions of dollars for the non-profit or campaign of your choice. You can raise unlimited amounts of money, once you learn the right way of asking people.
You can become the greatest Fundraising financial asset your organization has ever had.
This course will teach you a step-by-step process to use when asking people to donate to your favorite charity, political campaign, university or college. You can raise money for causes you believe in, if you follow basic principles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>S Corporation Income Tax - Form 1120S</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/s-corporation-income-tax-form-1120s/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 19:42:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/s-corporation-income-tax-form-1120s/</guid>
      <description>This course currently consists of a comprehensive problem showing the data input process of an S Corporation tax return into Form 1120S. This course will put together a systematic format of entering data into a Form 1120S that will minimize errors, isolate problems as they happen, and remove the possibility of having to start the process all over again. We will enter each M-1 adjustment individually into both the tax return and an Excel worksheet so that we fully understand how they work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Membership Site: Membership Recurring Home Business Model</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/membership-site-membership-recurring-home-business-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/membership-site-membership-recurring-home-business-model/</guid>
      <description>Two Certificates for the Price of One! Finish your Udemy course and Contact us to get your Continuing Professional Development (CPD) Certificate!
Why Membership Sites Are Perfect For Passive Income?
If you’re interested in making money online, then it’s probably because you like the idea of having more freedom to live and work wherever and however you want. The benefits of working online are many and varied and extend into every aspect of your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Business</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 09:03:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-business/</guid>
      <description>This course is designed to teach anyone new to business with the basic understandings of the four fields of business (marketing, business administration/management, finance, and hospitality &amp;amp; tourism). The four sections of this course each pertain to one of the four area. In total this course has eighteen videos that total nearly an hour of covering some of the specifics of each field. We also have included over fifteen pages of in-depth information about distinct topics pertaining to a certain field.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
