<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Media on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Media on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Journalism -TV Reporters, News Anchors Look Great on TV</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/journalism-tv-reporters-news-anchors-look-great-on-tv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/journalism-tv-reporters-news-anchors-look-great-on-tv/</guid>
      <description>Journalism for Broadcast. Imagine appearing on a network newscast as a reporter or anchor and you look as confident, poised and articulate as any childhood idol you grew up watching. Wouldn&#39;t it be nice to know that you can look and sound exactly the way you want when you are conducting interviews or anchoring a newscast? In this On-Camera Skills for TV Reporters and News Anchors Journalism course you will learn the following: * How to look comfortable, confident and relaxed on TV * How to sound conversational * How to rehearse using video, and how to critique yourself * How to make constant on-air improvements *How to prepare for broadcast journalism</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Broadcaster Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/open-broadcaster-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/open-broadcaster-basics/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to do use Open Broadcaster but don’t know where to start? Would you like to learn how to use Open Broadcaster? Then Open Broadcaster Basics is for you! Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course. Open Broadcaster is a in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. We’ll Cover everything you need to know about Open Broadcaster Basics from scratch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journalism: Be a Great Talk Show Host</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/journalism-be-a-great-talk-show-host/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/journalism-be-a-great-talk-show-host/</guid>
      <description>Journalism. Imagine yourself hosting a talk show and you are coming across as engaging, likable and totally natural. Wouldn&#39;t it be nice to know that you can host any talk show and appear to be confident, relaxed, conversational and able to talk to guests in a meaningful way? In this How to Be a Talk Show Host Journalism course, you will learn the following: * The difference between being a good talk show guest versus a good host * How to look comfortable and confident on TV * How to appear natural and sound conversational * How to rehearse using video *How to be comfortable in the medium of broadcast journalism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Questions That Easily Write Nonfiction Books - Revolutionary</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/questions-that-easily-write-nonfiction-books-revolutionary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 13:12:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/questions-that-easily-write-nonfiction-books-revolutionary/</guid>
      <description>This is a superior way to write non-fiction books.
My name is Ian Stables, author of more than fifty Kindle books. Since I discovered this method, writing books has been so much easier and quicker.
In fact, you can do more than just write books with this process. You can use it to write anything, articles, essays, Kindle book descriptions, Udemy course descriptions, blog posts, emails, and even business reports. It&#39;s that versatile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Micro-influenceurs Instagram  2022 : partenariats rémunérés</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/micro-influenceurs-instagram-2022-partenariats-r%C3%A9mun%C3%A9r%C3%A9s/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 13:12:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/micro-influenceurs-instagram-2022-partenariats-r%C3%A9mun%C3%A9r%C3%A9s/</guid>
      <description>Bonne nouvelle !!
Les micro influenceurs Instagram ont plus que jamais le vent en poupe. Finie l&#39;époque où il fallait avoir des centaines de milliers d’abonnés pour cartonner sur Instagram. Les internautes veulent faire confiance aux gens qu&#39;ils suivent, ils veulent pouvoir s&#39;identifier à eux. Envie de devenir micro-influenceur et d&#39;être repéré et contacté par des marques sur Instagram ? Je te propose cette formation complète et surtout concrète pour devenir un micro-influenceur sur Instagram et décrocher des partenariats rémunérés avec différentes marques et en faire ainsi une véritable source de revenu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journalism: Conduct Great Media Interviews</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/journalism-conduct-great-media-interviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/journalism-conduct-great-media-interviews/</guid>
      <description>Journalism-you can become a skilled media interviewer. Imagine yourself conducting interviews with news-makers, industry experts and colleagues and appearing confident and authoritative the whole time. Wouldn&#39;t it be nice to know how to look and sound your best and come across as a skilled interviewer anytime you have a chance to ask people questions on video or audio? In this How to Conduct Interviews Journalism course you will learn the following: *How to conduct interviews with newsmakers and industry experts for video and audio programs and podcasts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
