<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Media on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Media on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Journalism: Be a Great Talk Show Host</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/journalism-be-a-great-talk-show-host/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/journalism-be-a-great-talk-show-host/</guid>
      <description>Journalism. Imagine yourself hosting a talk show and you are coming across as engaging, likable and totally natural. Wouldn&#39;t it be nice to know that you can host any talk show and appear to be confident, relaxed, conversational and able to talk to guests in a meaningful way?  In this How to be a Talk Show Host Journalism course, you will learn the following:  *The difference between being a good talk show guest versus a good host  *How to look comfortable and confident on TV  *How to appear natural and sound conversational  *How to rehearse using video *How to be comfortable in the medium of broadcast journalism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journalism: Conduct Great Media Interviews</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/journalism-conduct-great-media-interviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/journalism-conduct-great-media-interviews/</guid>
      <description>Journalism-you can become a skilled media interviewer. Imagine yourself conducting interviews with news-makers, industry experts and colleagues and appearing confident and authoritative the whole time. Wouldn&#39;t it be nice to know how to look and sound your best and come across as a skilled interviewer anytime you have a chance to ask people questions on video or audio?  In this How to Conduct Interviews Journalism course you will learn the following:  *How to conduct interviews with newsmakers and industry experts for video and audio programs and podcasts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
