<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stress Management on </title>
    <link>/tags/stress-management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stress Management on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 09:14:03 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/stress-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Resilience Masterclass: Build a Refugee Mindset for Survival</title>
      <link>/resilience-masterclass-build-a-refugee-mindset-for-survival/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 09:14:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resilience-masterclass-build-a-refugee-mindset-for-survival/</guid>
      <description>Resilience Masterclass: Build a Refuge Mindset for Survival to Thrival
The Resilience Mindset- Survival Tips for the Worst Time of Your Life - For Refugees &amp;amp; Those Who Want Survival Skills
Refugees are persons who are outside their country of origin for reasons of feared persecution, conflict, generalized violence, or other circumstances that have seriously disturbed public order and, as a result, require international protection. This is what I experience. I will help you to prepare and get ready mentally and physically to travel and be a successful refugee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Over a Break up</title>
      <link>/how-to-get-over-a-break-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/how-to-get-over-a-break-up/</guid>
      <description>Breakups blow chunks. Whether it’s an amicable breakup or a horrible, crash-and-burn situation, you’ve invested a part of you into another person and must accept that a relationship that you once nurtured is dead and gone. Brain-mapping studies have shown that the same regions of the brain are activated when an addict is going through withdrawals as when someone is going through a breakup.
Whether the relationship lasted three weeks or three years, breakups can leave us feeling heartbroken, lost and even physically ill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effective Time Management Skills For A Productivity Boost</title>
      <link>/effective-time-management-skills-for-a-productivity-boost/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 11:42:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/effective-time-management-skills-for-a-productivity-boost/</guid>
      <description>This course approaches time management from 3 unique angles:
Time management in a single day
Time management in a week
Time management in your life to make sure that the tasks you work on are the right ones for your overall life direction, because if you are working on the wrong tasks, then all that time is mismanaged and wasted
Try this course and its unique approach which ends at you looking at the bigger picture of your life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mental Freedom: From PAIN To POWER</title>
      <link>/mental-freedom-from-pain-to-power/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 23:00:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/mental-freedom-from-pain-to-power/</guid>
      <description>Isn&#39;t It Bizarre That You Were Never Trained In How To Control &amp;amp; Get The Best From Your Own Mind? That Is INSANE! Yet That Is The Hand Everybody Is Dealt! Inside This Course You Will Learn The Secrets Of Psychology That Will Give You The Mental &amp;amp; Emotional Control You Always Wanted!
You Are About To Discover:
1) Discover The Secret Of How To SOLVE Problems ... Rather Than Live With Them</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turning to Religion to reduce STRESS</title>
      <link>/turning-to-religion-to-reduce-stress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2021 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/turning-to-religion-to-reduce-stress/</guid>
      <description>Notice: Please do NOT enrol on this course on impulse, thinking you might watch it later. Maybe show an interest on impulse, yes, but before you enrol, watch the Preview videos, read the Course Description and then make a decision. If you then enrol then please start the course as soon as possible. Watch the lectures, look at the workbooks and join in the discussions. Joining my courses is a serious business and I want you to get the most out of your study – but I also want you to enjoy the course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stress Management - For Relief From Stress of Life &amp; Work</title>
      <link>/stress-management-for-relief-from-stress-of-life-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/stress-management-for-relief-from-stress-of-life-work/</guid>
      <description>Stress Management: Stress can weigh you down until you can hardly think straight! Beat it Today with this Comprehensive Stress Management Course filled with Cutting-Edge Tools &amp;amp; Strategies - Feel better TODAY! Created by Master Therapist &amp;amp; Multiple Award-Winning Educator Prof. Paul J. Cline Ed.D ... Get His 35+ years of Expertise in Helping others Beat Stress ... Condensed down into this Training.
Here Are Just A Few Of the Skills You Will Gain:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
