<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Other Photography &amp; Video on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/other-photography-video/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Other Photography &amp; Video on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/other-photography-video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Create awesome videos from text using Pictory</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-awesome-videos-from-text-using-pictory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-awesome-videos-from-text-using-pictory/</guid>
      <description>In the creation and grading of visual or video content and brand stories, artificial intelligence and machine learning have become increasingly useful nowadays.
Can Artificial Intelligence (AI) help in video creation?
The answer is a big &#34;Yes&#34;. You can use AI to generate a video from your script or blog post content within minutes thanks to a powerful new-age tool that has emerged called &#34;Pictory&#34;. In this mind-blowing online training course on Udemy titled &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being Independent Movie Director</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/being-independent-movie-director/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/being-independent-movie-director/</guid>
      <description>We all know how hard it is to become a film director. We all know the saying that only one in a million makes it. To put it simply, the moment you will decide to become a movie director your life won&#39;t be the same anymore. Quite literally. You&#39;ll need to go above and beyond not only to make your films but also to maintain that life you&#39;re living. Being a movie director comes with enormous outside pressure, risks, challenges, and constant obstacles that you will have to battle on daily basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Edit A Feature Film By Yourself</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-edit-a-feature-film-by-yourself/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-edit-a-feature-film-by-yourself/</guid>
      <description>By independent director, producer and screenwriter Hank Orion. In this course we will dive deep into editing tips and techniques for independent films. From raw footage to final master and more. We will talk about stuff they don&#39;t teach you at film school. Some of the topics we will cover in this course are:
Preparing Your Footage To Edit
Importing Files To Premiere Pro
Creating Closing Credits Roll
Creating Film Opening Sequence</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Make Independent Feature Film On A Budget</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-make-independent-feature-film-on-a-budget/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-make-independent-feature-film-on-a-budget/</guid>
      <description>I never went to film school, I had to learn everything I know about filmmaking by making mistakes, on my own. And I will never regret I chose that route. Because for the past five years of my life I learned how to not just be a better filmmaker, but also how to make feature films by myself without relying on other people, make films with whatever equipment I have at my disposal be it an expensive cinema camera, an iPhone or even a GoPro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to VLOG 2022 : Complete Beginners Course &#43;YouTube</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-vlog-2022-complete-beginners-course-youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 20:03:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-vlog-2022-complete-beginners-course-youtube/</guid>
      <description>This course has everything you need to know about vlogging, from a current vlogger! How to film; plan a video, what&#39;s needed in a successful video, come with me filming and editing as well as all the extras of how to create a YouTube channel and your branding.
I have my own channel, i&#39;ve had two actually and I am constantly testing what works and what doesn&#39;t online, trends, video styles, lengths to see which are more successful, which get more views, subscribers and make more money for my channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro CC Essential Video Editing Zero To Hero</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-essential-video-editing-zero-to-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 20:40:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-essential-video-editing-zero-to-hero/</guid>
      <description>Hi There,
My name is Stephen Koel Soren and I am a graphics and web expert. If you are absolute beginner or if you never open Adobe Premiere pro cc before than this is a perfect class for you. This is a beginner level class so so together me you we will learn Adobe Premiere pro from basic to advance. This is a project base class so you will be able to apply your learned skill in real time class project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get 5 Million Free Images and Videos for Commercial Use</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/get-5-million-free-images-and-videos-for-commercial-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/get-5-million-free-images-and-videos-for-commercial-use/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the sixth course in Term 3 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Everybody loves free photos and videos, for sure and this is a huge requirement in the marketing industry. This mind-blowing yet innovative course focuses on &#34;Get 5 Million Free Images and Videos for Commercial Use&#34; and is created by Digital Marketing Legend Srinidhi Ranganathan with the help of Civil Engineering MasterMind Saranya Srinidhi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adobe Premiere Pro CC 2017 - The Complete Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2017-the-complete-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 10:44:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/adobe-premiere-pro-cc-2017-the-complete-guide/</guid>
      <description>Why Learn Premiere Pro?
Premiere Pro is one of the leading video editing software applications. It is an important application to know how to use for anyone wanting to work in television, video or film industries. Learning Premiere Pro is also useful for those editing video as a hobby or for personal use, as it can be used to create videos ranging from highly professional using high-definition footage to more basic videos captured with a camera phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures and Videos colorization by Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pictures-and-videos-colorization-by-artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 14:54:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/pictures-and-videos-colorization-by-artificial-intelligence/</guid>
      <description>How Apocalypse series and videos have been colorized?
Can we colorize all old movies such as Charli Chaplin, laurel and hardy, and so on .......
Revive the history Hello and Welcome to our course .... First Automated Colorization and Color grading course in the WORLD!
This course presents amazing techniques to colorize and upscale any noisy old black and Wight pictures, frames or videos based on artificial intelligence, machine learning, and deep learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Academy - The Complete 2021 Guide Beginner to Pro</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-academy-the-complete-2021-guide-beginner-to-pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 20:22:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/youtube-academy-the-complete-2021-guide-beginner-to-pro/</guid>
      <description>Everything you need to know from discovering what to make your channel about, planning, branding, filming, equipment; how to upload; how to use the best tags and titles to get more views, how to get more subscribers, get monitized; what makes the most money; and how to review your analytics to grow. The complete guide from A-Z for everything you need to know, all in one place for YouTube. Become a YouTube creator today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Graphics Design and Video Editing Masterclass</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-graphics-design-and-video-editing-masterclass/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 18:43:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-graphics-design-and-video-editing-masterclass/</guid>
      <description>Hi There,
My name is Stephen Koel Soren and I am a graphics and web expert. This is a combo course for learning adobe premiere pro cc and adobe photoshop for learning video editing and graphics design. If you are absolute beginner or if you never open Adobe Premiere pro cc and Adobe Photoshop cc before than this is a perfect class for you. This is a beginner level class so so together me you we will learn Adobe Premiere pro and Photoshop from basic to advance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
