<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Finance on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/finance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Finance on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/finance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #16 Convertible Bonds &amp; Warrants</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#16-convertible-bonds-warrants/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#16-convertible-bonds-warrants/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover convertible securities. We will discuss convertible bonds, warrants, &amp;amp; derivative securities.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.
Convertible securities are securities that can be converted from one asset type into another asset type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance/</guid>
      <description>We will learn how to read financial statements and how to use them for decision making.
A primary tool we will use is ratio analysis. Ratio analysis is a very useful skill in a wide area of topics, and financial analysis is a great place to learn the skill.
Ratios are necessary when measuring performance, including most any job performance. For example, we must apply ratio analysis when measuring the job performance of sports athletes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corp Finance #17 Merger, Acquisition &amp; Foreign Currency</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corp-finance-#17-merger-acquisition-foreign-currency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corp-finance-#17-merger-acquisition-foreign-currency/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover mergers, acquisitions &amp;amp; foreign currency.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.
We will discuss what acquisitions and mergers are and how they may be structured, including cash acquisitions and stock for stock acquisitions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #6 Management of Current Assets</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#6-management-of-current-assets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#6-management-of-current-assets/</guid>
      <description>This course will discuss how to manage current assets from a corporate finance perspective.
It will include many example problems, some in presentation format, some using Excel worksheets. Each Excel problem will include a downloadable Excel workbook having at least two tabs, one with the answer, another with a preformatted worksheet you can populate along with the step-by-step instructional videos.
Current asset classes we will consider include cash, accounts receivable, inventory, and marketable securities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #9 Valuation-Bond, Common /Preferred Stock</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#9-valuation-bond-common-/preferred-stock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#9-valuation-bond-common-/preferred-stock/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover the valuation of financial assets including bonds, common stock, and preferred stock.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance #1 Goals, Planning, &amp; Time Value of Money</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance-#1-goals-planning-time-value-of-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance-#1-goals-planning-time-value-of-money/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover the core introductory concepts related to personal finance.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.
We will discuss what personal finance is and what the differences between personal finance, corporate finance, economics, and accounting are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Finance Fundamentals | Infrastructure &amp; Energy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-finance-fundamentals-infrastructure-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:33:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/project-finance-fundamentals-infrastructure-energy/</guid>
      <description>Whether you are a fresh graduate or looking for a shift in your career, whether you are coming from an engineering, finance, or law background; delving into the world of Infrastructure Project finance &amp;amp; PPPs might be challenging. The problem begins at the interview stage: The lack of technical knowledge and basic skills could hurt your chances to land your dream job and break into the sector.
We have been there, too, and we completely understand your frustration!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop vs QBO Multiple Currencies</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-vs-qbo-multiple-currencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-vs-qbo-multiple-currencies/</guid>
      <description>The course will start by discussing how to get access to both QuickBooks Online and QuickBooks Desktop. Intuit, the owner of QuickBooks often offers a free 30-day trial for each software package. This will be a project based course. We will enter transaction in Excel before entering them into the accounting software, QuickBooks desktop and QuickBooks Online. Excel is more transparent, making it easier to understand the process. QuickBooks will then automate the process making it more efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Financial Planning Course- Beginners to advanced</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-financial-planning-course-beginners-to-advanced/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 20:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-financial-planning-course-beginners-to-advanced/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the complete Personal Financial Planning Course...!!!
This course covers managing your money as well as saving and investing. It encompasses budgeting, inflation, net worth, insurance, CIBIL Scores, Credit Card, loans, financial planning thumb rules, power of compounding, financial goals, risk profile, asset allocation, mutual fund &amp;amp; shares investments, retirement planning, tax planning, etc.
Also included in this course is an Excel spreadsheet like a cash flow statement, know your worth- Networth statement, Loan calculator, All in one Financial Goal Calculator Template, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xero Cloud Accounting Basic to Pro Complete Course 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/xero-cloud-accounting-basic-to-pro-complete-course-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 21:50:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/xero-cloud-accounting-basic-to-pro-complete-course-2022/</guid>
      <description>This course takes you from beginners level and gives enough knowledge so you feel comfort while using Xero , this training program is ideal for Freelancers , who want to learn how Bookkeeping , accounting and payroll work is performed on clients projects practically
About This Training
This Xero Cloud Accounting Training Comes with scenario-based activities covering in practical assignments. This course covers essential accounting skills and you will get a certificate upon completion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABA CTFA Certified Trust and Financial Advisor Practice Exam</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aba-ctfa-certified-trust-and-financial-advisor-practice-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aba-ctfa-certified-trust-and-financial-advisor-practice-exam/</guid>
      <description>What Exactly Is Certification?
Certification is an amazing pathway to getting a high paying career in some of the best jobs in the world without spending thousands of dollars attending a four-year college.
Get Ready To Prepare Like You’ve Never Prepared Before
As we often say at AFAQ Formations, work smarter not harder. You are about to see a study guide that took hours of hard collection work, expert preparation, and constant feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Budgeting for Beginners in this Post Pandemic World</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-budgeting-for-beginners-in-this-post-pandemic-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-budgeting-for-beginners-in-this-post-pandemic-world/</guid>
      <description>The world is getting more and more uncertain in this post pandemic environment, with many big companies going bankrupt and many jobs being less secured. Aside from that, as we were not taught financial literacy in school, many families has declared themselves bankrupt. It is truly a scary time. Having said that, those who saved money are less impacted and they are doing a little better at this very uncertain time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Step by Step Guide to Get Out of Debt Easily</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-step-by-step-guide-to-get-out-of-debt-easily/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:20:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-step-by-step-guide-to-get-out-of-debt-easily/</guid>
      <description>I know its a very difficult time for many families including for us right now as businesses are recording losses and many are losing their jobs during this period. Personally when I walk around, I notice many shops closing up and I see worried faces among grocery buyers as the illusion of &#39;job security&#39; is shattered. In our instinct, among the questions running in our heads is &#34;How do I gain more control on my finances ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance/Budgeting Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance/budgeting-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance/budgeting-basics/</guid>
      <description>In this course we will cover the basics on how to create and balance a budget. Save for the future, retire, and adjust your mindset for future financial success. 6 in 10 Americans don&#39;t have enough saved to cover an emergency. After this course, you will have the foundation built to keep you from becoming one of them. This course has helped over 1,000 students on Udemy take control of their finances.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Company Registration In UK~ Make paypal &amp; Stripe Business</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/company-registration-in-uk~-make-paypal-stripe-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 16:38:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/company-registration-in-uk~-make-paypal-stripe-business/</guid>
      <description>Earn in many ways by selling this skill on fiverr &amp;amp; register companies for people in UK who are mostly dropshipping. (This training in Urdu/Hindi only enroll if you understand the language)Whatsapp Group Access &amp;amp; lifetime mentorship is only for students who enroll through my website.
Register a company in UK
Buying a virtual address
Buying UK number from Pakistan
Opening a bank account in UK
VPS (Virtual private Server)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ABA Certified Regulatory Compliance Manager Practice Exams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aba-certified-regulatory-compliance-manager-practice-exams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 19:15:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/aba-certified-regulatory-compliance-manager-practice-exams/</guid>
      <description>What Exactly Is Certification?
Certification is an amazing pathway to getting a high paying career in some of the best jobs in the world without spending thousands of dollars attending a four-year college.
Get Ready To Prepare Like You’ve Never Prepared Before
As we often say at AFAQ Formations, work smarter not harder. You are about to see a study guide that took hours of hard collection work, expert preparation, and constant feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Risk Measurement: A Beginner&#39;s Guide to Process Metrics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/risk-measurement-a-beginners-guide-to-process-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 21:48:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/risk-measurement-a-beginners-guide-to-process-metrics/</guid>
      <description>A risk measure is used in financial mathematics to calculate the amount of an asset or collection of assets (traditionally cash) that should be kept in reserve. The goal of this reserve is for the regulator to accept the risks that financial institutions, such as banks and insurance firms, take. Convex and coherent risk measurement has received a lot of attention in recent years.
In this course:
We will talk about how risk and uncertainty are measured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixed Income Securities: Become a Bond Analyst &amp; Investor</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fixed-income-securities-become-a-bond-analyst-investor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 21:10:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/fixed-income-securities-become-a-bond-analyst-investor/</guid>
      <description>Investing in bonds has a lot of financial benefits for investors. It provides a regular stream of income and widens their investment portfolio. Bonds also carry low market volatility.
It is a safe investment plan which allows investors to preserve and increase their capital. Investing in top-quality government bonds doesn&#39;t come with a default risk for investors.
This course is for investors and individuals who show interest in widening their scope on the fundamentals of fixed-income instruments and exploring the structures and features of the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CFA level 1, Ethics and Standards of Professional Conduct</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cfa-level-1-ethics-and-standards-of-professional-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cfa-level-1-ethics-and-standards-of-professional-conduct/</guid>
      <description>If you have come to this page looking for a quick solution to ace this topic then rest assured this course is for you.
A deep dive into the Code of Ethics and Standards of Professional Conduct for CFA level 1. In this course we cover
Code of Ethics and Standards of Professional conduct
Guidance for Standards I- VII
Ethical Decision Making Framework
Global Investment Performance Standards
Practice questions with answers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CFA Level 2, Ethics and Standards of Professional Conduct</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cfa-level-2-ethics-and-standards-of-professional-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cfa-level-2-ethics-and-standards-of-professional-conduct/</guid>
      <description>A comprehensive course covering Code of Ethics and Standards of Professional conduct for CFA level 2. In this course we cover
Code of Ethics and Standards of Professional conduct
Guidance for Standards I-VII
Application of the Code and Standards
Practice questions with answers
This course simplifies the theoretical concepts in short easy to follow videos. It summarises the key points for effective retention. The content is power packed with examples and is designed to help you score on this topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CFA Level 3, Ethics and Standards of Professional Conduct</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cfa-level-3-ethics-and-standards-of-professional-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cfa-level-3-ethics-and-standards-of-professional-conduct/</guid>
      <description>A deep dive into Code of Ethics and Standards of Professional Conduct for CFA level 3. In this course we cover
Code of Ethics and Standards of Professional Conduct
Guidance for Standards I-VII
Application of the Code and Standards
Asset Manager Code
Professionalism in Investment Industry
Global Investment Performance Standards
Practice questions with answers
This course simplifies the theoretical concepts in short easy to follow videos. It summarises the key points for effective retention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chargeback Reason Codes in Card Payments</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/chargeback-reason-codes-in-card-payments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/chargeback-reason-codes-in-card-payments/</guid>
      <description>THE CHARGEBACK WAY OF LIFE
You may know that a merchant (or their bank, the acquirer/merchant bank), chargebacks are a nightmare.
In short, a credit card owner claims they should obtain their money back due to something that went wrong in a transaction.
Fraud, disputes over the goods, authorization errors, and many other types come in here.
Chargebacks represent difficult obstacles for both acquiring and issuing bank.
Each chargeback is usually represent by something called the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Out of Debt and on Budget for Your Future</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-get-out-of-debt-and-on-budget-for-your-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-get-out-of-debt-and-on-budget-for-your-future/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you will learn how to get yourself out of debt so you can build your credit score and get onto a healthy budget. Getting your personal finances under control can be intimidating and daunting if you don’t know what to do to get ahead. My goal is to give you the opportunity to learn what I learned the hard way. When I was in debt, I never thought I would get out, but I tried different things and got my finances under control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Finance</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-finance/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Introduction to Finance Course by TSI! This is a course that is designed for complete beginners— no experience is required. If you are interested in finance, then you have come to the right place. We start off by introducing finance as well as clearing up a lot of the common misconceptions people have regarding the field. We then cover money and inflation. Then we cover loans and interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consumer Lending Risk Management Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/consumer-lending-risk-management-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/consumer-lending-risk-management-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Have you wondered what a consumer lending risk management professional does on a daily basis? Do you want to explore the world of consumer lending, which is closely tied with millions of people&#39;s lives? This introductory course, Consumer Lending Risk Management Fundamentals - A Beginner&#39;s Guide, will walk you through: Consumer lending products and ecosystem
Risk management types and framework
Risk management practices in consumer lending
Risk management throughout credit life cycle</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Payment Dispute Resolution</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-payment-dispute-resolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/introduction-to-payment-dispute-resolution/</guid>
      <description>WHY DISPUTE RESOLUTION?
Payment disputes are an important issue to solve, either as a merchant, cardholder or bank.
There are many reasons for disputes, and multiple methods for dispute resolution. All of these can affect the results of a dispute for the different parties involved.
In order to be effective at dispute resolution, it&#39;s important to understand not just the reasons for disputes, but also the mechanisms for their resolution, and the consequences of each.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
