<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Finance on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/finance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Finance on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/finance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project Finance Fundamentals | Infrastructure &amp; Energy</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/project-finance-fundamentals-infrastructure-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 10:01:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/project-finance-fundamentals-infrastructure-energy/</guid>
      <description>Whether you are a fresh graduate or looking for a shift in your career, whether you are coming from an engineering, finance, or law background; delving into the world of Infrastructure Project finance &amp;amp; PPPs might be challenging. The problem begins at the interview stage: The lack of technical knowledge and basic skills could hurt your chances to land your dream job and break into the sector.
We have been there, too, and we completely understand your frustration!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance/</guid>
      <description>We will learn how to read financial statements and how to use them for decision making.
A primary tool we will use is ratio analysis. Ratio analysis is a very useful skill in a wide area of topics, and financial analysis is a great place to learn the skill.
Ratios are necessary when measuring performance, including most any job performance. For example, we must apply ratio analysis when measuring the job performance of sports athletes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop vs QBO Multiple Currencies</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-desktop-vs-qbo-multiple-currencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 10:06:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-desktop-vs-qbo-multiple-currencies/</guid>
      <description>The course will start by discussing how to get access to both QuickBooks Online and QuickBooks Desktop. Intuit, the owner of QuickBooks often offers a free 30-day trial for each software package. This will be a project based course. We will enter transaction in Excel before entering them into the accounting software, QuickBooks desktop and QuickBooks Online. Excel is more transparent, making it easier to understand the process. QuickBooks will then automate the process making it more efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Out of Debt and on Budget for Your Future</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-get-out-of-debt-and-on-budget-for-your-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-to-get-out-of-debt-and-on-budget-for-your-future/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you will learn how to get yourself out of debt so you can build your credit score and get onto a healthy budget. Getting your personal finances under control can be intimidating and daunting if you don’t know what to do to get ahead. My goal is to give you the opportunity to learn what I learned the hard way. When I was in debt, I never thought I would get out, but I tried different things and got my finances under control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Finance</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 14:40:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-finance/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Introduction to Finance Course by TSI! This is a course that is designed for complete beginners— no experience is required. If you are interested in finance, then you have come to the right place. We start off by introducing finance as well as clearing up a lot of the common misconceptions people have regarding the field. We then cover money and inflation. Then we cover loans and interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chargeback Reason Codes in Card Payments</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/chargeback-reason-codes-in-card-payments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/chargeback-reason-codes-in-card-payments/</guid>
      <description>THE CHARGEBACK WAY OF LIFE
You may know that a merchant (or their bank, the acquirer/merchant bank), chargebacks are a nightmare.
In short, a credit card owner claims they should obtain their money back due to something that went wrong in a transaction.
Fraud, disputes over the goods, authorization errors, and many other types come in here.
Chargebacks represent difficult obstacles for both acquiring and issuing bank.
Each chargeback is usually represent by something called the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consumer Lending Risk Management Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/consumer-lending-risk-management-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/consumer-lending-risk-management-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Have you wondered what a consumer lending risk management professional does on a daily basis? Do you want to explore the world of consumer lending, which is closely tied with millions of people&#39;s lives? This introductory course, Consumer Lending Risk Management Fundamentals - A Beginner&#39;s Guide, will walk you through: Consumer lending products and ecosystem
Risk management types and framework
Risk management practices in consumer lending
Risk management throughout credit life cycle</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Payment Dispute Resolution</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-payment-dispute-resolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/introduction-to-payment-dispute-resolution/</guid>
      <description>WHY DISPUTE RESOLUTION?
Payment disputes are an important issue to solve, either as a merchant, cardholder or bank.
There are many reasons for disputes, and multiple methods for dispute resolution. All of these can affect the results of a dispute for the different parties involved.
In order to be effective at dispute resolution, it&#39;s important to understand not just the reasons for disputes, but also the mechanisms for their resolution, and the consequences of each.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #6 Management of Current Assets</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance-#6-management-of-current-assets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/corporate-finance-#6-management-of-current-assets/</guid>
      <description>This course will discuss how to manage current assets from a corporate finance perspective.
It will include many example problems, some in presentation format, some using Excel worksheets. Each Excel problem will include a downloadable Excel workbook having at least two tabs, one with the answer, another with a preformatted worksheet you can populate along with the step-by-step instructional videos.
Current asset classes we will consider include cash, accounts receivable, inventory, and marketable securities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
