<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Money Management Tools on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/money-management-tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Money Management Tools on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/money-management-tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Online Bank Reconciliation</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-bank-reconciliation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-bank-reconciliation/</guid>
      <description>If we are a business owner who would like more assurance about our books, a business professional who would like to advance our career by learning the importance of bank reconciliations, or an accounting student who would like to see the critical internal control of bank reconciliations applies to real work software, this QuickBooks course is a course for us. Why choose this course?
The bank reconciliation process is the second biggest internal control for most companies and one both large and small companies can, and should, implement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Online Multiple Currencies</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-multiple-currencies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-multiple-currencies/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to get access to QuickBooks Online including a possible free 30-day trial version often offered by Intuit, the owner of QuickBooks Online.
The course will discuss accounting for multiple currencies, outlining the process in Excel to provide a more transparent look at the process. Then we will enter the transactions into QuickBooks, the software automating some of the steps required.
We will learn how to turn multicurrency on, and which accounts will be affected most by multicurrency transactions including cash account types, accounts receivable account types, and accounts payable account types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xero Accounting Software</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/xero-accounting-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/xero-accounting-software/</guid>
      <description>This course will start at the basics, assuming you know nothing about the software or accounting.
We will then go through the purchasing process, the downloading process, and the installation process. Xero often offers a free 30 day trial which is a perfect tool to practice with. The first half of the course will be dedicated to navigating the software, getting a feel for the major components of the software, and the primary accounting cycles such as the customer section or revenue cycle, the vendor section or payments cycle, and the employee section or payroll cycle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cost Accounting and Artificial Intelligence Tools (2022)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cost-accounting-and-artificial-intelligence-tools-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cost-accounting-and-artificial-intelligence-tools-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Cost Accounting and Artificial Intelligence Tools (2022)&#34;.
Ready to learn the basics of cost accounting with a glimpse of Artificial Intelligence technology usage in accounting?
Cost accounting is an important aspect of an accounting policy that calculates the total cost of producing an item or providing a service by looking at all costs within the supply chain. It is done for the purpose of planning the budget and evaluating productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Statement Analysis – Ratio Analysis</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-statement-analysis-ratio-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/financial-statement-analysis-ratio-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Learn tools to analyze financial statements, including vertical analysis, horizontal analysis, and ratio analysis.
This course will provide resources such as downloadable PDF files and preformatted Excel spreadsheet to help understand and apply the concepts.
We will list and describe the tools for financial statement analysis, including vertical analysis, horizontal analysis, and ratio analysis.
Below is more detail about the concepts we will learn.
This course will help us understand, calculate, and analyze horizontal analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managerial Accounting / Cost Accounting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/managerial-accounting-/-cost-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/managerial-accounting-/-cost-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Comprehensive managerial and cost accounting course. Topics include:
· Job order costing
· Process costing
· Cost volume profit analysis
· Master Budgets
· Flexible Budgets
· Responsibility accounting
· Relevant costs
· Time value of money
This course will go into detail about each topic. We will include”
· Practice Excel files with both an answer tab and a practice tab
· Lecture PDF files that can be downloaded and reviewed without internet access</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover personal finance concepts, starting from the basics, and moving to complex topics. We will cover each step thoroughly.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Capital Free Financial Planner Application</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-capital-free-financial-planner-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-capital-free-financial-planner-application/</guid>
      <description>Personal Capital is currently a free software that can connect to financial institutions, pulling in financial asset and liability balances, as well as transaction detail, into one location.
The strong areas of benefit of using Personal Capital software are its ability to provide net worth or balance sheet information, investment management information, and planning tools such as retirement planning and other large planning goals.
The Personal Capital software also downloads transaction detail and allows for the categorization or assigning of accounts and tags that can then be used to generate an income statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corp Finance #12 Capital Budgeting &amp; Investment Risk Tools</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corp-finance-#12-capital-budgeting-investment-risk-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corp-finance-#12-capital-budgeting-investment-risk-tools/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover the use of risk assessment tools as they relate to capital budgeting and investment decisions and how to use them.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #4 Leverage &amp; Break-Even Analysis</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#4-leverage-break-even-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#4-leverage-break-even-analysis/</guid>
      <description>In this course we will cover the concepts of leverage and break-even analysis from a corporate finance perspective.
Leverage is a critical component of decision making in corporate finance and is an area of debate as to the optimal amount of leverage. Finding the best level of leverage may allow a business to grow much faster.
We will discuss the concepts of operating leverage, financial leverage, and combined leverage and include practical practice problems related to these critical concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance #2–Financial Statements &amp; Budgeting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance-#2financial-statements-budgeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance-#2financial-statements-budgeting/</guid>
      <description>This course will focus on personal financial statements, a fundamental tool for personal financial planning.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.
Financial statements are the core tool we used to measure our current financial position as well as our past performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop vs. Excel</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-vs.-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-vs.-excel/</guid>
      <description>Would we like to run our business better using accounting software? Would we like to better understand accounting concepts, how they apply to accounting software, and work accounting problems MUCH faster?
Would we like to advance our career by increase our skills with business software?
This comprehensive QuickBooks &amp;amp; Excel course can help to achieve these goals
Why choose this course?
Current video content means all QuickBooks lectures are done recently as of this post rather than adding a few new videos to content from prior years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Online vs. Excel</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-vs.-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 21:29:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-vs.-excel/</guid>
      <description>Would we like to run our business better using accounting software?
Would we like to better understand accounting concepts, how they apply to accounting software, and work accounting problems MUCH faster?
Would we like to advance our career by increase our skills with business software?
This comprehensive QuickBooks Online &amp;amp; Excel course can help to achieve these goals
Why choose this course? Current video content means all QuickBooks lectures are done recently as of this post rather than adding a few new videos to content from prior years.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
