<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Money Management Tools on </title>
    <link>/tags/money-management-tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Money Management Tools on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/money-management-tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #4 Leverage &amp; Break-Even Analysis</title>
      <link>/corporate-finance-#4-leverage-break-even-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/corporate-finance-#4-leverage-break-even-analysis/</guid>
      <description>In this course we will cover the concepts of leverage and break-even analysis from a corporate finance perspective.
Leverage is a critical component of decision making in corporate finance and is an area of debate as to the optimal amount of leverage. Finding the best level of leverage may allow a business to grow much faster.
We will discuss the concepts of operating leverage, financial leverage, and combined leverage and include practical practice problems related to these critical concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managerial Accounting / Cost Accounting</title>
      <link>/managerial-accounting-/-cost-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/managerial-accounting-/-cost-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Comprehensive managerial and cost accounting course. Topics include:
· Job order costing
· Process costing
· Cost volume profit analysis
· Master Budgets
· Flexible Budgets
· Responsibility accounting
· Relevant costs
· Time value of money
This course will go into detail about each topic. We will include”
· Practice Excel files with both an answer tab and a practice tab
· Lecture PDF files that can be downloaded and reviewed without internet access</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance</title>
      <link>/personal-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/personal-finance/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover personal finance concepts, starting from the basics, and moving to complex topics. We will cover each step thoroughly.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Capital Free Financial Planner Application</title>
      <link>/personal-capital-free-financial-planner-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 16:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/personal-capital-free-financial-planner-application/</guid>
      <description>Personal Capital is currently a free software that can connect to financial institutions, pulling in financial asset and liability balances, as well as transaction detail, into one location.
The strong areas of benefit of using Personal Capital software are its ability to provide net worth or balance sheet information, investment management information, and planning tools such as retirement planning and other large planning goals.
The Personal Capital software also downloads transaction detail and allows for the categorization or assigning of accounts and tags that can then be used to generate an income statement.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
