<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing Fundamentals on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/marketing-fundamentals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing Fundamentals on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/marketing-fundamentals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MBA Course: Marketing and Business Strategy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mba-course-marketing-and-business-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mba-course-marketing-and-business-strategy/</guid>
      <description>MBA Marketing strategy course designed by an MBA graduate from the syllabus of top Universities in the world This course is very helpful for all those who are either preparing for GMAT or planning to do an MBA. It is divided into four different sections like Marketing Basics Overview, Marketing insights and analysis, Branding and communication, and Business Strategy and will cover all the important topics of Marketing in MBA. The last section of the module will further help you in understanding various strategies used by companies</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Come creare una corretta strategia di Marketing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/come-creare-una-corretta-strategia-di-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 18:19:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/come-creare-una-corretta-strategia-di-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Questo corso è per coloro che vogliono creare un proprio business, che sia un Brand o un Corso, che sia uno Store o un singolo prodotto. Ti spiegherò cosa è il Marketing e i suoi Principi fondamentali, in modo da creare la Strategia che ti farà avere successo nel lungo termine. Faremo in modo che sarà il prodotto a vendere da solo una volta applicati i Principi argomentati e descritti. Imparerai:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEST of Digital Marketing Essentials 2022: Learn FUN &amp; FAST</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/best-of-digital-marketing-essentials-2022-learn-fun-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:36:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/best-of-digital-marketing-essentials-2022-learn-fun-fast/</guid>
      <description>HI AND BIG WELCOME TO OUR INTRODUCTION TO THE ESSENTIAL OF DIGITAL MARKETING, SOCIAL MEDIA, AND SEO. MAKE SURE YOU’RE SITTING COMFORTABLY, AS YOU’RE ABOUT TO GET A COMPREHENSIVE OVERVIEW OF EVERYTHING RELATED TO DIGITAL MARKETING, SOCIAL MEDIA, AND SEO. THIS DIGITAL MARKETING COURSE IS MADE FUN! IT HAS BEEN FILLED WITH HQ ANIMATED VIDEO EXPLAINERS, INTERACTIVE QUIZZES WITH QUESTIONS A, B, C, D AND ASSIGNMENTS.
IF YOU WANT TO BE SUCCESSFUL ONLINE TODAY, YOU NEED TO HAVE STRONG DIGITAL MARKETING SKILLS AS INTERNET BUSINESS HAS NEVER BEEN MORE COMPETITIVE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Masterclass in Marketing Psychology</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/masterclass-in-marketing-psychology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/masterclass-in-marketing-psychology/</guid>
      <description>This course aims to make you a Jedi of Marketing Psychology within approx. 3.5 hours. This Udemy course is to learn what works and how to get results – fast! In this course I will show you how to:
· How to create effective messaging for Marketing Campaigns: online(#Digital Marketing) and offline
· How to advertise products for making the right impact
· How to establish trust through body language</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Manipulation Works in Marketing/Copywriting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-manipulation-works-in-marketing/copywriting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-manipulation-works-in-marketing/copywriting/</guid>
      <description>MARKETING OR MANIPULATING?
You probably know that marketers and copywriters do a great job of making a product (or offer) seem appealing.
The only problem is when those techniques turn into actual lies or manipulation.
As a persuasion expert, I&#39;ve catalogued all different possible types of manipulation.
And in this course, you will find out about how every single one of them is using in marketing.
LET ME TELL YOU... EVERYTHING</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMMP Exam: Marketing Management --&gt; Practice Test 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cmmp-exam-marketing-management--practice-test-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cmmp-exam-marketing-management--practice-test-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Interview in Marketing Management ? Don’t be stressed, Take our Marketing Management Based Mock Test and prepare yourself for the Exam. Here you will get Marketing Management based Multiple Choice Question for your Next Exam.
What you will get in These Mock Test ? It contains sample questions which are likely to be asked in the Exam.
These Marketing Management based MCQ questions help you with self-study and self-assessment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
