<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing Fundamentals on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/marketing-fundamentals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing Fundamentals on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/marketing-fundamentals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Masterclass in Marketing Psychology</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/masterclass-in-marketing-psychology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:23:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/masterclass-in-marketing-psychology/</guid>
      <description>This course aims to make you a Jedi of Marketing Psychology within approx. 3.5 hours. This Udemy course is to learn what works and how to get results – fast! 
In this course I will show you how to:
· How to create effective messaging for Marketing Campaigns: online(#Digital Marketing) and offline
· How to advertise products for making the right impact
· How to establish trust through body language</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Manipulation Works in Marketing/Copywriting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/how-manipulation-works-in-marketing/copywriting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 10:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/how-manipulation-works-in-marketing/copywriting/</guid>
      <description>MARKETING OR MANIPULATING?
You probably know that marketers and copywriters do a great job of making a product (or offer) seem appealing.
The only problem is when those techniques turn into actual lies or manipulation.
As a persuasion expert, I&#39;ve catalogued all different possible types of manipulation.
And in this course, you will find out about how every single one of them is using in marketing.


LET ME TELL YOU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEST of Digital Marketing Essentials 2021: Learn FUN &amp; FAST</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/best-of-digital-marketing-essentials-2021-learn-fun-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 22:18:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/best-of-digital-marketing-essentials-2021-learn-fun-fast/</guid>
      <description>HI AND BIG WELCOME TO OUR INTRODUCTION TO THE ESSENTIAL OF DIGITAL MARKETING, SOCIAL MEDIA, AND SEO. MAKE SURE YOU’RE SITTING COMFORTABLY, AS YOU’RE ABOUT TO GET A COMPREHENSIVE OVERVIEW OF EVERYTHING RELATED TO DIGITAL MARKETING, SOCIAL MEDIA, AND SEO. THIS DIGITAL MARKETING COURSE IS MADE FUN! IT HAS BEEN FILLED WITH HQ ANIMATED VIDEO EXPLAINERS AND INTERACTIVE QUIZZES WITH QUESTIONS A, B, C, D.
IF YOU WANT TO BE SUCCESSFUL ONLINE TODAY, YOU NEED TO HAVE STRONG DIGITAL MARKETING SKILLS AS INTERNET BUSINESS HAS NEVER BEEN MORE COMPETITIVE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Page &amp; Facebook Ads Made as FUN: 10 DAYS Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/facebook-page-facebook-ads-made-as-fun-10-days-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 15:46:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/facebook-page-facebook-ads-made-as-fun-10-days-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Step by step Facebook ads &amp;amp; Instagram ads course for beginners (ready for ios 14.5+ restrictions) - Accept our 10 days challenge and learn how to set up Facebook business page &amp;amp; Facebook business manager. Install Facebook Pixel ready for iOS 14.5+ restrictions. Use Facebook Creator studio. Launch your first Facebook read ads &amp;amp; Facebook engagement campaigns. Generate leads with Facebook lead generation ads. This Facebook ads course includes essential info so you can prep for the Facebook Pixel API for iOS14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CMMP Exam: Marketing Management --&gt; Practice Test 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cmmp-exam-marketing-management-practice-test-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cmmp-exam-marketing-management-practice-test-2021/</guid>
      <description>Dear Friends,
Are you Preparing for Interview in Marketing Management ? 
Don’t be stressed, Take our Marketing Management Based Mock Test and prepare yourself for the Exam. Here you will get Marketing Management based Multiple Choice Question for your Next Exam.
What you will get in These Mock Test ? 
It contains sample questions which are likely to be asked in the Exam.
These Marketing Management based MCQ questions help you with self-study and self-assessment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
