<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paid Advertising on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/paid-advertising/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Paid Advertising on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/paid-advertising/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Facebook Traffic Ads (Facebook CPC) Course 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-facebook-traffic-ads-facebook-cpc-course-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-facebook-traffic-ads-facebook-cpc-course-2022/</guid>
      <description>Gain More Clients, Maximise Sales, and Push more Traffic to your Website with the most Comprehensive and Current Facebook Traffic and Marketing Course out there
&#34;I love Tom. He is the man. He really knows what he&#39;s talking about when it comes to Facebook marketing. A true expert in the field! Don&#39;t hesitate to take this course, because I promise you that you will not be disappointed! You are in great hands with Tom when it comes to learning and mastering Facebook marketing!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook &amp; Instagram Dynamic Ads: Dynamic Retargeting Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/facebook-instagram-dynamic-ads-dynamic-retargeting-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/facebook-instagram-dynamic-ads-dynamic-retargeting-course/</guid>
      <description>Completely Updated Facebook Ads &amp;amp; Instagram Ads Retargeting Course! This Is Your Ultimate Step-by-step Guide To Becoming A Master Of Facebook Remarketing And Dynamic Retargeting.
&#34;This is the best Facebook Ads &amp;amp; Instagram Ads Course for the starter with advanced level for Facebook Ads Mastery.&#34; H M Shuja
&#34;Amazing Facebook Ads Course. I learn a lot from this course. He is just awesome. Thanks for such an amazing course.&#34; Rokeya</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Ads &amp; Instagram Ads Course 2022: The Art of Selling</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/facebook-ads-instagram-ads-course-2022-the-art-of-selling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/facebook-ads-instagram-ads-course-2022-the-art-of-selling/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to Sell with Facebook Ads &amp;amp; Instagram Ads in 2022:
I will Walk you through the Complete Process of Planning Facebook Ads Campaign, Executing it, Leading it &amp;amp; Optimising the Budget. You can Get Real Insights about Selling with Facebook Ads &amp;amp; Instagram Ads. You can Watch Real Case Study. I will walk you walk. You can watch hands-on Sales Campaigns. You can Understand how Sales &amp;amp; Revenue are Produced with Facebook Ads &amp;amp; Instagram Ads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate YouTube Advertising Course for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-youtube-advertising-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-ultimate-youtube-advertising-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;The Ultimate YouTube Advertising Course for Beginners&#34; in 2022 created by Digital Marketing Legend &#34;Srinidhi Ranganathan&#34;.
As digital marketing expands and evolves, the tools we use to advertise ourselves must also develop. Whereas outbound marketing was formerly the sole option, inbound marketing&#39;s development and resounding success have opened up a slew of new marketing strategies and techniques. These new tools are not only beneficial to know, but also crucial to grasp if your company wants to thrive in this increasingly digital world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sell More: Facebook Ads &amp; Instagram Ads for E-Commerce 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sell-more-facebook-ads-instagram-ads-for-e-commerce-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sell-more-facebook-ads-instagram-ads-for-e-commerce-2022/</guid>
      <description>Get Maximum Conversions with hands on Training and Learn How to Sell using Facebook Conversion Ads, Instagram Conversion Ads, Dynamic Ads, Custom Audiences, Lookalike Audiences, Business oriented Leading of Sales Campaigns &amp;amp; Complete Customer Journey ready for all iOS &amp;amp; EU changes. &#34;Excellent Facebook Ads &amp;amp; Instagram Ads Course. Would highly recommend this course to someone who is looking to learn or for that matter even gain knowledge. No institute or a YouTube video teaches this in so much detail as much as Tomas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Page &amp; Facebook Ads Made as Fun: 11 Days Challenge</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/facebook-page-facebook-ads-made-as-fun-11-days-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:33:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/facebook-page-facebook-ads-made-as-fun-11-days-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Step By Step Facebook Ads &amp;amp; Instagram Ads Course For Beginners (Ready For Ios 14.5+ Restrictions) Accept our 11 days challenge and learn how to set up Facebook business page &amp;amp; Facebook business manager. Install Facebook Pixel ready for iOS 14.5+ restrictions. Use Facebook Creator studio. Launch your first Facebook read ads &amp;amp; Facebook engagement campaigns. Generate leads with Facebook lead generation ads. Drive traffic to your website with Facebook traffic ads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best of Facebook Ads: Facebook Ads 2022 Ultimate Pro Edition</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/best-of-facebook-ads-facebook-ads-2022-ultimate-pro-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/best-of-facebook-ads-facebook-ads-2022-ultimate-pro-edition/</guid>
      <description>Upskill Yourself And Ensure You&#39;re Never Out Of Work Or Out Of Clients, With The Best Of Facebook Ads, Instagram Ads &amp;amp; Messenger Ads Pro Edition 2022. Learn everything you need to know to become a Professional Facebook Ads Consultant, and start a new career online, or boost your local or e-commerce Business. Completely updated for Apple iOS 14.5+ restrictions. Setup Conversion API on WordPress in 10 minutes. Learn complete customer journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consultor de Marketing y Publicidad</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/consultor-de-marketing-y-publicidad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/consultor-de-marketing-y-publicidad/</guid>
      <description>★★★★★ TE INVITO A VER LAS RESEÑAS ★★★★★
★★★★★Carlos Heredia Goitiabuena elección, la primer clase, me quedaron en claro muchas cosas que son básicas y que nadie en la escuela o en el trabajo me había explicado.
★★★★★Julio Cesar Lopez de LeonComprensible y práctico
★★★★★ESTER SILVAMe ha gustado mucho. He aprendido aún más!
★★★★Christian OdedDesde la introducción ya me dejó algunos conceptos y prácticas qué recordar para la creación de las publicidad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Ads Fundamentals: Fast-Track Practice Quiz Exam</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-ads-fundamentals-fast-track-practice-quiz-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-ads-fundamentals-fast-track-practice-quiz-exam/</guid>
      <description>Some people enjoy taking quizzes simply for the fun of it, while others are seeking a challenge. Are you ready to opt for a challenge by taking part in the &#34;Google Ads Fundamentals: Fast Track Practice Quiz Exam?&#34;. This quiz may be a little bit technical and helpful for professionals who are already well-versed in the field of digital marketing and as a result, more practice is required to master it if you are an amateur or new to this concept topic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Ads 2022. How to drive sales with PPC!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-ads-2022.-how-to-drive-sales-with-ppc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2022 20:40:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-ads-2022.-how-to-drive-sales-with-ppc/</guid>
      <description>Do you want to start your first Google Ads campaign? Are you interested in increasing your online sales but afraid of going over budget? Do you want to drive traffic to your websites, reach new customers and increase sales?
This is an in-depth course to get started with Google Ads.
In this Google Ads training, we will walk through all the steps of launching a search ads campaign. In this PPC class, you will get a complete understanding of how to efficiently work with Google Ads and create successful campaigns to get loyal customers, increase traffic and grow your business online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Ads, YouTube Ads, Bing Ads &amp; Google Retargeting Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-ads-youtube-ads-bing-ads-google-retargeting-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-ads-youtube-ads-bing-ads-google-retargeting-guide/</guid>
      <description>Learn Google Ads, Youtube Ads, Bing Ads &amp;amp; Google Retargeting Fast &amp;amp; Fun!
Setup your Google search campaign today. Enjoy interactive quizzes A, B, C, D. Learn how to set up your Google ads account, use Google coupon, write your Google ad copy, create your first campaign, and get your advertising up &amp;amp; running. In this Google ads course you will walk-through setup, configuration, creating ad copy, adding your keywords, and optimising your ads to drive traffic to your website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Search Ad In Google Ads &amp; Easy SEO For Beginners-2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/run-search-ad-in-google-ads-easy-seo-for-beginners-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 20:12:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/run-search-ad-in-google-ads-easy-seo-for-beginners-2022/</guid>
      <description>Here is your chance to get started with Google Ads with its core features explained in just 1 hour in this comprehensive training. Enroll now and get started with advertising on google network like in no time. It&#39;s very easy to understand and apply.
Topics explained in detail are : Introduction Of Google Adwords With a $45 Credit !! Campaign Objectives and campaign types Campaign Types, Budget, and Extensions Explained</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Ads &amp; Instagram Ads 2022: Overcome Apple Apocalypto</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/facebook-ads-instagram-ads-2022-overcome-apple-apocalypto/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:15:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/facebook-ads-instagram-ads-2022-overcome-apple-apocalypto/</guid>
      <description>Learn Facebook Ads &amp;amp; Instagram Ads with me. I promise I will not let you down. I have helped more than 600.000 students on Udemy. This is my Best Fast Progress Facebook Ads Course. I honestly hope &amp;amp; believe you will love this course. This Facebook Ads Course consists of Practical hands-on screen recordings (New Facebook interface), Animated video explainers, Face2face explanations &amp;amp; Interactive quizzes making learning fun! I have optimised curriculum for fast progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AD’s Hacker 1.0: Growth Hacking Certification for Marketers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ads-hacker-1.0-growth-hacking-certification-for-marketers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 13:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ads-hacker-1.0-growth-hacking-certification-for-marketers/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the third course in Term 2 as part of the series &#34;MBA in Artificial Intelligence Digital Marketing&#34;.
Time to set the advertising industry on fire with AD&#39;s Hacker 1.0 !!!
There is no denying that we have changed the way we work on the World Wide Web and the Internet. For presents or gifts, we no longer visit the city centre– we’re going to an eCommerce marketplace like Amazon and getting it shipped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Adwords Crash Course 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-adwords-crash-course-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 18:19:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-adwords-crash-course-2022/</guid>
      <description>Here is your chance to get started with Google Ads with its core features explained in just 1 hour in this comprehensive training. Enroll now and get started with advertising on google network like in no time. It&#39;s very easy to understand and apply.
Topics explained in detail are : Introduction Of Google Adwords With a $45 Credit !! Campaign Objectives and campaign types Campaign Types, Budget, and Extensions Explained</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Blog Perk Method - How To Get Free Products</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-blog-perk-method-how-to-get-free-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 21:12:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-blog-perk-method-how-to-get-free-products/</guid>
      <description>The Blog Perks method is quite simple, you just have to communicate in the right way, use the right words and approach and the company you are contacting for a free product, or products, will jump at the opportunity to send you some of their products. The approach is to communicate to the company that you are a blogger and have influence in your industry. If you are in the health industry, they want to know you can influence people and their decisions around health, if you are in the finance industry, relationship industry, diet industry, fitness industry, spirituality industry, DIY space, whatever it may be, they want to see what you have going for yourself and see that you have some influence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
