<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Other Design on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/other-design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Other Design on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/other-design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence in Video Creation: Supreme Edition</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-in-video-creation-supreme-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-in-video-creation-supreme-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the most amazing 2022 course titled &#34;Artificial Intelligence in Video Creation: Supreme Edition&#34;. The new-age technologies in video creation are here.
This incredible artificial intelligence video creation course 2022 will cover the tools called Biteable and Lumen5 which are the world&#39;s simplest video makers offering hundreds of free animated, live-action, or photo scenes in lots of different styles made by top designers.
I will teach you to easily add your own text, photos, colours, and sound to customise your video and edit it all on a simple drag-and-drop timeline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event Management in 3D Virtual Worlds (2022 Grand Edition)</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/event-management-in-3d-virtual-worlds-2022-grand-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/event-management-in-3d-virtual-worlds-2022-grand-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the online course focussed on Event Management in 3D Virtual Worlds (2022 Grand Edition).
&#34;Virtual and augmented reality techniques are changing the way that organizers, sponsors, and vendors engage with attendees at various events.&#34; The metaverse has emerged and the technology is expanding quite rapidly. It is predicted that at every level, the metaverse will spark a thriving new economy. It means another revenue stream for content creators and VR developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create lightning-fast videos with InVideo in 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-lightning-fast-videos-with-invideo-in-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-lightning-fast-videos-with-invideo-in-2022/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience &#34;Create lightning-fast videos with InVideo in 2022&#34;.
Video creation was a tough process - until now !!! Do you want to learn to produce some incredible videos without all the hassle of using complex editing software, without straining yourself too much?
Are you looking to create wow-inspiring videos to promote your brand to the highest level?
You&#39;ve come to the right place, finally. This amazing course on Udemy will introduce you to the world’s most versatile video creator for Quick &amp;amp; Professional videos called &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence (AI) Logo Design Tools: 2022 Edition</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-ai-logo-design-tools-2022-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/artificial-intelligence-ai-logo-design-tools-2022-edition/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience the online course &#34;Artificial Intelligence (AI) Logo Design Tools: 2022 Edition&#34;.
When designing a logo for your new company or project, the first step is to determine which design method fits your budget, schedule, and creative needs.
A new wave of graphic design has come to the limelight with artificial intelligence gaining prominence in all fields of technology, providing an affordable alternative for bootstrapped entrepreneurs and startups. As a powerful and easy alternative to DIY logo design (which is extremely time-consuming) and hiring a designer (which is more or less expensive), an AI-powered logo creation tool is a smart way to create logos that look professional and appealing to your target audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experto en Diseño de Espacios para Mascotas</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/experto-en-dise%C3%B1o-de-espacios-para-mascotas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/experto-en-dise%C3%B1o-de-espacios-para-mascotas/</guid>
      <description>Experto en Diseño de Espacios para Mascotas
Conviértete en un Experto en el Diseño de Hogares y Espacios destinados a todo tipo de Mascotas
Instructores: Arquitecto Álvaro García y Arquitecta Lucía Fernández Actualizado: Mayo de 2022 Estudiantes: +3.000 Descripción del Curso:
La formación te permitirá convertirte en un experto en la materia, y todo ello desde una formación principalmente práctica. A través de variadas actividades y proyectos completos podrás adquirir los conocimientos suficientes para ejercer profesionalmente de forma solvente.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Proven Steps to Make a Silver Ring</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/8-proven-steps-to-make-a-silver-ring/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 15:57:40 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/8-proven-steps-to-make-a-silver-ring/</guid>
      <description>Are you curious about silver jewellery making but don&#39;t know where to start, unsure what tools you need or whether you&#39;ll enjoy jewellery making? Would you love to learn jewellery making but don&#39;t want a big expense and commitment? Are the courses you&#39;ve researched too long, unavailable right now, not near you, at inconvenient times or fully booked?
On this course you will :-
Learn how to set up your workspace at home with 5 short easy to follow videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Super-Fast Videos and Online Courses with WeVideo</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-super-fast-videos-and-online-courses-with-wevideo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 22:09:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/create-super-fast-videos-and-online-courses-with-wevideo/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to experience the course &#34;Create Super-Fast Videos and Online Courses with WeVideo&#34;.
Are you looking to learn how to create incredible videos fast and easily without installing complex software? Are you still worried about the videos you edited that are taking ages to render?
Want to create wow-inspiring videos to promote your brand to gain maximum exposure? Welcome to the next generation of cloud-based video creation with WeVideo. WeVideo caters to all the needs mentioned above and also gives you the power to do more with fewer resources, time, and effort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Substation Power Engineering Fundamentals</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/substation-power-engineering-fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 15:17:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/substation-power-engineering-fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Substation Power Engineering Fundamentals is a comprehensive video course where you can learn industry specific knowledge about power substations that you would not have known unless you worked within the utility industry for a number of years.
I have handcrafted this course to allow students to acquire core fundamental knowledge on substations as well as key pointers to look out for in substation designs, such as site preparations and equipment specifications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
