<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Photography on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/photography/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Photography on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 13:24:05 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/photography/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Practical Photography for Absolute Beginners: 9 Courses in 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/practical-photography-for-absolute-beginners-9-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2021 13:24:05 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/practical-photography-for-absolute-beginners-9-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>=== Students reviews on this course ===
&#34;I had a great love for this course. Through this photography course, I learned so many new things that I never heard of. The teaching method is very simple and beautiful which can be learned easily by anyone.&#34; -- Naveen Yes
&#34;Awesome all are understanding and point to point&#34; -- Naman Verma
&#34;It was great course. I now have a better understanding as to which camera to purchase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Photography : 21 Courses in 1 [Beginner to Expert]</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-photography-21-courses-in-1-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 11:25:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-photography-21-courses-in-1-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Our students&#39; reviews regarding this course --
&#34;This course has been broken down to explain some difficult photography lingo and setting into plain easy to understand English and the teacher goes nice and slow so you don&#39;t feel bombarded with tons of info at once!&#34; -- Christi Guimar
&#34;I found this course really helpful and I learned more about some of the technical aspects that will help me improve my photography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals Of Photography</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/fundamentals-of-photography/</guid>
      <description>If you just bought a DSLR, a mirrorless or just a point and shoot camera, and are wondering what the next step should be, enrol in the most comprehensive course to learn the basics and fundamentals of photography with World Photographers Club.
Learn everything about your camera, which lenses are good for you, basic concepts like shutter speed, aperture, ISO, white balance, focal length, and more, and see how they affect your photography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Photography Masterclass: 4 courses in 1</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-photography-masterclass-4-courses-in-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/complete-photography-masterclass-4-courses-in-1/</guid>
      <description>----- Our students reviews regarding this course ------
&#34;fantastic o am learn a lot from this lecture.. I always think i know a lot about photography but when i follow this course which is so easy to understant.. now i feel i know nothing... thanks for the explanations&#34; -- Eva
&#34;It&#39;s good and straight to the point.. and covers a lot of basic aspects you might need in photography and photo editing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
