<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Other Finance &amp; Accounting on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/other-finance-accounting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Other Finance &amp; Accounting on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/other-finance-accounting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Excel Accounting Problem</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-accounting-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-accounting-problem/</guid>
      <description>This course will walk through a comprehensive accounting problem using Microsoft Excel in a step-by-step process. You may also use another spreadsheet software like Google Sheets.
Learners will learn how to navigate Microsoft Excel as well as how to create a well-designed accounting worksheet, complete with a general journal, trial balance, general ledger, subsidiary ledgers for accounts receivable, accounts payable, &amp;amp; inventory, financial statements and much more.
Excel is a very good tool to learn accounting because it is much more transparent than a database program, like accounting software, QuickBooks being a common example of accounting software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #15 Dividend Policy</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#15-dividend-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#15-dividend-policy/</guid>
      <description>This course will cover corporate dividend policy.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.
Dividends represent earnings that a corporation distributes to owners. Dividends for a corporation can be compared do withdrawals from a sole proprietorship or partnership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #5 Financing Decisions</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#5-financing-decisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#5-financing-decisions/</guid>
      <description>This course will discuss company financing decisions from a corporate finance perspective.
Financing is often a critical component to company growth, optimal financing allowing companies to grow much faster while mitigating risk.
We will consider general financing patterns of a corporation.
Financing options can be broken down into short-term financing needs and long-term financing need. To determine financing needs, a company will often have to estimate future sales, future sales allowing them to estimate production levels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporate Finance #7 Short Term Financing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#7-short-term-financing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/corporate-finance-#7-short-term-financing/</guid>
      <description>This course will discuss short term financing options from a corporate finance perspective.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.
Learners will understand accounts payable and trade credit as options from the perspective of short-term financing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance #3–Financial Services &amp; Bank Reconciliation</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance-#3financial-services-bank-reconciliation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance-#3financial-services-bank-reconciliation/</guid>
      <description>This course will focus on the importance of performing the bank reconciliation process and how to complete a bank reconciliation.
We will include many example problems, both in the format of presentations and Excel worksheet problems. The Excel worksheet presentations will include a downloadable Excel workbook with at least two tabs, one with the answer, the second with a preformatted worksheet that can be completed in a step-by-step process along with the instructional videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See 27 Ways to Make Money Online with Your Smartphone!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/see-27-ways-to-make-money-online-with-your-smartphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:57:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/see-27-ways-to-make-money-online-with-your-smartphone/</guid>
      <description>Would you like to make money online with your smartphone? Do you wanna see real money-making apps that pay in 2021?
Then this course is PERFECT FOR YOU!
I created this course because every single day people ask me for the best way to get paid just by using their smartphones.
Learn just 1 strategy and you&#39;ll earn your course price back. The rest will be pure profits for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance fundamentals for beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance-fundamentals-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/personal-finance-fundamentals-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>We keep hearing about financial terms all the time in the news, in conversations, and in almost every kind of media that reaches us. But most of the time we just filter out that information as noise due to the tiresome jargon. What if you just spend a couple of hours and get a basic framework to start making sense of that noise? The main objective of this course is to create awareness about the bigger picture of the finance ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Speaking: You Can Give Great Financial Presentations</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-you-can-give-great-financial-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:36:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/public-speaking-you-can-give-great-financial-presentations/</guid>
      <description>Public Speaking. Imagine giving a financial presentation and your audience is following you closely, understanding your key points and remembering the most important numbers and trends. Would you like to be able to give a financial presentation knowing that you will appear confident and relaxed, and that your audience can clearly understand your key takeaways? In this How to Give Financial Presentations Public Speaking course you will learn the following: *How to avoid the most common blunders in financial presentations that make most audience members zone out *How to use PowerPoint effectively *How to get audiences to understand complex financial concepts *How to get your audience to remember your most important numbers and messages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn about Credit and Credit Repair from Scratch</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-about-credit-and-credit-repair-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-about-credit-and-credit-repair-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>Sadly, many people get into a debt spiral that soon goes out of control. They have trouble keeping their head above water, and soon they fall under as the weight of debt drags them down.
Thankfully, credit can be managed and all it takes is having the ability to change how one lives their life. By implementing the lessons explained in this course, an individual will be able to take their credit and repair it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
