<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Office Productivity on </title>
    <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/office-productivity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Office Productivity on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jobready.courseintern.com/tags/office-productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Clarity for Web Analytics :  A-Z Complete Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-clarity-for-web-analytics-a-z-complete-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 20:43:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-clarity-for-web-analytics-a-z-complete-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>This course on Microsoft Clarity will help you learn how to leverage this new FREE tool by Microsoft - that makes you understand the actual user experience and gain actionable insights for your website - some insights that are currently only offered by Clarity - like Recordings, Heatmaps, dead clicks and more !
Top Reasons why you should take this Course :
Currently the only course on Udemy on Microsoft Clarity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop Job Costing</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-job-costing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 20:43:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-job-costing/</guid>
      <description>This QuickBooks Desktop Job Costing course will provide the resources for learners to develop a solid understanding of job costing concepts and the tools QuickBooks provides to create an effective job costing system.
The course will include four example problems demonstrating different job costing systems and methods that can be used.
We will provide backup files so learners can jump forward in the problems or rework any component of a problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel - الاكسل من الصفر للاحتراف</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%83%D8%B3%D9%84-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B5%D9%81%D8%B1-%D9%84%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%83%D8%B3%D9%84-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B5%D9%81%D8%B1-%D9%84%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Excel من البرامج الهامة في حياتنا ولعل اشهرها هو Spread sheets برامج ال هذا الكورس يتكون من 56 فيديو قصير ستتمكن من خلالهم .فهم جميع ادوات البرنامج بكل سهولة خطوة بخطوة وايضًا ستتعلم تقنيات واساليب تساعدك علي توفير الوقت والمجهود من خلال شرح مبسط وعملي
ايضًا ستتعلم طريقة اظهار بياناتك بشكل افضل و تعديلها بسهولة عن طريق الجداول والرسوم البيانية
في النهاية ستتعلم كيفية الاستفادة الكاملة من برنامج ميكروسوفت اكسل واضافة البيانات و تحليلها واجراء العمليات الحسابية بكل كفاءة وسهولة **مرفق مع كل درس ملف التدريب**</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft PowerPoint  - البوربوينت من الصفر للاحتراف</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-powerpoint-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A8%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%A8%D9%88%D9%8A%D9%86%D8%AA-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B5%D9%81%D8%B1-%D9%84%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-powerpoint-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A8%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%A8%D9%88%D9%8A%D9%86%D8%AA-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B5%D9%81%D8%B1-%D9%84%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81/</guid>
      <description>من أفضل البرامج المستعملة في تصميم عروض تقديمية إحترافية وعمل البريزنتيشن البوربوينت البوربوينت يتم استخدامه كأداة عرض رئيسية في المدارس والشركات ويجب ان يكون مهارة اساسية تتعلمها و تضيفها لمجموعة مهاراتك نظراً لأهميته و كثرة الطلب عليه فى سوق العمل لاحتوائه على مجموعة من القوالب الأنيقة التي تجعل إنشاء العروض التقديمية أكثر بساطة.
تستطيع ان تتعلمه من الصفر للاحتراف من هذا الكورس
هذا الكورس يتكون من ثلاثة اقسام
القسم الاول : ستتعلم فيه جميع اوامر البوربوينت مع تطبيقات عملية</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Word - الوورد من الصفر للاحتراف</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-word-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%88%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%AF-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B5%D9%81%D8%B1-%D9%84%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-word-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%88%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%AF-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B5%D9%81%D8%B1-%D9%84%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81/</guid>
      <description>ميكروسوفت وورد من البرامج الهامة في حياتنا والاكثر احتياجًا في سوق العمل لذلك لا يمكننا التخلي عنه فبرنامج الورد يتم استخدامه من أجل كتابة و تعديل النصوص و إضافة الصور التوضيحية و يمكن عمل تصاميم مختلفة من خلاله
سيقوم هذا الكورس بمساعدتك لفهم جميع ادوات البرنامج بكل سهولة خطوة بخطوة وايضًا ستتعلم تقنيات واساليب تساعدك علي توفير الوقت والمجهود ايضًا ستتعلم طريقة اظهار بياناتك بشكل افضل عن طريق الجداول والرسوم البيانية والاشكال التوضيحية في النهاية ستتعلم كيفية الاستفادة الكاملة من برنامج ميكروسوفت ورد و تعديل المستندات بكل كفاءة وسهولة هذا الكورس يتكون من ثلاثة اقسام</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Online vs Xero Accounting Software</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-vs-xero-accounting-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 19:44:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-vs-xero-accounting-software/</guid>
      <description>This course will compare two leading online accounting software applications, QuickBooks Online and Xero, in a step by step format.
This is a comprehensive accounting course.
We will discuss the purchasing options and the best tools to learn these accounting software packages at the lowest cost.
Learners will understand how to set up a new company file in each software package.
The course will demonstrate how to navigate each software package and how to generate, analyze, and customize common financial reports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel Accounting 2–Worksheet, Opening Balances, &amp; Subledger</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-accounting-2worksheet-opening-balances-subledger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-accounting-2worksheet-opening-balances-subledger/</guid>
      <description>In this course we will create an accounting system starting from a blank Excel worksheet and add begging balances to our accounts.
Learners will learn how to navigate Microsoft Excel as well as how to create a well-designed accounting worksheet, complete with a general journal, trial balance, general ledger, and subsidiary ledgers for accounts receivable, accounts payable, &amp;amp; inventory. Excel is a very good tool to learn accounting because it is much more transparent than a database program, like accounting software, QuickBooks being a common example of accounting software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Microsoft Word Tutorial - Basic to Advance</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/full-microsoft-word-tutorial-basic-to-advance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/full-microsoft-word-tutorial-basic-to-advance/</guid>
      <description>If you are a beginner (with zero experience) or someone with some knowledge of using Microsoft word and you want to upscale your skillset and take your document preparation and editing to the next level, then this course is for you.
Hi, I am Dr. Rasheed, a speech and presentation coach, I have used Microsoft Word over the last 20 years to write and edti academic and no-academic reports, journals, articles and have written thesis and dissertations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Looker Masterclass: Looker &amp; LookML A-Z 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-looker-masterclass-looker-lookml-a-z-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-looker-masterclass-looker-lookml-a-z-2022/</guid>
      <description>5 Reasons why you should choose this Google Looker course
Carefully designed course, teaching you not only frontend of Looker but also the LookML part
Concise - you can complete this Google Looker course within one weekend
Business-related examples and case studies
Downloadable resources for learning Google Looker
Your queries will be responded by the Instructor himself
Start using Google Looker to its full potential to become proficient at Google Looker and LookML today!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Spreadsheets: Empieza desde cero</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-spreadsheets-empieza-desde-cero/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-spreadsheets-empieza-desde-cero/</guid>
      <description>¿Por qué aprender Google Sheets?
La forma en que usamos las hojas de cálculo está cambiando. La mayor parte de nuestro trabajo y colaboración se realiza a través de canales en línea, nuestras hojas de cálculo también se están moviendo en línea. Google Sheets es un programa de hojas de cálculo en línea que ofrece soluciones que muchas empresas necesitan en este momento.
En el pasado, el principal requisito que tenían las empresas era que los profesionales tuvieran sólidos conocimientos en Microsoft Excel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel: Intermedio, Funciones, Tablas Dinámicas y &#43;</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-intermedio-funciones-tablas-din%C3%A1micas-y-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:28:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-intermedio-funciones-tablas-din%C3%A1micas-y-/</guid>
      <description>¡El curso de Microsoft Excel que te da más valor!
¿Quieres aprender una habilidad que te ayude a incrementar tus ingresos? Si es así, entonces ¡Este curso es para ti!
Excel es utilizado por todas las empresas del mundo para procesar su información. Saber como sacar provecho de la información para hacer propuestas de valor con esta herramienta te pondrá un paso adelante de los demás.
¿Qué esperas?
Saber trabajar Excel, nos abrirá muchas puertas en el mercado laboral debido a que el Excel es una herramienta que nos permite llevar a cabo un montón de tareas diferentes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cost Volume Profit Analysis (CVP) – Managerial Accounting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cost-volume-profit-analysis-cvp-managerial-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/cost-volume-profit-analysis-cvp-managerial-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Managerial and cost accounting topics of cost volume profit analysis (CVP).
We will review managerial accounting concepts and the difference between managerial accounting and cost accounting.
The course will start out introducing our primary CVP tool, a contribution margin income statement. The contribution margin income statement will give us an idea of where we are going as we then zoom into more detail going forward, focusing on the nuances of each step in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Costing QuickBooks Online - Contractors</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/job-costing-quickbooks-online-contractors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/job-costing-quickbooks-online-contractors/</guid>
      <description>This QuickBooks Online Job Costing course will provide the resources for learners to develop a solid understanding of job costing concepts and the tools QuickBooks provides to create an effective job costing system.
We will discuss the process of setting up QuickBooks for a job costing system.
The course will describe the terminology used by software and by the industry, such as jobs, sub customers, and projects.
Learners will understand how to set up projects and how they function to track costs and revenue per job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Online Not for Profit Organization</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-not-for-profit-organization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-not-for-profit-organization/</guid>
      <description>Learners will understand how to set up QuickBooks Online for a Not for Profit Organization.
The course will show how to use free resources to optimize learning.
We will demonstrate the use of class tracking to generate Not for Profit reports.
Learners will see how to create and use donation receipt forms.
We will show how to create and use pledge receipt forms.
The course will demonstrate how to enter and track restricted resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xero Job Costing – Projects</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/xero-job-costing-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 16:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/xero-job-costing-projects/</guid>
      <description>This Xero Job Costing course will provide the resources for learners to develop a solid understanding of job costing concepts and the tools Xero provides to create an effective job costing system.
We will discuss the process of setting up Xero for a job costing system.
The course will describe the terminology used by software and by the industry, such as jobs, sub customers, and projects.
Learners will understand how to set up projects and how they function to track costs and revenue per job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel Pivot-Tabellen für Job und Beruf</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-pivot-tabellen-f%C3%BCr-job-und-beruf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2022 21:42:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-pivot-tabellen-f%C3%BCr-job-und-beruf/</guid>
      <description>Hast Du schon einmal mit großen Tabellen in Microsoft Excel gearbeitet und das Gefühl gehabt, zu ersticken? Hast Du mit dem Autofilter zu kämpfen und können einfach nicht die richtigen Daten finden? Dann sind Pivot-Tabellen genau die richtige Lösung für Dich! Mit ein paar Klicks verwandelst du deine Daten in praktische Dashboards, die Du blitzschnell ändern kannst. Pivot-Tabellen indizieren alle Deine Daten und bereiten sie für Dich auf. Das Ergebnis ist eine Tabelle, aus der Du Summen, Durchschnittswerte oder beliebige Zwischenergebnisse generieren kannst - alles, was Du willst!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Power BI DAX: Aprende las funciones más avanzadas</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/power-bi-dax-aprende-las-funciones-m%C3%A1s-avanzadas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/power-bi-dax-aprende-las-funciones-m%C3%A1s-avanzadas/</guid>
      <description>¡Vuélvete un experto en el Business Intelligence con DAX de Power BI!
Si eres un estudiante o profesionista que quiere potenciar su carrera profesional te tengo una buena noticia:
¡Encontraste el curso indicado!
¿Sientes que tu carrera profesional esta estancada?
¿Tu perfil no destaca entre el de los demás?
¿Sientes que en la escuela no aprendiste nada útil para el mundo laboral?
¿Crees que Excel es la única herramienta para analizar datos y hacer gráficas?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel: Análisis de datos con tablas dinámicas</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-an%C3%A1lisis-de-datos-con-tablas-din%C3%A1micas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 21:22:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-an%C3%A1lisis-de-datos-con-tablas-din%C3%A1micas/</guid>
      <description>¡El curso de Microsoft Excel que te da más valor!
¿Quieres aprender una habilidad que te ayude a incrementar tus ingresos? Si es así, entonces ¡Este curso es para ti!
Las tablas dinámicas son la herramienta mas poderosa de Excel. Con ellas podemos analizar y resumir una gran cantidad de información de una manera rápida y sencilla.
Excel es utilizado por todas las empresas del mundo para procesar su información. Saber como sacar provecho de la información para hacer propuestas de valor con esta herramienta te pondrá un paso adelante de los demás.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel Accounting 6–Adjusting Entries &amp; Financial Statements</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-accounting-6adjusting-entries-financial-statements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-accounting-6adjusting-entries-financial-statements/</guid>
      <description>This course will focus on period-end adjusting entries, entries needed to report financial statements accurately on an accrual basis.
Learners will know how to navigate Microsoft Excel and use a well-designed accounting worksheet, complete with a general journal, trial balance, general ledger, subsidiary ledgers for accounts receivable, accounts payable, &amp;amp; inventory, financial statements, and much more.
Excel is an excellent tool to learn accounting because it is much more transparent than a database program, like accounting software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel Masterclass for Business Managers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-masterclass-for-business-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 20:40:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-masterclass-for-business-managers/</guid>
      <description>7 Reasons why you should choose this Excel course
Carefully designed curriculum teaching you only the most used functionalities of Microsoft Excel in business environment
Concise - you can complete this Microsoft Excel course within one weekend
Business related examples, data analysis and case studies solved using Advanced Excel.
You will learn various data analysis techniques using MS Excel
Ample practice exercises on data analysis, MS excel (basic &amp;amp; advanced), because Excel requires practice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ms Excel/Excel 2022 - The Complete Introduction to Excel</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ms-excel/excel-2022-the-complete-introduction-to-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:33:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/ms-excel/excel-2022-the-complete-introduction-to-excel/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft Excel is definetly not an easy application to learn and to use. This is why sometimes it&#39;s better to have someone that help us learning how to properly work with this amazing APP. Indeed, wether you are: - A student looking to learn how to use this APP for a school project
- Looking to learn microsoft Excel for professional goals
- Want to improve your knowledge and learn new skills</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete SAP Analytics Cloud Course 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-sap-analytics-cloud-course-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 20:33:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-sap-analytics-cloud-course-2022/</guid>
      <description>Become an SAP Analytics Cloud master by setting up BI, planning, and making prediction through real-world projects
SAP analytics cloud consultant is one of the hottest careers in tech. Have you ever wondered what&#39;s the best path for me or what&#39;s my first step in building a technical career in SAP business analysis?
I&#39;m going to take you through the process of understanding how to use SAP analytics cloud. Whether you&#39;re looking to discover the core BI features or use planning module at work, this course will get you ready to plan and start to use SAP analytics cloud quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Google Sheets In 1 Day With Fascinating Projects</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-google-sheets-in-1-day-with-fascinating-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-google-sheets-in-1-day-with-fascinating-projects/</guid>
      <description>Learn Google Sheets in a fascinating way by doing real-world, highly-applicable projects.
As I walk you through every important feature of Google Sheets, I&#39;ll be showing you real-world examples of situations where you can use your new Google Sheets skills. This way the course will stay interesting and move along more quickly.
Our first example will be for how to manage your SEO marketing by tracking progress in a spreadsheet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel Accounting 4–Enter Data &amp; Track Current Month &amp; YTD</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-accounting-4enter-data-track-current-month-ytd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-accounting-4enter-data-track-current-month-ytd/</guid>
      <description>This course will enter a month&#39;s worth of data input into an accounting system using Excel, which has already been set up and includes one month of data input.
Learners will learn how to navigate Microsoft Excel and use a well-designed accounting worksheet, complete with a general journal, trial balance, general ledger, subsidiary ledgers for accounts receivable, accounts payable, &amp;amp; inventory, financial statements, and much more.
Excel is an excellent tool to learn accounting because it is much more transparent than a database program, like accounting software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NUMBERS es el EXCEL para ipad y iphone - Curso completo</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/numbers-es-el-excel-para-ipad-y-iphone-curso-completo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 21:30:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/numbers-es-el-excel-para-ipad-y-iphone-curso-completo/</guid>
      <description>Con Numbers puedes crear hojas de cálculo asombrosas con tablas e imágenes increíbles. Incluso puedes usar el Apple Pencil en el iPad para agregar diagramas e imágenes coloridas. Y las funcionalidades de colaboración en tiempo real permiten que tú y tu equipo trabajen al mismo tiempo usando un Mac, un iPad, un iPhone o incluso un PC.
En este curso, descubrirás lo fácil, lo intuitivo y lo poderoso de Numbers, las hojas de cálculo dejan de ser pesadas y aburridoras, podrás compartirlas en diferentes formatos o incluso imprímelas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airtable Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/airtable-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/airtable-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to project management but don&#39;t know where to start?	Would you like to make amazing projects and apps and bring your ideas to life?	Then Airtable Ultimate Course is for you!	Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Airtable is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. We&#39;ll Cover everything you need to know about Airtable from scratch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Drive Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-drive-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-drive-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Google Drive but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Docs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Google Drive 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Google Drive is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building Docs like an expert with Google Drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Forms Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-forms-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-forms-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>SO, YOU’RE LOOKING FOR A COURSE THAT WILL TEACH YOU GOOGLE FORMS QUICKLY &amp;amp; IN A FUN MANNER?
I’ve got just the course for you!
Welcome, my name is Josh Werner with Learn Tech Plus and I’ve put this course together to help people just like you quickly master Google Forms...Whether you’re a beginner or experienced with Google Forms!
If your goal is to become a master of Google Forms, then this course is perfect for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft OneDrive Ultimate Course 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-onedrive-ultimate-course-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-onedrive-ultimate-course-2022/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Microsoft OneDrive but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to manage Files and bring your ideas to life?
Then Microsoft OneDrive 2022 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Microsoft OneDrive is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start managing files like an expert with Microsoft OneDrive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Outlook</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-outlook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 21:38:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-outlook/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Microsoft Outlook but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to manage emails and bring your ideas to life?
Then Microsoft Outlook 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Microsoft Outlook is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start managing emails like an expert with Microsoft Outlook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asana Ultimate Course 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/asana-ultimate-course-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/asana-ultimate-course-2022/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Asana but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Projects and bring your ideas to life?
Then Asana 2022 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Asana is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start projects like an expert with Asana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Docs Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-docs-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-docs-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Google Docs but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Docs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Google Docs 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Google Docs is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building Docs like an expert with Google Docs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Workspace (G Suite) Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-workspace-g-suite-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-workspace-g-suite-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Google Workspace but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to manager accounts and bring your ideas to life?
Then Google Workspace 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Google Workspace is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start adding accounts like an expert with Google Workspace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft 365 Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-365-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-365-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Microsoft 365 but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to manager accounts and bring your ideas to life?
Then Microsoft 365 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Microsoft 365 is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start adding accounts like an expert with Microsoft 365.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Teams Ultimate Course 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-teams-ultimate-course-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-teams-ultimate-course-2022/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Microsoft Teams but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to create Teams and bring your ideas to life?
Then Microsoft Teams 2022 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Microsoft Teams is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start creating Teams like an expert with Microsoft Teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Word Ultimate Course 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-word-ultimate-course-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-word-ultimate-course-2022/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Microsoft Word but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to create Docs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Microsoft Word 2022 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Microsoft Word is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start creating Docs like an expert with Microsoft Word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail Productivity Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gmail-productivity-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gmail-productivity-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Gmail but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Email and bring your ideas to life?
Then Gmail 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Gmail is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building Emails like an expert with Gmail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel Ultimate Course 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-ultimate-course-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-ultimate-course-2022/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Microsoft Excel but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to create Spreadsheets and bring your ideas to life?
Then Microsoft Excel 2022 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Microsoft Excel is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start creating spreadsheets like an expert with Microsoft Excel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft OneNote Ultimate Course 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-onenote-ultimate-course-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-onenote-ultimate-course-2022/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Microsoft OneNote but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to manage Notebooks and bring your ideas to life?
Then Microsoft OneNote 2022 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Microsoft OneNote is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start managing Notebooks like an expert with Microsoft OneNote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Planner Ultimate Course 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-planner-ultimate-course-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-planner-ultimate-course-2022/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Microsoft Planner but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to manage plans and bring your ideas to life?
Then Microsoft Planner 2022 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Microsoft Planner is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start managing plans like an expert with Microsoft Planner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Power BI Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-power-bi-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-power-bi-basics/</guid>
      <description>SO, YOU’RE LOOKING FOR A COURSE THAT WILL TEACH YOU MICROSOFT POWER BI QUICKLY &amp;amp; IN A FUN MANNER?
I’ve got just the course for you!
Welcome, my name is Josh Werner with Learn Tech Plus and I’ve put this course together to help people just like you quickly master Microsoft Power BI...Whether you’re a beginner or experienced with Microsoft Power BI!
If your goal is to become a master of Microsoft Power BI, then this course is perfect for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Publisher</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-publisher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jun 2022 19:56:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-publisher/</guid>
      <description>SO, YOU’RE LOOKING FOR A COURSE THAT WILL TEACH YOU MICROSOFT PUBLISHER QUICKLY &amp;amp; IN A FUN MANNER?
I’ve got just the course for you!
Welcome, my name is Josh Werner with Learn Tech Plus and I’ve put this course together to help people just like you quickly master Microsoft Publisher...Whether you’re a beginner or experienced with Microsoft Publisher!
If your goal is to become a master of Microsoft Publisher, then this course is perfect for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel: Excel course for beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-excel-course-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-excel-course-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Learn Excel and its main features in this course
Why take my course?
Most courses on Udemy are hours long, why take my 30 minutes course? Well, a longer course isn&#39;t always a better one. When I started to script my course I knew what I was going to include into it, but I asked me how can I deliver all these ideas as concisely as possible?
Why did I do that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Outlook - Grundkurs für alle Einsteiger:innen</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-outlook-grundkurs-f%C3%BCr-alle-einsteigerinnen/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-outlook-grundkurs-f%C3%BCr-alle-einsteigerinnen/</guid>
      <description>In diesem Kurs lernst Du, Outlook effektiv zu nutzen, so dass auch Du produktiver wirst und eine Ordnung in Dein Postfach bekommst.
Outlook ist mittlerweile eines der meistverwendeten E-Mail Programme der Welt und dennoch wenden die meisten nur grundsätzliche Funktionen an. Das tolle an Outlook ist, dass E-Mails, Kalender, Kontakte, Aufgaben und vieles mehr an einem Ort gebündelt wird.
In diesem Kurs lernst Du alle wichtigen und grundlegenden Funktionen kennen, damit auch Du mit Outlook richtig durchstarten kannst, ohne dabei wichtige Zeit zu verlieren.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Online-Bookkeeping Business-Easy Way</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-bookkeeping-business-easy-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:31:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-online-bookkeeping-business-easy-way/</guid>
      <description>QuickBooks Online bookkeeping business designed for small business clients or small businesses who want a simple cash basis format for entering data. This course is designed for bookkeepers and is also useful for small business owners who want a simple system for entering financial data into QuickBooks for financial planning and year-end tax preparation. The bookkeeping system we discuss will also describe the relationship between the bookkeeper, the business, and the year-end tax and financial statement preparers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tax &amp; Adjusting Entry Year-End Accounting Excel Worksheet</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tax-adjusting-entry-year-end-accounting-excel-worksheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 20:12:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tax-adjusting-entry-year-end-accounting-excel-worksheet/</guid>
      <description>Create a new Excel worksheet from scratch to be used in the adjusting and tax entry process. This course is most beneficial to tax preparers and public accountants who enter adjusting entries but is also useful to anybody in accounting. Similar Excel worksheets to the ones we will construct can be useful for analyzing many areas of accounting, and the Excel skills learned in creating them are also very applicable both inside accounting and outside of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel in Hindi - हिंदी में सीखें MS Excel A-Z</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-in-hindi-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%96%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-ms-excel-a-z/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-in-hindi-%E0%A4%B9%E0%A4%BF%E0%A4%82%E0%A4%A6%E0%A5%80-%E0%A4%AE%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-%E0%A4%B8%E0%A5%80%E0%A4%96%E0%A5%87%E0%A4%82-ms-excel-a-z/</guid>
      <description>7 Reasons why you should choose this Excel course
Carefully designed curriculum teaching you only the most used functionalities of Microsoft Excel in business environment
Concise - you can complete this Microsoft Excel course within one weekend
Business related examples, data analysis and case studies solved using Advanced Excel.
You will learn various data analysis techniques using MS Excel
Ample practice exercises on data analysis, MS excel (basic &amp;amp; advanced), because Excel requires practice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop Pro -Personal Bookkeeping-Accounting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-pro-personal-bookkeeping-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-desktop-pro-personal-bookkeeping-accounting/</guid>
      <description>QuickBooks for personal bookkeeping, finance, and accounting. Enter personal financial data, create and analyze financial statements including personal balance sheet and income statements or profit &amp;amp; loss statement, &amp;amp; track important tax data.
The course will provide backup files that can be used to jump forward or to rework any component of the course. Backup files and the ability to use multiple QuickBooks files, in a similar way we use multiple Microsoft Word documents, is a HUGE benefit to learning QuickBooks and accounting that QuickBooks Desktop offers us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tax Credits - Family &amp; Dependent Tax Credits</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tax-credits-family-dependent-tax-credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:29:57 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tax-credits-family-dependent-tax-credits/</guid>
      <description>Family &amp;amp; dependent tax credits in 2018 including the earned income tax credit, child tax credit, child &amp;amp; dependent care tax credit, other dependents tax credit, credit for elderly or the disabled, and adoption tax credit.
This course will provide a detailed look at these tax credits, including a discussion of the amount of the tax credits and the qualifications to take the tax credits.
We will use tax software and forms to show how the tax credits are input into the tax forms and to test variations in qualifications for the tax credits including income limitations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP Project Essentials: Implementing SAP S/4HANA and SAP ERP</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sap-project-essentials-implementing-sap-s/4hana-and-sap-erp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sap-project-essentials-implementing-sap-s/4hana-and-sap-erp/</guid>
      <description>SAP S/4HANA is here, and the stakes are high. Get your project right with this guide to SAP Activate and Accelerated SAP (ASAP).
Help your business team prepare for and participate in the SAP project journey!
Get an early read on timelines, processes, responsibilities, and potential setbacks. Understand how your implementation, upgrade, or migration is structured, how to assemble the deliverables, and how to dodge common pitfalls. With this preview of what to expect, what questions to ask, and when to take which steps, you can execute planning, go-live, and post-go-live activities without tripping up or getting lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel -Basic Excel/ Advanced Excel Formulas</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-basic-excel/-advanced-excel-formulas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-basic-excel/-advanced-excel-formulas/</guid>
      <description>If you want to improve your Excel skills, learn to use new functions or simply interested in becoming better in this amazing Microsoft APP then this course is for you. My name is Yassin Marco and I have been lucky enough to have the privilege to teach more than 250 000+ students in more than 190+ countries around the world. Since teaching is my passion, I decided to design this course to help people achieve there full potential with Microsoft Excel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Payroll - QuickBooks Online</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-payroll-quickbooks-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 May 2022 20:32:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quickbooks-payroll-quickbooks-online/</guid>
      <description>QuickBooks Online payroll will describe the payroll process for a small business in detail, so bookkeepers, accountants, and business owners can better understand how to set up payroll, process payroll, and troubleshoot problems related to payroll. This course will introduce the payroll set-up in the QuickBooks Online system, walking through payroll screens. We will discuss payroll legislation that will affect payroll calculations within QuickBooks Online and list the payroll forms we will need to generate from Quickbooks Online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Order Costing System – Managerial Accounting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/job-order-costing-system-managerial-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/job-order-costing-system-managerial-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Job cost system – Managerial Accounting
We will start by introducing managerial accounting or cost accounting topics that apply to companies that manufacture using either a job cost system or a process cost system. The course will describe classifications for costs and the importance of being able to classify costs in different ways. We will list and describe an outline of the process costs go through as they flow through the accounting process in a manufacturing company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel: Desde cero para profesionales</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-desde-cero-para-profesionales/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2022 20:27:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-desde-cero-para-profesionales/</guid>
      <description>Excel es una hoja de calculo creada por Microsoft compatible con diversos Sistemas Operativos es por ello que su popularidad y uso es grade, además de ser muy potente, tener diversas áreas de aplicación y ser de gran capacidad
Es por ello que hoy en día, de acuerdo a los avances tecnológicos en aprendizaje de Excel es indispensable para el mundo escolar y laboral.
Excel es increíblemente fácil de utilizar, pero a muchos de nosotros no nos enseñaron como hacerlo en la escuela.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alteryx Masterclass for Data Analytics, ETL and Reporting</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/alteryx-masterclass-for-data-analytics-etl-and-reporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:57:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/alteryx-masterclass-for-data-analytics-etl-and-reporting/</guid>
      <description>5 Reasons why you should choose this Alteryx course
Carefully designed curriculum teaching you only the most used functionalities of Alteryx in business environment
Concise - you can complete this Alteryx designer core certification course within one weekend
Business related examples and case studies for learning Alteryx and becoming an Alteryx designer
Downloadable resources on Alteryx
Your queries will be responded by the Instructor himself
A Verifiable Certificate of Completion is presented to all students who undertake this Alteryx course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Data Studio Complete Beginners to Advanced Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-data-studio-complete-beginners-to-advanced-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 19:57:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-data-studio-complete-beginners-to-advanced-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>This Google Data Studio course will help you to become a Data Visualization Expert and will enhance your skills by offering you comprehensive knowledge, and the required hands-on experience on this widely used Cloud based BI tool, by solving real-time industry-based projects.
Top Reasons why you should learn Google Data Studio : Google data Studio is the #1 cloud based Free Business Intelligence tool used industry wide.
The demand for BI professionals is on the rise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Microsoft Publisher | Complete Microsoft Publisher</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-microsoft-publisher-complete-microsoft-publisher/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 20:03:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-microsoft-publisher-complete-microsoft-publisher/</guid>
      <description>Learn the Microsoft Publisher Designing Skills By joining this Complete Microsoft Publisher Training Course.
Microsoft Publisher is one of the Products of Microsoft Office. Microsoft Publisher interface looks very much like other Microsoft office products as Microsoft Word but it is extensively used for designing. Microsoft Publisher is used for different design work. Microsoft Publisher can be used for advertisements design, certificate design, newsletter design, flyer or brochure design, banner design, business card design, or letterhead design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Access Training | Master the MS Access</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-access-training-master-the-ms-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2022 20:03:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-access-training-master-the-ms-access/</guid>
      <description>Learn the Microsoft Access Skills by joining this MS Access Training Course.
Microsoft Access is one of the products of Microsoft Office. Microsoft Access has an interface that looks like other Microsoft Office products but there are so many other tools in MS Access that you can&#39;t see in other Microsoft Office applications as it is specially designed for a unique purpose. Microsoft Access is extensively used in data handling or creating the database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Your Excel Look Like a Standalone Program</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/make-your-excel-look-like-a-standalone-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 20:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/make-your-excel-look-like-a-standalone-program/</guid>
      <description>DO YOU WANT TO CHANGE THE INTERFACE OF YOUR EXCEL SHEET TO LOOK LIKE A NORMAL COMPUTER PROGRAM? You may have needed to create your own program based on an idea that you had in mind, but the challenge has always been that learning a programming language can be a long process that consumes A LOT OF TIME!! Using Microsoft Excel can make this process much simpler, especially when you can make your Excel spreadsheet have the interface of a Standalone Computer Program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master all the MS Excel Macros and the basics of Excel VBA</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-all-the-ms-excel-macros-and-the-basics-of-excel-vba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 16:10:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/master-all-the-ms-excel-macros-and-the-basics-of-excel-vba/</guid>
      <description>Working with microsoft Excel is not always easy and learning to automate your work with the use of VBA is even harder. Indeed, VBA is a programming language that is really useful in Microsoft Excel especially if you want to be able to automate all the tasks that you want to accomplish. If you :
- Are in school and want to learn how to program With VBA
- Need to learn Excel VBA for work or task automation - Want to start a personal project that requires you to have Excel VBA knowledge</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel - MS Excel Formulas &amp; Functions in just 3hrs</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-ms-excel-formulas-functions-in-just-3hrs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-ms-excel-formulas-functions-in-just-3hrs/</guid>
      <description>Start using Excel to its full potential to become proficient at your Excel tasks today! Either you&#39;re new to Excel, or you&#39;ve played around with it but want to get more comfortable with all the popular functions in Microsoft Excel, either way, this course will be great for you.
A Verifiable Certificate of Completion is presented to all students who undertake this Excel course.
Why should you choose this course?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Google Drive Course - Mastering Google Drive</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-google-drive-course-mastering-google-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-google-drive-course-mastering-google-drive/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to The Complete Google Drive Course. This course will teach you to understand how to use and become familiar with the storage and productivity component of Google Suite: Google Drive and Google Apps.
Google Drive is a safe and secure online file storage service that allows for easy collaboration and sharing. It is compatible with all types of files, ranging from PDFs to images to videos. Unlike its competitors, Google Drive offers up to 15 GB of free storage and a variety of online tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools for Working From Home - Google Apps, Trello &amp; Zoom</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tools-for-working-from-home-google-apps-trello-zoom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/tools-for-working-from-home-google-apps-trello-zoom/</guid>
      <description>You&#39;re looking for a complete course on Work from Home tools to increase your productivity while working remotely, right?
You&#39;ve found the right &#34;Tools for remote working&#34; course. This course teaches you about different free tools available to increase your productivity, manage products and effectively communicate with your team.
What is covered in this course?
Mastering remote work is all about finding the right tools to stay productive and connected. This course will have you and your team synchronized and working in harmony, wherever you happen to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zero to Hero in Microsoft Excel: Complete Excel guide 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/zero-to-hero-in-microsoft-excel-complete-excel-guide-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 17:34:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/zero-to-hero-in-microsoft-excel-complete-excel-guide-2022/</guid>
      <description>7 Reasons why you should choose this Excel course
Carefully designed curriculum teaching you only the most used functionalities of Microsoft Excel in business environment
Concise - you can complete this Microsoft Excel course within one weekend
Business related examples, data analysis and case studies solved using Advanced Excel.
You will learn various data analysis techniques using MS Excel
Ample practice exercises on data analysis, MS excel (basic &amp;amp; advanced), because Excel requires practice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Microsoft Excel Formulas &amp; Functions - 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-microsoft-excel-formulas-functions-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 12:48:24 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-microsoft-excel-formulas-functions-2022/</guid>
      <description>Recent Student&#39;s Reviews ***I Really Enjoyed This Course. I Have Been Using Excel For Years But Found This To Be Very Helpful Information. Thank You! - Sandra Inglis***
***It’s Something I Was Searching For A Long Time - Krati Maheshwari***
***Thank You Very Much For This Course, This Has Given Me Very Good Knowledge Of Excel And Most Important Thing Is The Resources Available For Download And Practice. Once Again Thank You Very Much For This Nice Course With Very Nice Explanation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EXCEL para principiantes enfocado a los  negocios</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-para-principiantes-enfocado-a-los-negocios/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 16:38:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-para-principiantes-enfocado-a-los-negocios/</guid>
      <description>¿Alguna vez te has preguntado cómo empresas usan Excel en el manejo de sus datos?
Realizado con la ultima versión disponible para 2021 de este programa. Este curso persigue que los estudiantes adquieran destrezas en el uso de Excel, pero con un enfoque orientado a los negocios. Al finalizar el curso, podrás crear archivos tales como: Nóminas, informes financieros, gráficos estadísticos, presupuestos y todo documento relacionado con hojas de cálculo .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel - Learn MS EXCEL For DATA Analysis</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-learn-ms-excel-for-data-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 16:38:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-learn-ms-excel-for-data-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Whether you are interested in learning
- Different ways of how to properly use Microsoft Excel
- Learn the basics of Data Analysis
- Learn how to create different Excel Apps
- Just grow your Knowledge about this amazing Microsoft App
Or any other reason, this course is definitely for you. The way this class have been designed was to offer to the student an easy way to learn Microsoft Excel and the basics of Data analysis at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Microsoft Outlook | Complete Microsoft Outlook Guide</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-microsoft-outlook-complete-microsoft-outlook-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 17:17:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/learn-microsoft-outlook-complete-microsoft-outlook-guide/</guid>
      <description>Learn the Microsoft Outlook Skills by joining this Complete Microsoft Outlook Training Course.
Microsoft Outlook is one of the products of Microsoft Office. Microsoft Office products usually have almost the same kind of interface &amp;amp; the same is the case for Microsoft Outlook. Microsoft Outlook is extensively used for office work. Microsoft Outlook is used for different kinds of office work. Microsoft Outlook is mainly used for sending or receiving emails.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft OneNote Training | Master the Microsoft OneNote</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-onenote-training-master-the-microsoft-onenote/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2022 17:17:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-onenote-training-master-the-microsoft-onenote/</guid>
      <description>Learn the Microsoft OneNote Skills by joining this Microsoft OneNote Training Course.
Microsoft OneNote is one of the products of Microsoft Office. Although Microsoft OneNote has almost the same interface as other Microsoft Office products, in addition to this Microsoft OneNote also has some other useful tools which are not available in other Microsoft Office products. Microsoft OneNote as the name indicates is extensively used in academic work or any office work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Workspace: Docs, Sheets, Slides  من الصفر للاحتراف</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-workspace-docs-sheets-slides-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B5%D9%81%D8%B1-%D9%84%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 22:09:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-workspace-docs-sheets-slides-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B5%D9%81%D8%B1-%D9%84%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81/</guid>
      <description>Google Office ابدأ تعلم جوجل اوفيس (مستندات جوجل , جوجل سلايدز , جوجل شيت) من البرامج القوية التي تستخدم كبديل قوي لبرامج ميكروسوفت اوفيس(الوورد , البوربوينت
, الاكسل) التي نحتاجها تقريبًا في كل شىء معظم الوقت
ما يميز حزمة برامج جوجل اوفيس او جوجل ورك سبيس انها مجانية تماما وايضًا اونلاين لا تحتاج لتنزيل اي شىء على جهازك غير انها مرتبطة بجوجل درايف وتقوم بحفظ كل شىء تلقائيًا في هذا الكورس سوف نتعلم اهم برامج جوجل اوفيس ; مستندات جوجل , جوجل شيت , وجوجل سلايدز Google Docs - اولًا مستندات جوجل</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Advanced Data Entry Application in Microsoft Excel</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-advanced-data-entry-application-in-microsoft-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 22:09:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-advanced-data-entry-application-in-microsoft-excel/</guid>
      <description>Reasons why you should choose this Complete Advanced Data Entry Application In Microsoft Excel course
Carefully designed curriculum By Proficient In Microsoft Excel Expert
you can complete this course In Short time
Advanced data entry application related examples ,case studies &amp;amp; Practical Examples Explained By Instructor
Your queries will be responded by the Instructor With In Short time
A Verifiable Certificate will Be Provided On the Completion
Well-designed and easy-to-understand materials</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft MyAnalytics Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-myanalytics-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-myanalytics-basics/</guid>
      <description>SO, YOU’RE LOOKING FOR A COURSE THAT WILL TEACH YOU MICROSOFT MYANALYTICS QUICKLY &amp;amp; IN A FUN MANNER?
I’ve got just the course for you!
Welcome, my name is Josh Werner with Learn Tech Plus and I’ve put this course together to help people just like you quickly master Microsoft MyAnalytics...Whether you’re a beginner or experienced with Microsoft MyAnalytics!
If your goal is to become a master of Microsoft MyAnalytics, then this course is perfect for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Power Automate (Flow) Ultimate Course 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-power-automate-flow-ultimate-course-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-power-automate-flow-ultimate-course-2022/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Microsoft Power Automate but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to create Flows and bring your ideas to life?
Then Microsoft Power Automate 2022 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Microsoft Power Automate is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start creating Flows like an expert with Microsoft Power Automate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft PowerPoint Ultimate Course 2022</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-powerpoint-ultimate-course-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-powerpoint-ultimate-course-2022/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Microsoft PowerPoint but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to create Presentations and bring your ideas to life?
Then Microsoft PowerPoint 2022 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Microsoft PowerPoint is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start creating Presentations like an expert with Microsoft PowerPoint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft To Do Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-to-do-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-to-do-basics/</guid>
      <description>SO, YOU’RE LOOKING FOR A COURSE THAT WILL TEACH YOU MICROSOFT TO DO QUICKLY &amp;amp; IN A FUN MANNER?
I’ve got just the course for you!
Welcome, my name is Josh Werner with Learn Tech Plus and I’ve put this course together to help people just like you quickly master Microsoft To Do...Whether you’re a beginner or experienced with Microsoft To Do!
If your goal is to become a master of Microsoft To Do, then this course is perfect for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Stream Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-stream-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-stream-basics/</guid>
      <description>SO, YOU’RE LOOKING FOR A COURSE THAT WILL TEACH YOU MICROSOFT STREAM QUICKLY &amp;amp; IN A FUN MANNER?
I’ve got just the course for you!
Welcome, my name is Josh Werner with Learn Tech Plus and I’ve put this course together to help people just like you quickly master Microsoft Stream...Whether you’re a beginner or experienced with Microsoft Stream!
If your goal is to become a master of Microsoft Stream, then this course is perfect for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Sway Basics</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-sway-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 14:41:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-sway-basics/</guid>
      <description>SO, YOU’RE LOOKING FOR A COURSE THAT WILL TEACH YOU MICROSOFT SWAY QUICKLY &amp;amp; IN A FUN MANNER?
I’ve got just the course for you!
Welcome, my name is Josh Werner with Learn Tech Plus and I’ve put this course together to help people just like you quickly master Microsoft Sway...Whether you’re a beginner or experienced with Microsoft Sway!
If your goal is to become a master of Microsoft Sway, then this course is perfect for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Gmail Productivity Course -  More Productive Email</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-gmail-productivity-course-more-productive-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:15:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-gmail-productivity-course-more-productive-email/</guid>
      <description>Complete Gmail Productivity Course - More Productive Email: Boost Productivity - Master Gmail Tips, Tricks, and Techniques - Learn Email Strategies To Make Your Time More Effective
Secure, smart, and easy to use email: Get more done with Gmail. Now integrated with Google Chat, Google Meet, and more, all in one place. Email that&#39;s secure, private, and puts you in control. We never use your Gmail content for any ads purposes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Google Sheets Course - Google Spreadsheet Tips</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-google-sheets-course-google-spreadsheet-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 21:15:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-google-sheets-course-google-spreadsheet-tips/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Google Sheets Course - Google Spreadsheet Tips: Learn Google Sheets from Beginner to Advanced - Learn Pivot Tables - Graphs -Dashboards - More!
Google Sheets is a spreadsheet program included as part of the free, web-based Google Docs Editors suite offered by Google. The service also includes Google Docs, Google Slides, Google Drawings, Google Forms, Google Sites, and Google Keep. Wikipedia
We can do much cool stuff in Google Sheets, Collaborate on data, from anywhere Establish a ground truth for data in your online spreadsheet, with easy sharing and real-time editing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slack Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/slack-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2022 19:20:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/slack-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to do project management but don&#39;t know where to start?	Would you like to make amazing projects and apps and bring your ideas to life?	Then Slack Ultimate Course is for you!	Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Slack is an in-demand skill in 2022. The course begins with the basics. We&#39;ll Cover everything you need to know about Slack from scratch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel: From Beginner to Expert</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-from-beginner-to-expert/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 19:15:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-from-beginner-to-expert/</guid>
      <description>Excel is used for many purposes in various fields. For example, one can enter, edit, store and sort, data, perform calculations, track anything, use it as a calendar and schedule events, create charts, diagrams, etc. All of the aforementioned actions will be easy for you after taking our Excel course.In this course, you will learn and practice Microsoft Excel most important functions and features. Course curriculum includes topics that are in great demand and essential for those whose work or studies require basic Excel skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Slides - جوجل سلايدز من الصفر للاحتراف</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-slides-%D8%AC%D9%88%D8%AC%D9%84-%D8%B3%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%8A%D8%AF%D8%B2-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B5%D9%81%D8%B1-%D9%84%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 21:02:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-slides-%D8%AC%D9%88%D8%AC%D9%84-%D8%B3%D9%84%D8%A7%D9%8A%D8%AF%D8%B2-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B5%D9%81%D8%B1-%D9%84%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81/</guid>
      <description>مهارة تصميم البريزنتيشن من أهم المهارات المطلوبة
شرائح جوجل او جوجل سلايدز من افضل البرامج التي تقوم بهذه المهمة فهو من افضل بدائل البوربوينت ما يميز جوجل سلايدز انه مجاني تماما وايضًا اونلاين لا تحتاج لتنزيل اي شىء على جهازك غير انه مرتبط بجوجل درايف ويقوم بحفظ كل شىء تلقائيًا
ستتعلم فى هذا الكورس جميع اوامر جوجل سلايدز مع تطبيقات عملية وطريقة تصميم عرض تقديمي احترافى
ثم سنقوم بتجميع كل ما تعلمناه لتصميم مشروع عملى في نهاية الكورس</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail - Grundkurs für jeden Einsteiger!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gmail-grundkurs-f%C3%BCr-jeden-einsteiger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2022 21:29:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/gmail-grundkurs-f%C3%BCr-jeden-einsteiger/</guid>
      <description>In diesem Kurs lernst Du, Gmail effektiv zu nutzen, so dass auch Du produktiver wirst und eine Ordnung in Dein Postfach bekommst.
Gmail ist mittlerweile eines der meistverwendeten E-Mail Programme der Welt und dennoch wenden die meisten nur grundsätzliche Funktionen an.
In diesem Kurs lernst Du alle wichtigen und grundlegenden Funktionen kennen, damit auch Du mit Gmail richtig durchstarten kannst, ohne dabei wichtige Zeit zu verlieren.
Wenn Du heute noch anfängst, Gmail mit samt seinen Funktionen zu nutzen, wirst Du schnell Routine bekommen und Du wirst einen super Überblick in Deinem Postfach erhalten.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantity Surveying With Rate Analysis And Take Off-Beginners</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quantity-surveying-with-rate-analysis-and-take-off-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 21:10:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/quantity-surveying-with-rate-analysis-and-take-off-beginners/</guid>
      <description>This course will help you to understand the roles and responsibilities of a Quantity Surveyor, the skills and educational qualifications required to start a career in Quantity Surveying, the basics of rate analysis and the required knowledge to take off quantities from construction drawings using two globally used software’s Bluebeam Revu and Planswift.
By the end of this course you will gain knowledge regarding the different element to be included while pricing your construction project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>كورس الإكسيل الإحترافى - Advanced Microsoft Excel</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D9%83%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%B3-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A5%D9%83%D8%B3%D9%8A%D9%84-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A5%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81%D9%89-advanced-microsoft-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 16:17:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D9%83%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%B3-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A5%D9%83%D8%B3%D9%8A%D9%84-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A5%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81%D9%89-advanced-microsoft-excel/</guid>
      <description>مايكروسوفت إكسل Microsoft Excel
يعد مايكروسوفت إكسل Microsoft Excel أحد أهم البرامج بسبب دوره الرئيسي في العديد من القطاعات حيث إنه برنامج جداول البيانات الأكثر استخدامًا في الحسابات وفي العديد من أنشطة الأعمال والفصول الدراسية وحتى تنظيم البيانات الشخصية.
أهمية برنامج إكسل :
برنامج الأكسل هو من أروع برامج حزمة الأوفيس و هو برنامج مجانى مفيد فى العديد من المجالات منها المحاسبية و الهندسية و الإدارية وهو فى الأساس برنامج للجداول و التعامل مع الأرقام بشكل متميز .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel - Advance Level MS Excel Training Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-advance-level-ms-excel-training-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2022 23:34:32 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-advance-level-ms-excel-training-course/</guid>
      <description>Enhance your Microsoft Excel Skills By Learning this Advance MS Excel Training Course.
Microsoft Excel is one of the most commonly used products of Microsoft office. It is used for data entry, data analysis, data presentation, or calculation. The best thing about Microsoft Excel is that this totally depends on your skill level. You can use MS Excel for any beginner or advanced level task it will be equally efficient &amp;amp; easy to use in either case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Evernote to Increase Productivity</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-use-evernote-to-increase-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:37:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/how-to-use-evernote-to-increase-productivity/</guid>
      <description>Work more efficiently. Organize Yourself. Get more orders Evernote functions as a second brain, and the best part is that it never forgets anything.
You record, organise, and share your ideas with others. That&#39;s all there is to it.
Do you have a fantastic idea? Put it in Evernote.
You can refer to it whenever you want. Don&#39;t worry about remembering every detail of your life; instead, declutter it. Then, when you&#39;re ready to make your ideas a reality, Evernote will be there to put everything together for you at your leisure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improve Your Business Productivity with Google Suite Apps</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/improve-your-business-productivity-with-google-suite-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 16:37:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/improve-your-business-productivity-with-google-suite-apps/</guid>
      <description>Greetings, Friend
Google Apps is a robust set of productivity tools. Learn how to use Google Apps and tap into its full potential at business , college or school.
Those who do not utilize cloud computing today will undoubtedly pay for it later. You have a lot of overhead to deal with as a business. There&#39;s always something to pay attention to. Every day, you only have a limited amount of time to dedicate to everything that&#39;s happening on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Word: Como hacer un índice</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/word-como-hacer-un-%C3%ADndice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 18:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/word-como-hacer-un-%C3%ADndice/</guid>
      <description>Los documentos de texto extensos y con muchos apartados suelen estar provistos de un índice o tabla de contenidos que permita a los lectores hacerse una idea rápida del contenido y, además, indique dónde encontrar cada tipo de información.
En Word no es necesario redactar los índices manualmente copiando cada una de los títulos y los números de página, ya que el procesador de texto ofrece una función para crear enlaces que facilita el trabajo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statistics and data analysis with Excel</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/statistics-and-data-analysis-with-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 16:53:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/statistics-and-data-analysis-with-excel/</guid>
      <description>In this practical course, we are going to focus on how to perform advanced statistical calculations and data analysis using Microsoft Excel.
Excel is a very used tool in several companies and has very powerful data analysis capabilities that can be used by data analysts and marketing experts. Even if you work with a lot of statistics you&#39;d be surprised at how valuable Excel is for calculating hypothesis tests and the most common metrics you can calculate on a dataset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primavera P6 Complete Course of Project Planning 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/primavera-p6-complete-course-of-project-planning-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 13:47:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/primavera-p6-complete-course-of-project-planning-2021/</guid>
      <description>Project Management is not complete without a reliable and strong programing tools to develop project plan, logically linking activities, resource loading, project monitoring and reporting. The strong reliable partner in Planning Software widely used in the world presently is Primavera p6 from oracle. This planning software is widely used across industries from manufacturing, defense, shipping, oil and gas, construction and software development projects.
The course aims to disseminate practical application of Primavera P6 for aspiring project manager, planners, schedulers, project developers and owners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>تعلم معالج النصوص &amp; العروض التقديمية من الصفر للأحتراف</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%AA%D8%B9%D9%84%D9%85-%D9%85%D8%B9%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AC-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%86%D8%B5%D9%88%D8%B5-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B9%D8%B1%D9%88%D8%B6-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AA%D9%82%D8%AF%D9%8A%D9%85%D9%8A%D8%A9-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B5%D9%81%D8%B1-%D9%84%D9%84%D8%A3%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 19:59:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D8%AA%D8%B9%D9%84%D9%85-%D9%85%D8%B9%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AC-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%86%D8%B5%D9%88%D8%B5-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B9%D8%B1%D9%88%D8%B6-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%AA%D9%82%D8%AF%D9%8A%D9%85%D9%8A%D8%A9-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B5%D9%81%D8%B1-%D9%84%D9%84%D8%A3%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81/</guid>
      <description>أهلاً بيك في كورس تعلم معالج النصوص &amp;amp; العروض التقديمية من الصفر للاحتراف
سنتعلم في هذا الكورس كيفية أستحدام برامج الأوفيس كالوورد والباوربوينت
سنتعلم كيفية إنشاء الملفات في كل من البرنامجين سنتعلم وسائل الامان في كلا من البرنامجين
أولاً : كورس الورد
سنتعلم النص التلقائي سنتعلم محاذاة النصوص وهي مكونه من جزئين
سنتعلم أستخدام أداة الصور سنتعلم كيفية تقسيم الصفحة
سنتعلم أداة الأشكال
سنتعلم أداة الرؤوس
سنتعلم أداة قراءة النصوص</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 TOP MS EXCEL Templates and Dashboards with applications</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2021-top-ms-excel-templates-and-dashboards-with-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 17:51:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2021-top-ms-excel-templates-and-dashboards-with-applications/</guid>
      <description>2021 TOP MS EXCEL Templates and Dashboards with applications
Save your time and effort and automate your daily tasks and events with Ready awesome MS Excel templates.
Free Excel templates to help you create spreadsheets with ease
Microsoft Excel is one of the most versatile and useful programs in the Office suite. It doesn’t matter if you need Excel templates for budgeting the next fiscal year, tracking your business inventory, planning out meals, or creating a fantasy football draft sheet, there are plenty of Microsoft Excel templates for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curso Excel y Power BI – Análisis y Visualización de Datos</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-excel-y-power-bi-an%C3%A1lisis-y-visualizaci%C3%B3n-de-datos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 19:14:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-excel-y-power-bi-an%C3%A1lisis-y-visualizaci%C3%B3n-de-datos/</guid>
      <description>Si quieres aprender Data Science y Business Intelligence, empieza a hacerlo con Excel y Power BI. Aprende como hacer visualización de datos y crear informes con ejemplos y ejercicios prácticos.
DESCRIPCIÓN DE CURSO
Lleva tus datos a otro nivel con tablas dinámicas de Excel y dashboards en Power BI. Microsoft es el proveedor de ambos productos: Microsoft Excel siendo parte de la Suite de Microsoft Office – Microsoft Power BI siendo un software y servicio con tecnologías de Business Intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Einstieg in Office 365</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/einstieg-in-office-365/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 22:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/einstieg-in-office-365/</guid>
      <description>Allgemein
Office 365 gehört mit den Programmen Outlook, Word, Excel und PowerPoint wohl zu den wichtigsten Software-Tools. Sowohl im Büro als auch im privaten Bereich.
In diesem Kurs lernen Sie die wichtigsten Funktionen von der Basis auf an. Somit ist der Kurs ideal für Anfänger geeignet.
INHALT
Outlook - Dauer ca. 1 Stunde Einer der Vorteil von Microsoft Outlook ist es, dass mehrere organisatorische Tools (Mails, Kalender, Aufgaben) in einer Software kompakt zusammengefasst sind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel VBA Advanced - Schneller arbeiten mit Apps in Excel</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-vba-advanced-schneller-arbeiten-mit-apps-in-excel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 22:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-vba-advanced-schneller-arbeiten-mit-apps-in-excel/</guid>
      <description>Kennst Du das Problem, dass bestimmte Aufgaben in Excel sehr viel Zeit kosten und Dir den letzten Nerv rauben? Wir alle arbeiten regelmäßig mit Microsoft Excel und kennen diese Aufgaben, die einfach zu viel zeit fressen.
Ich habe in meinem Leben schon Hunderte Stunden verloren durch wiederkehrende Aufgaben in Microsoft Excel. Manchmal findest du auch einfach die Funktion nicht, und das kann einen wahnsinnig machen!
Wie Du Dir denken kannst, habe ich fieberhaft nach einer Lösung gesucht, um solche einfachen und nervigen Aufgaben ein für alle Mal in den Griff zu bekommen, ohne mich jedes mal neu konzentrieren zu müssen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Der Komplette Excel Kurs - Vom Anfänger zum Profi in 40h !</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/der-komplette-excel-kurs-vom-anf%C3%A4nger-zum-profi-in-40h/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 13:12:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/der-komplette-excel-kurs-vom-anf%C3%A4nger-zum-profi-in-40h/</guid>
      <description>Letzte Aktualisierung: 2.1.2022
*** DER KURS WIRD LAUFEND ERWEITERT -&amp;gt; neue Inhalte jeden Monat! *** LERNE EXCEL VON DER ERSTEN FORMEL BIS HIN ZUM KOMPLEXEN VBA MAKRO! Damit kannst Du jedes Excel-Problem lösen - das bedeutet, Du bist im Berufsleben unverzichtbar!
Darf ich Dir zunächst ein paar Fragen stellen?
Möchtest Du mit Microsoft Excel wirklich durchstarten - um Dir Deine Jobs in Zukunft aussuchen zu können?
Lernst Du auch gerne durch PRAKTISCHE Erklärungen mit ECHTEN Beispielen?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft PowerPoint Course - Zero to Hero in MS PowerPoint</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-powerpoint-course-zero-to-hero-in-ms-powerpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 14:59:14 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-powerpoint-course-zero-to-hero-in-ms-powerpoint/</guid>
      <description>Don&#39;t go forward without having a look at this Microsoft PowerPoint course.
Microsoft PowerPoint is one of the most used products of Microsoft office. This MS PowerPoint course is for anyone who just wants to gain skill but mainly for the one who wants to learn MS PowerPoint for their routine tasks. Anyone who can be a student, a teacher, an author, a writer, an employee, a businessman, or an entrepreneur can learn this software &amp;amp; without any doubt, it can be said that this course really going to help you somewhere even if you don&#39;t need this right now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Office: Word, Excel, PowerPoint  من الصفر للاحتراف</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-office-word-excel-powerpoint-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B5%D9%81%D8%B1-%D9%84%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Dec 2021 15:40:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-office-word-excel-powerpoint-%D9%85%D9%86-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%B5%D9%81%D8%B1-%D9%84%D9%84%D8%A7%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81/</guid>
      <description>برامج الاوفيس من البرامج الهامة في حياتنا , نحتاجها تقريبًا في كل شىء معظم الوقت
(ICDL Course) في هذا الكورس سوف نتعلم اهم برامج الاوفيس ; الورد , الاكسل , والبوربوينت Microsoft Word - اولًا الورد
ميكروسوفت وورد من البرامج الهامة في حياتنا والاكثر احتياجًا في سوق العمل لذلك لا يمكننا التخلي عنه فبرنامج الورد يتم استخدامه من أجل كتابة و تعديل النصوص و إضافة الصور التوضيحية و يمكن عمل تصاميم مختلفة من خلاله</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mega Microsoft Office Course | Covers Seven Office Products</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mega-microsoft-office-course-covers-seven-office-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 12:27:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/mega-microsoft-office-course-covers-seven-office-products/</guid>
      <description>Get this Microsoft Office Training Course to learn Microsoft Word, Microsoft PowerPoint, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Outlook, Microsoft OneNote &amp;amp; Microsoft Access.
Microsoft Office applications are the most used applications across the world. Microsoft Office has many products like Microsoft Word, Microsoft PowerPoint, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Publisher, Microsoft Outlook, Microsoft OneNote &amp;amp; Microsoft Access. In this course of MS office, all these seven above-mentioned Microsoft Office products are covered.
Microsoft Word is used for writing books, letters, applications, resumes, reports, or it can be used for any kind of documentation work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VIDEOSCRIBE AVANZADO</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/videoscribe-avanzado/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 12:27:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/videoscribe-avanzado/</guid>
      <description>Descripción del curso
Crea tus cursos virtuales...
Aprende a crear fácilmente vídeos animados para tus estrategias de marketing, para tus exposiciones, presentaciones de productos, de procesos complejos o de resultados en pocos minutos. Sin necesidad de diseñar y sin ser un experto programado.
Ahorra mucho dinero creando los vídeos tú mismo.
Este curso ha sido diseñado para cualquiera persona con o sin conocimiento previo.
En este curso aprenderás a crear videos de INFOGRAFIAS que es el elemento usual más utilizado hoy en las redes sociales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel - Einfach und leicht von Anfänger zu Fortgeschritten</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-einfach-und-leicht-von-anf%C3%A4nger-zu-fortgeschritten/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 13:18:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-einfach-und-leicht-von-anf%C3%A4nger-zu-fortgeschritten/</guid>
      <description>Das Ziel dieses Kurses ist es, möglichst kompakt alle typischen Excel-Anforderungen des Berufsalltages vollständig zu vermitteln. So dass Du als Teilnehmer*in dieses Kurses professionell und selbstbewusst alle typischen Excel-Herausforderungen im Berufsalltag meistern kannst.
Lerne Schritt für Schritt - ausgehend von Deinem aktuellen Kenntnisstand – Excel sicher und kompetent einzusetzen. Durch die zahlreichen Übungen wirst Du wertvolles praktisches Wissen erlangen.
Wenn Du also in möglichst kurzer Zeit alle typischen Excel-Fähigkeiten des Berufslebens entspannt und erfolgreich bestehen willst, dann ist dieser Kurs goldrichtig für Dich.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel: Essential of excel from beginner to advance</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-essential-of-excel-from-beginner-to-advance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 14:13:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-essential-of-excel-from-beginner-to-advance/</guid>
      <description>Regardless of whether you&#39;re beginning from the starting point or trying to turn into a flat-out Excel power consumer, you&#39;ve come to the perfect spot.
This course will provide you with a profound comprehension of the Excel equations and capacities that change Excel from a fundamental accounting page program into a dynamic and incredible analytics device. I won&#39;t prepare you to disgorge capacities and equation punctuation; I will show you how to THINK like Excel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curso Completo de Excel. Básico, Intermedio y Avanzado</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-completo-de-excel.-b%C3%A1sico-intermedio-y-avanzado/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:46:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/curso-completo-de-excel.-b%C3%A1sico-intermedio-y-avanzado/</guid>
      <description>Curso Completo de Excel. Básico, Intermedio y Avanzado
Un curso de aprendizaje para ti. Desde lo básico hasta avanzado, pasando por las fórmulas más utilizadas, gráficas, validación de datos y manejo de datos.
Captarás el mejor manejo con el Excel para las 3 partes importantes del manejo de la información.
1) Entrada de Datos. Donde operarás la validación de datos, tipos de datos, listas enlazadas, aprendiendo todos los comandos de Inicio e Insertar, donde aprenderás a utilizar todas las opciones de representaciones visuales que tiene el Excel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel : Conception Tableau de bord</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-conception-tableau-de-bord/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 12:41:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-conception-tableau-de-bord/</guid>
      <description>Ce cours vous permettra de comprendre la philosophie de la conception des bases de données Excel et de lier ces bases de données avec les tableaux croisés dynamiques. Ces derniers permettent de réaliser plus de focus sur les données demandées et d&#39;avoir une synchronisation fiable. Ensuite vous aurai l&#39;opportunité de lier ces tableaux croisés dynamiques avec des graphes et segments.
L&#39;objectif de ce cours est de vous montrer comment tirer parti des fonctionnalités d&#39;Excel pour créer et gérer de meilleurs mécanismes de génération de rapports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel Interactive Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-interactive-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 22:36:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-interactive-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>In this course, you will learn how to use charts &amp;amp; pivot tables to create amazing dynamic dashboards. But to do that you must first learn the basic charts and how to insert and edit pivot tables, slicers and pivot charts which will be taught in this course as well. During that journey, you will learn additional uncommon charts that requires an out of the box thinking as they are not an excel standard charts, such as the dynamic doughnut chart, rounded edges progress donut chart, dynamic line charts, overlay image charts and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Microsoft Excel Pivot Tables and Pivot Charts</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-microsoft-excel-pivot-tables-and-pivot-charts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 12:26:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-microsoft-excel-pivot-tables-and-pivot-charts/</guid>
      <description>Recent Student&#39;s Reviews
***Great course with interactive dashboard, pivot charts, pivot table and exercises to help student understand the course - Clark Belle Ortega*** ***Very good course! Excellent! It&#39;s definitely one of my favorites - Luis Fernando***
***It Is Very Helpful And Easy To Understand. I Have No Doubts Regarding Pivot Tables And Its Formatting After Going Through It. Thank You For The Wonderful Teaching And Technical Support. - Deepak Kumar Kanaujia***</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Calendar :  Virtual Assistant</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-calendar-virtual-assistant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Oct 2021 19:22:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-calendar-virtual-assistant/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Google Calendar: and help you if you are a virtual assistant I&#39;ll be your calendar coach! Learn everything you need to know about Google Calendar with this complete guide!
Managing your own appointments and calendars can be daunting and stressful if you are working as a virtual assistant. ! With Google Calendar and this course, you will learn how to use all the features available to provide very powerful calendar management services</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Usage Of Excel Vlookup,Hlookup,Index,Match &amp; More</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-usage-of-excel-vlookuphlookupindexmatch-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/advanced-usage-of-excel-vlookuphlookupindexmatch-more/</guid>
      <description>Recent Student&#39;s Reviews
***Very informative course. The professor explained how to manage an inventory system in Excel and ERP9 in a detailed manner - Avijoy Barberan***
***Great full knowledge for improve my existing skill and also advance level for helping in corporate level - Mevasiya Kashyap Nileshbhai*** ***Exellence course! - Phi Vu Song Ho ***Really easy to understand - Jash Ruparalia***
Nine Reasons why you should choose this Advanced Usage Of Excel Vlookup,Hlookup,Index,Match &amp;amp; More Course</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP Business Analytics Essential Training</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sap-business-analytics-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Oct 2021 16:10:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/sap-business-analytics-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>If you have been looking to move to business analyst, this video will provide you with enough information to do so. Not only understanding the basics, but how to make your first business analytics project successful.
Being a great data analyst is about helping your organization make better and more informed decisions.
According to Gartner research, Bl platform software and services sales will be tallied at $30 billion in 2020, and SAP Business intelligence solution has taken up to 10% of market share, so mastering SAP Bl platform is a must.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Formulas &amp; Functions Masterclass in MS Excel [2021]</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-formulas-functions-masterclass-in-ms-excel-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-formulas-functions-masterclass-in-ms-excel-2021/</guid>
      <description>Become a top-tier professional by mastering Microsoft Excel. This course will guide you from essential Excel functions to “master-level” proficiency, allowing you to solve complex problems and impress with your extraordinary analytic skills. We will start with fundamentals and advance to structured, real-life-based courseware that will enable you possess a versatile and effective toolbox to solve most workplace problems with great ease. Not only will you have the basic and advanced formulas at your fingertips, you will be able to build your own formula combinations to RADICALLY CUT DOWN YOUR WORKFLOW and PERFORM UNPARALLELED ANALYTICS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete SAP S/4HANA Bootcamp 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-sap-s/4hana-bootcamp-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 12:30:29 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-sap-s/4hana-bootcamp-2021/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for a course that will help you land that elusive 6-figure salary?
With so many different options out there it can be hard to know where to turn, so why not focus all your efforts on something a select few have been profiting from for years?
Every large business is working constantly on streamlining their processes and improving their efficiency, and they all use the SAP ERP platform to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Complete Google Slides from Scratch</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-google-slides-from-scratch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/complete-google-slides-from-scratch/</guid>
      <description>Google Slide is a free web-based tool offered by Google. It is an alternative to Microsoft Powerpoint. Although, it is not so powerful as Microsoft Powerpoint and it has most of the similar features that Powerpoint has and it is completely free.
This is a complete Google Slides Course where you will learn -
Design Great looking professional presentations in Google Slides
Create a customized template or theme for work or clients</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Essential &amp; Popular Excel Formulas And Functions - 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/most-essential-popular-excel-formulas-and-functions-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 15:40:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/most-essential-popular-excel-formulas-and-functions-2021/</guid>
      <description>Recent Student&#39;s Reviews
***This Course Is Really Too Good For Who Want To Learn Excel And Intermediate Level. The Trainer Demonstrates The Good Examples To Understand The Things In Better Matter, Not Only That He Provides Practical Methods That Is Really Awesome, Thank You So Much For Your Efforts And All The Best. - Vinaykumar Karne***
***Excellent Experience - Daniel Chong SÃ¡Nchez***
***One Of The Best Excel Course For The Beginners, He Clearly Explains All The Important Things In A Short And Crispy Way Which Make The Course Easy To Learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Word 2019 - Grundkurs für jeden Einsteiger!</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-word-2019-grundkurs-f%C3%BCr-jeden-einsteiger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 10:36:08 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-word-2019-grundkurs-f%C3%BCr-jeden-einsteiger/</guid>
      <description>Professionelle Dokumente mit Word erstellen.
Word ist mittlerweile das meistverwendete Textverarbeitungsprogramm der Welt und dennoch wenden die meisten nur grundsätzliche Formatierungsfunktionen an.
In diesem Kurs lernst Du alle wichtigen und grundlegenden Funktionen kennen, die Dein Dokument professionell aussehen lassen, ohne dabei wichtige Zeit zu verlieren.
Wenn Du heute noch anfängst, Word mit samt seinen Funktionen zu nutzen, stichst Du schneller aus der Masse heraus.
Du musst dafür kein PC-Profi sein, im Gegenteil, ich zeige Dir alle Funktionen Schritt-für-Schritt, so dass Du meinen praktischen Erklärungen + Beispielen im gesamten Kurs folgen kannst.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel Lessons - Zero to Pro for Teachers and Office Workers</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-lessons-zero-to-pro-for-teachers-and-office-workers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 10:00:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-lessons-zero-to-pro-for-teachers-and-office-workers/</guid>
      <description>Some reasons why you should choose this Excel course
Carefully designed curriculum teaching you only the most used functionalities of Excel in school and office environments
You can complete this course within one weekend
Office-related and school-related examples and case studies
More practical exercises because Excel requires practice
Downloadable resources
Your queries will be responded to by the Instructor
Start using Excel to become a hero in your office or school!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Data Studio A-Z for Data Visualization and Dashboards</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-data-studio-a-z-for-data-visualization-and-dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/google-data-studio-a-z-for-data-visualization-and-dashboards/</guid>
      <description>6 Reasons why you should choose this Google Data Studio course
Carefully designed course, teaching you not only how to draw all types of charts in Google Data Studio, but also advanced Data studio specific features
Concise - you can complete this Google Data Studio course within one weekend
Business-related examples and case studies
Ample practice exercises because Data Visualization and Google Data Studio require practice
Downloadable resources for learning Google Data Studio and Data Visualization</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel 2021 Intense Crash Course</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-2021-intense-crash-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 11:48:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-excel-2021-intense-crash-course/</guid>
      <description>2021 Microsoft Excel Skills You Need Through Intense Excel Tutorials!
Although This 2021 Excel Course is Short, It Covers All The Skills You Need to Master Microsoft Excel in no time, as Basic and Advanced Excel Topics and formulas are Explained in This Course.
What distinguishes this excel course from the ocean of excel tutorials online is that this course is super-fast and covers basic and advanced excel topics in one hour through to-the-point excel tutorials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>كورس الباوربوينت الإحترافى - Advanced Microsoft PowerPoint</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D9%83%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%B3-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A8%D8%A7%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%A8%D9%88%D9%8A%D9%86%D8%AA-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A5%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81%D9%89-advanced-microsoft-powerpoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 09:38:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D9%83%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%B3-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A8%D8%A7%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%A8%D9%88%D9%8A%D9%86%D8%AA-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A5%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81%D9%89-advanced-microsoft-powerpoint/</guid>
      <description>مايكروسوفت باوربوينت: (Microsoft PowerPoint) ‏
هو أحد البرامج المتوفرة ضمن حزمة أوفيس وهو مخصص للعروض التقديمية، حيث يوفر البرنامج مجموعة من الأدوات لإنشاء شرائح افتراضية عليها كتابات وصور تستخدم على جهاز عرض (بروجيكتور) مرتبط بحاسوب من قبل شخص (المقدم) في حضور مجموعة من الأشخاص (المجتمعين) وهو كثير الاستخدام في الشركات والمراكز التعليمية التي تتوفر بها تلك المعدات اللازمة.
يستخدم البوربوينت كوسيلة من وسائل التعليم، من خلال عرض الشرائح، بما تحويه من معلومات سبق إعدادها وتصميمها.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evernote Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/evernote-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/evernote-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Evernote but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Projects and bring your ideas to life?
Then Evernote 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Evernote is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start projects like an expert with Evernote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel-Kurs für Einsteiger. Arbeiten mit Excel und Formeln.</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-kurs-f%C3%BCr-einsteiger.-arbeiten-mit-excel-und-formeln./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-kurs-f%C3%BCr-einsteiger.-arbeiten-mit-excel-und-formeln./</guid>
      <description>Praxis statt Formelsammlung!
Du magst praktische Erklärungen mit echten Beispielen? Du willst nicht nur für den Kurs vorbereiteten Beispiele, die in der Praxis doch nicht relevant sind?
Du willst echte Fälle und echte Probleme kennenlernen?
Du willst Erfahrungen und Fallstricke aus 20 Jahren Excel-Erfahrung hören?
Dir ist den Hintergrund wichtig, und nicht nur die möglichst knappe Erklärung einer Funktion?
Du willst die Funktionen in der Reihenfolge lernen, in der Du sie brauchst?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>كورس الوورد الإحترافى - Advanced Microsoft Word</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D9%83%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%B3-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%88%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%AF-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A5%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81%D9%89-advanced-microsoft-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 09:01:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/%D9%83%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%B3-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%88%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%AF-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A5%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81%D9%89-advanced-microsoft-word/</guid>
      <description>برنامج مايكروسوفت وورد Microsoft Word هو معالج كلمات &#34;معالج نصوص&#34; ، يمكنك استخدامه لمعالجة، وحفظ، وطباعة، ومشاركة المستندات النصية في أي وقت ومع أي شخص
سهولة استخدام البرنامج وميزاته الفريدة والقوية كانت السبب الأول لانتشاره في المكاتب، والمنازل، والمدارس، والجامعات على نطاق واسع
يحتوي برنامج الوورد على عدد من الميزات المهمة التي لا يمكن أن تجدها في أي برنامج آخر مثل التدقيق الإملائي والنحوي، وتنسيق النص، والخط
من مميزاته :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft PowerApps Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-powerapps-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 12:05:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/microsoft-powerapps-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Microsoft PowerApps but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to manage Apps and bring your ideas to life?
Then Microsoft PowerApps 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Microsoft PowerApps is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start managing Apps like an expert with Microsoft PowerApps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Professional MS EXCEL Course with Real Applications</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2021-professional-ms-excel-course-with-real-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 10:31:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/2021-professional-ms-excel-course-with-real-applications/</guid>
      <description>2021 Professional MS EXCEL Course with Real Applications
The Key objective of the course is Mastering MS Excel with applications and Boost your Career and Business.
MS Excel is a spreadsheet program developed by Microsoft in 1985, with the sole purpose of helping businesses compile all their financial data, yearly credit, and yearly debit sheets. Fast forward to the future after 31 years, it is now the most commonly used program for creating graphs and pivot tables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel - Microsoft Excel Beginner to Advanced [2021]</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-microsoft-excel-beginner-to-advanced-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 10:31:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/excel-microsoft-excel-beginner-to-advanced-2021/</guid>
      <description>In this special Microsoft Excel - Excel From Beginner to Advanced course you can learn the most important features of Excel focusing on data visualization and productivity. I&#39;m using the version Microsoft Excel 2019 which is similar to Office 365 Excel, but the course is 90-95% compatible with Ms Excel 2010, 2013, 2016 versions.
If you&#39;re a beginner, in the first section you can learn Excel basics in 30 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Microsoft Teams Course - Master Microsoft Teams</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-microsoft-teams-course-master-microsoft-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/the-complete-microsoft-teams-course-master-microsoft-teams/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Microsoft Teams Course - Master Microsoft Teams: Managing Microsoft Teams - Microsoft MS-700 - Microsoft Office 365 - Sharepoint - Microsoft OneDrive
Microsoft Teams is a persistent chat-based collaboration platform complete with document sharing, online meetings, and many more extremely useful features for business communications. Having an excellent team space is key to being able to make creative decisions and communicate with one another. But don&#39;t worry this course will help you build a fast and complete skill over Microsoft Teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PowerPoint: Basics For Work &amp; Studies</title>
      <link>https://jobready.courseintern.com/powerpoint-basics-for-work-studies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jobready.courseintern.com/powerpoint-basics-for-work-studies/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the PowerPoint Basics course. If you are a student, a teacher or an office worker no matter what your position or job is PowerPoint is one software that everyone needs to know nowadays and most people use the software without knowing the basics of the software that makes it easy tasks difficult and makes less time-consuming tasks time consuming and results in sitting in front of the computer for more then necessary hours.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
