<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Office Productivity on </title>
    <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tags/office-productivity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Office Productivity on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jobready.ml/tags/office-productivity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel 2021 Intense Crash Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-excel-2021-intense-crash-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-excel-2021-intense-crash-course/</guid>
      <description>2021 Microsoft Excel Skills You Need Through Intense Excel Tutorials!
Although This 2021 Excel Course is Short, It Covers All The Skills You Need to Master Microsoft Excel in no time, as Basic and Advanced Excel Topics and formulas are Explained in This Course.
What distinguishes this excel course from the ocean of excel tutorials online is that this course is super-fast and covers basic and advanced excel topics in one hour through to-the-point excel tutorials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Online vs Xero Accounting Software</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-online-vs-xero-accounting-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-online-vs-xero-accounting-software/</guid>
      <description>This course will compare two leading online accounting software applications, QuickBooks Online and Xero, in a step by step format.
This is a comprehensive accounting course.
We will discuss the purchasing options and the best tools to learn these accounting software packages at the lowest cost.
Learners will understand how to set up a new company file in each software package.
The course will demonstrate how to navigate each software package and how to generate, analyze, and customize common financial reports.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tax &amp; Adjusting Entry Year-End Accounting Excel Worksheet</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/tax-adjusting-entry-year-end-accounting-excel-worksheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/tax-adjusting-entry-year-end-accounting-excel-worksheet/</guid>
      <description>Create a new Excel worksheet from scratch to be used in the adjusting and tax entry process. 
This course is most beneficial to tax preparers and public accountants who enter adjusting entries but is also useful to anybody in accounting. Similar Excel worksheets to the ones we will construct can be useful for analyzing many areas of accounting, and the Excel skills learned in creating them are also very applicable both inside accounting and outside of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xero Job Costing – Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/xero-job-costing-projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:04:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/xero-job-costing-projects/</guid>
      <description>This Xero Job Costing course will provide the resources for learners to develop a solid understanding of job costing concepts and the tools Xero provides to create an effective job costing system.
We will discuss the process of setting up Xero for a job costing system.
The course will describe the terminology used by software and by the industry, such as jobs, sub customers, and projects.
Learners will understand how to set up projects and how they function to track costs and revenue per job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel - Learn MS EXCEL For DATA Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-excel-learn-ms-excel-for-data-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 21:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-excel-learn-ms-excel-for-data-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Whether you are interested in learning
- Different ways of how to properly use Microsoft Excel
- Learn the basics of Data Analysis
- Learn how to create different Excel Apps
- Just grow your Knowledge about this amazing Microsoft App
Or any other reason, this course is definitely for you. The way this class have been designed was to offer to the student an easy way to learn Microsoft Excel and the basics of Data analysis at the same time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cost Volume Profit Analysis (CVP) – Managerial Accounting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/cost-volume-profit-analysis-cvp-managerial-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/cost-volume-profit-analysis-cvp-managerial-accounting/</guid>
      <description>Managerial and cost accounting topics of cost volume profit analysis (CVP).
We will review managerial accounting concepts and the difference between managerial accounting and cost accounting.
The course will start out introducing our primary CVP tool, a contribution margin income statement. The contribution margin income statement will give us an idea of where we are going as we then zoom into more detail going forward, focusing on the nuances of each step in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Calendar :  Virtual Assistant</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/google-calendar-virtual-assistant/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/google-calendar-virtual-assistant/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Google Calendar: and help you if you are a virtual assistant I&#39;ll be your calendar coach! Learn everything you need to know about Google Calendar with this complete guide!

Managing your own appointments and calendars can be daunting and stressful if you are working as a virtual assistant. ! With Google Calendar and this course, you will learn how to use all the features available to provide very powerful calendar management services</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Docs Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/google-docs-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 23:21:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/google-docs-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Google Docs but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Docs and bring your ideas to life?
Then Google Docs 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Google Docs is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building Docs like an expert with Google Docs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gmail Productivity Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/gmail-productivity-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/gmail-productivity-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to Gmail but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Email and bring your ideas to life?
Then Gmail 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Gmail is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start building Emails like an expert with Gmail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Sheets: Empieza desde cero</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/google-sheets-empieza-desde-cero/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 08:39:11 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/google-sheets-empieza-desde-cero/</guid>
      <description>¿Por qué aprender Google Sheets?
La forma en que usamos las hojas de cálculo está cambiando. La mayor parte de nuestro trabajo y colaboración se realiza a través de canales en línea, nuestras hojas de cálculo también se están moviendo en línea. Google Sheets es un programa de hojas de cálculo en línea que ofrece soluciones que muchas empresas necesitan en este momento.
En el pasado, el principal requisito que tenían las empresas era que los profesionales tuvieran sólidos conocimientos en Microsoft Excel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Microsoft Excel Pivot Tables and Pivot Charts</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-microsoft-excel-pivot-tables-and-pivot-charts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 21:16:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-microsoft-excel-pivot-tables-and-pivot-charts/</guid>
      <description>Recent Student&#39;s Reviews
***It Is Very Helpful And Easy To Understand. I Have No Doubts Regarding Pivot Tables And Its Formatting After Going Through It. Thank You For The Wonderful Teaching And Technical Support. - Deepak Kumar Kanaujia***

***Very Detailed Illustration And The Instructor Knows Well How To Use His Tools. Happy To Attend This Course And I Believe I Am Gonna Use It A Lot In My Work. - Mohamed Eltantawi***</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alteryx Masterclass for Data Analytics, ETL and Reporting</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/alteryx-masterclass-for-data-analytics-etl-and-reporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/alteryx-masterclass-for-data-analytics-etl-and-reporting/</guid>
      <description>5 Reasons why you should choose this Alteryx course
Carefully designed curriculum teaching you only the most used functionalities of Alteryx in business environment
Concise - you can complete this Alteryx designer core certification course within one weekend
Business related examples and case studies for learning Alteryx and becoming an Alteryx designer
Downloadable resources on Alteryx
Your queries will be responded by the Instructor himself
A Verifiable Certificate of Completion is presented to all students who undertake this Alteryx course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Desktop Job Costing</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-desktop-job-costing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 19:26:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-desktop-job-costing/</guid>
      <description>This QuickBooks Desktop Job Costing course will provide the resources for learners to develop a solid understanding of job costing concepts and the tools QuickBooks provides to create an effective job costing system.
The course will include four example problems demonstrating different job costing systems and methods that can be used.
We will provide backup files so learners can jump forward in the problems or rework any component of a problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evernote Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/evernote-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/evernote-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Evernote but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Projects and bring your ideas to life?
Then Evernote 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Evernote is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start projects like an expert with Evernote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel-Kurs für Einsteiger. Arbeiten mit Excel und Formeln.</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/excel-kurs-f%C3%BCr-einsteiger.-arbeiten-mit-excel-und-formeln./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 09:40:06 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/excel-kurs-f%C3%BCr-einsteiger.-arbeiten-mit-excel-und-formeln./</guid>
      <description>Praxis statt Formelsammlung!
Du magst praktische Erklärungen mit echten Beispielen? Du willst nicht nur für den Kurs vorbereiteten Beispiele, die in der Praxis doch nicht relevant sind?
Du willst echte Fälle und echte Probleme kennenlernen?
Du willst Erfahrungen und Fallstricke aus 20 Jahren Excel-Erfahrung hören?
Dir ist den Hintergrund wichtig, und nicht nur die möglichst knappe Erklärung einer Funktion?
Du willst die Funktionen in der Reihenfolge lernen, in der Du sie brauchst?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zero to Hero in Microsoft Excel: Complete Excel guide 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/zero-to-hero-in-microsoft-excel-complete-excel-guide-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 12:22:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/zero-to-hero-in-microsoft-excel-complete-excel-guide-2021/</guid>
      <description>6 Reasons why you should choose this Excel course
Carefully designed curriculum teaching you only the most used functionalities of Microsoft Excel in business environment
Concise - you can complete this Microsoft Excel course within one weekend
Business related examples, data analysis and case studies solved using Advanced Excel.
You will learn various data analysis techniques using MS Excel
Ample practice exercises on data analysis, MS excel (basic &amp;amp; advanced), because Excel requires practice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Data Studio A-Z for Data Visualization and Dashboards</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/google-data-studio-a-z-for-data-visualization-and-dashboards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 10:48:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/google-data-studio-a-z-for-data-visualization-and-dashboards/</guid>
      <description>6 Reasons why you should choose this Google Data Studio course
Carefully designed course, teaching you not only how to draw all types of charts in Google Data Studio, but also advanced Data studio specific features
Concise - you can complete this Google Data Studio course within one weekend
Business related examples and case studies
Ample practice exercises because Data Visualization and Google Data Studio require practice
Downloadable resources for learning Google Data Studio and Data Visualization</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master all the MS Excel Macros and the basics of Excel VBA</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/master-all-the-ms-excel-macros-and-the-basics-of-excel-vba/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 10:48:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/master-all-the-ms-excel-macros-and-the-basics-of-excel-vba/</guid>
      <description>Working with microsoft Excel is not always easy and learning to automate your work with the use of VBA is even harder. Indeed, VBA is a programming language that is really useful in Microsoft Excel especially if you want to be able to automate all the tasks that you want to accomplish. If you :
- Are in school and want to learn how to program With VBA
- Need to learn Excel VBA for work or task automation - Want to start a personal project that requires you to have Excel VBA knowledge</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel -Basic Excel/ Advanced Excel Formulas</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-excel-basic-excel/-advanced-excel-formulas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 10:48:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-excel-basic-excel/-advanced-excel-formulas/</guid>
      <description>If you want to improve your Excel skills, learn to use new functions or simply interested in becoming better in this amazing Microsoft APP then this course is for you. My name is Yassin Marco and I have been lucky enough to have the privilege to teach more than 250 000+ students in more than 190+ countries around the world. Since teaching is my passion, I decided to design this course to help people achieve there full potential with Microsoft Excel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 TOP MS EXCEL Templates and Dashboards with applications</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-top-ms-excel-templates-and-dashboards-with-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 22:23:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-top-ms-excel-templates-and-dashboards-with-applications/</guid>
      <description>2021 TOP MS EXCEL Templates and Dashboards with applications

Save your time and effort and automate your daily tasks and events with Ready awesome MS Excel templates.

Free Excel templates to help you create spreadsheets with ease
Microsoft Excel is one of the most versatile and useful programs in the Office suite. It doesn’t matter if you need Excel templates for budgeting the next fiscal year, tracking your business inventory, planning out meals, or creating a fantasy football draft sheet, there are plenty of Microsoft Excel templates for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Workspace (G Suite) Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/google-workspace-g-suite-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 22:23:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/google-workspace-g-suite-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Google Workspace but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to manager accounts and bring your ideas to life?
Then Google Workspace 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Google Workspace is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start adding accounts like an expert with Google Workspace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft 365 Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-365-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 22:23:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-365-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Microsoft 365 but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to manager accounts and bring your ideas to life?
Then Microsoft 365 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Microsoft 365 is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start adding accounts like an expert with Microsoft 365.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>كورس الوورد الإحترافى - Advanced Microsoft Word</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/%D9%83%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%B3-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%88%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%AF-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A5%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81%D9%89-advanced-microsoft-word/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 09:01:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/%D9%83%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%B3-%D8%A7%D9%84%D9%88%D9%88%D8%B1%D8%AF-%D8%A7%D9%84%D8%A5%D8%AD%D8%AA%D8%B1%D8%A7%D9%81%D9%89-advanced-microsoft-word/</guid>
      <description>برنامج مايكروسوفت وورد Microsoft Word 
هو معالج كلمات &#34;معالج نصوص&#34; ، يمكنك استخدامه لمعالجة، وحفظ، وطباعة، ومشاركة المستندات النصية في أي وقت ومع أي شخص
سهولة استخدام البرنامج وميزاته الفريدة والقوية كانت السبب الأول لانتشاره في المكاتب، والمنازل، والمدارس، والجامعات على نطاق واسع
يحتوي برنامج الوورد على عدد من الميزات المهمة التي لا يمكن أن تجدها في أي برنامج آخر مثل التدقيق الإملائي والنحوي، وتنسيق النص، والخط
من مميزاته :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Excel Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-excel-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 12:05:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-excel-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Microsoft Excel but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to create Spreadsheets and bring your ideas to life?
Then Microsoft Excel 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Microsoft Excel is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start creating spreadsheets like an expert with Microsoft Excel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft PowerApps Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-powerapps-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 12:05:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-powerapps-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Microsoft PowerApps but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to manage Apps and bring your ideas to life?
Then Microsoft PowerApps 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Microsoft PowerApps is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start managing Apps like an expert with Microsoft PowerApps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 Professional MS EXCEL Course with Real Applications</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-professional-ms-excel-course-with-real-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 10:31:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/2021-professional-ms-excel-course-with-real-applications/</guid>
      <description>2021 Professional MS EXCEL Course with Real Applications

The Key objective of the course is Mastering MS Excel with applications and Boost your Career and Business.

MS Excel is a spreadsheet program developed by Microsoft in 1985, with the sole purpose of helping businesses compile all their financial data, yearly credit, and yearly debit sheets. Fast forward to the future after 31 years, it is now the most commonly used program for creating graphs and pivot tables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Excel - Microsoft Excel Beginner to Advanced [2021]</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/excel-microsoft-excel-beginner-to-advanced-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Sep 2021 10:31:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/excel-microsoft-excel-beginner-to-advanced-2021/</guid>
      <description>In this special Microsoft Excel - Excel From Beginner to Advanced course you can learn the most important features of Excel focusing on data visualization and productivity. I&#39;m using the version Microsoft Excel 2019 which is similar to Office 365 Excel, but the course is 90-95% compatible with Ms Excel 2010, 2013, 2016 versions.
If you&#39;re a beginner, in the first section you can learn Excel basics in 30 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP Project Essentials: Implementing SAP S/4HANA and SAP ERP</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sap-project-essentials-implementing-sap-s/4hana-and-sap-erp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sap-project-essentials-implementing-sap-s/4hana-and-sap-erp/</guid>
      <description>SAP S/4HANA is here, and the stakes are high. Get your project right with this guide to SAP Activate and Accelerated SAP (ASAP).
Help your business team prepare for and participate in the SAP project journey!
Get an early read on timelines, processes, responsibilities, and potential setbacks. Understand how your implementation, upgrade, or migration is structured, how to assemble the deliverables, and how to dodge common pitfalls. With this preview of what to expect, what questions to ask, and when to take which steps, you can execute planning, go-live, and post-go-live activities without tripping up or getting lost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete SAP S/4HANA Bootcamp 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-sap-s/4hana-bootcamp-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 19:07:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-sap-s/4hana-bootcamp-2021/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for a course that will help you land that elusive 6-figure salary?
With so many different options out there it can be hard to know where to turn, so why not focus all your efforts on something a select few have been profiting from for years?
Every large business is working constantly on streamlining their processes and improving their efficiency, and they all use the SAP ERP platform to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantity Surveying With Rate Analysis And Take Off-Beginners</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quantity-surveying-with-rate-analysis-and-take-off-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 22:45:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quantity-surveying-with-rate-analysis-and-take-off-beginners/</guid>
      <description>This course will help you to understand the roles and responsibilities of a Quantity Surveyor, the skills and educational qualifications required to start a career in Quantity Surveying, the basics of rate analysis and the required knowledge to take off quantities from construction drawings using two globally used software’s Bluebeam Revu and Planswift.

By the end of this course you will gain knowledge regarding the different element to be included while pricing your construction project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Power Automate (Flow) Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-power-automate-flow-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:42:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-power-automate-flow-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Microsoft Power Automate but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to create Flows and bring your ideas to life?
Then Microsoft Power Automate 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Microsoft Power Automate is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start creating Flows like an expert with Microsoft Power Automate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete SAP Analytics Cloud Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-sap-analytics-cloud-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 22:42:45 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-sap-analytics-cloud-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Become an SAP Analytics Cloud master by setting up BI, planning, and making prediction through real-world projects
SAP analytics cloud consultant is one of the hottest careers in tech. Have you ever wondered what&#39;s the best path for me or what&#39;s my first step in building a technical career in SAP business analysis?
I&#39;m going to take you through the process of understanding how to use SAP analytics cloud. Whether you&#39;re looking to discover the core BI features or use planning module at work, this course will get you ready to plan and start to use SAP analytics cloud quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SAP Business Analytics Essential Training</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/sap-business-analytics-essential-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 18:05:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/sap-business-analytics-essential-training/</guid>
      <description>If you have been looking to move to business analyst, this video will provide you with enough information to do so. Not only understanding the basics, but how to make your first business analytics project successful.
Being a great data analyst is about helping your organization make better and more informed decisions.
According to Gartner research, Bl platform software and services sales will be tallied at $30 billion in 2020, and SAP Business intelligence solution has taken up to 10% of market share, so mastering SAP Bl platform is a must.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Microsoft Teams Course - Master Microsoft Teams</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-microsoft-teams-course-master-microsoft-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 09:53:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/the-complete-microsoft-teams-course-master-microsoft-teams/</guid>
      <description>The Complete Microsoft Teams Course - Master Microsoft Teams: Managing Microsoft Teams - Microsoft MS-700 - Microsoft Office 365 - Sharepoint - Microsoft OneDrive
Microsoft Teams is a persistent chat-based collaboration platform complete with document sharing, online meetings, and many more extremely useful features for business communications. Having an excellent team space is key to being able to make creative decisions and communicate with one another. But don&#39;t worry this course will help you build a fast and complete skill over Microsoft Teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Usage Of Excel Vlookup,Hlookup,Index,Match &amp; More</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/advanced-usage-of-excel-vlookuphlookupindexmatch-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/advanced-usage-of-excel-vlookuphlookupindexmatch-more/</guid>
      <description>Nine Reasons why you should choose this Advanced Usage Of Excel Vlookup,Hlookup,Index,Match &amp;amp; More Course
Best Rated Course on Udemy
Latest updated and Doubts Are Solved in this course
Carefully designed curriculum By Proficient In Excel Expert 
you can complete this course In Short time
VLOOKUP,HLOOKUP,PICTURE LOOKUP,INDEX,MATCH,SUMIFS,COUNTIFS And More Excel related examples and case studies Provided
12 Example And practice exercises Are Able to Download in The Recourse Section</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Teams Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-teams-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/microsoft-teams-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Microsoft Teams but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to create Teams and bring your ideas to life?
Then Microsoft Teams 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Microsoft Teams is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start creating Teams like an expert with Microsoft Teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most Essential &amp; Popular Excel Formulas And Functions - 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/most-essential-popular-excel-formulas-and-functions-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 13:11:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/most-essential-popular-excel-formulas-and-functions-2021/</guid>
      <description>Recent Student&#39;s Reviews

***This Course Is Really Too Good For Who Want To Learn Excel And Intermediate Level. The Trainer Demonstrates The Good Examples To Understand The Things In Better Matter, Not Only That He Provides Practical Methods That Is Really Awesome, Thank You So Much For Your Efforts And All The Best. - Vinaykumar Karne***

***Excellent Experience - Daniel Chong SÃ¡Nchez***

***One Of The Best Excel Course For The Beginners, He Clearly Explains All The Important Things In A Short And Crispy Way Which Make The Course Easy To Learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asana Ultimate Course 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/asana-ultimate-course-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:17:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/asana-ultimate-course-2021/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn Asana but don&#39;t know where to start?
Would you like to make amazing Projects and bring your ideas to life?
Then Asana 2021 Ultimate Course is for you!
Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Asana is an in-demand skill in 2021. The course begins with the basics. I&#39;ll take you through everything you need to know to start projects like an expert with Asana.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn Microsoft Publisher | Complete Microsoft Publisher</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-microsoft-publisher-complete-microsoft-publisher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/learn-microsoft-publisher-complete-microsoft-publisher/</guid>
      <description>Learn the Microsoft Publisher Designing Skills By joining this Complete Microsoft Publisher Training Course.
Microsoft Publisher is one of the Products of Microsoft Office. Microsoft Publisher interface looks very much like other Microsoft office products as Microsoft Word but it is extensively used for designing. Microsoft Publisher is used for different design work. Microsoft Publisher can be used for advertisements design, certificate design, newsletter design, flyer or brochure design, banner design, business card design, or letterhead design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PowerPoint: Basics For Work &amp; Studies</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/powerpoint-basics-for-work-studies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/powerpoint-basics-for-work-studies/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the PowerPoint Basics course. If you are a student, a teacher or an office worker no matter what your position or job is PowerPoint is one software that everyone needs to know nowadays and most people use the software without knowing the basics of the software that makes it easy tasks difficult and makes less time-consuming tasks time consuming and results in sitting in front of the computer for more then necessary hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slack Ultimate Course</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/slack-ultimate-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 00:48:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/slack-ultimate-course/</guid>
      <description>Have you always wanted to learn how to do project management but don&#39;t know where to start?	Would you like to make amazing projects and apps and bring your ideas to life?	Then Slack Ultimate Course is for you!	Hi, I’m your instructor Josh Werner and I’ll be leading you through this course.
Slack is an in-demand skill in 2021.&amp;nbsp; The course begins with the basics. We&#39;ll Cover everything you need to know about Slack from scratch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>QuickBooks Online-Bookkeeping Business-Easy Way</title>
      <link>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-online-bookkeeping-business-easy-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:04:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.jobready.ml/quickbooks-online-bookkeeping-business-easy-way/</guid>
      <description>QuickBooks Online bookkeeping business designed for small business clients or small businesses who want a simple cash basis format for entering data.&amp;nbsp; 
This course is designed for bookkeepers and is also useful for small business owners who want a simple system for entering financial data into QuickBooks for financial planning and year-end tax preparation. 
The bookkeeping system we discuss will also describe the relationship between the bookkeeper, the business, and the year-end tax and financial statement preparers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
